Dear viewers, good evening
Breaking news coming in right now
A mysterious death has occured in this city
It happened under the oriental bridge
The victim is a young female
The cause of death in unknown
Police are currently investigating
Those with information please contact the police
Participants can be rewarded up to $10,000
Boss, what do you need from us?
Look this up for me
I want this outfit
Look up where I can buy it
Woah! Chicken wing costume!
Boss sure has a good eye
Leave it to us
Spirit sis?
Monsters...
Hey, I'm still bathing, you should...
So you're all here at once
How insolent!
Spirit sis?
This is um...
Prepare to be eliminated!
Come back here!
Wait!
Don't get reckless
We can negotiate!
She's dangerous!
Humans must keep their distance from monsters
There's no excuse!
Let go of Yeyan
Come forth and be eliminated
Wait
You've misunderstood
Save us boss!
Boss?
So you really were working with those monsters
That's why you always try to harm me
Unforgivable
Wait!
Let me explain!
What is there to explain?
To be allied with monsters
You must be an evildoer!
These monsters have already been tamed
Like I'd believe you!
Eat steel!
Ah help us!
There's nowhere to run now!
Big sis, don't be rash
So you are working with monsters
Today I'll carry out the will of the heavens!
Hey, you alright?
So this was your secret weapon
How vile
Crazy women!
Hold it!
Under the glimering stars
This generation of censorates sure are lively
Looking at them reminds me of when I was younger
Dahm spirit, this is getting ridiculous
Come back!
I'll have to use it
Chaos Beast!
Freaking amateur
Fill the world with ice and darkness
Comply to my laws and decrees
Million Seal Barrage!
It's those two brats again, cut it out!
You're messing with the headmasters youth
Stop yelling
I'll have them learn a lesson from this old geezer
Headmaster, you
Lift!
My children!
Halt!
Headmaster?
Headmaster!
You two, do you know what you've done?
You've injured the headmaster!
It was clearly his own fault
Old people really should restrain themselves
I'm not talking about you
This isn't settled yet
Enougth!
I've lost my patience
Listen up!
Not only am I the headmaster, I'm also the Minister of the Night Command
The name is Wang Sheng-Li
The Night Command gold badge?
May the minister be in good health
Don't try to suck up now!
My face is ruined
Don't you know to respect your elders?
Give back my youth!
We know that we're wrong
Headmaster please calm down
Enough with the bullcrap!
This generations of Elite Censorates, also known as the Night Command is the student council at Xiahou middle
Report to my office tomorrow and wait for your orders
So tired
That beastly women kept me up all night
This morning, a female body was discovered in the western district
Again?
There are no signs of injuries on the body
Police beleive that it is sudden death
No
This isn't sudden death
It's zombification
There's definitely monsters behind this
You take quite an interest in corpses I see
Monster!
It was a reflexive action
Hey, don't sneak behind other people like that
I was just trying to tell you that you're going to be late for school
Ehya, I really am late
What an excellent ressource
I've waited for long
Getting in my way first thing in the morning, what do you want?
It has nothing to do with me
I'm the one looking for you
This generations Night Command is Xiahou Middle School's student council
I'm sure you already know that
Night Watcher Yeyan
Stray Spirit Huang Xiao-Yan
Your recent actions have seriously affected the reputation of student council
In just a couple days
Street fighting
Obstructing traffic
Carrying weapons
Architectural damage
Assaulting medical personnal
And...
In short
Xiahou Middle has become a target of public criticism
The headmaster is pissed
You two, this is a task for yous
Task?
Anyways, you better behave yourselves in front of the new student council president when he returns
So our task was to repair the damaged buildings
Hard labour
Yeyan
Sorry about yesterday night
Huh?
I considered what the secretary said to us
I forgive you, it was nothing really
He was right
The goal of the Night Command is to kill monsters and promote peace
The hatred between me and you will only worsen if left that way
In the end, it may be difficult for us to ever reconcile again
In this world we only meet once
Let's go get along for the sake of the people
In the future, it may be difficult to say this again
With that said, I don't have to worry anymore
My hand hurts!
Watch out!
It was an accident, are you alright?
It really was an accident!
That's weird, my hand suddenly lost its strength
My skin's rotting!
This is zombiefication
Could it be...
There's definitely something suspicious about that guy
According to unofficial sources
An unidentified object has appeared in the sky
He floods the land with bliss
And fills the sky with music
Areas it passes by are affected by average or heavy rain
Observers should prepare rain equipment
Now is live footage of the phenomenon