Humans and monsters share the same world
They exist on opposite side of the Ying Yang
So they coexist peacefully
But recently,
The system is in disarray
The Yin Yang has broken
And abnormalities occur
The world is in chaos
I must find the key to saving this earth
Or,
I'll become the key itself
Student, don't make rash decisions
90% of people are troubled in some way
Living will result in facing those problems
Sports betting is harmful
Avoid the World Cup
Any problem came be overcome
The struggles in life will only improve your brilliance
Student, do not make rash decisions
What is with this tone of pity?
I never said I was jumping!
Also,
Is this the only thing you know how to say?
Enough is enough!
I'm not going to jump!
How many times to I have to say it!
AHH!!!
You,
Who are you?
What's your business here?
Huh?
That should be my question
Alone by yourself on the 20th floor
And also wearing such strange clothes
Take a look at yourself!
I'm just expressing myself
It's called the lonely mushroom
If it wasn't for your humanity
Then I would've cut you down already!
Stop it! You guys!
Stop repeating!
So many police have been dispatched
Is it really necessary?
I'm not going to jump!
Do what your supposed to do!
Can you not hear me?
I'm seriously not going to jump!
Please believe in me!
You can leave now
Hurry up and leave!
Please, please, please
Angle is OK
Direction is OK
Gravity is OK
Young girl,
I'm here to save you
Here I come!
How did it really turn into a suicide?
I didn't do it on purpose!
Phew,
At least she didn't die
Class is finally over
If it doesn't end, then I'll just leave
My cravings have already kicked in
Big bro, take it easy
If our teacher saw you smoking in class he'll probably have a heart attack
That old man really is older than dirt
Hey, give me a smoke
Oh, so relaxing
AHH!!!
Big, bro,
I'm really really sorry
Sorry, it's my fault
I didn't do it on purpose, please spare me!
You know,
I value cleanliness over everything!
Hmph,
Lets go!
I need to pee
Huh?
Is he alright?
Relax,
His ability is to take beatings
Big bro,
Big bro!
Let me pee with you!
Wow!
As expected from big bro
He even excels in peeing!
Of course, of course, hehehe
That's why I'm big bro
Not anyone can become big bro
Got a lighter?
AHH!!!
It's a monster!
Save me!
Do you have a lighter or not?
Are you human or mushroom?
Of course I'm human
Do humans dress like that?
Oh,
This is how I express myself
Last night I had this feeling
A mushroom that was reborn
Larger than before
More yellow
More beautiful
And living once again!
Fuck me,
So it was a cosplay
That scared the shit out of big bro
Huh?
Fuck me!
I peed all over my pants!
Woah!
So much pee!
Someone's going to die!
Run for your lives!
There's trouble, big bro wet himself!
Big bro has OCD, he really values cleanliness
How do you want to die?
So do you have a lighter or not?
AHH!!!
(What's happening?)
Huh?
Way too brutal!
Hey bro
Don't just resort to violence
I'm well trained
Dealing with you ordinary people
It feels like I'm bullying you
I'll have to show them
That I'm not worth picking on
Don, don, don, don't kill me!
It's just a lighter
You, you
Just what type of person are you?
Me?
I'm a new transfer student
Yeyan is my name
We'll be going to the same school together
Please look after me
90% of people are troubled in some way
Living will result in facing these problems
Sports betting is harmful
Avoid the World Cup
Any problem can be overcome
The struggles in life will only improve your brilliance
90% of people are troubled in some way
That freaking mushroom
I,
I'll never let you get away with this!
Acho!
This is also the feeling I had yesterday
A suicidal young girl
It's artistic isn't it?