Times have changed
The earth is crumbling
Humans excessively breach the night
The monsters are getting more resentful
A disaster could happen anytime
Yes
It really is tougth
Fortunately, the successors of the three great academies are maturing
hehe
Without the help of the original censorates
Do you think these newbies can hold them off?
hehe
A new generation should come with new hope
I can see it
Menpai Middle School's new nightwatcher has already revealed himself
You've got guts
This is our turf, how dare you stroll in broad daylight with a weapon in hand.
Get out
Or I'll show you the strength of the strongest law enforcers in the galaxy
Sirs
Big bro said to come here to beat someone up
I suggest you go patrol somewhere else
What a joke
This little scat thinks he's a gangster
If any gangster dares come here
I'll hit him till his parents can't recognize him
Are you talking about us?
b,b,b, big bros...
We'll never pick on you guys again
I...
Hate people who wear armbands
What's the progress on the task I gave you?
Big bro, it's completed
We've found a skill one
Okay, don't disappoint me
That Yeyan  really can fight
(What's happening?)
So these scraps are your people?
Hehehehe
Can't take a single blow
Is... Isn't this gangster middle's buff bro?
He's a serial killer!
(Kill?...)
Run for it!
Hehe
Of course it's big bro, he's calm even when in front of a serial killer
Take your pants off
Huh?
What?
I told you to take your pants off
Huh?
Why I'm I wearing big bro's pants?
Somehow, I'm feeling exited
Your thinking to much, when buff bro is here there's no one he can't beat
Teach those kids a lesson, let them stay in the hospital
I'll definitely not give them mercy
Unless I can kill them, then you go deal with them
Um, th, this, th this...
Big bro, is that Yeyan kid coming to fight us in disguise?
So conspicuous, he thinks nothing of us
Big strong bro, it's up to you
Prepare...
Follow him
Big bro, you sure he's a serial killer and not a thief?
Huh?
The clouds are gathering
The time has come!
Woah! He's burst his clothes!
Wah! He's even wearing a thong!
Hmph
Those commoners
I look weird to them because they cannot see my transformation
Kid
Go to hell!
Huh? A bear?
Taking people's clothes off the moment you meet them, what a sexually frustrated bear
A demon flag?
Could you be?
I am a censorate of the night
Nightwatcher
Yeyan is my name
What a strong sinister aura
Could monsters be active during the day?
Kid
To bother a censorate
Are you tired of living?
I don't care, I'll kill you guys!
Big strong bro is um...
This type of reaction is really interesting
It looks like he's punishing himself
As expected from a noble
Sorry, I'm wrong!
Please spare me!
Then just let me capture you for my own use
That's no good
I'll let you reconsider
If I'm captured by a nightwatcher
Then I won't be able to reincarnate
Also all my freedom will also be taken away!
Following Yan bro has alot a prospects
We welcome you
But... I don't want to
Look! A bird!
How dare you run!
Hehe, those guys are lacking in intelligence
Everyone move aside!
I will kill those who defy!
Huh? Buff bro is...
Streaking?
That's vile!
Not good!
Son of a bitch
This fat turd will kill someone for the sake of escaping
I guess I'll have to...
Huh?
In the light of day
Yet you commit crimes and harm lives