I'd never thought that the damage would get this bad
It'll cost a fortune to repair
President?
Hurry and apprehend her!
What's happeing right now?
Thanks sir
(your welcome)
Huang Xiao-Yan, what are you doing?
Is it because she is a fellow disciple?
(my hip)
Correct, and that's why I will deal with her personally
Outsiders should not interfere
You can leave now
Today, I'll clean the filth that has graduated from my academy
She's a stray spirit, run!
That idiot, she let her get away, hold it!
Wait!
Thank's alot spirit sis
Let's meet again
[Listen to my command]
Return to the earth!
Dahm it, could it be?
Zombie research, you've committed a great crime!
It's people like you that ruin our reputation and damage the academy
There's no excuse
I'll make you pay right now
This is a forcefield
That hurt, what was that?
A forcefield
Forcefield?
It's a special type of forcefield, the two sides fight to the end, it will only disappear when one side admits defeat
So then outer forces can't interfere
That's right
Do you really have to go that far? Don't you know we're from the same school?
It doesn't matter
I'll still defeat you
Hmph, I'm tired of your attitute
Take this!
You still don't repent!
Die!
You dare research zombies!
Give us bad reputation
You think that I won't do anything?
You've got guts
I'll burry you right here!
What a violent bunch of people
When it comes to hand to hand combat, no one can beat Huang Xiao-Yan
Sis, I'm wrong, I'll never do it again!
Stop hitting me
Dispose of all your research, and I won't hurt you
If that's what big sis wants...
Psych! I'll never bow down to you!
Dreaded Metal Calabash!
Huang Xiao-Yan!
It was all an act!
Dahm it, how do we break this?
Wait, look carefully
[Cloud Force]
She caught it
This evil stray spirit has some pretty evil tricks
I won't go easy on you anymore!
I'll pound you into dust!
[Volumetric Growth!]
What's happening?
What's this enormous energy?
The forcefield has broken
This is?
She transformed
Giant!
I used my Calabash to transmute the zombie gas into my current form
Huang Xiao-Yan, leave this place!
I'll call for reinforcements
I don't need your help, I'll do this alone
You wanna flee?
Today, none of you guys are getting away alive!
Monster, take this!
[Spell barrage!]
What's the point of this
This time, our school's treasuries are toast
Not good!
The president is still unconscious
President!
Pull him outta there!
There's not enough time!
[Bind!]
This is bondage!
No! It's a binding spell
Nice trick, but do you think you can beat me with this?
This is phase one; limiting your mobility
Now I only need a couple of minutes
[Cardinal Blood Spell!]
Blood spell? Could it be?
Secrets of the academy
[Arts of the Void!]
She's used a cardinal spell
If hit, I'll be vaporized
Let magic flow from within
Bestow the power of divine right
Hear out my request!
The binding won't last
Hurry!
She's free
The spell's taking too long
It won't end well at this rate
There's no choice, secret weapon!
[Reignite the soul!]
Wow, it's fixed
In anime, anything is possible
It worked!
Awesome, just in time
Idiot
Huang Xiao-Yan!
Her spell was interupted
This is the end
(Protect spirit sis!)
Huang Xiao-Yan!
Nice one, if it wasn't for your Soul Gong, then I might as well be turned into dust
How ironic
It's because of me again
This... makes me...
Very angry!
Huang Xiao-Yan, I'll prove to you what I'm worth
Let the bloodbath begin!