Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Battle Ship Takes Off!"
Domino Stadium...
The stage only the chosen tournament finalists will know the location of.
Right now, several have gathered to fight for the title of Duel King.
Just seven more to go!
The other man who holds a God Card, Seto Kaiba, was the first to arrive, eh?
Hey Rishid...
You haven't forgotten the agreement you made with my father, have you?
Of course not...
Very good...
I'm going to put an end to the cursed inheritance
that my family has suffered for the past 3,000 years...
By taking Yugi's life.
In Ancient Egypt, the Pharaohs forced their subjects to build pyramids...
These pyramids were shaped like solidified beams of light pointed towards the sun.
The were a monument to the Pharaoh's absolute power.
But one day, a man who worshiped darkness came forth.
There was a war...
And the Court Magicians created seven items to seal the darkness away.
One of them, the Millennium Puzzle, is in the shape of a reverse pyramid.
That is the symbol of darkness!
In order to protect the seal on that darkness, my family suffered massive losses.
It is written in the prophecy handed down in my family...
"An evil power was sealed in darkness along with the spirit of a young Pharaoh...
But after thousands of years of slumber,
the evil power will rise once again...
And when that happens, the Pharaoh's soul will awaken...
He will wander this world seeking the memories he has lost."
And only I know how to find these memories.
I will never give him his memories back.
I'll use the power of the Sun God Ra to bury Yugi back in the world of darkness!
That's the only way I'll ever be free.
Isono, turn on the stadium lights.
Huh?
Aim the lights at the stands!
Yes!
Turn the lights above the stands on!
Big brother, Yugi and the others are here.
So this is the location of the finals?
Isn't it still under construction?
Are we really gonna do it here?
Welcome.
You have discovered the location of the tournament finals...
We recognize you three as participants in the final tournament...
Of course you do!
We congratulate you.
Please accept these I.D. cards.
Hey! Where are the other finalists?
Currently, only Seto-sama and the three of you have arrived.
Only four remain...
And Malik is among them.
So a new Duelist has shown himself?
Is he Malik?
He's...
Namu!
If it isn't Namu?!
Are you alright?!
We were worried about you!
And you two as well! I'm so glad you're safe!
Are you alright after what happened before...?
Come to think of it...
Right when this guy asked me tips on Dueling, the Ghouls attacked us.
And how come this guy's all safe and sound when we got captured?
I guess they didn't bother with me since I don't have any rare cards!
And all those crazy incidents happened after we met this guy...
Could he be...?!
Yugi, let me introduce you.
This is Namu.
He tried to save us when we were being attacked by the Ghouls.
Right, Jounouchi?
Y-Y-Yeah!
It's an honor to meet you!
I'm Namu!
Nice to meet you.
You must be really strong.
It takes more than luck to win and get this far.
Well with so many tough looking people here,
I think I just lost my self-esteem!
Am I thinking too much?
B-Bakura!
Why's he here?!
Bakura-kun!
What the heck are you doing here?!
Bakura-kun, is your wound alright now?
Grandpa told me on the phone that you were in critical condition!
Y-Yeah...
We should take him back to the hospital!
How'd he even get here with his body in the shape it's in?
Bakura-kun! That Duel Disk...
Of course it's so I can participate in the tournament finals.
-What?!
See?
Bakura!
Oh, I see you managed to gather enough Puzzle Cards in such a short time.
I can't believe Bakura-kun's actually participating in the final tournament!
When the heck did you even enter?!
More than that, you even won six Puzzle Cards to qualify?!
It can't be...! Again...?!
Look, it's the seventh Duelist.
He's... Malik!
He's the owner of Ra!
He's...!
Are you Malik?
I am.
You bastard!
There's no way in hell I'll let you off the hook!
So we meet once more.
I wanna beat the hell outta you right here and now,
but I'd rather settle this fair and square in a Duel!
You better prepare yourself!
Malik of the tournament's evil organization...
I'm free to disqualify you from this tournament...
But rather than do that now...
I'll beat you to a bloody pulp and take your God Card away from you!
That's right!
My big brother's gonna take revenge for everyone!
Malik...
Even I could feel his tremendous fighting spirit...
Will the seven Duelists please give me your attention!
I have an announcement to make.
All of you have won in the prelims and assembled here at the final location, Domino Stadium.
However, this will not be the location of the finals.
The real stage should appear before us momentarily...
What'd you just say?
The real stage?
What's that?!
There it is!
Amazing!
That's...
A blimp?!
That's the place of the finals?
That's right!
And it's called... the Battle Ship!
Battle Ship?
You mean...?!
That's right!
The tournament finals will take place 1,000 meters in the air!
Now please board.
We will take off once the eight Duelist arrives.
At 7 sharp.
Dueling in the sky sounds pretty fun!
Mhm-hm!
And the Ghouls can't touch us 1,000 meters in the sky.
Yeah! I'm pumped now!
Let's go in, Shizuka!
H-Hey! You can't board without an I.D. card!
-No way!
-You're kidding!
No way!
And I was looking forward to watching my brother Duel in the final tournament!
Can't you let it go?
Man, c'mon!
Let us ride!
Please!
I'm begging you!
"No" means no!
Hey! I don't have an I.D. card either!
Just let them ride!
But, Mokuba-sama...
Right, big brother?
Do as you wish.
Then we'll accept your kind words!
H-Hey!
Just pretend you didn't see them.
Y-Yes...
Set the blimp off!
But we still don't have eight...
We can't depart without-
I don't care.
The ones holding the God Cards have already gathered.
What do we do?
Hmmm...
We need eight for the tournament to run smoothly...
Very well.
Battle Ship, take off!
Wow! You can see all of Domino City from up here!
You're amazing to be able to Duel all the way up in the sky, big brother!
I know it!
I guess strong Duelists can even fly through the sky!
It doesn't take much to excite some people, Deadbeat Duelist.
D-Deadbeat?!
Deadbeat, meaning average at best.
I'm sure you'll freeze up when you face the more challenging Duels that lie ahead.
You'd better enjoy the feeling of being a tourist while you can.
That bastard!
I swear to God I'm gonna kick his ass in this tournament!
Yugi, let me give you one piece of advice.
In one of the Battle City Preliminary matches,
you left your God Card out of your deck, for whatever foolish reason.
I noticed this while working with you in that Tag Duel against the Ghouls.
Listen! I will not accept that during our fight!
I'm sure you know...
In this final tournament, we are about to step foot into the domain of the gods!
The winner will be determined by the three God Cards!
A fight that will go down in legend is about to begin!
I will beat you and Malik, obtain the three God Cards,
and become the world's strongest Duelist!
We have arranged rooms for all eight Duelists.
You may access them with your Identification Cards.
The tournament will begin in one hour.
The match-ups will be announced at that time.
This room is really pretty!
You can see the night view really well!
Hmm? Oh, yeah.
Ah... It's the street lights!
They're beautiful!
Big brother, do you remember your promise to take me to the ocean again?
Right, of course I do.
The sun shining on the ocean water is beautiful too.
To be honest...
I started to think I'd never get to see such a beautiful view with my big brother ever again.
Before, anyway...
Shizuka...
Big brother.
Thanks to you, I got to finally see such a lovely view again!
You better believe it!
From now on, you'll get to see tons of beautiful scenes like this!
Thank you!
Big brother!
Just you watch, Shizuka!
I'll win straight through the tournament with the courage you gave me.
This time I'll fight Yugi in a fair match and become a True Duelist!
Wow! This is a nice room!
Gah! Why the hell did you guys just prance on in here?!
Couldn't be helped.
The cheering section wasn't given rooms!
Whoa! The fridge is packed with food and drinks!
I'm starved!
There's even room service!
Everyone but Shizuka GET OUT!
Oh c'mon, brother!
It's more fun with everyone here!
"F-Fun"...?
Shizuka, Duelists need a little nervousness before a Duel...
I'll ask Shizuka-chan if she wants to look at the beautiful view with me!
Shizuka-chan, the view sure is pretty!
It is!
Damn you, Otogi!!
Hey look! You can see Domino Pier from up here.
You're right!
Sorry, Jounouchi.
I know this coulda been time for you to spend with Shizuka-chan.
Yo Honda, if you know that why don't you to to a different room?
Like Yugi's room, for example...
Idiot, Yugi's busy preparing for his Duels, you know!
I can't bother him right now!
I'm a Duelist too!
Oh yeah!
My god...
Thank you, Honda.
For bringing Shizuka...
Stupid! Don't worry about that!
Just win, Jounouchi!
Yeah!
What are you two doing outside my brother's room?
The eight Duelist just arrived moments ago.
We wanted to inform him.
Don't bother my brother!
You should know how important the time before a Duel is to a Duelist!
I humbly beg your forgiveness!
The tournament is finally starting.
I will beat both Yugi and Malik...
and then I'll be sure to add the three God Cards to my personal collection.
The members of this group should prove to be fun...
I failed to achieve what I wanted back in Duelist Kingdom,
but this time around I'll win the tournament and fame!
I cannot afford to lose.
For our family, and for Lord Malik as well.
Lord Malik!
Yugi, I'm happy to have become one of your friends!
It's a good thing I made arrangements prior to our meeting...
Due to the fragment of myself still within that girl, I can control her whenever I want.
And as for the other one...
Bakura...
I couldn't get rid of the evil mind inside him...
But I brainwashed his outer persona!
Everything is in place!
Yugi...
The glyphs carved onto my back...
Written in my flesh is the location of your memories.
But I won't let you have them.
I'll condemn you to eternal darkness with a Dark Game!
And when I obtain the three God Cards,
I'll become the new Pharaoh!
That's my ultimate goal in this battle!
Now the battle of 1,000 years has begun, Yugi!
My other self is searching for the pieces of his memories.
And we must win in order to accomplish that.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
A God Card...
I better put the God Card in my deck.
Alright...
It's finally starting... a fateful battle for the other me...
Yes...
When this battle is won... will I really regain my memory?
I'm certain.
We have to fight the possessor of a Millennium Item, the owner of Ra card...
Malik!
And the owner of Obelisk, Kaiba!
A battle of three gods clashing!
I will win it!
But there's two things bothering me...
One of them is Bakura-kun.
Right.
Why did Bakura-kun enter the tournament finals?
How did he obtain a Duel Disk?
Hmm...
Not enough blood!
For a brief moment before, Bakura-kun seemed like
he was being controlled by his dark personality.
Yeah...
I felt it too.
Bakura...
You are a duelist of the Dark Games, aren't you?
Bakura? I'm not Bakura.
What is your objective?
Yugi... you should know this.
Whoever gets all the Millennium Items will have everything he wants from this world.
Forgive me, Bakura!
But it can't be the evil being of the Millennium Ring,
because Honda-kun said he threw it away at the Duelist Kingdom.
Don't underestimate the dark powers of the Millennium Items.
Bakura may once again be under the control of that being.
No way!
So what else is bothering you?
It's the eight Duelist.
Nobody knows who it is...
I was just thinking the same thing.
I wonder who exactly this person is...
The first round of the tournament will now begin!
All participating Duelists and everyone else, please assemble in the central assembly hall!
Big brother!
It's finally starting!
Let's go!
-Yup!
-Right!
Whoops-
I'm beating that guy!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yo, Namu!
If we end up fighting in the first round,
take it easy on me, okay?
Sorry!
I'm not the kind of Duelist who'd ease up because I'm fighting a friend!
Eh, I see.
Then when the time comes, let's give it our all!
Yup!
No matter who I fight,
Even if it's Yugi...
I will win!
Let's go, Partner!
Yup!
"Preview"
Yugi and Bakura-kun are chosen to fight in the first round.
I do feel bad for Bakura-kun, but this Duel will be a breeze for Yugi!
They fight one another in the Duel Ring aligned with harsh wind from the sky.
Huh? Bakura-kun's acting a bit strange...
Ah?! That's the Millennium Ring!
He's being controlled by the Millennium Ring again!
Next time!
"The First Sky Duel: Yugi VS Dark Bakura"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise