Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of a memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns the sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The grand opening of Kaiba Land USA has been settled to
the Duel Tournament, "KC Grand Prix".
Chosen Duelists from all around the world are against each other. It's pretty exciting.
After Jounouchi-kun, Rebecca also won the first round.
At last, the Best Eight have been grouped.
The opponents are getting increasingly tougher,
but let's keep our spirits high and do our best!
"Jounouchi VS Sieg - A Beautiful Duel"
Now finally, sponsored by Kaiba Corporation,
The KC Grand Prix Tournament, featuring the strongest Duelists...
...has gathered its Best Eight!
First up is the unbeatable boy genius, Leon Wilson!
He has prevailed in this tournament without sweating in any of his Duels!
And the one who will be competing with this genius boy...
...is the ferocious man-eating shark who dominated his Duels!
Ethan Shark!
Let's stop wastin' time and get Dueling!
Calm down, Jounouchi.
Everyone's using this down time to reconstruct their strategies.
Jounouchi-kun, you should also be looking through your deck.
Yup, yup!
After all, your opponent is that guy over there who beat Ryuzaki and Haga in just one turn.
I won against Ryuzaki and Haga, too.
And even if I struggle now, it won't suit me.
That's for sure. In Jounouchi's case, thinking is a waste of time.
What'd ya say?
Because Jounouchi-kun's strong point is sharp perception and and the strength of luck.
Hey! Isn't that like I ain't thinkin' at all?
Is that wrong?
YOU...
Sup? Wanna go?
Knock it off! You're troubling the others!
Shut up!
What are you doing, Jounouchi?
Leon-kun?
As expected from Jounouchi-san. He sure is calm.
I'm super nervous!
What are you saying?
You're also one of the Best Eight.
You should have more confidence and prepare yourself, that's all.
It's just...
When I stop and think that I get to face Yugi-san if I win, I get all nervous!
Listen to the guy! He's already talking like he's won the thing!
Wait a sec. If you win the next match, your opponent in the Semi-Finals will be me.
And I won't hand over the right to Duel my Darling so easily.
Yes, please go easy on me.
Well, so long as we all agree not to hold a grudge against the winner.
Sorry to keep you waiting. Please standby.
Sweet! Let's do this!
They call you Sieg, right?
Let's both have a good Duel.
Hey! Wait up!
How about showing some manners towards the guy you're about to fight here, huh?!
Hey! You listening, ya jerk?!
I ask of you not to lay your hands on me.
What?
Jounouchi-kun.
I hardly have the time to be concerned with an opponent who will vanish instantly before me.
Don't decide that before we start the battle!
The most foolish ones are those who do not know their own ability.
You do not even have a mere one percent chance of victory.
What did you say?
You're talking to a Duelist who made the Best Four in Battle City!
Don't look down on me!
Then keep up the futile resistance to your heart's content.
You will know your place very soon.
You jerk!
Cut it out, Jounouchi!
That bastard!
If I let him say that...
Get off, Honda!
I'm gonna settle this in our Duel!
Jounouchi...
Will Jounouchi-kun be alright?
His opponent shook him up before the Duel even started...
Darling, you guys should go cheer for Jounouchi.
Rebecca...
I'm not worried, but I think Jounouchi's a bit at risk here.
At least cheer him a bit.
Is it really okay?
In return, just support me in the next match.
But if Jounouchi wins and remains, support me instead, Darling!
Do your best, Rebecca.
You heard her. Let's cheer enough for Jounouchi to cover Rebecca, too.
That's right. If it's Becky, there's no need to worry.
Yugi, we need to talk for a minute.
Mokuba-kun.
My brother told me that we need to keep a close eye on the Duelists here.
What do you mean by that?
Before the tournament began, when we first came here,
the computer ran wild and we got locked in the Duel Stadium, right?
At that time, the guy who hacked the computer...
My brother said it's strange that we couldn't do anything to stop it.
There's a high possibility that the enemy has already infiltrated this place.
The guy who did the hacking?
If someone wants to get in the way of the comeback of Kaiba Corporation,
he just has to make this tournament fail.
However, I have perfected my blog
so that it's impossible for anyone to hack it from the outside.
Even so, if he is planning something, he will have to slip into this tournament.
I see, he slips into the Duelists in the tournament and....
Yes. The guy will definitely appear.
And the moment he does...
I'll crush him so badly that he won't ever think to lay a hand on Kaiba Corporation again.
I'm researching the Duelists as we speak.
Mokuba, keep a thorough eye out for anyone doing anything suspicious.
Because I can trust you guys, I want you to cooperate.
Report anyone acting suspicious to me right away!
Someone acting suspicious, huh...?
Every single one of the freaks here seem a little suspicious, though...
Maybe those guys?
"Those guys"?
Ryuzaki and Haga, I meant.
Didn't they sneak into this place before?
Ah! But it can't be those two.
I already had their butts sent straight back to Japan against their will.
Guess that leaves us with no one else to suspect...
Yeah.
It's kind of... disappointing.
Yugi?
Just when I thought we could just have fun Dueling with everyone...
Now there's someone out there trying to spoil it...
Partner...
You went through the trouble of recruiting people from around the world...
I wanted to enjoy Dueling against everyone.
Yugi...
Don't worry!
I will definitely make the tournament a success!
And we'll help you out!
Anyway, let's go cheer for Jounouchi while looking out for any suspicious looking guys.
Right, Yugi?
C'mon. If we don't get moving, Jounouchi's match will start without us.
Let's go!
Here and now, the Best Eight will clash!
Out of the eight present, who will win?!
The core of the Earth, huh?
I feel like I've seen an attraction like this before...
Over there! He's over there!
We came to cheer you for you, Jounouchi!
Do your best!
Ah! Leave it to me!
I'll make you regret what you said earlier.
Where the heck're you looking?
Don't ignore me!
Okay...
You think Jounouchi's going to be okay?
Don't get so frustrated, Jounouchi.
Relax! Relax!
I won't let myself lose to someone like you!
Then come before me, foolish one.
Now, let the Duels start!!
Duel!!
Tch... Looking down on me with that look on his face... He's just like Kaiba!
Jounouchi, calm down and go!
Stay calm!
I'll make him realize my skills...!
My turn first!
Draw!
Let's go!
What's the matter with Jounouchi?
Jounouchi-kun?
O-Oh shit!
I got no Monster Cards I can Summon!
Whatever could be the matter?
Are you not going to show me these "skills" you claim to possess?
I play a reverse card and end my turn!
Only a set card?
There was no Monster Cards in his hand?
Jounouchi!
It is my turn.
I draw.
Here he comes...
I invoke a Magic Card from my hand. Angel's Charity.
Due to this card's effects, I draw three cards from the deck and send two to the Cemetery.
I then place one reverse card to end my turn.
That man didn't draw a Monster Card either?
All right! That was lucky, Jounouchi!
Partner...
Other Me...
Do you think this person really didn't draw a Monster Card?
No, there is something else here...
What the hell was that? You couldn't even Summon a Monster?!
And here you were boasting up a storm just a second ago!
You really make me laugh, man!
Are you watching, Kaiba?
You must be desperately following my trail about this time.
But I grow bored.
So I will grant you just a small hint.
It is time!
Cool! My turn, draw!
What the?!
A loud show, huh?
This is strange...
This wasn't set up.
Is that so?
But isn't this tournament being broadcast around the world and is the introduction of Kaiba Land?
That's why they're showing off so much, right?
My turn! Draw!
Well, Marco, what should we go with next?
All right, this one! Good boy!
What?!
What?
From my hand, a Magic Card...
What is this?
He came, as I figured he would!
Seto-sama, strange things at the attractions....
I'm well aware!
Access from the outside should be completely blocked.
When he hacked last time, he placed a timed virus?
To be able to slip through my eyes and come this far....
This audacious young girl...?!
No, that can't be right...
But there's not many people who could get this far...
This is a simple matter for me.
I thank you sincerely for the invitation.
As expected from you, Mr. Kaiba.
You chose a splendid successor.
However, he will not lose either.
For he is also a genius.
You have "This party is boring" written all over your face.
Perhaps you would like if I spiced it up a bit for you?
What happened?
Gozaburo-sama.
A computer virus?
That's absurd.
There should be a strict protective firewall on the main computer.
Who could have done this?!
This is a simple matter for me.
No, I speculate you could pull it off as well.
As we are both branded as geniuses, it would be most beneficial if we got along.
Could he...? No, that happened a long time ago.
I was just reaching the climax of my highlight scene.
Let's go! I Summon the Rifleman of Landstar in Attack Position!
Then I activate the Equipment Magic, Landstar Shot, from my hand!
This is an Equipment Magic only for Rifleman of Landstar.
It elevates its Attack Power by 600 points!
Go on, Rifleman of Landstar, and Direct Attack the guy!
My Trap Card activates.
Wotan's Judgment.
This Trap activates when the opponent's Monster attacks.
As per this effect,
I exchange one Magic Card from my hand with the first card in my deck and shuffle.
The opponent's attack is then negated as the Battle Phase is forced to a close.
So close! That was such a good chance, too.
The Trap from before.
I don't think it was just to end the Battle Phase.
Yeah. He's trying to get a new hand so he can accomplish something.
As I thought, there's a reason he was chosen for this tournament.
My turn is over.
It is my turn. I draw.
My Magic Card will activate. Pot of Greed.
I draw two new cards.
I will then invoke a Magic Card.
Goddess of Earth - Erda's Guidance.
Erda, Goddess of Earth, is capable of seeing into the past, the present and the future.
Your hand is the future.
Your field is the present.
Your Cemetery is the past.
Due to this card's effect,
I send one Magic Card from my hand to the Cemetery...
...return one Trap Card from the Cemetery...
...and set it on the field.
That's a Trap Card. It's got to be the one he used before, Wotan's Judgment.
I will end my turn.
What?
He didn't Summon a Monster?!
Does that mean he doesn't have a Monster Card in his hand again?
That can't be!
As I figured, this guy is waiting for a particular card.
When Jounouchi-kun attacks on the next turn,
he will draw another card due to Wotan's Judgment.
Maybe it's the card that defeated Haga-kun and Ryuzaki-kun?
It seems you are meeting some unexpected difficulties, Kaiba.
If you cannot deal with this, it would mean I overestimated you.
Hey, you!
What the hell do you keep looking at?!
I'm over here, ya know!
Are you that confident that you won't even focus?!
Concentrate on the Duel!
I do not feel the need to go all out on someone like you.
As far as I am concerned, you are merely a clown performing for my amusement.
A clown?!
Just as a clown is meant to do, you must dance and make us laugh.
What's with this guy?!
I won't let you provoke me.
And if you underestimate me so much, you're gonna be in for some pain!
My turn! Draw!
I offer Rifleman of Landstar as a sacrifice...
...to Summon Android - Psycho Shocker in Attack Position!
The Special Effect of Psycho Shocker activates!
Negate all of his Trap Cards!
Trap Search!!
What?
And I attack you directly with Psycho Shocker!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
How's that?
Wake up yet?
There's a Duelist standing in front of you, and it's me!
Name's Katsuya Jounouchi!
He did it!
Beat that guy down even more!
My turn is over now. This time, come at me seriously!
You have touched something you should never dare to touch!
Foolish fool, you will pay retribution for what you have done!
Now that you have forced me to get serious, it is far too late for you to lament!
It is my turn...
I draw!
I will show it to you as well.
My beautiful young warrior maidens who travel amidst time itself!
That card is....
I knew it!
I initiate a Magic Card!
Walkuren Ritt!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The guy Mokuba-kun told us about, who is trying to get in the way of this tournament...
Did he really slip into it?
If that's so, the strange movements in the attractions is because of him?
It is bothering me, but now we have to concentrate on the support of Jounouchi.
And the card this Sieg guy dressed in purple drew.
Maybe it is that card that defeated Haga and Ryuzaki in an instant.
Next time!
"The Goddesses of Monster Extermination"
Duel standby!