Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Ironheart guided me to the Gate of Mystery.
Which lies deep within the Stone Wilderness.
It's a place where wandering souls gather.
And it's a place where you can confront your own heart.
Once there, I met the soul of my Partner.
Through a Duel, he was able to relay his feelings to me!
Thank you, Partner.
I'm no longer in doubt!
"The Orichalcos Soldier"
Partner...!
Partner, you always...
Yugi!
Use your card to slit my throat!
HERE I GO, KAIBA!
Elf Swordsman!
Other Me!
Partner!
I believe in you, Other... Me...
Partner!!
For my sake...!
The one who had the true courage...!
It wasn't me...!
The True Duelist here, Partner...
It's you...!!
Yugi...
That's...
So you've gone there, have you?
This time, the nameless Pharaoh's soul...
What the hell is this?!
Give it up, Rafael.
That place is home to the Grim Reaper.
You cannot possibly step foot in there in your current state.
Take the shard of Orichalcos...
...and toss it down there!
Yes, sir!
Wh-What's this...?!
Wh-What the...?
Grandpa!
So you've noticed us...?
Something's coming...
Oh no!
What in the world is this thing...?!
Damn him...
So he's resurrected the servant of evil forces?
Servant of evil forces?
That's Lord Dartz's...!
Orichalcos Soldier...
Dispose of the Nameless Pharaoh!
What are...?
Something's about to happen...!
Wh-What is...?!
That vision just now...
That's Kris!
Ironheart!
What was that just now...?!
And this beast...!
That creature dates back to the ancient days of my time period.
The spirits of the soldiers who served under Altantis's army.
Soldiers of Atlantis?
Mmm...
I can say with confidence that this is the sacred ground we ruled over along with the Atlantis soldiers.
What?!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Yugi!
I've been trapped...!
What?!
It Summoned a Monster?!
Orichalcos Gigas!
Send the nameless Pharaoh to his doom!
Yugi!
The souls of our comrades sleeping within this terrain...!
Nameless Pharaoh!
Your Duel Disk!
The spirits shall aid your Monsters with the power they require!
My Monsters...?!
Help me out, my Monsters!
Show yourself!
Winged Phantom Beast Chimera!
Chimera Impact Dash!!
What!? This beast regenerated with a power-up?!
Chimera!!
So this Monster gains Attack Points whenever it's destroyed...!
Then the Magic Card Fissure!
Did it work?!
What?
Magic Cards have no effect!
Take this!!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Traps won't work either...?
There's no end to this...!
Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Elf Swordsman!
If this goes on... I'm done for...!
Nameless... Pharaoh.
Yugi!
This will be bad if we let it continue...
Grandpa!
Oh, Timaeus...
This shall be our final mission.
O Legendary Dragon, Timaeus...!
Let us return peace and harmony to this land once more!
Again...
What's the meaning of this vision?
Ironheart!
Kris! Sunny!
Timaeus!
Who is...?
I beseech thee, Thunder!
Crash down asunder, ablaze the form of a speeding rabbit! Tear through my enemies!
Come to me!
Timaeus!
Be gone!
Great "Legendary Dragon"!
Nameless Pharaoh!
The evil spirits are being drawn towards my grandpa!
Sunny!!
Kris!
Thy spirits lying in the earth!
Grant me thine divine protection!
That man...!
The Duel Monsters...!
Just who is he?!
Kris...
Ironheart...
Who exactly are you guys...?
Nameless Pharaoh!
The card...!
Ironheart!
You annoying ghost from the past!
Get out my my way!
I beseech thee, Thunder!
Ironheart!!
Grandpa!!
N-Nameless Pharaoh...!
The Timaeus card...!
Ironheart!
Ironheart!!
Grandpa!!
Pull yourself together!
K-Kris...
T-Take this card...
Carry out...
...our task...
Grandpa...!
Sunny!
Kris!!
Elf Swordsman!
Kuriboh!!
Yugi!!
Kris!!
Sunny!
Stop this, Kris! Stay away from me!!
Yugi!!
Take the card...!
Kris!!
Th-The card...!
Kris!
P-Please...
You are... our last hope...!
Please... save... the world...
Kris...!
Kris!
Timaeus...
This isn't just my fight...!
Partner...
Kris...
Ironheart...
And everyone else...
What you can see, yet cannot see...
It's something very important to me!
I no longer have any doubt!
My power...
It's meant to protect that very same thing!
I sacrifice Elf Swordsman!
I Summon Black Magician Girl!
Timaeus!
Grant me your power once again!
Timaeus...!
Nameless Pharaoh! Have you brought back the Legendary Dragon?!
Black Magician Girl...
Combine with Timaeus!
Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!!
Also, a Magic Card!
Excalibur!!
Attack, Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Black Dragon Burst!!
Hey, up ahead.
The Hermos card...!
Has something happened to Yugi?
Hey, Jounouchi!
Hold up!!
Timaeus...
Black Magician Girl...
Please fight alongside me once again.
So you're back to normal, Nameless Pharaoh?
That's fine.
I shall be the one to defeat you.
So these guys were warriors who fought alongside the Legendary Dragon ages ago...
Their souls were trying to guide you, Yugi.
I will never forget what you guys have done for me...
With your will, I will definitely...
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Ironheart and Chris...
Harboring their memories, Yugi has gained new motivation to take down Doma.
Yugi's spirit has grown considerably while facing this large ordeal.
Meanwhile, as for Otogi-kun and the others we left behind...
They encounter one of Doma's Musketeers, Varon!
Don't be reckless! Rebecca! Otogi-kun!
Next time!
"Varon Engages!
The Mysterious Armor Deck"
Duel standby!