A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"The Big Five's Trap:
Duel Monsters Quest"
I'm betting you guys weren't counting on me showing my face here again, were you?
It's clear you five aided Pegasus in his attempted take over of Kaiba Corporation.
That's right! Because of you jerks, we...
The act of treason you've committed isn't something that can be forgiven.
As president of this company, I hereby fire every one of you!
P-Please wait a moment!
The plain sight of you disgusts me!
W-We only did what we did because of your loss to Yugi Mutou.
What?!
Seto-sama, we only agreed to work with Pegasus to save the company's reputation from plummeting.
Right. We only acted on the best interest of our reputation.
And in order to save it, we have developed a new adventure game based off of Duel Monsters.
Adventure game...?
That is correct, president.
Why don't you play a little game with us, gambling on your firing us.
If we are to lose this game, we will humbly accept our loss.
If we are to win, you cannot fire us.
I see.
So you're challenging me to a match?
Very well.
Huh? Big brother?
I, Seto Kaiba, will accept any game.
Big brother!
Brother, why'd you go and accept?!
It's clearly a trap!
I'm well aware of that.
Then why...?
I'm simply going to make sure they never think of trying to get their revenge against me.
I'm gonna beat them into next week.
And demonstrate my power over them!
Please insert cards in Deck Case.
Setting position. Please sit patiently.
Position locked. Beginning game. Standby.
Brother! This can't be good for you!
Don't fret it! Start it up, Mokuba!
Big brother...
I'm gonna win no matter what!
Big brother?!
Big brother...
Challenging me to this level of game?!
Come forth! Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Blue-Eyes!!
What!?
The Dragon-Type Sealing Jar!
B-Blue-Eyes...!
Brother!
Brother...!
Brother...! Pull yourself together, big brother!!
And with that, the president has been trapped within the game.
What'd you say?!
Unless you can win the game, Seto-sama's consciousness will forever remain trapped within the game's world.
And thus, Kaiba Corporation now belongs to us!
That is correct!
Mokuba, allow us to take you hostage once more.
Big brother...
Where's Mokuba?!
Shit! Ain't that...?!
So he got away?!
Mokuba got away!
You imbeciles!
Find him immediately!
Yes, sir!
There is no reason to get so worked up.
Mokuba will return to us in no time for sure.
What was that?!
There is no way that over-obsessive little brother would abandon Seto-sama.
But he may get help!
No matter who he gets to help him, the result of this game is very clear.
Here ya go! The new cards you ordered!
Wow! Thanks a lot!
Y-Yugi...
Mokuba-kun...
Kaiba-kun got trapped in the Adventure Game's world?!
So you mean if he loses, he can't escape the game?! That's no game at all!
Yugi... My big brother... Please save my big brother...
But we're up against the top executives of Kaiba Corporation. This is a serious matter.
Big brother... Big brother's true dream...
...is to build Kaiba Land around the world so kids all over can enjoy themselves.
I don't believe it... Kaiba had a dream like that...?
Yeah. It's true.
It's because of that my big brother put his life on the line for Kaiba Corporation.
No one realizes how much he puts his heart into it.
Relax, Mokuba.
None of us are gonna just abandon him.
Right! We're fully aware of how strong the bond between you two is!
Yugi...
We're off, Grandpa!
Be careful, will ya?!
Right!
I'm going, too!
You've really grown into a reliable man, Yugi.
Kaiba Corporation has been taken over by the Big Five!
Then what'll we do?
I believe that the simulators at Kaiba Land have the same programming they used.
Here they are.
Good. They're working.
We've got access.
1, 2, 3...
So only three people can go...?
Me and Yugi...
And the other guy is...!
I'm gonna go!
Mokuba?
If you lose the game, you won't be able to come back, you know.
There's no meaning for me in a world without my big brother!
Mokuba...
That decides it.
Honda! You're on house duty!
You guys better return.
Just relax!
We'll come back for sure!
With Kaiba-kun.
Honda! Go for it!
Alright!
Here goes!
I believe in you guys.
So they left...?
So they came back, just as I thought.
Damn that Mokuba...
So he brought that Yugi Mutou with him?
Sawatari.
I want you to trap Yugi Mutou and his friends in the Game World at Kaiba Land!
Yes, sir!
I wonder if this world is related to Duel Monsters somehow...
What rules must we follow in this world?
We still don't know yet.
Be careful, guys.
I know that.
This is...
Doesn't feel like your ordinary graveyard...
I feel like I've seen this terrain somewhere before...
S-Something appeared!
Murder Circus Zombie...
Armored Warrior Zombie...
Dragon Zombie...
Duel Monsters, huh?!
Then...
So, how do I do this?
Go, Rude Kaiser!
Come out, Black Magician!
Attack!!
So you just have to order them to attack?
They're persistent!
Go, Flame Swordsman!
Burning Fighting Spirit Sword!!
Oh, no!
Stop your attack, Jounouchi-kun!
Flame Swordsman just...!
Their Attack Points increase whenever they revive!
They're immortal!
Jounouchi-kun, think back to when you fought Kotsuzuka back in the Duelist Kingdom.
You should be aware of what to do.
The way to beat Zombies.
That's it!
Zombies have 0 Defense Points!
Activate! Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand!
Alrighty!
Now's our chance!
Go, Black Magician!!
Black Magic!!
We did it!!
Seems we got some gold.
This appears to be this world's currency.
My Life Points didn't return!
I get it.
So this is our...
Shit!
What happens when it reaches 0?
A sprite?
When sprites appear in a game,
it's usually some kind of hint!
Hey! Wait up!
Huh?
It got away!
What's wrong, Mokuba-kun?
It's a town.
Can you really eat these?
Jounouchi-kun!
Super Rare Cards!
Let's buy em!!
No way.
Take a look at the price.
2,000 gold...?
We got a card when we beat that Monster earlier...
Just 5!?
No good...
More importantly, let's hurry up and look for my brother.
Okay.
Let's go get some information!
Guys, did you find anything?!
No~ Nothing at all~
I found out something good.
They saw someone they didn't recognize being carried up to the Cave of Death located in those mountains.
Who could it be?
Is it Kaiba?
It has to be!
Seems the only way to get to the Cave of Death is to cross this desert.
Sounds easy...
Mokuba-kun!
H-h-h-hey!
This is impossible!
Let's head back, Mokuba-kun!
Shut up!
I won't... without big brother...
What the?
A sand storm?!
Yugi...
Yugi!
You alright?
This is...!
We were blown all the way back to the town.
Mokuba-kun...
You can't cross the desert like that.
Gramps! Ya know something about it?
If ya plan on crossin' the desert, ya need the Cluck card!
"Cluck"?
You mean the card!
Mister, do you know how we can get that card?
If ya plan on crossin' the desert, ya need the Cluck card!
You just said that a second ago...
-Keeps on sayin' the same thing...!
-So if we don't get the Cluck card...
We can't get out of this town?
Anyway, let's focus on finding out how to get the Cluck card!
There's got to be a way to get it!
Yugi Mutou...
You shall not succeed in rescuing Seto Kaiba!
Man, haven't they been gone for a while now?
Don't rush them.
Even if Yugi's a gaming genius,
there's no way he could clear it that fast.
I suppose that's true, but...
That's right!
I'll tell you all about the first crush I ever had!
The story of Hiroto Honda's First Ever Love Interest!
I don't really wanna hear it.
R-Really?
Then I'll tell you about my writing class' essay!
"My Dream is to be a Pilot!"
How's that sound?
You know...
Do you even know the situation we're in?
Seems the enemy has infiltrated the base.
Anzu, let's make a barricade in front of the door.
Got it.
No good...
We came up with nothing...
It took us so much effort to get to this town, too...!
Maybe it's come kind of computer bug...
Well, let's go look again...
What's wrong?
Yugi!
I found it!
What?!
"Won't you challenge us for a shot at Champ?"
"The current prize for victory is the Cluck card."
"So, your trial is waiting for you."
"-The Ruler and Killer of Darkness"
Alright!
We found it!
What?
Youse gonna enter for a shot at Champ, gecko?
Now, now. Winnin' ain't no easy task, gecko.
It'd be alot of trouble fer us if we had a weakling as the Champ, gecko.
Alrighty, yer fine.
I'll sign you guys up, gecko.
Now then, here's the mask and mantle you gotta wear.
Uhm...
Is it that dangerous?
Whatever do ya mean?
Ya just fight each other till one of yer Life hits 0.
Until your Life reached 0...?
I'll do it.
Jounouchi-kun!
Anyone whose Life hits 0 can't return to the real world alive.
But if your Life hits 0, then...
You dumbass.
You can easily win without my help.
But without you, we can't clear the game.
But...
Jounouchi...
Don't feel bad.
I decided to do this on my own.
Ladies and gentlemen!
It's been too long since we've had a challenger for our invincible Champ, has it not, gecko?
Tonight, we got a ferocious man comin' to challenge the Champ's position!
He wears a pig mask, and is unshaken by death!
The Piglet Warrior, Joe, gecko!
He's gonna fight the Champ for her title!?
You dumbass!
Like hell the Champ'll lose!
I-I got a bad feeling about this...
You can do it, Jounouchi-kun!
Now then!
Behold out invincible Champ!
Madam Butterfly, gecko!
The Champ's a woman?
The identity of the warrior woman standing before Yugi and the others in the Coliseum...
...is none other than Mai Kujaku-san!
With Mai joining, Yugi and his party cross the desert to save Kaiba-kun.
Even though they were able to make it to the Cave of Death,
They didn't find Kaiba-kun, but a girl that looks exactly like Mokuba-kun!
Eh?
Yugi and the guys are the chosen legendary heroes?!
Next time! "Duel Monsters Quest 2: The Legendary Hero, Yugi"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship