With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
What the...? What the?!
What are those?
Thanks to Call of the Living Dead, all of my Monsters return as Zombies!
What'd you say?!
Go!!
Dragon Zombie, attack!
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
This is… really bad.
The Shield in the Right Hand, The Sword in the Left Hand!
How do like it?
Thanks to Call of the Living Dead, all of the Monsters you killed have returned as Zombies!
You've got no hope of winning against Zombies that hold the power of the dead!
Hey, hey! It’s your turn!
Damn it all!
Go, Beast-Warrior Garoozis!
Crush those zombies!
Alright!
Instant kill Five-Point Slash!!
It’s useless!
What?
I thought I told you.
Thanks to Call of the Living Dead, my Monster come back from the grave!
It revived again?
And that’s not all.
All killed Zombie Monsters gain a 10% power boost when they’re killed off and revive!
What did you say?
Murder Circus’ original Attack Power was 1350.
With the 30% he gains from the Zombie Field Power Source, he increases his Attack to 1755.
And with the 10% bonus he received from reviving, he’s up to 1890!
How’s that? Garoozi’s Attack is only 1800!
Oh no…
Murder Circus Zombie, attack!
Acrobatics of Hell!!
We’re all here, right?
Yup.
Eh? Where’s Bakura?
Did we get separated?
What should we do, Yugi?
This is problematic…
That’s…
Bakura-kun!
Down here, Bakura!
Hey! Wait for me!
Hey, wait!
Jesus, keep your fetished jokes to yourself!
I’m tired, I can’t move…
Well, thanks to that, we’ve gotten pretty far.
Sorry about that.
Anyways Yugi, Which way should we go?
This is just getting creepier by the second.
Come to think, Jounouchi can’t stand occult stuff.
At any rate, We need to find Jounouchi-kun as soon as we can!
Wha?
What’s that sound?
Sorry, It’s my fault—
Quiet.
It’s getting louder.
It sounds bad.
Just what is making that sound?
Why’d it come this way?
Hell if I’d know!
I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry! I’m sorry!
Bakura-kun!
No!
Bakura!
What?!
A dead end?!
Damn it!
That’s crazy, Honda-kun!
Honda!
A balloon?
It’s a speaker.
That way it could sound like the real deal.
Are you okay, Bakura-kun?
It looks like we were played.
I’M GONNA FREAKIN’ KILL THAT PEGASUS BASTARD!!!
Even if I kill them, they just revive and power up their Attack Points
and return as immortal Zombie Monsters.
Just how do I fight that?
No matter how much you think it through, you can’t win this.
Our bro’s plan is perfect.
Just hurry up and surrender!
If I lose these Star Chips, it’s over!
Loser dog!
I'm not a loser dog about to give in!
I can’t lose, for Shizuka’s sake.
I’ll win by believing in myself, and betting on my next draw.
Time Wizard!
This card’s given miracle after miracle, and brought me to victory many a time.
Even with this Zombie Army, with Time Magician's Time Magic...
Go, Time Wizard!
Time Wizard...?
That’s bad.
If he uses Time Magic, odds are the zombies’ll be offed.
Time Roulette!!
Bro…
Don’t be afraid.
The Time Wizard is a gambler's card that one bets with.
He’s making this a battle of luck.
Hope you’re lucky.
I’m betting on you, Time Wizard.
Miss! Miss!
It slowed down!
W-What?!
It missed!
The price for losing with Time Magic…
The Time Wizard and the Flame Swordsman
are sucked off your field and sent into the dimension of time!
Wait!
And on top of that…
Half of the removed Monsters’ Attack Points will be deducted from your Life Points!
This is great! He finished himself off!
Losing the Time Roulette does this much damage…
Now then, bring out some more Monster sacrifices for my zombies!
I’ve got nothing left in my hand!
Go, Dragon Zomb-
Wait a sec!
Even if you kill that weakling, it won’t lower his Life Points.
Focus on increasing the strength of your Zombie Army instead!
Go! Play the Ghost King card!
I gotcha!
Come out, Pumpking!
W-Wha?!
The king of ghosts, Pumpking!
Power up from the field bonus!
Ghost king…
And Pumpking has a Special Effect, too.
Mega-Plasmic Breathing!
What the hell is happening?
Ghost King, Pumpking…
He injects his own Ectoplasm, energy of the dead, into all Ghost Zombie Monster cards on the field.
…giving them a 10% power boost each and every turn!
What'd you say?!
The Zombie Monsters themselves are growing with their Attack Power!
Go Dragon Zombie!
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
The Demon Hunter, huh? He’s barely worth killing.
Damn…
Another card in Defense Mode!
Mega-Plasmic Breathing!
Zombie Army, power up!
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
Even Lizard Armor…
This is amazing! Bro's combo worked perfectly!
Not quite yet.
When he draws that, his ultimate card combo will be complete!
The best I can do is defend…
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
This is great! Awesome!
Damn it, at this rate…
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
Every turn, they become even stronger!
My Zombie Army is unstoppable!
Bro’s Ghost Combo is absolutely perfect!
Now then, bring out the next sacrificial lamb!
Can I even win this?
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Yugi, everyone!
Hey!
There’s a Duel Ring here?
Jounouchi, why the hell are you Dueling here?
It’s not like I wanted to!
These guys ganged up on me and dragged me here!
What?
Who’re you?
You’re not messing with this Duel.
What’d you say?
If you want to, you have to get through us.
Fine by me!
Honda-kun!
Honda!
Damn it!
Hold up!
If you leave the Duel Ring, you surrender. And we get your Star Chips.
What?
This Duel’s illegal!
Yeah!
Shit your mouths! No matter what the circumstances, he accepted the match, so it will continue.
Jounouchi…
You damn well better not lose to them!
You have something to protect!
You can’t lose track of that.
Honda…
So you gonna continue or give in?
I could care less either way, since your Star Chips are mine.
You've been spouting alot of crap since the start...
Who the hell are you?!
Me?
I’m Bandit Keith.
Bandit Keith?!
I’ve heard of him somewhere before…
Kaiba-kun mentioned a tournament that Pegasus won before.
He’s the Card Professional Pegasus beat!
That’s the same guy who’s been back-seat driving my Duel?
Well now that you know, you might as well give up.
I’ve given him the ultimate strategy.
You can’t win, no matter how hard you try.
It’s been decided long ago that the four of us would be going to Pegasus’ castle!
This is your grave!
So long as these Zombie Monsters are free to move on this Graveyard Field!
Graveyard Field…?
Hurry up and play your next card!
Shizuka…
Damn it all! I won’t lose!
You talk big for someone in such a terrible position.
What do you mean? You can’t hurt me if I put monsters in Defense Position!
But that won’t last forever.
What?
There’s still another card in his deck to make this combo perfect.
If he draws it, you’ll lose!
There’s more to his Ghost Combo?
Let’s go!
I did it, bro! It's the Defense Seal card!
Defense Seal?
That’s bad. If he plays that…
Next turn, you won’t be able to run into Defense Mode.
Mega-Plasmic Breathing!!
Zombie creatures, power-up!
Go, my invincible Dragon Zombie!
Kill off his last defense!
Zombie Deadly Breath!!
It’s over kid!
You can’t run now!
You can’t just give up, Jounouchi!
You can do it!
If you lose, you won’t forget it!
Of course!
I won’t give up!
Not until the very end!
Let’s go!
Come on out, Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
What? Why does this brat have such a rare card?
If I can’t defend, then I’ll attack!
Red-Eyes, slaughter that squash king!
This is bad…
His Attack Power’s higher!
Black Fire Bullet!
Alright!
Yes! Now the Zombie Monster’s Attack Points won’t increase anymore!
Pumpking was originally a Ghost Monster,
so I can’t revive him with Call of the Living Dead.
Don’t freak, Kotsuzuka.
Your Zombie Army is plenty powered up already.
That’s right!
Zombie's Deadly Breath!
Rot away, Red-Eyes!!
Red-Eyes!
Even Red-Eyes is no match!
My ultimate card, Red-Eyes…
This is the end, kid!
Jounouchi…
What do I do?
The only Monster Card I have in my hand is Kung-Fu Fighter Ultimator,
but his Attack Power is way too low…
Hurry up and play a card to end this.
Yugi, is there any way for Jounouchi to win?
Even if you ask me…
The power of his Zombie Army is practically unlimited,
and with that Trap Card there, he can’t go into Defense Mode.
Defense?
That’s it!
There’s a way, Jounouchi-kun!
There’s a card in your deck that can reverse this!
What?
Oh… Ain't you interesting.
Your name was Yugi, right?
You may have beaten Kaiba, but this combo’s perfect.
No way in hell are you gonna reverse this!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi…
Alright then!
I’ll believe your words!
This…
The Shield in the Right Hand, The Sword in the Left Hand?
A Magic Card that flips Attack and Defense…
I get it!
The Zombie Army may have unfathomable Attack Power,
but if it’s reversed with their Defense Power…
I’m gonna just gonna have to give it a go!
Kung-Fu Fighter Ultimator in Attack Mode!
So he’s the last sacrifice, huh?
And...!
I’ll play this Magic Card to turn the tables!
What?!
Go!!!
Dammit! Zombies are kindred spirits, unwilling to die, so…
The entire Zombie Army’s Attack went down to 0!
Ultimator’s Attack and Defense Points switch as well!
Here it comes, zombie freak!
Ultimate Screw Knuckle!
Zombies with 0 Attack Points won’t revive!
I… I lost…
Alright!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
I did it, Yugi!
Hey, we’re leaving!
Bro…
Bro!
Bandit Keith!
If you call yourself a Duelist, next time you’ll fight me fair and square!
“Fair and Square?”
Don’t make me laugh!
In a card game, the only damn thing that matters is outwitting your opponent.
All that matters is winning! No matter what methods you use!
Keith… I’ll beat you for sure!
Now I wonder if you’ll ever be able to fight me?
Jerk.
Yugi!
I’m sorry to have worried everyone.
Damn straight! Bakura nearly died looking for you.
It couldn’t be helped.
It wasn’t his fault.
Well, you beat them, so I’ll forgive you.
Seriously, that was amazing, Jounouchi!
You’re amazing, Jounouchi-kun!
It was all luck~.
It wasn’t luck!
It was your strong devotion and feeling that got you the victory.
Now I just need two more Star Chips.
Wait for me, Shizuka.
Let’s hurry up and get out of here.
Yeah!
It’s the exit!
W-What?!
Now they’ll be trapped in there forever!
Alright, good job!
Did we have to go so far…
Souta-kun!
B-Bro...
I can’t believe you lost…
No way…
I just did as you said—
SHUT UP!!!
Ten on the mark.
Although it was kinda underhanded, I get to go solo to Pegasus’ castle.
Just you wait, Pegasus.
I’ll beat you down!
Damn it! It’s not moving at all!
Are we trapped in here for good?
What are we gonna do?
Damn it!
Keith! Let us out! Let us out!
"Preview"
While searching for another exit to the cave,
we stumble across the Player Killers, the Labyrinth Brothers.
We have to win a Tag Duel, and have them tell us the way out,
or we’ll be trapped in here forever!
I can’t say that with a straight face!
Go, Yugi, Jounouchi!
If you combine your powers, you’ll definitely win!
Next time! "The Labyrinth Tag Duel"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship