"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Bonds"
I did it!
Oh! Awesome!
Hey! You brats are in the way!
Get outta the road!
Man! What the hell are they doing this early in the morning?!
You! Sorry, but you'll have to turn around!
What'd ya mean?
Right now, Kaiba Corporation has closed the entire city for their event.
Sorry.
They can do that for just one event?!
Well, Kaiba Corporation has bought this city.
W-What nonsense!
Even if you say that, there's nothing you can do.
Turn around.
O-O-Oi!
Man!
"Kaiba" this, "Kaiba" that... he's so full of himself!
Big brother we're almost as Domino Port.
Everyone... please be safe...
The man aiming for the God Cards and the leader of the Ghouls...
he was called "Malik", right?
What do you know about the man who owns Ra the Winged Dragon?
I've never seen him face-to-face.
All I know is that, like me, he owns a Millennium Item.
How ridiculous.
This talk of occult nonsense again?
Kaiba, you should have experienced the power of Pegasus's Millennium Item first hand.
My attack!
Devil Box!
Goodbye, Mokuba...
Goodbye, Yugi...
You have no cards left in your hand.
Therefore, you lose.
You shall suffer the same fate as Mokuba boy!
Mind Card!!
Your mind has now been sealed within this card.
You will now eternally become my servant,
forced to carry out my every bidding.
That was some kind of trick!
To believe or not to believe is your freedom, but...
My true identity is a soul trapped within the Millennium Puzzle.
What?!
Right. The me right now is Yugi, but also not Yugi at the same time.
Yugi Mutou awakened me when he completed the Millennium Puzzle.
I'm his other personality.
Impossible...!
If you're not Yugi, what the hell are you?!
More than likely...
The soul of a Pharaoh from Ancient Egypt who's lost his memories.
Pharaoh, you said?!
Pharaoh...?
That woman...
At that time, the woman named Ishizu showed me the Stone Tablet at Domino Museum.
Th-This is...!
They're exactly like Duel Monsters!
Yes.
Pegasus created Duel Monsters after viewing this palette.
Please look at this other palette.
This is what I wanted to show you.
Th-This is...!
Yugi...!
And the thing above him...!
Black Magician!
The names of the 18 pharaohs were recorded here.
In other words, the identity of the kings.
Kings?
However, no one knows anything about this king.
In other words, this is the only king to be completely erased from existence.
A nameless Pharaoh from 3,000 years ago.
I don't know what she said to you,
but it seems you have also been shown that image from the occult-obsessed woman named Ishizu.
No, the words Ishizu said to me were...
An enemy will soon appear before you.
One wielding a new Millennium Item.
And then he appeared.
I've been waiting for this moment!
Trap Card open!
Chain Destruction!!
Disappear!!
Impossible...
My... Exodia...
Help me!
He's here... He's here...!
The wadjet symbol of the Millennium Items?!
Malik-sama...!
We haven't met in a long time, Yugi.
The great Duelist who defeated Pegasus.
Whoops. I didn't mean to surprise you.
The man speaking with you isn't the one before you.
I'm in a place a bit further away.
I've implanted a bit of myself in him.
So I can control him whenever I want.
Who are you?!
Like you, I'm one of the ones chosen by the Millennium Items.
I'm controlling everything he does, with the power of the Millennium Rod!
Millennium Rod?!
In any case, I was merely introducing myself.
My name is Malik.
Malik!
Black Magician Girl, Direct Attack Player Pandora!
Black Burning!!
Why do you wanna kill us?! Answer me!
It doesn't concern you...
But I have business with the soul you contain!
Revenge...
I am the heir of the clan of Tomb Guardians who lived in darkness for 3,000 years.
And I will avenge them!
My clan must avoid all contact with the outside world,
living only to protect the Millennium Items we were handed...
And...
We must die for this fate.
We must return the Pharaoh's memory to his soul.
Memory...? Does that mean the Pharaoh's memory stone tablet
and the 7 Items are related?
Yes. I hold one of the seven secrets as well.
I must guard it, even if it means my life, until I present it to the Pharaoh's soul.
That's what I was taught as a child.
The problem is finding the Pharaoh's soul.
The only clue is written in the original Ancient Egyptian hieroglyphic text
of the Pert Em Heru, the Book of the Dead.
It says of the Pharaoh "You will know him by the three God Cards he wields."
In other words, the one who collects the three God Cards will be crowned the title "Pharaoh"
and regain the Millennium Items and his lost memories!
3 God Cards...?
Lost memory?!
I will put an end to the curse laid upon us...
And to do that, I will take revenge on the Pharaoh's soul and kill him a second time!
And if the prophecy says that the Pharaoh will wield the three God Cards...
...then I will obtain the cards and become the new Pharaoh!
Malik's objective isn't just to obtain the 3 God Cards...
His true objective is to kill me, the Pharaoh's soul!
Get him! Almost there!
A fight that has continued from over 3,000 years ago in Ancient Egypt...?
And Yugi's confrontation with the Ghouls is related to that?
Don't go buying this, Mokuba.
Yugi, do you really believe in such baseless stories?
But Kaiba, you saw it with your own eyes.
At that time...
I can't win...
I can't... defeat Osiris...
Stand up, Yugi!
Your life as a Duelist doesn't end here!
Kaiba!
If there's a god standing in your way...
Mow the god down!
I understand, Kaiba!
Just you wait!
I will now...
Defeat God!
Buster Blader, attack Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Dragon Buster Blade!!
This is my trump card!
The Magic Card Brain Control!
I Regenerate Summon this guy on my field!
What do you think happens next?
Revival Slime will revive again...
Damnit!
Osiris's Special Ability will activate again,
Revival Slime will be destroyed,
and then regenerated...
I then will have to draw 3 cards...
And then Osiris will attack once again!
This will continue infinitely...!
In an infinite loop!
One who can no longer draw a card from his Deck...
Can no longer continue playing the game!
I win, Malik!
He did it!
Yugi won!
Yugi!
Are you gonna try and take back the God Card?
You don't give up easily, Malik!
Using your friends, I can easily take back the God Cards.
The Ghoul Rare Hunters have been keeping a close eye on your friends.
I can use them whenever I want.
How far will you fall, Malik?!
It's your fault.
If you had lost to me here,
your precious friends would have been left out of this.
And then at that time...
Disappear, weaklings!
God Hand Crusher!!
Malik?!
Ma... li...
What the?
His personality's changed...!
Yeah.
Right now, he's being controlled by another person altogether.
Impossible!
By who, exactly?
The leader of the Ghouls!
Malik!
The man who owns the final God Card!
The owner of Ra the Winged Dragon?!
Pleased to meet you, Kaiba-kun.
It's stated in psychology that it's possible to control human beings through brainwashing.
If you truly won't believe me, that's fine.
But the fact that the Ghouls are now after Jounouchi-kun and the others because of me is reality.
I'll save them no matter what!
Jounouchi-kun. This is your card.
Yugi.
Right now I can't take Red-Eyes back.
Right now, if I took it back so easily, I won't be able to become a True Duelist.
And he won't approve either.
A True Duelist.
Even when you meet an evil Duelist, you always Duel fairly.
You taught me a lesson.
What I was missing before is a Duelist's pride.
Red-Eyes is an irreplaceable card to me.
He is a partner that has been with me until now.
That's why, I can't take him back now.
No. Even if I did take him back, Red-Eyes won't forgive me.
That's why, Yugi,
I'll leave that card with you for now.
I want to become a True Duelist.
No. In this Battle City, I willl show you.
Yugi. Wait for me until I win in this Battle Ground, until I can respect myself as a True Duelist.
When the time comes, please fight me again.
I understand.
I'll fight you again then, Jounouchi-kun!
Thank you, Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun, I'll wait for you.
I will properly look after your Red-Eyes.
And you, in order to realize yourself as a True Duelist,
engaged in painful fights,
in order to fight me again!
Here I go, my Battle Phase!
Both Monsters attack together!
Wyvern!
Dragon Sword!
Damage the Player!
Go, Swordsman of Landstar!
After this, the winner and loser will be determined!
I won't let you move on!
Trap Card open!
Activate Spiritual Operation!
Trap Card?
Monsters that have fallen into this Trap will become my servant for two turns.
I use Swordsman of Landstar as a sacrifice to Summon Android - Psycho Shocker!
Equipment Card "Amplifier"
I equip this on Psycho Shocker.
Psycho Shocker's Attack gains another 500 points.
What?!
Psychic Shocker, attack.
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Jounouchi-kun, it's your turn.
You can always surrender.
Surrender? Are you kidding?
I will definitely continue.
Attack, my queen!
Queen's Hell Breath!!
Panther Warrior is beaten!
My future...
Is this hideous monster really going to shatter it?
You can do it, Jounouchi!
You can't give up!
But...!
I can't do a single thing...!
Jounouchi!
It's not like you to just give up like this!
Weren't you going to become a True Duelist and battle Yugi again?!
True Duelist...!
Jounouchi-kun.
I'll properly look after this card until then.
That's right!
I made a promise with Red-Eyes and Yugi!
That the moment I become a True Duelist...
At that time, I'll fight you once more.
You can do it, Jounouchi!
Don't you lose to that little punk!
Jounouchi!
I won't give up!
I'll definitely continue onward!
Fortress Whale is fried to a crisp!
Alright!
Good job!
How's that, Kajiki?
Jounouchi, my turn
hasn't come to
an end yet!
I play the Magic Card Revival of the Dead!
I revive a Monster this turn!
So... that means...
Then... he'll revive Fortress Whale!
So it's useless, eh?
What's wrong?! Now hurry and come!
After all that boasting you did before, show me how you fight!
I can't afford to lose here!
I have my sea to fight against!
I can't give up until the very end!
Magic Card activate!
Hurricane!
What?!
After all, I can't let this card stay in the Graveyard.
Don't just stare! Now come and get me, Jounouchi!
Panther Warrior, attack!
Your true feelings...!
There's no way the Ghouls can match up to them!
I can see Domino Port!
Wait for me, Jounouchi-kun!
The one waiting for Yugi at Domino Port is...
Jounouchi, under the control of Malik!
The true Duel between Yugi and Jounouchi begins, with both of their lives on the line!
Stop it, you two!
This won't be a win like it was back in Duelist Kingdom!
For such a terrible match to begin...!
Next time!
The Cold-hearted Duel
Yugi VS Jounouchi
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...