Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Location of the Finals - Alcatraz"
I apologize, Mokuba.
I'll give your body back now.
Noah... What are you going to do?
I'm going back to Father.
But...! You...!
It was only for a short while, but I got a real body again.
I was happy.
Don't go, Noah!
I think I've been able
to get my heart back.
It's all thanks to you, Mokuba. Thank you!
I need to get a hold of myself.
I need to live in
the Real World for Noah, too.
And to do that, I can't rely on my big brother all the time.
What's wrong, Mokuba?
Uh... It's nothing...
We're almost there, big brother!
Yeah... It's the pitiful wreckage symbolizing Gozaburo's remains.
This island, Alcatraz, was built as a military industrial facility by Kaiba Corporation.
Atop the wreckage stands the Duel Tower.
That will be the final battlefield for this Battle City Tournament.
The time has finally come to settle things.
Malik holds the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra.
This is the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Yugi holds Osiris the Heaven Dragon.
And I hold Obelisk the Great War God.
The one to obtain all three cards...
...as well as stand atop the Duel Tower in victory, will be me!
Big brother...
Just you wait, Alcatraz!
The climax of this fight is about to start!
Big brother...
What's Mai's condition?
I see...
Mai...
Malik, what the hell did you do to her?!
As we speak, that woman is falling deeper and deeper into darkness.
She'll wander in immeasurable loneliness, doomed to never regain conscious again.
If you defeat me, there's a chance she'll recover.
Wait for me, Mai!
I'll kick Malik's sorry ass and save you!
Big brother, you've got to win!
Yeah! I'll take care of it!
It's finally begun... the final battle.
Dear sister, you lost so soon in this fight that you have the pleasure of quietly watching from the sidelines.
Not a care in the world!
Malik!
Where is Rishid?
I do not know.
Don't play dumb with me!
It's so obvious that you were the one who hid him!
Even if I did know, there's no way I would ever tell you.
I thought you'd act this way...
However...
And this is one of them.
This originally belonged to you.
You gave your Millennium Tauk to the Pharaoh, did you not?
It's written all over your face right now!
You have nothing to fend off this Millennium Rod with!
It would be a simple task for me to brainwash you and take my time having you tell me where Rishid is.
I love that look of fear on your face!
I never thought I would see you making that face, dear sister...
But...
I have no time for such acts of pleasure.
Attention! We are about to arrive at Alcatraz.
All participating Duelists should prepare their decks.
Rishid was struck by the wrath of Ra.
It won't be all that easy to wake him up.
In fact, he may never wake up...
And if you're waiting for Kaiba or Yugi to save the day, you may as well save the effort.
Before the Ra I hold, all that awaits them is failure!
Now them, I'm off.
After I'm done crushing the Pharaoh in the upcoming Duels, I'll take my sweet time killing Rishid.
Dear sister, you had better keep your mouth shut and watch closely.
Watch as the little hope you have left is swallowed by the darkness of death!
Malik...
So Bakura-kun really disappeared...
Yeah. Bakura lost to Malik's Dark Game.
Anyone who loses a Dark Game won't return until the one who created it is defeated.
So you came here, Yugi?
Where did you send Bakura?!
Who knows?!
Nobody knows where those who lose a Dark Game are sent!
I wonder where Bakura-kun is...
There have been so many sacrifices in these Duels...
I'm sorry.
Other me?
All of this happened because of the memory I lost.
Malik hates me.
And he's sacrificing those who own Millennium Items or who are involved in some way.
He wants to bury everything in darkness.
All of it is my-
You're wrong! You're not at fault here!
Partner...
How can you be responsible for memories you don't even remember?!
Aren't you always trying to protect everyone?!
And there still might be a way to save them all.
So don't you go giving up on me!
You're right.
All we can do is go forward bravely.
We wouldn't be True Duelists if we gave up in the middle of the game.
There you are!
We've been looking for you, Yugi!
We're about to arrive at our destination.
While we're here, I wonder where Bakura went off to...
I wonder if he'll be alright with those wounds he had...
I just hope he's not being controlled by the Millennium Ring again...
It's okay! Bakura-kun will be back before you know it!
Yup! We just gotta believe in him!
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Yup!
Now! It's time to go, Duelists!
I give you permission to step into my fortress of pride!
So this is it...
It's the location of the Final, right?
Man, it's so big! It almost seems to go straight through the sky!
You said it.
Right! This is a battleground where Duelists battle for their place at the top!
The Duel Tower!
Kaiba-kun.
I'll defeat you, Yugi!
And I'll be the one standing at the top!
Kaiba! Don't forget about me!
When I'm done kicking your ass,
you'll know that you're nothing but the king of this rubble!
You'll end up on the scrapheap of Duelist history, you deadbeat...
Why don't you go bury
yourself in the ruins?!
WHAT?!
Cut it out, Jounouchi!
Y-Y-You know...! I'm also one of the final participants!
Relax!
He's right! You'll settle things in the Duels, right?
Tch! Fine!
Then let's get moving!
Follow me.
The atmosphere here really puts you on edge, doesn't it...?
How about you, his majesty?
Malik! You bastard!
OOH-AH!!
Honda... you're still
talking like a monkey?
By the way, Mr. host!
Have you decided the order of battle for the Semi-Finals?
Just hold your horses!
You'll find out what's gonna happen when you get to the tower and learn your fate!
By fate, I presume you mean all of your losses and deaths...
All Duelists and observers, welcome to Duel Tower.
We will now hold the Battle City Tournament Semi-Finals!
There's nothing in here.
So how exactly are they going to Duel?
You'll see very soon.
The four remaining Duelists
will head to the top of the tower through four different doors!
Four doors...?
Please choose one out of the four doors presented before you!
None of the doors give one any sort of advantage in this Duel.
So please don't worry...
Even if you say that,
it's still hard to choose.
Which one are you gonna pick, Yugi?
I'm fine with either one.
Really?
Then...! "Eeny, meeny, miny, moe..."
An indecisive, deadbeat fool like yourself can just take whichever one is left.
"...catch a tiger by the toe... If he hollers let him go,"
"Eeny, meeny, miny, moe!"
Cool! I pick that door!
Hey! I just picked that door, ya jerk!
Jounouchi-kun, I'm heading in.
H-Hey! Yugi!
Guess this is the only one left...
Alright! We're headed this way!
Jounouchi, sometimes the last one is the luckiest one!
Just do your best.
This is... a Card Battle System?
I wonder what they're up to...
This way! Over here!
Wow! It's so high, you can't see the ceiling!
They're gonna do this inside here?
Now that you mention it, how are the match-ups going to be decided?
That is about to be decided.
Jounouchi?!
What the?! What the heck?!
What are you doing, Jounouchi?
Like I know?!
Oi, Kaiba! Explain!
Be quiet already! It's about to be explained so even a deadbeat can understand it!
Bastard! Wanna say that again?!
For proud Duelists such as yourselves,
it would be unfair to decide your opponents with a mere lottery.
So the Semi-Finals shall be decided with a game!
Decide our opponents for the Semi-Finals with a game...?
The rules are simple!
This will be a four-way Duel between the remaining Duelists.
The first two to arrive at the top...
...as well as the two
remaining at the bottom...
...will be paired up for the Semi-Finals!
Meaning... it's a four-person Battle Royale!
Of course the game will be Duel Monsters.
You will start with 4,000 Life Points.
As you lose Life Points, your gondolas
will climb higher and higher toward the top of the tower.
In other words, the two who lose first will be the first to the top.
Let me explain the rules.
Each player will use your regular 40-card deck which you prepared for the game tournament.
Shuffle it and set it in the Duel Disk.
When you connect your Duel Disk to the gondola,
your cards, as well as the other players', will be displayed on the viewing screen.
All four players will take separate turns,
You may attack any player you choose.
The first two Duelists who rise to the top will be in the first match of the Semi-Finals!
Wow, that's a lot better than I was expecting.
So the outcome of this match has nothing to do with the tournament rankings.
No, you're wrong.
This is the most important Duel of the tournament!
What do you mean by that, Otogi?
It means you get to choose the opponent you want to Duel.
For example, let's say Jounouchi-kun wants to fight Yugi-kun first in the Semi-Finals,
The other two could end up supporting Yugi so they can fight him.
And on the other hand, the two could gang up on him and attack all at once.
I get it.
So this Battle Royale is all about who you crush first...
So that means the
first person they'd go after...
What the hell are you staring at?!
Hey man, do your best so you don't lose in the first round!
Can it!
Talking all kinds of crap down there...
The objective of this game is to split us into pairs...
With good strategy, it should be possible to choose your opponent...
Who do I want to fight
in the Semi-Finals?
There's only one person it can be...
Malik's Ra card has overwhelming power...
In order to beat him, I'm going to need two God Cards...
So my opponent for these Semi-Finals has to be the other God Card wielder.
It has to be Yugi!
My opponent, eh...?
Yugi... I've wanted to kill you for so long...
Yugi! I got this far in Battle City because I want to fight you!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
I understand.
We'll fight each other then, Jounouchi-kun!
Thank you, Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun, I'll wait for you.
I'll take care of your Red-Eyes until then!
Mhm-hm!
I remember our promise!
And I haven't forgotten about my Red-Eyes you're holding onto!
I have to fight you in order to get him back! And I have to win!
But to save Mai, I've got to beat him!
Malik!
Are you all ready?
We will now decide who goes first and the order of play amongst the four of you!
And to do that...?!
Each player must choose one Monster Card from your deck!
Whoever has the highest Attack Power takes the first turn!
However, that Monster Card must be removed from your deck for the duration of this Duel!
You have to sacrifice a Monster with high Attack Power in order to go first...!
If you get the initiative, you can strike the first blow against any opponent you want...
You're bound to take
the lead by doing that...
Getting the upper hand is worth it...
What do I do?
Which card...?
The mind games have begun!
Now please present your card!
It's just a card I got as an ante...
I don't care if I lose it.
I've got the first strike!
I don't wanna give up any of my cards with high Attack Points...
The order has been decided!
Seto Kaiba will be taking the first turn!
Then Malik Ishtar...
Yugi Mutou...
...and Katsuya Jounouchi in the rear!
There's two players to avoid in the Semi-Finals...
I have to make sure they end up fighting each other in the first game...
Him...
And that deadbeat who's not even a Duelist!
As a Duelist, I want to fight Yugi...
I want to so bad, I can taste it!
But before that...
I...
Who should I fight against?
Other me...
Are you having trouble deciding?
Partner!
Yeah, to be honest, I'm having trouble.
I have many reasons to fight all of them!
No, there's a few objectives I have to fulfill!
It says of the Pharaoh "You will know him by the three God Cards he wields."
In other words, the one who collects the three God Cards will be crowned the title "Pharaoh"
and regain the Millennium Items and his lost memories!
In order to regain my memories, I must face my true enemy, Malik!
This time we'll fight each other fair and square, as True Duelists.
My promise to Jounouchi-kun as a Duelist!
I'm sure you know...
In this final tournament, we are about to step foot into the domain of the gods!
The winner will be determined by the three God Cards!
I will beat you and Malik, obtain the three God Cards,
and become the world's strongest Duelist!
My fated battle with Kaiba!
I have more than enough reasons to fight all of them!
Yup! In that case, just fight whoever you feel you must!
The person I'm going to fight is...
The Battle City Final Match Preliminary Round will be held as a Battle Royale!
Duel start!!
I go first!
Draw!
I place one card face-down and Summon Blood Vorse!
Attack Mode!
Turn end!
I can't attack
a player on the first turn...
But as soon as my next turn comes, I'll make my move...
My turn then, is it?
Draw!
I Summon Newdoria!
In Defense Mode!
Turn end!
This fiend's Special Ability
is quite useful!
My turn! Draw!
In order to determine
the opponent I'll fight...
I'll follow the vector
of my Duelist's soul!
I Summon Big Shield Gardna in Defense Position!
I'll also play two face-down cards!
Turn end!
My turn!
My hand sucks!
I don't even have a
Monster Card to sacrifice!
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
My turn!
The ecosystem of battle!
The food chain of battle!
You weak small fry! I'll show you that barking dogs are no match for a lion!
Blood Vorse! Go ahead and Direct Attack this deadbeat of a nobody!
Crap! Jounouchi doesn't have any Wall Monsters to protect him!
Jounouchi!
Go! Blood Vorse!
I won't let you!
Reverse card, open!
Permanent Trap!
The Regulation of Tribe!
What?!
Yugi!
The chosen Type selected by this Trap Card cannot attack!
And the Tribe-Type I've chosen is the Beast-Warriors!
Yugi!
As a Duelist...
...I've chosen to fulfill the promise I made to my friend!
The Battle Royale is meant to determine the match-ups for the Semi-Finals.
As a result, the selected four battle it out viciously.
Yugi intends to keep his promise with Jounouchi.
But Jounouchi intends to face Malik in order to save Mai-san.
Kaiba-kun aims to face Yugi so he can win his Osiris and use it to fight Ra.
And Malik intends to kill them all!
And as a result, the Duel soars towards its climax!
Next time!
"Battle Royale!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise