Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
"The Final Trial"
This place...
The Stone Slab of Memories...
I guess we're back in our world.
Guys...
Is the other Yugi...
I mean, Atem.
Yeah. Did he get back to us okay?
Other Me...
I'm right here.
Atem!
Thank goodness!
Thank you, everyone.
If you all hadn't followed me, there's a good chance I wouldn't have won that Dark Game.
Why are you being so darn formal?
We're always with you.
He's right. Because you're our precious friend.
And yet, you got your butt controlled by Bakura so easily.
D-Don't keep bringing that up!
Besides, you seem to always become a problem for us every time!
Cut it out, Jounouchi!
As the Pharaoh 3,000 years ago, I had my priests...
And now I have everyone here...
Atem...
You think it's okay to keep calling you "Other Me" for now?
Because we're both
still inside this same body.
Partner...
You bet!
But I'm really glad you made it back here safely.
Yeah. I wasn't sure what would happen there for a while.
That wasn't just a dream...
Yugi!
It's something you need, right?
The Millennium Eye?
Why the heck did you have this?
Kaiba!
Hey, Kaiba!
Hold it!
Give us an explanation here!
Bakura!
Huh? Everyone...
Where are we?
Where? You...
...don't remember anything?
Oh yeah...
I was being chased by something...
After that...
Stay with us, Bakura!
Bakura!
I'm so hungry~!
The guy just passed out!
Bakura-kun!
Couldn't be helped.
Anyway, let's carry him outside.
Yeah!
It'd be better if you hang onto this.
Yeah.
Let's move, Honda!
Yup!
The evil within the Millennium Ring has disappeared...
Bakura became a victim in all this again.
Anzu! Give us a hand!
O-Okay!
Shadi...
Your soul has also disappeared, hasn't it?
Thank you...
Seto...
The world of memories is different from the real world,
but I can tell that after I was sealed within the Millennium Puzzle,
you became a great Pharaoh and protected the country.
And you left evidence of that engraved within this Stone Slab of Memories.
Now that the previously sealed Zorc has been destroyed,
I must also...
Other Me...
Let's go, Partner.
Kaiba.
Pharaoh!
I assume that you were able to retrieve your memories?
I was.
That means our duties as Tomb Guardians has truly come to an end.
No, all seven of the Millennium Items have been gathered together.
All that remains...
Yes.
Before anyone can get their hands on them again, I must seal them with my own hands.
By "seal", you mean...
That's my final duty.
I understand, but...
Doesn't that mean your soul has to return to the Afterlife, Atem?
Pharaoh.
The Stone Slab of the Underworld we Tomb Guardians have been protecting has
been brought back to the Temple of the Underworld.
The Stone Slab of the Underworld?
It is written in the
Temple of the Underworld...
"Placing the seven Millennium Items here will connect the Door of the Afterlife.
The final necessary key to open it is the Pharaoh's name."
The Pharaoh's name?
Atem...
Atem?
So that is the lost name of the Pharaoh?
Then that means all of the necessary conditions have been met.
Your decision has not changed?
It hasn't.
Then we will guide you to the Temple of the Underworld.
The heck?
We're not going by plane?
We can only get to the stone slab by boat.
It doesn't really matter, does it?
A boat ride could be pretty sweet!
The hell are you being so laid back for?
Ah, yeah, guess there's no need to rush.
You said it!
In Ancient Egypt, people believed that ships carried Pharaohs or people back to the Gods,
traveling from this world to the Land of the Dead.
The Land of the Dead...
It is also believed that this "Land of the Dead" is located only where the sun sets.
That is where the Temple of the Underworld lies.
So you can say that us going there by ship carries with it a separate meaning altogether.
Hey~!
Yugi!
Over here, over here~!
Grandpa?!
Otogi?!
Even Mokuba?
You really took your time, guys.
Big Brother!
Mokuba...
We couldn't find you guys, so we've been waiting in the city for a while now.
What are you doing here?
Well, after you all left, I started feeling like I should go to Egypt myself...
And I ended up coming myself.
I just happened to contact you guys so I could meet with you.
I had no idea you all had come here.
So I ended up tagging along.
And we met Mokuba-kun when we arrived at the airport.
Brother, you just left without telling anyone.
Sorry...
This was something I had to settle on my own no matter what.
I know. But you had me worried.
When I got here, I couldn't get in contact with you.
But Otogi...
You didn't have to come
all the way to Egypt!
What's that supposed to mean?
This is a very important time for Yugi-kun, isn't it?
Don't you think it's a little cruel to not tell us about this?!
I'm sorry, Otogi-kun!
I informed all the others about this.
Though it was pretty sudden.
The others?
All the people who are involved with Yugi-kun in some way.
Since I contacted them last-minute, there wasn't enough time for them to come...
But I know they're all thinking about you.
No matter how far away they are...
It is finally time, eh, Yugi boy?
Thinking back, it may have all been the work of fate.
When I received the Millennium Eye during my trip to Egypt...
...and finding the stone tablet in which I got the hints to create Duel Monsters.
All of it was for this day.
I bet fate was leading me to you.
It's pretty, but it also has a really sad feeling to it.
Yugi...
Hey, you over there! Why the heck did you guys come along?
It doesn't really matter, does it?
Right, Brother?
Kaiba-kun...
He is also hoping to bring his involvement in all of this to an end.
As one of those wound up in this destiny.
Destiny...?
Yugi.
There's something else I need to discuss with you.
Malik...
There is something else written on the epitaph in the Temple of the Underworld.
It talks about the "Rite of the Duel".
"Rite of the Duel"?
A Ceremonial Battle?
I would like the Pharaoh to hear this.
It is written as such on the epitaph...
"The Pharaoh's soul cannot start his homeward journey
to eternal rest while
still holding his sword."
What does that mean?
The sword symbolizes the tools to fight in this world.
For us Duelists, it would be our cards.
Our cards...
I must be bested at cards.
It means I have to lose in a Duel.
So it means someone has to Duel with the Other Me and win?!
I see!
If you consider the other Yugi-kun's Dueling history,
his spirit won't be released unless someone can overcome him.
But who could possibly...?
None of the Duelists here could defeat him.
Hey, Yugi...
Do you remember?
Sailing under the stars like this...
It reminds me of when we went to the Duelist Kingdom!
Yup.
Yugi, will you listen to
the one desire I have?
Could you toss the Millennium Items over the edge?
Just kidding!
It was a joke!
Jounouchi-kun!
Awrighty, it's decided!
I'm gonna Duel with Atem!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Don't be crazy!
Call it crazy all you like!
If I fight Atem, he'll-
You stay back, Deadbeat!
Kaiba!
If this is really the end for him...
...I'm going to settle my vendetta with him!
My connection with him!
Kaiba-kun...
Kaiba! You jerk!
I just got through saying-
Bastard!
I came along to settle the score with you and the other Yugi!
This time I will leave as the victor!
Kaiba-kun...
You're right.
You've been constantly fighting against the Other Me up until now.
Then it's decided.
But I apologize.
I'm going to fight him.
My other self!
What?!
Yugi!
I can't let anyone else do this.
I get it.
Looks like you've made up your mind.
Jounouchi-kun...
Cut the bullshit!
There's no way in hell someone like you can beat the other Yugi!
Knock it off, Kaiba!
But this is something I have to do myself, no matter what!
Yugi!
Mokuba!
Kaiba!
You asshole!
Use the cards inside this briefcase.
If you're going to Duel him, a half-assed Duel will not cut it!
Use these to build the perfect deck.
Thank you, Kaiba-kun.
But...
I won't be needing them.
What!?
I'm going to use the cards we've been sharing this entire time
to build the deck I'll fight the Other Me with.
Yugi!
Do whatever you please!
Wait up, Brother!
Kaiba-kun...
Yes?
Sorry, but can I bother you for a minute?
Anzu?
Sure. What is it?
Ishizu-san said we'll arrive Temple of the Underworld in the morning.
Okay...
So you're really going to fight with him, huh...? With the other Yugi?
Yeah...
This is the last thing I
can do for the Other Me.
That can't-
What did the other Yugi say about it?
He hasn't shown himself from the depths of my heart.
He's going to stay there until I finish putting my deck together.
I see...
I guess they've both decided to go through with this...
Anzu?
N-No, it's nothing!
I just wanted to tell you about us arriving tomorrow morning.
Well then, don't push yourself too much.
Good night.
Right, good night...
Anzu... You wanted to see the Other Me, didn't you...?
Sorry.
The other Yugi... Atem... doesn't belong in this era...
He has to return to his original home - his place to return.
I shouldn't try to stop him...
When I got the Millennium Puzzle from Grandpa, it was in pieces.
And on the day I finally completed it after eight years...
If I hadn't taken you into my heart that day, you probably would still be trapped there.
And I became more courageous after being with you.
I believe I've gotten stronger, if only a little bit.
And that's why I'll use all my strength to help you now.
Jounouchi!
You sure you're okay with this?
This is your last chance to fight against the other Yugi-kun.
Back then, I was still so weak!
I was a hack who even lost against elementary schoolers.
But you know...
That all came to an end.
While fighting against the other Yugi...
I had some fun Duels. And I got stronger.
I made the guy my goal.
Jounouchi...
And that's why I want
to do what he wants.
Yugi's the only one who can take him on.
Yeah!
You said it.
There's a very high chance he'll be using the gods in this Duel.
How will you fight them, Yugi?
Do you honestly think you can win against the gods?
Up until now, I've always prepared my deck with the Other Me.
But this is now my deck.
It's a deck I made in order to fight the Other Me!
It's done!
Have you finished making your deck yet, Partner?
Other Me!
You waited until I completed my deck, didn't you?
Yeah.
I couldn't watch the opponent I'm about to fight making his deck, after all.
Thank you for taking my final trial.
Mm-hmm!
I'm going to draw out all of my strength to fight with you!
Okay!
Now it's your turn to make your deck.
I should warn you, though.
I know all the weaknesses of the deck you've been using.
I made my new deck while coming up with strategies to use against it.
If you take this lightly,
you're in for some hurt!
Well, I'm about to head for the depths of my heart.
In truth, I don't want to fight you.
But if I don't, you'll never be free.
You'll always be trapped in my heart.
Defeating you is my duty.
There isn't much time left...
I'd really like to use this little time to talk with you!
But...
As a Duelist, I made the decision to fight. I must stay silent!
I've fought many
enemies along the way...
But this is by far the most difficult battle of them all.
This Ceremonial Battle...
Partner accepted this battle, which will determine my fate.
This ordeal is not mine alone.
Within this box lies the deck he put all of his heart into.
Partner...
I'll pull together all of my feelings and put them into this deck!
It's finished! My strongest deck!
This game will decide my fate!
Will I win and stay here?
Or will I lose and head to the future?
I challenge you, Partner!
You're late, Yugi!
Everyone!
Yugi...
Now let's get outta here!
Okay!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
This is the other Yugi's final trial.
The Ceremonial Battle!
But why does Yugi have to fight the other Yugi?
And if Yugi wins, the other Yugi will...
After placing the seven Millennium Items on the Stone Slab of the Underworld,
their battle has finally begun!
Which one of them should we even root for?
Next time!
"The Fated Last Duel"
Duel standby!