I can't afford to lose here!
I have my sea to fight against!
I can't give up until the very end!
Magic Card activate!
Hurricane!
What?!
After all, I can't let this card stay in the Graveyard.
Don't just stare! Now come and get me, Jounouchi!
Panther Warrior, attack!
I'll be sure to cherish this card!
I'm countin' on ya!
Next time, I'll be sure to win!
I'll continue to get even stronger!
"Spell of the Mask:
Skyscraper Duel"
I did it, Shizuka!
I finally made it into the tournament Finals!
Oh, amazing!
Congratulations, big brother!
Well, things are just starting from here on out.
But you were able to defeat a bunch of really strong people, right?
You're really amazing!
R-Really?
I'm happy to hear that from you.
I got 6 Puzzle Cards.
And I've grown a bit as a Duelist.
Big brother.
What's up?
Can I come watch you in the finals?
But you're still not recovered yet, right?
Yeah...
But the doctor said my eyes will be alright.
And I promised!
That the first thing I saw when I took off the bandages would be my big brother Dueling!
I see.
Alright, I got it.
It's too dangerous for you to come by yourself.
Look, I'll come up to get you.
Thank you, big brother!
Yahooo~!
Hey! What the hell are you doing to my cell phone?!
Shizuka's coming to watch me Duel in the finals!
Shizuka-chan can see again?
Yeah, the higher-ups said her eyes will be just fine.
That's great to hear!
But I want to go pick her up,
but I have to head to the finals,
and there's no way I'll let her come alone.
I'll do it! ME!
Just leave the Shizuka-chan situation to me!
Hey! Honda!
Geez...
Yugi...
I'll be able to fulfill my promise with you.
Just wait.
Bakura-kun!
Bakura!
What's wrong?
Are you alright, Bakura?
What a terrible wound...!
He seems to have been attacked by someone.
Thank goodness.
Do you guys know this person?
Who's the bastard that did this?
Jounouchi-kun...
Bakura, what happened?
I-I don't know...
I don't remember.
I treated his injury, but it would be best to take him to a hospital.
That's true.
Sorry to have troubled you.
Just leave the rest to me.
Jounouchi.
Give me a hand.
Okay.
Leave Bakura-kun to me.
We're counting on you, gramps!
They must be around here.
Yeah.
Our Satellite Search System should be able to catch any Duel your friend engages in.
There's no doubt.
To be able to care so much for a nobody like him...
He's one guy that's hard to understand.
Thank you.
Uh, umm...
By the way, we haven't heard your name yet.
I'm Namu.
Nice to meet you.
It's Jounouchi.
Anzu.
Seriously, thank you.
No way.
I just did what anyone would do.
You're a Duelist.
Yeah...
Though please know I'm not very good,
so don't try to fight me or anything.
Too bad,
but I already qualified.
That's amazing! You must be strong!
I'd like to hear some advice from you.
Sure, it's fine if I give you some pointers.
We look almost like friends, don't we?
Yeah! We're friends!
Yup!
We're going, Namu.
Y-Yes!
Friends, eh?
Malik-sama!
We confirmed that Kaiba really does hold Obelisk.
I see.
Why is this Kaiba man able to wield Obelisk?
Not just any being can use the God Cards.
They choose their wielders.
You won't have to worry about that when we get Obelisk back.
It will be actually be rather humorous when he falls.
Can you take them back?
Obelisk the Giant War God...
And Osiris the Heaven Dragon that was taken by Yugi.
Of course.
If we use the God Seal Deck you prepared for us.
Alright.
You guys take the front line.
But don't go killing them off now.
The Pharaoh must endure suffering I inflict upon him.
So he feels the pain my tribe has endured protecting him.
I will then finish him off myself.
In case they happen to fail...
I have other body guards...
In order to make up for it, these guys...
Hey, Jounouchi-kun!
What's up?
I know this is a bit sudden,
but I was wondering if you could give me some Duel advice now.
Sure!
Sure thing!
I'd like to win at least once in Battle City.
You still have a chance.
If you take my advice, you might even make it into the finals.
Jounouchi-kun!
Anzu!
Guys...
Where'd you go?
You're talking a little arrogant, you know.
Is that alright?
Just leave it to me!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
What the hell are you guys doing?!
Are you guys the Ghouls?!
You're after Jounouchi-kun's rare cards, aren't you?!
Anzu-chan!
Jounouchi-kun!
Hurry and get out of here!
Namu-kun!
Stop it, you jerks!
How dare you do that to my friend?!
I won't bow down to an organization operating in darkness!
It's time I pay you back!
How's that?!
Anzu!
J-Jounouchi...
That's low! Let go of Anzu!
Jounouchi!
Namu-kun!
Hello?
Anzu?
Y-Yugi...
Hello?
Hello?!
Yugi...!
Help me...!
Anzu?
Anzu!
Anzu!!
Using your friends, I can easily take back the God Cards.
The Ghoul Rare Hunters have been keeping a close eye on your friends.
I can use them whenever I want.
Now!
If you don't hurry up and find your friends,
something bad might happen to them!
Malik!
Could it be the Ghouls have already...
Anzu didn't answer her cell phone.
They may have already been attacked by the Ghouls...!
Don't panic, Yugi.
I told Mokuba to contact me as soon as they found their location.
We'll find their location.
But tell me how it feels.
To walk side-by-side your enemy.
I tremble with desire...
Right now...
I can't think of anything else other than how much I want to defeat you.
Kaiba.
Right now I can only think of Jounouchi-kun and the others.
Big brother!
Mokuba, is it?
It's strange...
I've lost complete trace of Jounouchi and the others.
After his Duel earlier, Jounouchi's Duel Disk seems to have been locked...
I'm going back to Headquarters to search for alternatives!
Got it.
Good work, Mokuba.
We can't find the nobody's location.
Kaiba Corporation's Satellite System is perfect, but still...
You guys are...!
What's wrong?
You seem very happy today.
Big brother was able to make it to the Battle City finals!
Wow, that's amazing!
Yeah!
So I'm going to watch big brother in the finals.
Shizuka-chan, you made up your mind about removing the bandages?
I have the courage to do so if it's for big brother.
They're here.
Alright.
Why don'tcha guide em to the Duel Arena?
Leave it ta me!
Ghouls?!
Look at that!
That's...!
Mokuba!
Damn you, Ghouls!
You bastards!
If you dare harm Mokuba, I won't hold back in the least bit!
I'll use the entire influence of Kaiba Corporation,
and completely crush you all!
How scary!
But if you dare touch us, your cute little brother will...
Damn you...!
We'll be waiting for you atop that skyscraper over there.
If you don't show up, you don't know what will happen.
Mokuba!
You're to come as well, Yugi!
Ya better come if you want to ever see those friends 'a yours again.
What?!
So everyone really is...!
They ain't gettin' in the way.
Now hurry along!
To the real Duel Arena!
Yugi!
We have to go!
Right!
Let's crush them with everything we've got!
But don't misunderstand me.
I'm going for Mokuba.
And you're going for those annoying bastards you call friends.
I understand.
Good of you guys to come.
But we are yet to introduce ourselves.
We are the warriors of the Ghouls.
Mask of Light.
Mask of Darkness.
We are a Tag Team assembled for the sole purpose of getting the God Cards back!
Now then. Allow me ta explain the rules of this match.
This'll be a Tag Duel; us against the both of you.
Any Duelist to lose all their Life Points first will be removed from the game.
The remaining player must then work harder to defeat the opposing team.
But be careful.
Cuz losin' in this game means death.
The building we're fighting on is 300 meters above the ground.
On top of that, there's nothin' separating you from the solid ground if you were to fall.
Meaning the only thing holding up our very lives...
Are these glass windows, and nothing more.
Every Duelist's glass block has been equipped with a bomb.
The moment the Life Counter reaches 0,
the player's glass square will shatter!
The players will then fall right through and plummet to their deaths!
So that makes this an "Explosive Tag Match of Death"!
Ain't it entertaining?!
Don't got any comebacks?
Is that all you had to say?
You'd better tell me where Mokuba is.
Right!
When this Duel ends, though.
In the small chance you guys are able to win,
he will of course be returned to you safely.
Looks like you Ghouls lack the most pride out of anyone.
In that case, my Deck will answer you with all my anger!
You really think you can beat us?
With my Mask Sealing Deck that holds the power of restricting,
ya can't use your God Cards!
There's no way you can win while facing the Mask of Light and Darkness Tag Team!
Here I go!
Let's Duel!
It's my turn first.
In a Duel Monsters Tag Battle,
the rule states that each team's players fight turns opposite from each other.
Draw card.
I set 2 cards.
Turn over.
Yugi, it's your turn.
Reverse cards?
Draw!
My card is...
Magnet Warrior Beta in Defense Mode.
Beta the Magnet Warrior
Turn over.
All players are unable to attack within the first turn.
What kind of strategy will they play?
My turn!
Shining Abyss! Defense Mode!
The moment Partner Summoned his Monster...
Magic Card?!
The Magic Card Mask of Brutality!
My Monster powers up because of that Mask Card!
What?!
Within one turn, they were able to play a Monster with 2600 Attack Points!
But, the drawback is that the Monster equipped with this card will cause us
to lose 1000 Life Points on our every Standby Phase, however...
You don't need to worry about that, Partner.
I'll also set the Continuous Magic Masked Doll.
This doll will now take all negative effects caused by our Mask Cards.
Which means the negative effects of Mask of Brutality have been negated.
You're the best, Partner.
Did you see?
This is me and Partner's Combination Play!
I see.
Within their Tag Duel,
they hold complete teamwork with one another, huh?
Nonsense.
Teamwork only holds one back in a fight.
Kaiba...
Yugi...
You are simply a tool I need to obtain victory.
I'll only need my power to win against these Ghoul weaklings anyway!
Here I come!
My turn!
Reverse card set!
I then Summon the Blood Demon - Blood Vorse!
I put this guy in Attack Mode and end my turn!
Attack Mode...
Is he luring the opponents to attack so he can play his reverse?
I already have a more powerful Monster in my hand...
Next turn I'll sacrifice Blood Vorse...
and Summon it.
Next turn he plans to sacrifice that Monster,
and Summon a High-Level Monster?
But that ain't gonna be that easy!
These guys have the advantage when it comes to a Tag Duel...
And in our case, Kaiba is fighting alone.
Can I really save Jounouchi-kun and the others in this situation?
Mokuba-kun was caught too?!
Just why are the Ghouls after us all anyway?
At the same time, Yugi and Kaiba-kun face a big obstacle against the Masked Rare Hunters!
Their Sacrifice Summon has been sealed,
so they can't Summon any High-Level Monsters!
Yugi and Kaiba-kun need to work together, but...
Kaiba-kun...
Next time!
The Sealed God Cards
Duel standby!