Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
I've taken over Kaiba's Duel and Noah throws a barrage of attacks at me from his Spirit Monsters!
If I'm careless,
I'll be finished with one strike!
Even after I got an advantage with Cyber Pod's Effect,
Noah's Deck Master Ability saved him,
and the gap between Noah's Life Points and mine just got even more outrageous!
But the odds were against me right from the start.
Either way, I can't afford to lose this Duel!
"10000 Life Points VS 100!!"
-Yugi!
Yugi-san!
It's over, Yugi!
Trap Card, activate!
I won!
Now I've achieved a complete victory!
Yugi!
-Yugi!
What's wrong, Noah?
I'm still very much alive!
That can't be! I just hit Kuriboh, of all things!
Take a good look at my side!
A Trap Card!
Indeed! It's called Strength Increasing Medicine Super Z!
This launches when I take 2000 points of damage or greater from my opponent.
Before the damage is calculated, you increase your life by 4000 points.
So my Life rose to 4100 points before I took the damage.
What a pity!
It looks like you made a major miscalculation in your prediction!
But while you are breathing a sigh of relief right now...
...you've only prolonged your situation to witness an even crueler reality.
What?
The fact that I laid damage on you in that battle hasn't changed.
As such, my Deck master Ability activates!
My Life returns!
And now for an Instant Play Magic Card!
Sebek's Blessing, activate!
When I am able to successfully lay damage to my opponent,
the damage you lost is added to my Life.
And then...
Come back to me, Yamata Dragon!
This moment I'll activate the Effects of Element Fountain!
What do you think, Yugi?
11000 Life Points!
How the heck do you drain that much Life, OOH-AH~!?
Kaiba... Mokuba...
Otogi...
My bond with them
isn't all that far away yet!
I can't afford to lose now of all times!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Magnet Warrior Alpha in Attack Position!
Direct Attack Noah!
Magnet Sword!!
Attacks of that level barely make me flinch, let alone harm me.
Turn end.
My turn!
But before that, Yugi...
...shall we begin the desperate countdown to the demise of you and your friends?!
Honda!
Honda-san!
Honda-kun!
Noah...!
Rotten scum!!
Every time I go to take a turn, one of your friends will vanish from your sight.
Bastard! There's no point in trying to do this!
Our trust in Yugi won't change, regardless!
Rest assured.
I'm awaiting the moment your little sister meets her end.
Big brother...
Stop this, Noah!
There's a simple way to put an end to this.
All you have to do is defeat me.
Simple, isn't it?
Give it a try!
Just try it, Yugi!
JUST TRY IT, YUGI!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon a Spirit Monster called Inaba White Rabbit!
This card can directly attack the opposing player, regardless of whether they have Monsters on the field or not.
What...?!
Direct Attack Yugi!
Return to me, White Rabbit!
And my Life Points increase once again due to my Deck Master Ability and the effects of Element Fountain.
Noah's Life went up again...
Big brother...
Don't worry, Shizuka.
Yugi's gonna win this!
My turn.
I set a face-down card.
And...
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Alpha!
In order to Summon the Black Magician Girl!
And because there is a black magician card resting in the Graveyard, her Attack Power increases by 300 points!
Go, Black Magician Girl!
Direct Attack Noah!
What's the matter, Yugi?
If that's the best you've got, you won't be saving your best friend's little sister anytime soon.
So, who's up next?
I...
...have to end my turn now.
Big brother!
My turn!
Desperate countdown!
Look out, brother!
Shizuka!
Shizuka-chan!
Big... bro...ther...
Shizuka...!
SHIZUKA!
I'm so sorry, Jounouchi-kun...
Yugi, I'll let you reflect on your weakness!
My turn!
Summon! Spirit Monster, Inaba White Rabbit!
Noah! I've been waiting for this moment!
Trap Card, activate!
Coffin of Black Magic's Revival!
A Trap, you said?!
Coffin of Black Magic's Revival activates the moment the opposing player Summons.
It takes the Monster you Summoned as an offering along with one of my own,
and revives a Black Magic User from my Graveyard.
As a result, Noah, I sacrifice your Monster, Inaba White Rabbit...
What?!
...along with a Monster of my own!
And the Monster I revive is...
Come forth, Black Magician!
How in the world...?!
If your Spirit Monster doesn't return to your hand, your Life Recovery Combo won't activate!
Keh! I set a card face-down and end my turn!
You sure that's a wise decision, Noah?
Your field is completely empty!
Just you wait, everyone.
I'll bring you back to normal, no matter what I have to do!
Draw!
Noah, allow me to show you the true power of my deck!
Magic Card, activate!
Chaos - Black Magic Ritual!
In addition, I sacrifice The Magnet Warrior - Magnet Warrior Valkyrion, an 8-Star Monster, from my hand!
Become the wind that bears this ceremony, my honorable sacrifice.
The heir to chaos, born from the deep darkness...
Magician of Black Chaos!!
Whae...?
Black Magician.
Black Magician Girl.
And Magician of Black Chaos!
The three Warriors of Black Magic have descended!
All three Black Magicians?
They have 7300
Attack Points altogether!
He can turn this around!
Go, Warriors of Black Magic!
Direct Attack Noah!
Take this!
Triple Black Magic!!
Gotcha.
How naive.
Trap Card, activate!
Barrier of Confusion - Chaos Field!
What?
Chaos Field is a Trap Card that activates when the opponent attacks with a Monster.
It selects the weakest Monster and forces it to fight the Monster with the highest Attack Power.
After that, the Battle Phase is automatically ended.
And my barrier will be...
Black Magician Girl!
Take the Black Magician of Chaos's attack!
Magician Girl...!
Your Battle Phase has now been forced to a close.
And the damage you just received is added to my Life.
Noah's Life just went up even higher now...
Seriously though, that was splendid, Yugi!
You possess both the judgment and the skill necessary to catch your enemies off guard the second they lose focus.
When you think about it, you and I have no reason to be enemies.
If you swear your loyalty to me,
I'll save all your friends from hell this very instant!
What...?
Although, Seto and Mokuba are a different story.
Turn them back to normal...?
Shizuka...
From the very beginning, both you and Seto existed to be enemies.
So why care what happens to Seto?
You have no obligation to protect him, you know!
You do want your friends back to normal, don't you?
Forget it, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Jounouchi...
It's true that Kaiba is our enemy.
But the feeling of siblings between those two are no different than they are for us!
I'm certain that Otogi, Honda and Shizuka would have said the same thing!
Fight, Yugi!
You have to fight!
And you have to win!
Jounouchi-kun...!
No one asked for your piss-poor answer, commoner.
It's my turn!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Noah! You're really sad!
What?!
Your knowledge may have advanced, but your heart has remained frozen!
You're still nothing but a child who knows nothing about the world or the people that inhabit it!
Heh, I shouldn't have expected commoners like yourself to understand my greatness.
But I'm sure someone chosen by victory will understand.
Yugi, I've chosen you!
Now all you have to do
is say you'll serve me!
Using your power to try and sway people's hearts...
How do you expect people to accept you if you do things like this?!
You're acting really stupid, Noah!
"Stupid"...?
You called me stupid...?
I-I'm sorry then!
That you're such a fool!
Then allow me to do as you wish!
Draw!
A Monster in Defense Mode!
I then set a card face-down!
And now...
Since death is on the horizon for you, I'll be happy to tell you what this special card is.
The card I'm about to set is...
Groundbreaking!
This card lets me add a Spirit Monster lying in the Graveyard into my hand.
And the card I've brought back is obviously Inaba White Rabbit.
You've only got a measly 300 points of your Life remaining.
I can put an end to this Duel with a simple attack from the 700 Attack White Rabbit.
Granting me my perfect victory.
I'm going to end my turn now!
This match isn't over yet!
Draw!
I choose this moment to activate the Trap Card, Groundbreaking!
I return Inaba White Rabbit to my hand!
No you don't!
Magic Card! Hand Obliteration!
You must now send every card in your hand to the Graveyard,
and draw the same amount of cards from your deck.
Magician of Black Chaos, attack his Defense Monster!
Chaos Magic: Death Ultima!!
You fell for it!
I activate Otohime's Special Effect!
She changes the Battle Position of one of the opponent's Monsters!
So...
I switch Black Magician
into Defense Position!
And now Black Magician's Battle Phase is forced to a close!
And because a Spirit Monster on my side of the field has been destroyed, the Trap Card, Vessel of Illusions, can be activated!
It Special Summons a Spirit Token onto the field.
So I'll Summon Otohime once again in Defense Mode.
It's my turn now, although...
...it sure is getting a bit lonely now that the peanut gallery down there has been reduced to one person.
Anzu...!
Mind sharing any last words you might have with us?
I know! You must be feeling really angry at Yugi right now!
Don't kid yourself!
Yugi...
Yugi will win this!
No matter what happens, I'll believe in Yugi!
Anzu...
Huh~? Well if that's the case, I'll just end my turn without getting rid of you this time.
I'm certain you'll feel differently the next time around.
After I use this card, anyway.
Magic Card! Change of Heart!
This card lets me control one of my opponent's Monsters until the end of the turn.
And the card I choose...
Black Magician!
How's it feel? Losing the main card of your deck?
I'll then sacrifice Black Magician and Otohime,
and Summon the Spirit Monster holding the strongest Attack Power!
Hino-Kagu-Tsuchi!
And now for a Spirit Equipment Magic!
Flaming Fist of Hell!
It increases the selected Monster's Attack Power by 200 points for one turn!
Go, Hino-Kagu-Tsuchi!
Crimson Extinction Fist!!
And thanks to both my Deck Master Ability and the damaging Effect of Flaming First, my Life Points increase!
And now I activate the Continuous Magic Card, Spiritual Energy Settle Machine.
I then discard one card from my hand!
As long as this card is in play, my Spirit Monsters won't return to my hand at the End Phase of the turn.
Now my Life stands proudly at 10,000 and casts your pitiful 100 in shame!
Do you still believe you can turn this around?
Stand up, Yugi! Please!
You fool!
Be gone!
Yu... gi...
Anzu!
Now you've lost them all!
Okay Yugi, this time for sure! I predict this is your final turn!
He has Hino-kagu-tsuchi on the field, which has 3000 Attack Points...
But I don't even have a Monster on the field...
And my hand is at zero...
It's impossible...
Am I going to lose here?
All the friends that believed in me...
Partner!
Other me!
I'm still here with you!
No... it's not just me!
C'mon!
This place...
It's the room of my soul.
Other me, it's true we still haven't found the Door of Truth in your room yet...
But we've made a new room instead!
A new room?
You bet!
So this is my new room?
Yup!
Jounouchi-kun!
Anzu!
Honda-kun!
Otogi!
Shizuka-chan!
I get it! So this...
It's the Room of Memories that you made after meeting all of us.
Yugi!
There's no way you'll ever have no one by your side!
He's right!
We're always here with you, Yugi.
And we're always cheering you on!
But...
I have no way of winning this time...
Yugi...
You're the man I acknowledge as my life-long rival.
Kaiba!
Mokuba!
Are you telling me you're going to give up in a place like this?
Kaiba...!
Both of our souls rest in the deck you're holding.
It's nothing short of the best!
We've got endless possibilities lying in this deck!
Possibilities that can turn the tables?
In our deck?
Fight, Yugi.
Believe in our deck!
We've still got... plenty of possibilities left!
Hey, are you seriously intending to fight in the condition you're in?
Noah, I still have things I need to protect!
Draw card!
Treasure from Heaven!
This card forces both players to raw until they both hold six cards in their hand!
Yugi.
Take it, Yugi.
Our feelings...
...are in you now!
Here, Yugi-san!
We're counting on you!
These cards hold all of their feelings...
Noah, let me say just one thing.
This is my prediction for the end of this Duel.
You won't be taking another turn!
The Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead!
And the Monster I'm reviving is...
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
Blue-Eyes!
Noah, take mine and Mokuba's anger!
Kaiba, I won't let your hard work go in vain!
Go, Blue-Eyes!
Toward our future!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
And now for my second Magic Card!
Fusion!
I polymerize the two Blue-Eyes in my hand with the Blue-Eyes I have on the field!
What the...?
Come forth, the strongest servant of Kaiba's deck!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!!
And yet another Magic Card!
Quick Attack!
Attack Hino-kagu-tsuchi!
Ultimate Burst!!
But I'm still not done!
I thought I told you, Noah...
That you won't be taking another turn!
Fusion Cancel!
Because Fusion Cancel automatically Summons three Blue-Eyes to the field, I still have a Battle Phase!
That can't be!
There has to be a way!
Noah, this holds the wrath of my friends! And the bonds we share!
Along with Kaiba and Mokuba's sadness!
It's all built up in a single blow!
Go on, Blue-Eyes!
Triple Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Impossible!
Is this...
...the strength of bonds!?
He did it! Yugi won!
Everyone is back to normal!
Huh? Honda!
Why are you still a monkey?
Noah, hurry up and give Honda back his body!
And let us out of this Virtual Space already!
Huh?! You said none of us can leave this place?
Noah, aren't you the one controlling this world?!
Next time!
"Darkness of the Kaiba Family"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise