Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Exodia Necross"
He counter-attacks with Dragon Sword!
That was one of the
fights from Battle City...
Without even realizing it, I was lost in a sea of memories.
You got me, Noah!
Now just you wait, Gozaburo!
I'll make you open an exit, even if I have to get rough!
Our road of battle won't end in a place like this!
Shit! So Noah tricked us in the end!
He got the best of us!
Jounouchi-kun, we still don't really know that yet...
But Mokuba's gone, too!
He probably got kidnapped by the jerk again!
Maybe Noah stole Mokuba's body and escaped to the Real World.
Yeah, it's possible...
I hope Mokuba-kun's alright...
What do you think, Other Me?
I...
Sorry. I just don't think the others are ready to forgive Noah.
Yeah...
Partner, I get that you want to believe in Noah.
But regardless, Noah went way too far.
OTOGI!
SHIZUKA!
Yu... gi...
I know you want everyone to trust Noah, but it's too difficult for them.
Yeah, I know that...
But still...
Kaiba-kun's gone, too!
Mokuba-kun may be with him!
That's certainly possible...
Anyway, let's just search for Noah. Otherwise we won't get out of this Virtual World.
OOH-OOH-AH! I'm starting to oohk like a moonkey!
Let's hurry oohp and find him, OOH-AH!
Not good. Honda-kun's starting to talk even more like a monkey.
We have to hurry up and find Noah!
Wh-What the hell is going on here?!
Shizuka!
Curse of Dragon!
Hell Flame!!
Oh yeah!
Let's go, Axe Raider!
Switching to Program File M2A5.
Changing missile target to floating mobile fortress.
Seto, I'll use a missile to blow you from this world.
Along with Yugi... and Father...
Seto... I'll have the last laugh.
Not you.
Good of you to come, Seto.
I've been waiting to have a nice, long chat with you.
Humph. Don't make me laugh.
Now don't be like that.
We've got plenty of time.
Even if we had a hundred years to sit and chat, I would only have one thing to say to you...
Let us return to the Real World at once!
You know, it's been some time since we used a game to settle one of our disputes.
Just like the time I took you on as my adopted son.
That would be a waste of time.
If you lost to me as a child, what makes you think you can beat me in Chess now?
You really think I would go all out on a small child?
It's a little berating of yourself to try and deny your loss.
Just forget it.
But we won't be playing Chess this time.
It'll be a Duel!
Say that again.
What's wrong? I'm saying that I'll be playing you in the game you're best at.
You bastard. So you're trying to get revenge for your defeat back then?
You'd been planning everything since then.
Planning to steal Kaiba Corporation from right under my nose!
Then let's hear it. Why are you going so far just to test your merits against mine in a match?
I hate you. Hate to the point of becoming unbearable.
You not only stole Kaiba Corporation away from me, but my very life along with it!
Are you saying that it's my fault you killed yourself just because I beat you?
That's why we're gonna settle things right now.
But it must be in the thing you like the best... a Duel!
And not only will I utterly destroy you,
but you'll crawl back to my feet when you learn how big the gap between us is!
Alright then. I'll be glad to Duel you.
Regardless of who it may be, I accept all challenges that come my way!
I accept this Duel!
I'll destroy everyone!
System down. System down.
Changing to backup generators.
Tch! How dare you get in my way?!
The lock has been undone!
Good! Let's get everything ready to leave!
Here I come, Seto!
My turn! Draw!
The Magic Card, Distressing Choice.
Distressing Choice?
Sometimes, being the manager of a company means making decisions.
Even if those decisions are quite difficult.
If you think that all difficult decisions are right decisions, you're more foolish than I thought.
Difficult Decision has me draw five cards from my deck and show them to my opp-
I don't need you to explain the card to me!
I choose one out of the five cards, and you send the rest to the Graveyard.
And the card I choose is added to your hand.
Now! Show me your cards already!
Seems I made the right choice.
Now, take a close look.
These are the five cards I have chosen!
Wh-What?! Those cards...!
Exodia... is it?
What a serious face you've got there.
Don't tell me that you thought I would challenge you to a Duel without doing my research?!
What?!
I have thoroughly analyzed your deck.
And the Duel that you
lost miserably in as well!
Impossible!
Exodia, you said?!
Light of Hellfire!
Exodo Flame!!
Filthy scum...!
Do you think I'm the kind of man that would lose to the same thing more than once?!
Just choose already!
But what's going on here...?
Exodia is the ultimate card that grants one instant victory the moment he collects all five cards in his hand.
So why would he want to send them to the Graveyard?
Come on and choose already, Seto.
Quick judgment is also an important trait for decision making.
That one.
Then I shall send the other remaining cards to the Graveyard?
I'll then place a Monster in Defense Position.
Turn end.
What could he be planning...?
My turn, draw!
System successfully recovered.
Good. This time for sure.
Missile target: locked on.
Very good.
You can join them.
It's game over for everyone.
30 minutes until missile launch.
This way, everyone!
Will they follow us in here?
I'm pretty sure we'll be okay in here...
Shit! They found us!
Damn! We've got no choice but to fight them!
25 minutes until missile launch.
The control room, eh?
Hmm~? What's this?
I have no clue what's going on here, but it looks damn interesting!
23 minutes until missile launch.
I've been wanting to
see you so badly, Father!
I've been alone here for so long!
I no longer have any use for you.
Why don't you all give up on leaving and stay here in this world with me as my father suggested?
It's more fun than it looks...
Noah!
I can't believe you're still saying that!
You were abandoned by Gozaburo, you know!
That hurts, Mokuba.
If you promise me that you'll stop trying to hurt my big brother,
I'll be happy to ask
my brother a favor for you.
To get you a new body.
I mean, we're brothers and all.
Man... He's a complete fool...
Brotherhood...
Comradeship...
Friendship...
I'll send all of it flying straight into hell aside those idiots with the missile.
21 minutes until missile launch.
With the missile...
I...
Chaos Soldier! Summon!
Chaos Blade!!
Go! Axe Raider!!
18 minutes until missile launch.
Shit...!
Who cares about brotherhood, comradeship or friendship?!
Shit! That guy must have done this!
Now the missile can't be stopped!
I place one set card face-down!
I Summon Blood Vorse!
I'm not sure what he set...
But a bluff won't work against me!
I'll destroy any enemy standing in my way!
Blood Vorse! Attack his face-down Defense Monster!
What?! You set one of the Exodia parts on the field?!
What the hell is this man plotting?!
Turn over.
I've been awaiting this moment.
My turn! Draw!
I play a Ritual Magic Card from my hand.
I activate Contract with Exodia!
Contract with Exodia?!
This Ritual Magic can only be activated when all five of the Sealed Cards are collected in the Graveyard.
At the cost of 1000 of my Life Points, I am able to initiate the advent of Exodia Necross!
Exodia Necross, you said?!
Correct.
Now, Seto.
You can see with your very own eyes!
The Exodia that beat you once before is about to be resurrected to the field!
Exodia!
Well?! Nostalgic, is it not?!
Quit the jokes! There's no way a weak Monster with only 1800 Attack Points will be able to beat me!
A weak Monster, you say...?
It looks as if you know absolutely nothing about Exodia to me!
Here goes! Exodia Necross attacks!
What?! You're going to attack my Monster with Exodia Necross even though it has less Attack Points?!
Why...?! Why wasn't it destroyed?!
Exodia Necross is immortal!
And its Attack Power go up by 1000 points every time it engages in battle!
What did you say?!
Exodia Necross continues to increase its Attack Power without enc until it destroys everything!
Turn over!
My turn! Draw!
Then I'll just use an Assassination Attack Combo until I destroy it!
I Summon Spirit Dragon!
Also, reverse card open!
I activate the Trap Card, Burst Breath!
I Tribute Spirit Dragon!
All Monsters on the field with Defense Points less than its Attack Power are automatically destroyed!
And that means, of course, Exodia!
What?! Why?
Why wasn't the 0 Defense Power Exodia destroyed?!
Allow me to explain!
Each of the Exodia parts in the Graveyard hide a unique Effect within them.
The Sealed Left Leg of Exodia gives it the Effect to be unaffected by any Magic abilities.
The Sealed Right Leg of Exodia gives it the Effect to be unaffected by Trap Cards!
The Sealed Left Arm of Exodia gives it the ability to not be destroyed by Monster Effects.
The Sealed Right Arm of Exodia's Effect increases its Attack Power by 1000 points every time it does battle.
And finally, Exodia the Sealed One protects it from being destroyed in battle.
It grants it the Effect of immortality!
What?! The pieces of Exodia have Effects like that when in the Graveyard?!
Not only is it unaffected by Magic and Trap Cards... it isn't even destroyed by a Monster Effect or in battle!
Exodia Necross... Is there even a way to beat this thing?!
Exodia Necross is invincible!
There's no way to beat it!
I set one reverse card!
I switch Blood Vorse into Defense Position and end my turn.
10 minutes until missile launch.
I Summon the Black Magician!
I Summon Rocket Warrior!
Black Magic!!
Invincible Mode!!
Can everyone in
Virtual Domino City hear me?
That voice...!
Noah!
Bastard! Where are you?!
Get the hell out here!
Seto. And you as well, Father.
I have taken Mokuba's body and am currently in the Real World.
What?! Damn you, Noah!
Shit! So he really tricked us all and went to the Real World all by himself!
Noah, you jerk! Just how low can you go?!
Give Mokuba-kun's body back this instant!
And my body as well, OOH-OOOH-AHH~!
Noah...
I have hardly any time here, but I have something to tell all of you.
A missile is targeting us as we speak.
And once it hits, both the Virtual World...
...and the fortress
will vanish without a trace!
What...?
Oh no! Why the hell is a missile of all things headed toward this floating mobile fortress?!
If we don't get out of here right now, this Virtual Space will be blown up!
It's suspicious enough that Noah has Mokuba-kun's body and is in the Real World!
But for now, we need to focus on getting out of this fortress!
But Kaiba-kun is trapped in a Duel with his father!
Please, Yugi!
Hurry and bring Kaiba-kun back!
Next time!
"Escape!!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise