Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Zorc has been defeated.
After returning to the real world, I am faced with my final ordeal.
The Rite of the Duel!
And it was you, Partner, who has taken me as
his opponent to decide my fate in my final Duel.
Thank you, Partner.
There's no one better to be my opponent than you!
Let's both fight each other with all our strength!
"The Fated Last Duel"
Here we are.
Anzu.
You know... I'm wondering why we have to be in such a rush about this...
Maybe we should spend a little more time with each other...
At the very least, just for today...
Anzu... What are you saying after we came all the way here...?
It's the same for me, you know...
Anzu...
This Battle Ceremony that will deliver the Pharaoh into the Afterlife
must be chosen to be conducted during the time both Duelists' strengths
are at their absolute peak.
And that time is now, after you have defeated the Wicked God
and regained the Pharaoh's memories.
There will be no other time.
If we let this day pass by, the Pharaoh's soul will forever wander the present day.
Even despite that, are you okay with that?
It's hard for me, too.
But this battle must take place, no matter what!
Because it's something my other self decided to do.
Yeah...
Sorry!
You're right.
We all know what you mean, Anzu.
But you know...
But we just couldn't say it.
You said what we were all thinking.
He's right.
I understand how you feel.
Yeah, Anzu basically just went and said what was on all of our minds.
Hmph. You better not start thinking of canceling this fight.
Seeing as you dragged me all the way down here...
D-Didn't you just go and follow us down here on your own?!
Let's go!
So that's the Stone Slab of the Underworld...
Yugi.
Place the seven treasures in the Slab of Memory and speak the name of the Pharaoh.
Then the door to the Afterlife will open and welcome the Pharaoh's soul.
However...
The Wadjet Eye must judge
him of the truth.
And the one who will take the Pharaoh's sword and quiet his restless soul...
If you accept this Rite of the Duel...
Please place the seven Millennium Items onto the slab.
Mm-hmm!
Thinking back on it, everything began on the day Yugi put together the Millennium Puzzle...
Back then, I...
I want friends!
This Millennium Puzzle granted my wish!
Thank you, Millennium Puzzle.
The eye on the door started to glow!
The Wadjet of Truth will see the truth that lies within
the soul of whomever accepts the Rite of the Duel.
Look!
Yugi's shadow...!
Yugi split into two...!
So that's the other...!
Yugi?!
Atem...
It's about to begin!
Their Duel!
I have no clue...! Which of them should we root for?
If Atem wins, he'll be able to spend his time with his friends like always...
I'm cheering for Yugi!
So Atem can set off to the Afterlife!
Right... I know...
It's hard, but we have to release Atem's soul!
So I'll root for Yugi!
Sister...
This trial is a battle that will determine both of their fates.
Only they themselves can find the answer.
Partner... I thank you
for taking on this Duel...
But I am a Duelist!
No matter what the cost, I will put everything into defeating my opponent!
That is my pride!
Other Me...
I have to be strong.
If I'm not, you'll never
be free from my heart...
And so...
I must defeat you!
This is a match betting the title of Duel King!
The ultimate battle is about to begin!
Yugi!
Atem...
Let's go, Partner!
Here I go, Other Me!
Duel!!
I take the lead!
Draw!
I discard one card from my hand...
...and Special Summon The Tricky in Attack Mode!
Furthermore...
I play one face-down card and end my turn!
Right off, he Special Summoned a 2000 Attack Point Monster...
My turn!
Draw!
I activate a Magic Card!
Sealing Swords of Light!
Now Atem can't attack for three turns!
Also, I Summon the Green Gadget in Attack Mode!
Now for Green Gadget's Special Effect!
I can add Red Gadget from my deck into my hand!
I set one reverse card.
Turn end!
Amazing!
Normally it'd appear that Atem-kun
has the advantage after Summoning a High-Level Monster,
but Yugi-kun instead changed the pacing of this battle in his favor!
There's no doubt that the God Cards are coming...
If he's seriously not showing any mercy here...
It's my turn.
Draw!
Partner, you should know that the Sealing Swords of Light can't block all attacks.
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Rebellion!
It targets one Monster on the field and forces it to attack its respective player!
The Monster I'm targeting is Green Gadget!
Direct Attack my partner!
I knew you'd do that!
Reverse card, open!
The Trap Card,
Stronghold the Moving Fortress!
After activation, it becomes a Monster Card!
It can be Special Summoned in Defense Mode
But you'll still receive the difference in damage done by your own Monster!
I get it!
Green Gadget is Yugi's Monster!
But he did keep from taking damage from his Direct Attack.
Turn end!
He did manage to evade major damage to his Life...
This card... Partner's using a deck he's never used before.
This is an original deck Partner created himself!
Other Me!
I've already gathered the finishing combo in my hand!
So be it.
Just as you wish!
My partner's showing me the improvement in his strength!
But as soon as he does, the great power of the Gods lying in my deck...
...will be triggered!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate a Magic Card!
Ties of the Brethren!
I pay 1000 of my Life.
I can Special Summon two Level Four Monsters
with the same Type as the Monster I have on the field!
Come to me!
Red Gadget!
Yellow Gadget!
I Special Summon them in Defense Mode!
Partner, you can't beat me with high guard alone!
You're mistaken!
What?
Go forth, Gadgets!
Become the gears of the fort!
Stronghold the Fort!
When all the gadgets are on the field in face-up position,
he becomes Stronghold the Fort Monster, with 3000 Attack Points!
So this is what Yugi was aiming for?!
I attack with Stronghold the Moving Fortress!
Steel Gear Crush!!
I activate the Magic Transfer Magic Card!
The Sealing Swords of Light will pass through this dimension
and will seal your Monster for three turns!
That was close!
But you've still got a long way to go, Partner!
That's the other Yugi for you!
He's thinking one step ahead.
He sure is strong!
Yeah...
I'm trembling... But not because I'm afraid.
I'm so happy that you're taking me seriously!
I switch Green Gadget into Defense Position!
Your eyes, Partner...
You still haven't given up.
But I am still far ahead of you!
My turn!
Draw!
By sending The Tricky into the Graveyard,
I can activate the Magic Card known as The Tricky's Magic Four!
For every Monster my opponent controls on their field,
I can Special Summon a Tricky Token in Defense Position!
Yugi's got four Monsters on his field!
From the beginning of this Duel, the other Yugi
had control over the number of Monsters on his field.
Here I come, Partner!
I'm going to show you my power! My true strength!
You don't mean...!
Is it coming?
And now I sacrifice the three Tricky Tokens!
To Summon Obelisk the Great War God!
Obelisk...!
He Summoned the god...!
Atem's deck is no joke!
He's not even trying to go easy on him even a little!
Yugi's created the strongest deck designed to thoroughly outrank his enemy!
Obelisk, attack!
Blast Stronghold the Fort apart!
God Hand Crusher!!
I set one reverse card and end my turn!
Yugi!
Yugi, pull yourself together!
Don't give up!
Yugi...
But he's Summoned one of the gods,
and Yugi-kun's Monsters can't attack because of the Sealing Swords of Light!
What's wrong, Partner?
Are you finished?
Does he still have something up his sleeve, even in this situation?
No. Yugi's been completely driven into a corner. He's got nothing he can do.
Then, why...?
Maybe Yugi-kun doesn't want to be separated from Atem-kun...
Don't talk stupid!
Nobody would grin when he's about to lose! Yugi's not that kind of Duelist!
Jounouchi...
He's... having fun.
How can you not enjoy yourself while Dueling against the other Yugi?
This is the first time he's fought the other Yugi.
They're both clashing into each other, heart to heart.
He was always following behind him up until now...
But now... They're coming at each other head-on!
Always... following...
Show him, Yugi...
Your strength!
My turn!
Draw!
I set three reverse cards!
I then Summon Silent Swordsman LV. 0!
Yes!
It's the Silent Swordsman that beat Bakura!
In Attack Mode! Turn end!
In Attack Mode?!
If he gets attacked next turn, this match is over!
Does he have some kind of plan to fight the gods?
The God Cards are a heavy burden.
You're likely to only get one of them out at best.
If he can manage to defeat Obelisk, he may have a chance...!
My turn! Draw!
I set one reverse card!
I then activate Treasure From Heaven from my hand!
Both players are to draw from their decks until they hold six cards in their hand!
Partner...
Other Me!
The both of us have to use all of our strength in this fight!
If we don't, we'll never have a true conclusion!
Mm-hmm!
I'm playing at my full strength!
Follow suit, Partner!
I'm going to surpass you with my full strength!
I attack Silent Swordsman using Obelisk the Great War God!
Here goes, Partner!
God Hand Crusher!!
Yugi!
Reverse card, open!
Ground Erosion!
I then activate my Quick-Play Magic, Turn Jump!
Both players will automatically shift their plays as if three turns have passed!
Silent Swordsman levels up from Level Zero to Level Three!
It's not enough, Partner!
You can't touch my Obelisk's 4000 Attack Points!
No!
My reverse Ground Erosion's Trap Effect activates by sacrificing this card!
Traps don't work on the Gods!
I'm not using it against your God!
I'm using it on the field your God is standing on!
What?!
Ground Erosion decreases the Attack Power of a Monster on the field
by 500 points for each turn this card remained in reverse!
In other words, counting the three turns skipped by Turn Jump,
1500 Attack Points are stolen from Obelisk!
The Silent Swordsman actually withstood one of the gods!
That means with Obelisk's current Attack Power, they'll kill each other.
Partner... I also activated a Trap!
The Permanent Trap, Summoning Clock!
It activates when my opponent activates a Magic or Trap Card on their field!
I sacrifice this card and my Monster.
I can Special Summon as many Monsters
from my hand without sacrifice as turns that have passed while this card was face-down!
Three Monsters?!
Then, as a result of King Knight's Special Effect,
I can Special Summon Jack's Knight!
And...
...I can Special Summon Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Impossible!
Two of the gods?!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack Power
is determined by the number of cards I have in my hand.
I have three cards in my hand!
Trap Card, open!
Ambush Shield!
It activates by sacrificing one of my Monsters!
The targeted Monster gains Attack Power equal to the Defense Power
of the Monster sacrificed until the end of this turn!
It's got 4000 Attack Points?!
Now Yugi's Monster's Attack Points are higher than Osiris'!
Not half bad, Partner.
In that case...
I attack Green Gadget and Yellow Gadget using Queen's Knight and King's Knight!
My Battle Phase will now end.
But I can still Summon a Monster this turn!
I sacrifice Queen's Knight, Jack's Knight and King's Knight!
He can't...!
No way!
The Hieratic... Text...!
Other... Me...!
The third God!
I Summon Ra the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Come forth, Ra the Winged Dragon of Ra!
The Winged... Sun Dragon of Ra...!
The Three Illusionary Beasts...
He Summoned all three gods?!
Partner! This is my full strength!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
It's finally started!
Atem and Yugi's Duel!
Now that Atem's gone and Summoned the three gods right off the bat,
Atem's given himself an untouchable overwhelming advantage.
Is there even any way for Yugi to fend him off now?
Does this mean Atem had no intention of returning to the Afterlife after all...
Next time!
"Defeating the Three Illusionary Beast Gods!"
Duel standby!