With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Yugi, this time I'll teach you what a
Duel of terror is all about.
BLUE-EYES ULTIMATE DRAGON!
Th-this is the fusion of 3 Blue-Eyes?
Here I come! Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon, attack!
Ultimate Burst!!
My victory is set.
I will not give up!
That's right. Come at me until the very end!
Yugi! I want to crush you
at your maximum strength!
I bet my life...
ON THIS CARD!
"Kuriboh Multiplies!
The Astonishing Conclusion"
Using Defense Mode will only lengthen your defeat.
There's no way he will draw something that can reverse the situation.
Kaiba, I just drew the ultimate card into my hand!
What?
This card...
Here I go!
Kuriboh in Attack Mode!
It can't be...!
The weakest monster with the lowest
Attack Points, Kuriboh!?
What the? That monster doesn't look so tough...
Yugi, it's your right to forfeit the match...
But who would've guessed you'd play this trash monster?
In Duel Monsters, it has the lowest Attack Points. It's the lowest card level.
I've never seen anyone keep it in their Deck.
Yugi, if you intend on using this card to make a joke out of our battle I'll never forgive you!
Kaiba, you're wrong.
This card is my trump!
It will defeat Ultimate Dragon!
Wh-what did you say? Impossible!
That weak monster will beat my Ultimate Dragon?
Here I go!
Also, I activate the Multiply Card.
This card multiplies a monster with
500 Attack Points or less.
Th-this is...!
The trashy monsters are multiplying...!
Indeed, this monster is a low level monster
with only 300 Attack Points.
But don't look down on it.
It has hidden powers that can overtake the strongest of monsters!
Impossible!
This trash in front of my Ultimate Dragon
will only make more corpses!
Attack!
Ultimate Burst!!
What?!
The Ultimate Dragon's attack didn't work...!
Don't tell me these trash monsters have the ability to
explode when they're hit by an attack?!
That's right! The moment an enemy makes contact with it, Kuriboh explodes!
In other words, Ultimate Dragon's attack
will never destroy Kuriboh!
Shit...!
These damn trash monsters...!
They keep on multiplying...!
Unless all of them are destroyed,
Kuriboh's combo will continue to multiply.
In other words, unless you defeat every Kuriboh,
you will never take my Life Points to 0!
But before that...
I will play my second trump card on my turn!
Second trump card...?
Here I go!
A three-card combo to destroy
the 3-headed Ultimate Dragon!
Mammoth Graveyard!
Fusion!
And the Arrow of Magical Effects card!
The Arrow of Magical Effects?
The Arrow of Magical Effects card
allows me to play my Magic Cards with the enemy's monsters.
I play this Magic Card with Fusion...
Also, one of my monsters, Mammoth Graveyard.
Just like you fused 3 Blue-Eyes to create Ultimate Dragon,
I'll fuse my monster with Ultimate Dragon!
What?!
What the hell?! This is...!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon is a living Light Monster.
When Ultimate Dragon is fused with a Dark
Undead type monster
the effects from Mammoth Graveyard fusing with it will take effect.
Its body will decompose!
My Ultimate Dragon is rotting...
The Attack Points of
Mammoth Graveyard are 1200.
In other words, every turn Ultimate Dragon will
lose 1200 Attack Points as a penalty.
Now the tables have turned, Kaiba!
I have the Attack Nullification
card in my Deck...
It blocks attack damage...
But it's useless against Fusion...
BOOYAH! He pulled off another successful combo!
He'll defeat Kaiba again!
Yugi!
You see that Kaiba?! Yugi's got no weakness!
Yugi, no matter how bad it got...
I still believed in the other Yugi's strength!
I can't believe Kaiba's triple fusion
was brought down with Fusion itself...
It's fighting fire with fire.
That Yugi brat's pretty damn smart!
N-not yet...!
This match is not over yet!
Attack, Ultimate Dragon!
Ultimate Burst!!
It's useless!
It's impossible to destroy all of
my landmine monsters in one attack.
These... TRASH WEAKLINGS!
I'll draw a card and end my turn.
Damn Yugi...! Are you going to just skip your turn?!
Attack!
Ultimate Burst!!
It's no use...!
The Ultimate Dragon loses Attack Points every turn and becomes weaker...
I will also declare my turn over.
Kaiba, you won't turn this around!
Lose?
I'll lose...?
Impossible...!
Mokuba...!
If I lose, Mokuba will...
Big brother...!
Big brother!
Big brother, help me!
Mokuba...!
Big brother...!
Help me...!
Mokuba!
Big brother!
Big... brother...
MOKUBA!
Why?!
Why didn't you help him?!
You can't even put your life on the line?!
WHY DIDN'T YOU HELP HIM!?
Mokuba...
Kaiba...
Are you going to forfeit your turn without doing anything?
That Kaiba bastard's just spacing out!
Does that mean he accepted defeat?
He didn't make a move, so his turn is over.
The Ultimate Dragon's Attack Points
is continuing to drop.
Okay! Now that the Ultimate Dragon's
Attack dropped this low, I can defeat it!
My turn!
I'll play another card!
Elf Swordsman!
Attack Ultimate Dragon!
ALRIGHT!
You're really amazing, other Yugi!
Ultimate Dragon's not dead yet!
That's right...! Ultimate Dragon is a fusion
of 3 Blue-Eyes...
So all 3 heads must be destroyed to defeat it?
But, Kaiba's Life Points have dropped greatly...
Next turn, if I attack again with Elf Swordsman, I win!
Yugi...
The game has just started...
During the last attack, I lost 500 Life Points...
If one of these squares on the ground
is equal to 100 of my Life Points...
Then I will move backwards for each point I lost.
What?!
500 points...
In other words, 5 squares.
That's dangerous...!
What's he doing...?
Kaiba!
I'm at the edge.
If you attack next turn,
you'll be taking my real Life, and I will die.
Kaiba!
I'll gladly die for a Duel!
Kaiba-kun! Don't do anything dangerous!
That bastard...!
Kaiba! That's playing cheap!
Are you gonna bluff like this to
keep Yugi from going all out on his last attack!?
But... what if he's serious?
Wha...?
That can't be...!
The other Yugi...
This Yugi has eyes that will do anything for victory...!
No one knows what's on these rich kids' minds!
Yugi.
On the next turn, your worth as a Duelist will be tested.
A game is like two mirrors held against each other...
How would you counter your own moves?
Furthermore, you must place yourself into
the mind of the opponent in order to obtain victory.
If I was you in this Duel...
I'd push myself over the edge
without a moment's hesitation.
But this Duel is not over yet.
This turn, I'll simply draw a card.
My card is...
Resurrection of the Dead!
I will use this card to resurrect
the killed Blue-Eyes head!
What?! Revive a Blue-Eyes head?!
Now a normal Blue-Eyes with its normal
3000 Attack power has been revived.
Because it was destroyed while it was fused,
I'll have to wait another turn to Attack.
I can't attack you until next turn.
Now, Yugi! It's your turn!
It's useless effort.
No matter which monster he resurrects
as long as I have Kuriboh...
his attacks won't work!
On this turn, if I defeat a weakened head of the Ultimate...
I win!
But.... Kaiba's life will....
Yugi!
Use your card to slit my throat!
I...
I...!
I cannot lose!
I absolutely can't lose!
That look of the other Yugi...!
He chose to throw Kaiba-kun over the edge...!
HERE I GO, KAIBA!
Elf Swordsman!
Yugi! DON'T!
STOP IT!!
Yugi, return to the normal Yugi!
Yugi!!
I win.
Burst Stream!!
Master Pegasus...
Right now, the match between
Yugi and Kaiba just ended.
The winner is Seto Kaiba.
I know.
Then, shall I allow Seto Kaiba into the castle?
No problem.
As you order.
Good job, Kaiba boy.
As you wished, I will be your next opponent.
In a Dark Game.
What's going on...?
That brat had the game won, but he gave it up.
Yugi!
I couldn't do it...!
If I continued the game...
Kaiba-kun might have died!
Yugi... you...!
You forfeited to save Kaiba...
That was the only way to stop
this unstoppable fight...
I'm scared.... I'm really scared!
Of this game.... and of the other....!
I'm sorry... I'm sorry, Yugi.
But Yugi, you did the right thing!
You showed weakness in the end.
So I've won, Yugi.
If you had the cold-heartedness to
push me off the ravine, you'd have won.
It's foolish to care about a Duelist's safety!
No!
You're wrong!
The one who lost the game, Kaiba-kun, is you!
What?
Kaiba-kun... you bet your chip of life
as if it were nothing!
You lost to yourself!
When you realized you would lose to Yugi,
you couldn't live anymore!
Real courage is protecting that chip
in your hands no matter what.
The moment you give that up you lose!
Yugi protected your chip instead of winning!
Now this was an interesting show.
10 Star Chips!
Gate lock deactivate!
Pegasus...!
I'm on my way!
"Preview"
Yugi is losing himself in his great shock.
No matter what we say, he won't listen at all!
Even when Mai-san tries to return
the Star Chips she owes him,
he won't accept them!
If this keeps up, he'll never get in!
Mai-san, Duel me with those Star Chips on the line!
I have to get Yugi into the castle!
Next episode: "Duel of Tears! Friendship"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship