The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Stolen Blue-Eyes White Dragon
Sir, it's meal time.
Dammit!
This is the greatest at any time!
Pardon me.
Master Pegasus.
The world's finest wine, and Gorgonzola cheese.
And then the world's finest comic.
These are my most peaceful times.
Shouldn't you know this?
Of course, please forgive me.
Well, it's alright.
Then, what's the problem?
Yes sir. That boy escaped from the castle.
Oh! I invited him specially as a guest.
I guess he is not satisfied with our service.
Well, don't worry.
I know what he is doing.
The duel tournament started 9 hours ago.
12 of the 40 duelists have been disqualified.
And are preparing to leave the island.
What about him?
Yugi Mutou has collected 5 Star Chips.
Wonderful!
Just as expected from Yugi boy.
He must make it to the castle for the finals.
You must keep your eyes on Yugi boy.
That boy will come against me sooner or later.
Next time, don't let him escape so easily.
Yes!
Since that boy escaped from the castle...
...we'll just have to wait and see.
Ryota Kajiki?
He's someone that I am not gonna dislike.
All Duelists have their own dreams and expectations.
Yup, they all must have pride like us.
Pride?
I guess so.
What was that?
Help!
Let me go!
Someone, please help me!
Wait, Wait!
Help!!
Alright!
It's over now.
Let go!
Stop wiggling!
Wait! Damn you, that's not right!
Don't be reckless.
This will become troublesome. You all, leave.
All of his Star Chips are gone.
That's not it!
They were stolen!
Both my Star Chips and my cards!
It doesn't matter! Duelists who don't have Star Chips can't stay here
That is the rule.
I've had enough.
Damn him!
Another one to leave.
Don't touch me!
I am the winner of the National Championship!
Don't get close to me!
If only my Star Chips weren't stolen...
Hey!!
You!
Who stole your Star Chips from you?
Which person?
I couldn't see his face.
Because there was a handkerchief around it.
He challenged me suddenly to a duel.
At the grassland ring earlier?
Yeah, he stole my Deck and my Star Chips when I set them on the table.
And then just disappeared!
We will look to find out who this guy is.
Until then, wait here.
This boat will depart from here in 30 minutes.
That's the time limit.
We will definitely find him.
And beat him up!
Yeah, the Star Chips are the Duelist's life.
The guy who stole your Star Chips...
...won't be forgiven by Katsuya Jounouchi!
Thanks!
By the way...
...if I catch the guy...
...will you give me half your Star Chips as a reward?
Alright! Let's go!
Don't be an idiot!
It was a joke! A joke!
But we have no clues to go off of here...
...how will we search for him?
The Star Chips were stolen in the ring over there just before.
What's going on, Yugi?
Don't criminals usually return to the place where they first committed the crime?
I guess that's true.
Can't we just take a break?
But, can we really catch this guy?
I found you, Yugi!
He showed up! Is he the criminal?
Beat him up!
Don't be violent!
Yugi!
Bastard!
Give back the Star Chips you just stole.
Wait, I think he came for me.
Do you want to duel with me?
If he tries to steal Yugi's Star Chips...
...I won't let him go.
Don't run away!
How many Star Chips do you want to bet?
Okay.
I'll bet all of my Star Chips.
As I thought...
Where's his invitation?
That boy doesn't have a Duel Glove!
That means...
Yugi doesn't have much time left.
Why does Yugi waste the time to accept his duel?
Maybe, Yugi knows this kid's identity too.
Duel!
I have to take revenge for my brother.
No!
What's wrong, Brother?
Dammit, I can't beat Yugi anymore.
Don't say that!
Didn't you always tell me that cards are power?
My cards of power were destroyed by the cards of Yugi's heart.
If I don't understand his heart...
...I won't be able to win.
Brother...
Mokuba, please hold this card for me.
That has secret information...
...which can unlock Kaiba Corporation's data.
But why...
I have to leave for a little while.
Mokuba, take care.
Wait, Brother!
Yugi, I have to beat you.
Man-Eating Plant in Attack Position.
My turn!
I'll challenge that...with this!
Guardian Dragon of the Fortress!
Smashing Fireballs!
You can't win over my monsters by stealing others' Star Chips.
Because your heart is not in your cards.
Yugi, I don't believe in your "cards have heart" theory!
Cards aren't meant for heart, but only for power.
I knew it.
Aren't you Seto Kaiba's little brother, Mokuba?
Shut up!
That guy...
Kaiba-kun's little brother?
My brother has been in much pain since the duel with you ended.
Because of you, Kaiba Corporation will be taken over by Pegasus!
What did you say? Pegasus!?
It's Pegasus's plan that the news of my brother's loss...
...was being known by the world so quickly.
Since that day, no more investors have been interested in Kaiba Corporation.
The company is quickly going downhill.
Pegasus knows about all of this.
I hope that you all will sell your shares on Kaiba Corporation to me.
We need to renovate Kaiba Corporation.
So, this is the only way.
We understand your inquiry.
However, there is one condition.
Oh?
The reason for this downturn is...
...because of that boy named Yugi.
In order to gain the trust from everyone back...
...you have to defeat that boy.
Mr. Pegasus
If you complete this condition...
...we will hold a board meeting without Seto Kaiba with a party of people about his dismissal.
Thenceforth, all of Kaiba Corporation will be in your hands.
To win over that boy Yugi will be very easy!
One more thing.
The key to the lock of the dismissal application...
...is with Seto Kaiba's little brother, Mokuba.
Oh, no problem! Leave that to me!
Hey! Lemme Go!
I will never tell you where the key is!
Mokuba boy, I invite you to come to my kingdom.
After staying with us as an important guest...
...I know you will surely give me the key.
LET ME GO!!
Yugi, it's all your fault!
I get the situation.
But you still shouldn't have stolen that other guy's card.
You shut-up! My next card is...
Go! Crocodilus!
It's useless to continue this fight.
You're playing with stolen cards...
...you can't win.
Right! Stealing someone's Star Chips is shameful!
Wrong! You just don't get it!
I have to take my brother's place, in order to save Kaiba Corporation!
Are you saying, before Yugi loses...
If his Star Chips are stolen, then he would be disqualified too, and never get to have that duel?
What do you mean?
Don't you get it?
I know, but...
Yeah...what do you mean?
If Yugi loses this duel...
...The plans between Pegasus and the Big Five can't happen.
That's what you mean.
Mokuba!
This is the only thing I can do!
Give them back, Mokuba!
Wait!
Mokuba, even this way you won't keep Kaiba Corporation from falling!
Kaiba is suffering right now.
But what he needs to do is to search for the heart in his cards.
He has to search for his true pride himself.
When he finds his cards' heart, he will definitely be alright.
You and your brother...
No, do you want Kaiba Corporation to lose its entire reputation?
I...
But then, what can I do?
You don't have to steal.
I promise.
I will defeat Pegasus!
If you want to understand...
...your brother's pain.
If you want to know the cards' heart.
Then the Star Chips and the Cards...
...return them to that boy.
I get it. Yugi, I trust you!
The ship will depart in three minutes.
Let's go, Mokuba!
Hey, hey! You have to work for me also!
Ah! The boat...!
The boat holding those who lost has left.
No way!
We still have one minute!
I don't know about that.
You lied to us, you bastard!
I have to return these Star Chips.
Please call for the boat!
What!?
Some of those Star Chips were Yugi's!
I'm sorry, Yugi.
If someone's Star Chips were stolen...
...then that duelist isn't bright enough...
...to be qualified here.
Mokuba!
If Mokuba wants to have Star Chips...
...then he must actually win a duel.
Now, let's return quickly. Pegasus-sama has been so worried.
Mokuba.
Let me go!
Wait.
I have just three Star Chips left.
To have a duel with you, I will bet all of them.
I won't accept...
But, if you really wish to...
...I will arrange a Duel opponent for you.
Meet me at the grassland area in an hour.
Why is Yugi so good at fighting?
His power isn't any better than mine...
Is it his strong feelings?
What he was bearing at that time was different from me.
Impossible... Exodia!?
That card was given to him by his Grandpa.
He fought all the way to protect the card's heart.
This new system...
...includes a super computer that I installed yesterday.
So I can duel anywhere.
If I can finish it...
...I will be able to fight on the same level as Yugi."
Don't move!
Kaiba Seto, come with us.
Understood.
Even if I said 'no', it wouldn't work.
That was good thinking.
Shit!
What?
If he jumped, that saves the trouble of us locking him up.
Dammit, lemme go!
Yugi!
Mokuba! Let Mokuba go!
I'll consider it if you win the duel.
Where is the opposing duelist?
He's already here.
Look!
Kaiba!
Brother!
Yugi, I have to take revenge.
I have to take revenge...
Why is Kaiba-kun here?
What? Did you say that's Kaiba-kun's order?
There's no way that he'd hold a grudge from the dead!
Yugi, in order to believe
We've found Pegasus's trap.
However, Kaiba-kun can't get to his Blue-Eyes White Dragon to help Yugi.
Don't lose, Yugi!
His invitation is weak!
Next time. "Back from the Dead! Magical Silk Hats".
Duel Standby.
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship