Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
We bet the last of our hope and Summoned the Three Illusionary Beasts.
We thought their overwhelming power would be enough to defeat Zorc.
But Zorc's Power of Darkness was enough to survive their attacks.
Our hope was stripped away...
Zorc beat the Three Illusionary Beasts!
Is despair the only thing we have left?!
"Zorc VS Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon"
The Pharaoh has regained most of his memories.
The labyrinth in his heart is beginning to disappear...
But...
Prince!
Pharaoh!
Please pull yourself together, Prince!
Prince!!
Prince!
Pull yourself together already...!
I am untouchable!
It is impossible for the likes of your Gods to defeat me!
Both the Gods and
our Pharaoh were beaten...!
This is horrifying...!
The Gods have abandoned us!
It's all over!
This country is going to be destroyed!
Run away!
Wait! Do not run!
Fight until the end!
Run! Run!
Mana, you must bring the Pharaoh to the royal palace and take cover.
I will hold Zorc.
Lord Seto!
Get going immediately!
Y-Yes!
Hang in there, Prince!
Take care of the Pharaoh, Mana.
Let's go, Kisara!
You fool.
You still intend to rebel against me?
Then you shall vanish!
Zorc, I will not let you take this country or this world!
I now ask of you to lend me your power!
Kisara!!
Come out! White Dragon!!
Blue-Eyes... White Dragon...!
That's...!
Is that white dragon on our side?!
It managed to knock Zorc down!
This is... the power of the White Dragon?
Kisara!
My strength...
...is being drained from me...!
The White Dragon holds power on equal footing of the Gods!
But it has no effect on me!
Because I am myself am greater than the Gods!
Ki... Ki... sa... ra...
So it's useless after all!
The Wicked God is unbeatable!
We're really finished this time!
The Blue-Eyes was beaten?!
Help us!
Great Wicked God Zorc...!
Hurry!
I'm scared, Brother!
I'm scared!
Get out of here right now!
Stop it!!
RUN AWAY!
Unforgivable...
I won't forgive you, you bastard!!
This is...!
Then come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
What?
I know you.
You are Seto Kaiba!
So you also plan to rebel against me?
Shut your mouth!
I don't know a damn thing about you or this world!
But I won't accept it...!
I can't possibly accept it!
The way you're toying with people's lives like they're just pieces of a game!
Nor my Blue-Eyes' loss!
This is the ultimate evolution transcending 3,000 years of time!
My mightiest servant!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!!
What?!
Take this, you monster!!
The light that will open the road of my future, which bypasses time itself!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Burst!!
Damn you...
I will show you firsthand what the act of scrutiny against me means!
I will burn your life away along with the Ultimate Dragon!
Counterattack, Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!
ZORC INFERNO!!
ULTIMATE BURST!!
I sacrifice the Monsters on my field, Marshmallon and Silent Magician...
...and Summon Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction!
What?!
Bakura-kun, there's only one card
resting in my deck that can break your "Undead Locked Dead" Deck...
A card that can break through my Undead Lock...?
Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction's Special Magic Attack!
Giga Rays of Destruction!!
An effect that destroys all the Monsters on the field...?!
I can't believe Yugi used a Monster like that...
This is the deck Yugi created himself...
He's become serious...
This is a Monster meant to represent his parting with the other Yugi.
Because of its Special Magic Attack, Gandora also...
...is destroyed!
And because one of my Monsters was sent to the Graveyard,
the spell of Spirit Sword of Sealing will be removed!
Come back, Silent Swordsman LV. 7!
It's got 4500 Attack Power?!
Silent Swordsman attacks!
Silent Sword Level Seven!!
You did it, Yugi!
Yugi!
A-A-Against a mere vessel...
Th-The great me lost...?
I win this Duel!
But I was able to slow you down more than enough.
The nameless Pharaoh's Ba has already been reduced to a candle in the wind.
Once he dies, this Ultimate Dark Game...
...will end in my victory.
Honda!
Honda-kun!
Hey! Snap out of it, Honda!
Huh? Where am I?
Why am I here?
You dummy!
Bakura put a parasite inside you!
Wha-? You're kidding!
No, it happens to be true.
We suffered through a ton of crap because of you.
Are you serious?
But it's all good now.
Because Yugi just defeated the Bakura parasite inside you.
Yugi did?
Forgive me, Yugi!
Forget about all that.
More importantly...
What was that?
Let's hurry!
We have to get to the Other Me!
- Right!
H-Hey! Wait up!
Hey, are we gonna go down from here?
Don't be a wimp! Let's roll!
R-Right.
These guys again!
They're trying to stop us no matter what.
Shit...!!
Hey, Honda!
- Honda!
- Honda-kun!
I caused you guys a ton of problems!
So I'm gonna make up for it here!
Honda!
Jounouchi-kun!
A Duel Disk!
Right!
In this world, what we think about becomes real!
I see!
In that case, allow me!
Let's go, Honda!
Yeah! It's been a while since we went wild!
Go, Gearfried!
Flame Swordsman!
Barbarian #1 and #2!
Yugi! Anzu!
Guys, try to visualize it!
That we're going to my other self!
- Yup.
Suh-weet!
We're really flying!
Then maybe if we imagine they're gone, they'll disappear?
Whoa, that's a pretty good idea, Honda!
- They're gone!
They're still there.
Guess things can't be that easy...
Let's hurry, guys!
To where the Other Me is!
Dammit, what's the deal?
We finally made it to Egypt, but I can't contact my brother at all!
What's that light?
Is that the Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon?
Just what has started to happen here?
That's...!
You mentioned something about opening a new future after beating me.
But your road, Kaiba,
is only lined with blood!
Damn you...
Prince...
I'll give you my Ba...
Prince!
Mana, I...
Don't push yourself!
That Monster...
After Lord Seto's Ka was beaten, a new Ka appeared and changed its form.
I'm not sure where this Ka came from, but it seems to be fighting for our side!
Kaiba...!
That's...
We don't have any time left...!
Mana, hand me the Millennium Scales!
Y-Yes!
I'll use the rest of my Ba in this one attack!
Betting my life to do so!
Kalim, lend me your strength!
Prince!
Kaiba!
Yugi!
Master of Dragon Knight!
Here I come, Zorc!
How pointless!
Did it work...?
How can he...?!
Pharaoh...
Guardian of the Pharaoh's soul!
Please guide me!
In the beginning, the world was formed from darkness.
It was then that light was created.
Dark and light...
In the end, darkness will always exceed light.
That is the fate of this world.
But foolish humans fear the darkness.
They cling to the light with what they label "hope"!
Powerless as you all are, you cling to the tiny scraps of this light with all you have.
That light, Nameless Pharaoh, is you.
A mere speck of a soul like yours never had a chance of defeating me!
Zorc, even if our light is destroyed,
someone will inherit the light of my soul.
It will never cease to exist!
Until you are defeated!
Then, just as you wish, you will vanish!
Hasan!
You're...!
Shadi!
Pharaoh, do not give up yet!
The light of hope you believe in is now headed this way!
Light of hope...?
Shadi...!
Shadi!
Wait for me, Other Me!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
After the Three Illusionary Beasts were beaten,
not even the ultimate Fusion Monster between Kaiba-kun and the Pharaoh,
Master of Dragon Knight, was able to beat Zorc.
The Pharaoh falls into despair.
But don't give up!
We found your real name!
We're going to bring it to you now!
We're going to give you the last of your hope!
Next time!
"In the Name of the Pharaoh!!"
Please look forward to it!