Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The other me is starting on his journey to search for his lost memories.
It's finally time to reveal the memories of three thousand years ago.
What kind of fate lies ahead for us when that happens?
But the God Cards were stolen before we set off on our trip to Egypt.
Ah! You're Bakura-kun!
"Dark Bakura on the Move"
You're... Bakura-kun!
There isn't a single soul out there not aware that you have the God Cards.
It's only natural that these people would want to steal them.
Isn't it your duty to protect them?
And these wretched losers, of all people...!
Haga-kun and Ryuzaki-kun!
That was a close shave!
You'd nearly lost them!
Here!
The cards are safe...
But...
You talking about this?
I'm sorry, but you'll need to lend this to me for the time being.
This was something that belonged to me originally, anyway.
I see...
You're the dark personality...
But rest assured.
All the Millennium Items are necessary When the Pharaoh regains his memory.
I'll return this to you when the time comes.
How much does Bakura-kun know about the Millennium Items?
I know the Tablet of the Pharaoh's Memories is in an underground temple in Egypt...
I heard that it has holes in it that match the Millennium Items.
Bakura-kun, do you know about that?
Do you know what happens when you fit all the Millennium Items into the tablet?
Hmph. You mean the Slate of Memories located in the village of Kul Elna?
That stone tablet is an artifact that connects this world to the world beyond.
It links our world to the world beyond?
When the seven Millennium Items are placed in the stone tablet...
...the Door of the Underworld will open.
The Door of the Underworld...?
My real aim is what lies beyond that door...
To open the door to the afterlife...
I'm sure you know what that means.
Yes, I know.
This Millennium Puzzle has sealed up the soul of the other me-
No, the Pharaoh's soul will return back to the afterlife, or the "Underworld".
Correct!
That is your mission.
I'll help you out however I can, if it means accomplishing that mission.
Bakura-kun, just what are you...
Bakura, what are you plotting?
Oh my, his majesty shows himself.
Are you worried about that I'd trick that vessel of yours?
Answer me, Bakura!
Don't be so cold.
I'm the same as you, a soul that was sealed 3,000 years ago.
What is your true identity?
Beats me. I can't remember that much about myself.
But the answer to that may be somewhere in your memories.
Bakura...
What do you say, Your Highness?
Isn't it about time we settled things?
On a stage most fitting for us...
Your Memory World.
My "Memory World"?
You really don't know anything about yourself, huh?
That impenetrable maze in your heart...
The complex games filled with mystery you continue to involve yourself with.
But if we trace those mysteries to the root source,
it all points in the direction
of your Memory World.
In other words, the Ultimate Dark Game is lying in wait there!
The Ultimate Dark Game?
You may not remember a thing...
But you were the one
who started that game.
I'm the one who started the Dark Game?
That is why it is the most fitting place for us to finish it.
The Ultimate Dark Game...
My Memory World...
Very well, Bakura.
I accept your challenge!
That's what I'm talking about...
When the door to your memory opens, the game will start.
I'm looking forward to the moment it does.
Now then, there are still some things that I need to do.
Prior preparations that I need in order to win the Ultimate Dark Game.
What's wrong?
Hey, President!
Thanks for working overtime.
You're Bakura...!
Mo-Mokuba!
Don't worry, he's only unconscious.
What the hell are you up to, you bastard?!
Nothing, this is just a greeting.
I wanted to have a Dark Game with you up on the big stage.
How about a Duel, Seto-sama?
Mokuba!
I've been waiting for you, President.
So, shall we start the Dark Game?
Dark Game? What nonsense.
For such a pathetic reason, you went after Mokuba...
But that's when your luck ran out!
Don't you dare think that you'll leave here unharmed.
That's the spirit.
You'll regret this, you cretin.
Here I go!
Duel!!
What's with this heavy, painful atmosphere?
Don't be so surprised.
This is the game you often experienced 3,000 years ago.
A game from 3,000 years ago?
For someone like me who always looks ahead, today's victory belongs to yesterday's glory.
If you're here to talk about ridiculous occult bullshit, go find Yugi!
Oh, yes.... Yugi is also joining this Dark Game.
What?
What lies ahead for me and Yugi is the Ultimate Dark Game.
For that purpose, I must be wary of all risks and dangers.
You see, a Monster capable of destroying the gods lies within your deck.
Let's start! I'll go first.
Draw!
I fuse Headless Knight and Ghost Earl from my hand!
To Summon The Dead Duke!
I can't attack on my first turn.
I end my turn here.
Humph. So, you Summoned a Monster with an Attack of 2000 in the first turn?
My turn, draw!
Appear, Blood Vorse!
But that guy's Attack Points aren't enough.
Hold on!
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Shrink!
It will reduce the Attack Power of one Monster on the field by half.
Go, Blood Vorse!
That Monster is one that cannot be destroyed in battle...
But rather than protect you, it will become your downfall.
Go on and do it then.
With that, I end my turn.
My turn!
With that Monster around, your Life should go down by 500 points each turn.
Are you planning to skip that?
You know some pretty trivial crap...
I sacrifice The Dead Duke to Summon Diabound Kernel.
In addition, I activate the Equipment Magic, Spirit Illusion, from my hand.
This Equipment Card allows me to Special Summon a Doppelganger Token
with the same attributes as the Monster equipped with it.
Regardless of how many weaklings you play, nothing will change here.
We'll see, won't we?
Go, Doppelganger Diabound!
What?
Doppelganger Diabound has Special Abilities as well.
The Attack Power of the Monster equipped
with Doppelganger Diabound will have its Attack Power reduced by its own Attack Points.
With that, your Monster's Attack Power is only 100.
Take this, Seto!
I set one reverse card, and end my turn.
My turn, draw!
I Summon Lord of Dragons!
The Lord of Dragons...
When this card is on the field face-up,
Dragon-Types cannot be targeted by Magic or Trap Cards.
Then I activate a Magic Card, The Flute of Summoning Dragon.
If Lord of Dragons is on the field,
I can call up to two Dragon-Types to the field from my hand.
Come forth!
The strongest creature lying in my hand!
My strongest and most beautiful servant!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
So you've finally appeared, blue-eyed white dragon!
The only Monster capable of going up against God!
What was... that vision just now...?
The two gods
have the same Attack Points!
What?!
Wh-What...
...is going on here?!
This fog's engulfed the town...!
What's this painful feeling...?
That was the vision that both Yugi and I saw when the two gods battled!
Hmm? What's wrong?
It's your turn.
Instead of trying to find out the reason, defeating this guy is more important now!
Here I come!
Blue-Eyes attacks!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
It's useless!
Trap Card, Spirit Shield!
What?!
What a pity!
Spirit Shield allows me to remove
one Fiend-Type or Undead-Type from the Graveyard,
in order to negate a Monster's attack.
And this effect continues as long as I have the Monsters needed for the cost in my Graveyard.
With this, I'm safe for the time being.
Petty tricks...
I set one card face-down and complete my turn!
Okay now...
If I don't defeat him, I can't achieve my aim.
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Pot of Greed.
This card's effect allows me to draw two cards.
I then activate another Magic Card! Grief Tablet!
Lord of Dragons!
All the abilities of the Monster trapped in that stone slab will be sealed.
You'll need to destroy it with your own hands if you want to get out of this predicament!
But that would mean losing 500 Life Points in the process.
Come on, Doppelganger Token!
Go get Blue-Eyes!!
Blue-Eyes!
Go, Diabound Kernel!
Death Spiral!!
I activate my Trap!
Attack Guidance Armor!
He got away?
I set two cards and end my turn.
My turn, draw!
This man certainly did his research on my deck...!
That just means that I'll be the true victor if I can win this!
For the sake of my deck...
For the sake of my Blue-Eyes..!
I activate the Magic Card, Life-Shaving Card Treasure, from my hand.
I can draw until I have five cards in my hand.
After five turns, I must discard all the cards in my hand to the Graveyard!
It doesn't matter what cards you draw...
...because I have the invincible Spirit Shield!
Then, I'll destroy that shield!
Magic Card, Soul Release!
With its effects, Ghost Earl and The Death Duke are excluded from your Graveyard!
Now you've lost all the Fiend-Type and Undead Zombie-Type Monsters in your Graveyard!
With that, your shield is destroyed!
In addition, I activate the Magic Card, Silent Death, from my hand.
I Special Summon Blood Vorse back from my Graveyard in Attack Position.
I then sacrifice Blood Vorse and Blue-Eyes...
Forgive me...
Rather than let you live on in that weak state, I'll let you be reborn in a new life!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
You sacrificed your Blue-Eyes to Summon another Blue-Eyes White Dragon?
The likes of you has no business touching my Blue-Eyes like that!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
As expected...
But this is not over yet!
I activate a Trap! Mirror Tablet!
Then I activate another Trap, Rebirth Tablet!
What?!
Rebirth Tablet is a Trap Card activated when a Monster is destroyed.
It allows me to revive a Monster in my Graveyard.
And then...
When a Monster is destroyed,
Mirror Tablet transfers half of the Attack Power of the destroyed Monster to another.
The selected Monster is then forced into battle.
Now, the Attack Power of Diabound Kernel is higher.
Go forth, Diabound Kernel!
Death Spiral!!
Blue-Eyes is immortal!
Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead!!
This is enough.
The true Special Ability of Diabound...
It holds the power to absorb the abilities of the Monsters it defeats.
For now, my goal has been fulfilled.
It's already this time...?
It's a pity, Seto.
I'll leave it at that for today.
What?! You plan to leave in the middle of a Duel?!
I'm about to head out on a trip, you see.
I'll give this to you to make up for it!
This is...!
Pegasus'...?
That's right, the Millennium Eye.
This is your invitation to the Ultimate Dark Game.
If you want to settle this, take that with you and come to Egypt.
Egypt? What nonsense!
I keep saying it! I have no interest in all this ludicrous occult business!
But aren't you at least a bit interested in the connection between you and Blue-Eyes?
Me and Blue-Eyes?
I'll be eagerly waiting for you, Seto.
The connection between me and Blue-Eyes...
-Hey~!
Yugi!
Huh?! Jounouchi-kun! Anzu! Honda-kun! All that luggage...!
The answer is obvious!
We're heading to Egypt too!
But...
Don't you worry about the expenses... Anzu will be paying.
Hey, Jounouchi!
I'm only lending you some of the funds I'll be using to study overseas!
I understand, Miss! I swear to work hard and pay you back when we return!
I had to beg my big sis for the money!
Besides, we can't possibly just send you off.
Yes! Besides, the other Yugi is our friend too!
That about sums it up!
Thanks guys!
Let's go! Let's head to Egypt.
Mm-hmm!
It's finally time to open the door to my Memory World.
And when that happens,
the Ultimate Dark Game between Bakura and me will start as well.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Of course we must go together to Egypt.
Using this way of sending the other Yugi off in search of his memory just doesn't seem right.
Because, after this, the other Yugi may...
No, I can't get depressed.
That is his greatest wish.
I must bid him a joyful farewell.
Along with Ishizu-san and her family, who were waiting for us in Egypt,
we finally head off for the Memory Tablet.
Next time!
"The Door of Memory Opens"
Please look forward to it!