Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Against Perfect Machine King's unfathomable Attack Power,
Otogi-kun and Shizuka-chan thought it was all over.
But after hearing
Jounouchi-kun's voice,
Shizuka-chan used the power of the card Honda-kun left for them,
and she was able
to beat the Big Five!
Yet, Honda-kun still
didn't come back...
"Kidnapped Mokuba:
Kaiba VS Psycho Shocker"
Huh? Everything seems bigger for some reason...
Yo!
Oi!
Honda-san...
Those guys said their goal was to get our bodies.
So that means Honda-kun hasn't disappeared yet.
That's right.
He may be around
here somewhere.
Let's split up and search for him.
Right.
Honda!
Where's everyone else?!
What the hell are you trying to pull?
Kaiba, I have a huge
grudge against you!
What the hell are you talking about?
Talking's pointless!!
Guys, over here!
Honda-kun!
Honda-san!
Yugi!
Honda! So you're safe?!
Thank goodness!
So you're here to get in my way?
I get it!
He's not Honda-kun!
What do you mean?
You don't think...!
That's right,
I'm one of the Big Five.
Soichiro Ota!
This body now belongs to me!!
Don't you underestimate my grade 5 kendo skills.
Let's finish it.
Wh-What the?!
Jounouchi-kun!
Piss off!
Wake up already!
Honda!!
Honda!
You alright?!
Big brother!
Kaiba, I'll be taking the thing you care most about with me!
Ota! You bastard!
Wait, Honda!
Honda!
Honda-kun!
H-Hey! You went too far!
Kaiba-kun!
Shit... Did Honda really
get his ass taken?
Honda-san!
It's the thing from before...
What the heck's with this thing?
Maybe this poor thing's been captured and turned into a robot.
It's dangerous, Shizuka-chan!
This guy could be
leading you into a trap!
It's certainly possible,
considering the world we're in.
If it's dangerous,
we should probably break it.
Wait! This little guy
could be trying to help us!
How can you tell that?
But he tried to save Kaiba-san!
Well I guess that's true...
I'm sure of it!
Right?
Since Shizuka-chan insists on it,
we'll spare your life.
Guys, let's follow Kaiba-kun!
That man inside Honda-kun should know where the real one's being held.
Shut up! If ya don't settle down, I'm seriously beat ya to a pulp!
Big brother!
Just hang on, Mokuba!
It's been quite some time, Seto Kaiba.
Who are you?
It's me.
Have you forgotten me?
What did you do with Mokuba?
Mokuba?
Now that you bring it up, I saw a man holding a kid drive past here a few minutes ago.
Noah-sama.
Ota, what's the meaning of this?
Well... this is to pay Kaiba back...
I believe I told you to refrain from using cheap methods.
But if I don't act now, I'll never get another opportunity to get my revenge.
You're looking pretty pathetic.
I will watch over the kid.
But-
Are you disobeying me?
I can't believe you'd do something as low as taking Mokuba hostage!
You're more naive than I thought.
What did you say?!
Where am I...?
Finally awake?
You...!
What do you want with me?!
I'm shocked.
I was the one who saved you.
What'd you say!?
Then bring my brother
here this instant!
Don't be in such a rush.
Take a look up there.
Big brother!
From this point on,
your big brother will begin his Duel.
My brother's going to Duel?
If you desire to go to where Mokuba is,
you are going to have to defeat me first.
How absurd.
There's no way you
stand a change against me!
But very well.
I'll accept your challenge!
Assemble your deck, Seto!
However, no matter how hard you look, you won't find the God Cards.
Those are forbidden cards.
If you're done building your deck, choose your Deck Master!
For my Deck Master, I choose...
The Lord of Dragons!
My Deck Master is...
I'd like to tell you, but I think it'd be funner for you to anticipate it later on.
That will make the shock that much greater for you later on.
An obvious bluff won't work against me.
A blue flame burns deep within me.
If you aren't afraid of it...
...then bring it on!
Let's go!
DUEL!!
I will make the first move.
My turn!
A Monster in Defense Position.
I'll then place
two more cards face-down.
My turn is over!
My turn! Draw card!
I Summon Spear Dragon!
Spear Dragon...
If it attacks a Monster whose Attack Power is lower than its Attack Power,
this card gives damage to the player as a result.
I won't let you keep a Wall Monster on the field!
Go, Spear Dragon!
Dragon Screw!!
What?!
Thanks to the Demon Scout you destroyed,
my opponent is forced to draw three cards, and if there are any Magic Cards among them, it must be discarded.
Now, toss aside any Magic Cards you are holding!
But I can still play a card face-down!
My set card is
the Deck Destruction Virus of Death.
So this match is as good as over.
I'll use this timing
to activate my Trap Card!
Blessing of God!
My turn!
Card draw!
Blessing of God is a card that increases my Life Points by 500 every time I draw a card.
As a result of this card's effect, I will increase my Life Points by 500 right now!
But Daimon, your deck will only live for one more turn.
And next turn, I'll give you heavy damage.
I place a Monster Card in Defense Position.
I then place one card face-down.
Turn over!
Strange...
Spear Dragon is a Monster that automatically switches to Defense Mode after dealing battle damage to the opponent.
And it has 0 Defense Points!
Even knowing that, he won't attack?
Now, come attack me...
I have no idea what you're planning,
but you're finished this very instant!
My turn!
I Summon Giant Virus!
And I switch Spear Dragon
into Attack Mode!
Spear Dragon, attack his Monster!
You're too naive, Seto!
Trap Card, activate!
Mask of Perplexity!
You fell for it!
Mask of Perplexity blinds you and causes you to be unable to see where you are attacking.
It's a card that lets me
switch the attack target!
Big brother!
Right now, you won't be able to tell who you are attacking.
Spear Dragon, attack him over there!
What?!
Too bad for you.
You just ordered Spear Dragon to attack your Monster.
Giant Virus!
But Daimon, you're the one who's been trapped.
I will use Giant Germ as the needed sacrifice to activate my Trap Card, Deck Destruction Virus of Death!
What in the-
Impossible!
Why was my Trap Card destroyed?
It couldn't be...
Your Deck Master...!
Right, that's correct!
My Deck Master is...
Psycho Shocker!
My Deck Master Ability holds the power to block all of my opponent's Traps!
Seto Kaiba, you will never be activating Trap Cards again!
I sold many Kaiba Corporation missiles and other weapons of war to other countries.
But the most popular was the virtual system you created.
Even now, the program you invented is being used around the world as a mean of combat.
And because of that, I...!
"...forced Gozaburo Kaiba to his death", am I right?
Gozaburo's first mistake was giving you a birthday present that would eventually lead to his doom.
Beginning today, Seto, your format education will come to an end.
Let me take this
opportunity to praise you.
Today is your birthday.
I have a present for you.
Please accept it!
Seto, Mokuba... As of today, you each hold two percent of Kaiba Corporation's stocks.
And Seto...
I am going to loan you this money, with the condition that you must pay it all back.
Loan?
That's right. Starting right now, your year-long test will begin.
You must return 100 times that money within that time period.
If you cannot accomplish something as small as this, you have no hopes of ever running Kaiba Corporation.
Now sign this IOU.
Or would you like to return to your previous home?
Very good.
I will have Daimon lend his aid.
And with that, I'll be looking forward to our meeting in one year.
Hey, what are you
going to do, big brother?
Paying back the money 100-fold is way too hard!
Relax. This is simply a game.
We've got 100 cards.
This card represents one percent of the total stocks...
In other words, it's a handicap.
There's a rule among stock marketers.
The person who holds this card cannot be bought out by any other.
Whoever holds the
card can't be bought out?
Meaning it makes 51%.
If a person holds at least
51 of the total 100 cards,
no other person will have anything higher.
You win the game.
Daimon, use all of the money to purchase 51% of the stocks of any company.
You want to spend it all right away?
Any company will do, so long as it is highly rated and traditional.
Come in.
Seto-sama, I have successfully purchased a company.
I have selected an old funeral home in which the workers are highly devoted.
Awesome! So that makes you the president of this company, big brother!
Becoming the president of such a small business will not serve my purpose.
It'll be impossible to earn 100 times the price in just one year.
But there is a way to make them pay it all to me.
Impossible!
You intend for me to buy my company back at five times the price?!
If you don't, I will fire both you and your employees.
It'll be a huge loss for you all.
I can't believe such a young boy could think up a plan so evil...!
Your ability to earn money far surpassed Gozaburo's expectations.
Gozaburo used the virtual system I invented for military weapons, crushing my dream in the process.
I decided then in my heart that I would do all it took to use that man and surpass him.
But all of that ends
right here and now.
Your dream will perish along with you!
Not yet!
I activate the Effect of Giant Virus!
I Special Summon the same card
from my deck onto the board!
Seto, thanks to the year I spent by your side, I've learned quite a bit about you and your territory.
Without Traps at your disposal, you can only use the power of your Monsters.
But I believe in my deck!
My turn!
Thanks to Blessing of God,
I regain 500 Life Points!
I'll then place two cards face-down and end my turn.
My turn!
Draw card!
Spear Dragon, attack his Wall Monster!
Dragon Screw!!
I activate the Effect of Cyber Pod!
All Monsters on the field are destroyed!
What?!
And both players
draw five cards from their deck.
You then Summon any Level 4 Monster Card you hold on the field.
So they're at a draw?
Big brother!
My turn.
Because of Blessing of God, I regain 500 Life Points.
I'll then use a Magic Card!
Watch Tranquilizer!
This device were designed by Gozaburo himself.
It was intended to be a new weapon developed by Kaiba Corporation.
Shall we give it a little test?
You'll be first!
Fire!!
Watch Tranquilizer is a Magic Card that drains an opponent's Monster 100 Attack Points times their level.
Thus, the Level 4 Blood Vorse's Attack Power will go down 400 points!
But he only has a 500 Attack Power Monster on the field!
I will also activate the Special Effect of Injection Angel Lily!
By paying 1000 of my Life,
I can raise Lilly's Attack Points by 3000!
She has 3400 Attack Points?!
Go, Lilly!
It's time to diagnose
the Seto Kaiba disease!
Here's your injection!
I then activate a Magic Card!
Sebek's Blessing!
Sebek's Blessing is a card that increases my Life by the amount of damage my opponent received.
That brings me another step towards victory!
I Summon a Monster in Defense Position.
My turn is over!
My turn!
Lilly's Attack Power has returned to 400.
The Worm Beast has 1400 Attack Points.
If I get through, I can heavily wound his Life Points.
But...
If he uses Lilly's Effect again to raise her Attack Points,
I'll take the hit instead and my Life will drop to 0.
I just have to endure it.
I've endured countless problems in my life.
I'll place a Monster in Defense Position!
Not going to attack...?
In that case, I'll activate another Trap before it shifts to your turn!
Life Absorbing Machine!
Life Absorbing Machine is a card that returns half of the Life Points you lost in your previous turn once per turn.
So he's setting up a Life Recovery Combo so he can use Lilly endlessly?!
My turn!
Thanks to the effect of Blessing of God,
I regain some of my Life!
Now I'll let you see it, Seto.
The greatest weapon Gozaburo ever built!
I'll sacrifice both Defense Monsters I have on the field!
In order to Summon this Monster!
Wh-What the...?
I wonder how long this road goes on for.
But it's netter if we don't run into any other roads!
That way we won't lose sight of our-
What's wrong, Jounouchi-kun?
Yugi, look at that thing.
What in the world is that?!
With Psycho Shocker as his Deck Master,
Kaiba-kun can't use any Trap Cards.
And thanks to Imperial Command of the Royal Palace, even all his Magic Cards have been sealed!
With no hopes of winning the Duel in site,
the Satellite Cannon targets Kaiba-kun from the sky!
Is there any way for Kaiba-kun to fight this thing?!
Next time!
"The Attack from Space: Satellite Cannon"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise