With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Clash! Blue Eyes vs. Red Eyes
Seto Kaiba is coming to my island?
You need not worry! We'll catch him in no time!
Kaiba can't hide in the Duelist Kingdom forever...
No! You aren't to lay a hand on Seto Kaiba!
The contract states that I have to defeat Yugi-boy and that will be no problem.
When that happens, Kaiba Corporation will be ours.
The Kaiba Corporation's advanced technology and the genius mind....
...of Seto Kaiba will belong to us.
Seto Kaiba... I'll be waiting for our meeting.
Yugi... his battle style is incomparable...
The card I just drew...
Is The Sealed One, Exodia!
Light of Hellfire!
Exodo Flame!!
Now matter how strong a card is...
It's useless if you can't connect your heart with that card.
When you connect your heart with the cards, miracles happen!
I want to battle with him once again!
But before that, there's someone that I want to defeat with this duel disc system.
Brother!
To take control of Kaiba Corporation...
I have to attack those traitors...
And the man that kidnapped Mokuba.
Pegasus J. Crawford!
I'm going to defeat you with my own hands!
What's wrong, Bakura-kun?
Look at this...
One of the needles of the Millennium Ring is pointing to Pegasus' Castle.
It's true.
It was the same when I was transferred to Domino High.
From today onwards, we'll have a new student with us.
How 'bout this?!
It's your turn, Yugi!
-That day, it was pointing to your Millennium Puzzle.
-What's with that card?!
Shit~!
Then, the Millennium Ring is pointing to the Millennium Item that Pegasus owns?
Millennium Item?
Maybe the Millennium Ring can locate the other Millennium Items.
What exactly are the Millennium Items? Where did they came from?
Right now, I don't know anything.
My Millennium Puzzle is not the only Millennium Item that exists.
When I completed the Millennium Puzzle, inside of me,
I discovered the existence of another me.
I would like to know... this puzzle...
If I can understand this puzzle...
I will be able to save my grandfather from the Dark World.
Wait until then, Grandpa.
What the...
Who is it? Doing such a thing at this time at night?
What? What?
Kaiba-kun!
It's been a while... Yugi!
That's right...
Here... Kaiba-kun's Deck...
I saved it for you.
For now, I'll thank you.
Kaiba-kun, you understand the heart of the cards now, right?
What is it?
Right now, I don't have the answer for this...
To protect Mokuba and Kaiba Corporation...
I will defeat Pegasus.
By any means necessary.
Kaiba-kun...
Wait a minute, Kaiba!
All people in Duelist Kingdom have to work hard to win 10 Star Chips...
...in order to fight that same Pegasus!
It doesn't matter what your reasons are, I won't forgive you if you pass over us!
Jounouchi-kun!
Are you alright, Jounouchi-kun?
Damn...
Jounouchi, it can't be that you are participating in this too, can it?
Don't underestimate me!
I may not look like much, but I was the Best Eight of a tournament!
It was the Regional Championship Tournament, right...?
If even someone like you is a Duelist here, this island's level must be pretty low.
What?!
Stop it, Jounouchi!
Wait, Kaiba!
I am not the same person as before!
That's true, Kaiba-kun! Jounouchi defeated Mai Kujaku-san and Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Fight! If you want to battle Pegasus, first you will have to face me off!
Stop with that!
That's true! You're gonna hurt yourself...
What's the problem, Kaiba? Here and now, fight with me!
Interesting.
I will shatter that glass confidence you have, until there's nothing left.
Kaiba-kun...
Don't worry... this battle won't put your star chips at stake.
I will only use Jounouchi's energy to test my new duel disk system.
New duel disk system?
Put that on your left arm.
What is this?
Duel Disk... the new card battle machine that I've created...
Even without a Duel Ring, it can create a field using a virtual simulation system.
First, fix the Deck Holder on your left arm.
So, what next?
Just watch!
Set your cards in the deck holder for its activation.
Draw the card from the Deck Holder, and set the card you will use in the duel on the Duel Disk.
After that, throw the Duel Disk in the field where you want.
Let's go!
Minotaur!
The card's data is read by the Duel Disk...
and the Hyper 3-D Engine projects its image...
That's shown as a Solid Vision!
Amazing! Kaiba-kun just evolved the card battles!
Interesting!
I'll battle with this card!
Battle!
Let's go!
Go! Armor Lizard!
Minotaur! Cut the enemy down!
All right! It didn't work!
Fool!
Go!
My card was...
When the monster is destroyed, pull back the duel disk.
Until you have played a monster, I'll pass my turn.
Don't look down on me!
Just watch!
Let's go!
Flame Swordsman!
If it's about Attack Points, he's got more!
Fighting Spirit Flame Sword!
Don't! Minotaur is strong against Flame Attacks!
Iron Axe!
Flame Swordsman is destroyed!
I knew it. You've gotta be the worst Duelist in existence.
The Fusion and Centaur cards...
Duel Disk set!
Stop looking down at me like that!
Let's go!
Barbarian #2!
Axe Raider!
Bull Devil!
Garoozis!
Cavern Genie! Ogre Rock!
Rude Kaiser!
What happened to the confidence you had before, Jounouchi? Gone already?
It's useless... I can't win like this... our levels are way too different...
Don't give up!
Stand up, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
That's right! I don't want to see you like that!
Shut up!
I understand.
I still won't give up!
The battle begins now!
Watch closely, my Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Jounouchi!
His trump is here!
Let's go!
Dark Flame Bullet!
All right!
Getting excited because you succeeded getting through one turn...
That's why I said you're the worst Duelist in existence!
What?!
I've been holding onto the card your friend got back for me in this deck.
Appear, Blue-Eyes!
Prepare yourself!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Dammit!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi...
Did you learn your lesson after dueling me?
With your incompetence, I don't know how you made it this far.
Jounouchi... it really suits you to be on your knees.
Like a loser dog unable to stand up after a single loss.
Kaiba-kun...
What? What do you think you know?
You don't know why Jounouchi is fighting...
Don't say anything if you know nothing of it!
That's right! Jounouchi-kun's sister's eyes are...
Stop it! Don't say anything more!
Even the weakest duelist on this island has a reason to fight, right?
The most important thing here is if you can protect that reason.
Jounouchi... it was a huge mistake to fight me.
Now you've got the eyes of a loser dog after fighting me.
You cannot stand up as a Duelist anymore.
Kaiba-kun... why are you...?
Pegasus's castle. That's where he awaits.
Pegasus J. Crawford...
The creator of Duel Monsters, a man with a terrifying power.
His mind created the rules... In his hands all the cards were created.
In this island, to get in that castle, all duelists are collecting stars.
But that's only what the god of the card kingdom wants them to do.
Yugi, even with your skills, defeating Pegasus is impossible.
I've seen him in the past once in a Duel...
No... I can't call that a duel.
It was in New York Duel Stadium, with the fight of the King of Duelists!
I was invited as a special guest to that battle.
Pegasus's opponent was America's Number One Card Professor, Keith Howard.
Because he was always pursuing big prizes in money, he was known as "Bandit Keith".
Fightin' with you will be an honor.
Well... when this duel is over, I'll be recognized as the world's number one.
Amazing! Who's gonna win?
I drew a good card...
Hey, what are you doing? The duel already started!
Pegasus just looked down on Keith and wrote on a piece of paper.
And called a kid that was seated behind me....
...to play in his place.
W-What?
Don't screw with me, Pegasus!
I’m not doing anything of the sort.
This young boy will duel with you in my place.
D-Do you think I can do it?
No problem. If you follow the instruction on this memo, you'll win.
Pegasus!
Hello, Kaiba-boy...
Oh.. yeah... I read the proposal you made me...
Card Battle Simulator System... I found it incredible!
Let's work together with Kaiba Corporation to make it real.
So you'd rather run away than lose to me?
Doesn't matter... as long as I get the prize...
I'll use this card, ya damn brat!
Let me see... when you play that card, I have to play this card in Attack Mode.
W-What?
It seems that I win with this attack.
Impossible! He knew all that I had in my hand in advance?
Oh my God! Oh my God!
Tom wins!
He used some kind of trick.
I don't know if the Duel Disks will be enough to win over this trick...
Pegasus...
Alright, I use this card.
The Devil Dragon card, am I right?
What?
I already knew that you would play this card.
That power... I have seen it...
Kaiba-kun... You...
This fight that you had with Jounouchi-kun was to...
Yugi... I'm going to Pegasus's place...
To defeat Pegasus and also...
To take back what is mine!
Kaiba! Just like you, we too have things that are precious and we don't want to lose.
Pegasus will be defeated by me.
Then, I'll say it in a different way...
I'm going to Pegasus' castle before anyone.
Welcome, Kaiba-boy!
After being defeated by Kaiba-kun, Jounouchi finds himself in a great pinch!
The former US Champ, Bandit Keith, plans to trap Jounouchi in a match.
Keith's followers ambushed Jounouchi and dragged him to a Graveyard Field where he has to fight with Ghost Kotsuzuka.
Wait! You can't accept a duel in this condition!
Next time: "Terror! Call of the Living Dead"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship