Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Semi-Final Match of Darkness: Jounouchi VS Malik"
This is going different than I originally planned, but alas.
I'm going to severely punish you for making me angry, Jounouchi.
Finally.
I'm going to beat Malik and save you, no matter what it takes.
Wait for me, Mai!
This is as it should be...
I'm the one who will obtain victory in this fated Duel with Yugi.
Everything will be settled once we reach the top.
They're gone...
Hey, you guys!
Over here!
We're gonna go cheer em on!
Uh, hold on a second!
Don't you think we should inform Shizuka-chan of what's going on first?
That Jounouchi-kun's Semi-Final match is about to begin, I mean.
Yeah, you're right!
Okay! I'll go do it!
Hold up!
This should be fine if you wanna contact her, right?
No, I'm going to remain here and continue looking after Mai-san.
I believe that my brother will win this!
Yes. Thank you.
Big brother...
So this is the final Duel arena...?
Kinda dreary, huh...?
Oh, don't fret over it.
I'll make it look
much more interesting...
A view much more entertaining than anything you have ever seen!
Look forward to it, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun intentionally sacrificed himself in the Battle Royale
so he'd be paired up with Malik...
And the reason he would want to Duel Malik so badly must be...
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun, we'll fight in the Final.
So you have to win!
Yeah! Don't you worry!
I'm gonna take Malik's God Card and then use it to keep our promise and fight you, Yugi!
You're not worthy to touch God, Jounouhi.
Ah?! What was that, Kaiba?
I hereby declare...
You will be killed instantly by Malik.
W-Why you bastard!
If you got something to say, then say it!
I won and got this far in Battle City, too, you know!
No way am I gonna go down that easily!
Neither of you know the true power of Malik's God Card.
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra has Special Abilities so terrifying they surpass mortal thought.
Eh...? I-Is it really that powerful...?
Kaiba... Are you trying to say that you know what Ra's Special Abilities are?
Yes... I've almost decoded it.
He translated the card's text from the Egyptian Hieratic Text...?
Can you decipher the script?
It contains the key to awakening the true powers of Ra!
Ra's true powers?!
That's right...
Ra has quite the terrifying Special Abilities hidden within it...
This is one of Ra's abilities.
God himself will serve the player who utters the sacred text!
Bring me victory!
Awaken, Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
This is the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Wh-What the...?
Big brother?
Impossible...!
I can understand what this text says!
And it tells about Ra's Special Abilities!
It's terrifying...!
Why the hell are you able to read it?
Kaiba really must have some connection to the history of the Millennium Items...
Yugi... Even you don't have a chance against Malik's Ra Deck!
Not even Yugi can win?!
Ra's Ability far surpasses the powers of my Obelisk and your Osiris.
In order for me to come up with a complete strategy to defeat him,
I need to watch
Malik fight one more time.
Jounouchi, you're suitable enough to be used as my bait to draw out Malik.
Bait?!
Yugi, if you had fought
Malik in the Semi-Finals,
there was a chance he could have gotten his hands on Osiris.
If that had happened, I would have had to face two God Cards.
Why do you always have to badmouth everyone?!
Kaiba, there's just one problem with your theory...
Your opponent in the Semi-Finals...
...will be me, remember?
Our fated Duel...
I'm looking forward to it, Yugi.
That son of a bitch...!
Big brother!
There you are!
Yugi! Jounouchi!
What's up, Jounouchi?
What's with the weird face?
Did something happen?
It's nothing!
What's the deal with him?
Jounouchi...
Damn that jerk Kaiba...!
He's just trying to intimidate me before the match... Must be part of his strategy...
But it won't work!
I'm sure his god's pretty tough...
But I've got all my cards from Battle City... with the soul of each Duelist I fought!
And above all...
Unless I beat Malik, I can't save Mai!
As long as Mai is suffering, I can't realize my promise to fight as a True Duelist with Yugi!
Watch me...!
I will win!
The Battle City Semi-Finals will now commence!
For the first Duel, we have Malik Ishtar!
And challenging him...
Katsuya Jounouchi!
Hell yeah!
Beat him, Jounouchi-kun!
You can do it, Jounouchi!
You better not lose!
There is nothing else I can do.
All I can do is sit here
and watch it unfold...
Begin the Duel!!
I'll go first! Draw!!
I Summon Gil Garth in Attack Position!
I'll then place a card face-down and end my turn!
Here goes!
My turn! Draw!
Malik's Gil Garth has
1800 Attack Points...!
None of my Monsters can beat it...
I set a reverse card!
And then...!
I Summon Wyvern Warrior
in Defense Position!
I won't allow myself to lose against someone like you...!
Turn ov-
Other me! This is...!
He isn't...!
Again?!
No way!
A Dark Game...!
Big brother...!
The Dark Game
starts now, Jounouchi.
A Dark Game...?
You want to see that woman, don't you?
Then I'll let you see her...
In the Dark World of death when you lose!
What?! What does that mean?
Didn't I tell you that the woman is not merely sleeping?
Even now as the two of us discuss this,
her spirit is slowly being devoured by the darkness!
I can hear them...
Her screams as she writhes in pain...
...makes for the sweetest music!
You bastard...!
It seems that another
Dark Game has begun.
Are you really looking to sacrifice another victim, Malik?
You scum...!
He knows that if he goes on with this Duel, he'll end up in the same condition as Mai!
And he's still going through with it?!
It's way too reckless!
Jounouchi's prepared for the outcome...
But despite all that,
if he can beat Malik...
Anzu...?!
I'm sorry, Yugi...
Jounouchi asked me not to tell you this...
Anzu, don't tell Yugi this.
But why?
The two of us promised to fight each other fair and square the day we become True Duelists.
True Duelists?
To be honest, I'm not sure if I'll be able to call myself that, even after all of this.
But there's one thing I do know for sure.
If I can't save Mai with my strength alone, I'm not qualified to become one.
So in order to keep
my promised with Yugi, I...
I'll beat the hell out of Malik with my own hands.
And I'll rescue Mai from her suffering!
Jounouchi wants to fight Malik so he can save Mai-san himself!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Other me! We have to stop Jounouchi-kun!
If he loses this Duel, he's going to end up just like Mai-san and Bakura-kun!
Partner... We can't do that.
Jounouchi took on this Duel knowing that it would be a Dark Game.
As a Duelist, this Duel is a test of belief in himself.
None of us can stop him now.
But...!
Believe in him, Partner!
Believe in Jounouchi-kun!
This is my battle!
I'll beat Malik with my strength and my strength alone!
I'll save Mai!
So wait for me at the end of this, Yugi!
I accept your Dark Game!
And I'm gonna crush you!
You seriously think you can beat me?
Amusing.
But I wonder how long that strong will of yours will last.
My turn! Draw!
Now that you've entered this Dark Duel Stage, you no longer have any hope of escaping.
Just like when I fought that woman, no one will be able to save you.
It's just the two of us, right up until your bitter end.
You're going to enjoy this thoroughly, Jounouchi!
Just shut up for once
and get on with it!
Before I do that, let me tell you about the Penalty Game that awaits the loser of this Duel...
The loser will sink into
a world of darkness...
Both your mind and body will slowly... slowly...!
...without even realizing it, slip into a world of death and pain!
Exciting, isn't it?!
I envy you, Jounouchi!
Oh, the things you'll feel...!
Why's this bastard saying
all that creepy stuff?
He's just trying to stack on extra mental pressure.
Never mind it, Jounouchi-kun!
It'll take more than that to scare me!
Say that while you still have the chance!
Look!
What the heck?
All of a sudden my Monster is connected to my body!
This is the ultimate game where the Duelists experience the same pain and fear as their Monsters!
So savor every moment!
And be sure to give me
plenty of enjoyment!
Just as that woman did!
Sonova...!
Let the real game begin!!
I Summon Drillago in Attack Mode!
Go! Drillago!!
Wyvern Warrior is dead!!
Big brother...
What the?! What's wrong, Jounouchi?!
As their Monsters take damage...
the players feel the same pain!
Jounouchi-kun!
What the hell is this?
The second my Monster was destroyed, I felt a throbbing pain in my chest...!
What do you think? The reality of this ultimate game is breathtaking!
But damage from a direct attack will far exceed what you just felt!
Go, Gil Garth!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!!
Jounouchi!!
Like hell I'll let you do that!
Reverse card, open!
Scapegoat!
What!?
Heh! These guys aren't Monster Cards!
So if you take em out, I feel no damage!
Yes! Nicely done!
So even someone like you can come up with a plan, eh?
Turn end.
My turn! Draw!
Sweet!
I Summon Jet Black Swordsman - Panther Warrior in Attack Position!
Here I go! I sacrifice one of my Scapegoats!
Attack Gil Garth!!
That's payback from before!
You're not half bad...
But this wouldn't be interesting if you weren't decent.
Quit playing cool!
Turn end!
Jounouchi's not doing too bad, big brother!
I guess.
My turn...
Draw!
I'll start by activating a Magic Card from my hand!
Buried Offerings!
What?!
This card is triggered whenever I go to Tribute Summon a Monster on the field.
By removing a Monster from each of our Graveyards,
I am able to Summon a High-Level Monster without Tribute!
I sacrifice my Gil Garth and your Wyvern Warrior!
In order to Summon
Hell Poet - Helpoemer!
The Monsters used as the tributes for this Monster are removed, and can never be used in this Duel again!
Helpoemer...
2000 Attack Points...?
He's equal with my Panther Warrior...
So he'll probably go after my Scapegoats...
I then place two cards face-down on the field and end my turn!
What?
Don't let your guard down, Jounouchi-kun!
Malik must be planning something!
My turn, draw!
Psycho Shocker!
If I use him, I can beat his Helpoemer.
But why didn't he attack one of my Scapegoats this turn...?
Is it possible he's scared
of me attacking him?
I have no idea what Helpoemer's Special Ability is.
It could be a mistake to rush in and attack him with Pyscho Shocker.
I'll just leave him to the side for now.
But I still have this guy!
Rocket Warrior!
Summon!
Attack Mode!
Got you!
I activate my Trap this very moment!
Hidden Soldier!
This Trap activates when your opponent Summons a Monster!
It lets me Special Summon any Four-Star or lower Monster from my hand!
I Summon Plasma Eel!
Wha-?!
I'll then activate its Special Power!
Go! Plasma Eel!!
Equip yourself to Panther Warrior!!
Plasma Eel's Effect reduces the Attack Power of the Monster it Equips by 500 points at the end of my opponent's turn.
But it'll be much more entertaining than that for you, Jounouchi!
You're about to feel hellish pain beyond description!
Jounouchi-kun!!
Jounouchi!!
How is it?! The same pain that woman suffered through!
Mai...!
Impossible!
This should only be Solid Vision...!
But I can't move!!
I thought I told you
that this is a Dark Game...
Everything that happens here is real!
Even the pain you feel from the attacks!
Directly attack the player!
Mai...!
This is the same pain you felt...
It hurts so much...!
But you fought 'till the end as a Duelist...!
Just you wait, Mai...!
I'll pay him back for what he did to you!!
Impossible! He's still strong enough to stand up?!
I'll never forgive you
for what you've done!
I activate Rocket Warrior's Special Ability!!
Here I come, Malik!
Attack Helpoemer!
Yes! Nice one!
Get him back, Jounouchi!
Also...!
I sacrifice a Scapegoat!
Attack, Panther Warrior!
Get him with your Sword Attack!!
This one's for what you did to Mai!!
Helpoemer is dead!
How do you like that!?
It feels good...
When a Duel goes exactly
as you planned...!
What did you say?!
I wanted you to beat Helpoemer...
...so I could activate his Special Power...
Special Power...?!
It activates the moment Helpoemer dies in battle while he is in Attack Position!
What?!
His card appeared
in my Disk's Graveyard...!
Hey, can't you hear the song...?
Let's see what happens...
What's this creepy music...?!
What the heck...?!
That arm isn't just there to scare you!
It's part of Helpoemer's frightening Special Power!!
Hey...!
My hand...!
That's right...
On every turn, after every Battle Phase,
it makes you randomly discard a card from you hand to the Graveyard!
It eliminates a part
of your hand every turn...!
This must be part of Malik's terrifying strategy...!
He sent my Psycho Shocker to the Graveyard...!
There's no way...!
Jounouchi... You will slowly step further and further into my strategy...
...and deeper into the pits of darkness as well...!
Because of the Dark Game Malik set up,
Jounouchi is consumed by pain every turn when the Plasma Eel attached to Panther Warrior strikes!
Despite the pain, Jounouchi continues to Duel...
...but Malik's combo forces a card out of his hand every turn...
...and his Life is further damaged!
He's going to be beaten if this continues!
Jounouchi! Don't you have a way to turn this around?!
Next time!
"The Hell Poet - Helpoemer"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise