Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Things have gotten
even worse than I feared!
To think the three of us would end up Dueling with Shizuka-chan included!
And out of the three of us, Honda-kun and Shizuka-chan are complete amateurs!
This Big Five bastard...
He's focusing all his attacks on Shizuka-chan!
In order to protect Shizuka-chan, Honda-kun's Life Points hit 0!
Honda-kun! I won't let your sacrifice be in vain!
"Saint Jeanue:
The Trinity Attack"
NO!!
Who was that screaming just now?
I've got a bad feeling about this...
Let's hurry!
Jounouchi-kun!
Hold up!
Wait for me!
Honda-kun...
Honda-san...
For me, Honda-san...!
Shizuka-chan...
Young lady!
It's your turn, is it not?
Stand up, Shizuka-chan!
What are you waiting for?
Hurry it up!
Stand up, Shizuka-chan!
Should we assume
she's declaring "turn end"?
Shizuka-chan...
If she keeps this up,
she won't be able to Duel!
I have to do something!
For my sake, Honda-san...
Why... for me...?!
Shizuka-chan, you've got to stand up!
I need you to fight with me!
The Duel's not over yet!
If we win, Honda-kun may return!
Shizuka-chan...!
My turn!
Draw!
Good!
This will help us a lot...!
It may even reduce his Life to 0!
I activate Worm Hole from my hand!
By Worm Hole's Special Ability,
I remove Dark Assassin from play!
And since the Dark Assassin
is not on the field,
your Machine King
loses 100 Attack Points!
You've only taken him
down by one gear.
Now I'll play this - a Magic Card!
There's not a single Magic Card that can be played on the Machine King right now!
Not even this?
What?! Dice Dungeon?!
When both Dimension Dice and Dice Dungeon are played on the field,
the Dungeon Dice Field
can be activated!
Is that set card...?!
Yeah, that's right!
It's Dimension Dice!
What the hell?!
Ryuji Otogi...
You're the creator of
Dungeon Dice Monsters, right?
I was honestly surprised when I saw these cards.
I can't believe you
actually had D.D.M. cards.
I see.
Pegasus must have processed your game data while he was active in Industrial Illusions.
He must have then hacked the info into the Kaiba Corporation computers.
I sacrifice The 13th Buried and Yaranzo!
I Summon God Orgoth!
And with that sacrifice, you've lost two Machine-Type Monsters!
Your Machine King's Attack Power drops by another 200 points!
Now we each choose a Monster to play on the field.
We place them in the Dungeon Area!
We will then both roll a die.
Each role changes the course of battle, or cancels the battle altogether.
Very well.
I use Machine King on my side.
I'll be using God Orgoth.
Here goes! Die Roll!!
Rolling a six doubles the Attack Power of the Monster on your field!
Nice one!
I'll double the Attack Power
of God Orgoth!
So all I have to do
is roll a good number?
Here!
So rolling a one reduces the Attack Power of the Monster on my field by 1000?
Shit...!
Let's go, God Orgoth!
Attack the Machine King!
Diamond Blade!!
Machine King is beaten!
Turn end!
Damn you...!
My turn! Draw!
I shall place myself, Deck Master Machine Sergent, onto the field in Attack Position.
I activate Scrap-Iron Recycling Factory directly from my hand!
This card allows me to call back a Machine-Type Monster sleeping in my Graveyard.
I can then fuse it with myself!
Become my power!
Revive! Machine King!!
Wh-What in the world...?!
Thanks to Perfect Machine King's Special Effect, I receive 500 extra Attack Points for every Machine-Type Monster on the field.
There's three on the field...
That's an additional 1500?!
No, I too am a Machine Monster.
So they go up by 2000 Attack Points!
And thanks to the Continuous Effect of Clockwork Knight,
that's an additional 500!
Shit! This guy's too much!
Now then, the Field Magic on your side of the field is still active.
So we've got to have a Dungeon Dice battle, right?
So we're betting on a dice roll...?
I'll be using God Orgoth, of course!
Here.
So rolling a five cuts the Attack Power of the Monster on my field in half...?
But even if my original
Attack Power is halved,
thanks to the Machine Monsters power up and Clockwork Knight's effect, my Attack Power remains at a high 3850!
God Orgoth has 2500 Attack Points...
If I don't roll a good number,
I can't beat him!
I won't let Honda-kun's
sacrifice be in vain!
Die Roll!!
The One Effect decreases all the Monsters on my field by 1000 Attack Points!
This match is over.
Hey now...
Disappear!!
God Orgoth!!
Finally, the remaining attacking missiles will assault the player!
Otogi-san...!
If this keeps up, Otogi-san will also...
And I can't do a single thing to stop it from happening!
It's just...!
And now that God Orgoth is gone, the Dice Dungeon also is destroyed!
Shit...! Even God Orgoth didn't cut it...?
If only Honda-kun were still here so the three of us could work together...!
You've got nothing left!
Turn end.
Taking amateurs as your opponents isn't a half-bad idea.
Hopefully you'll take
the other two out as well.
Even if this kid is intelligent enough to have invented Dungeon Dice Monsters,
he's still an amateur
when it comes to Duels!
Besides, beating these amateurs is not enough for me.
He's the one
I want to take revenge on!
Just as you ordered,
Alcatraz has been destroyed.
Very good.
Thanks for confirming that.
As of today, I will be closing the Military Department of Kaiba Corporation.
And we shall proceed with the plans to build the Duel Tower.
And me...?
I would say you're qualified enough to help dispatch the building material needed for the Duel Tower.
So long as you don't become underfoot and you listen the the on-site engineer.
That will be all.
Seto Kaiba...
I will never forget the humiliation you put me through!
I've gained a chance
to have my revenge!
After I take care
of these kids, you're next!
Shizuka-chan! It's your turn!
Pull yourself together!
Don't let Honda-kun
sacrifice himself in vain!
But if this keeps up, Otogi-san will also lose because of me...!
Hurry up already!
Or are you not
capable of fighting anymore?
I have to do something...!
But I don't think there's anything I can do!
What should I do, big brother!?
Stand up, Shizuka-chan!
If you give up, everything's over!
Stand up and fight
your hardest until the end!
This could very well be your last desperate attack!
Wouldn't it be best to just end her turn?
Like hell I'll end her turn!
Shizuka-chan!
Hold it!
Take a step further and I'll count it as discussing strategies!
Think back, Shizuka-chan.
You saw Jounouchi-kun's Duel as well.
No matter what happens, Jounouchi-kun never gives up.
My big brother's... Duel?
My turn! Selket attacks!
Our next sacrifice shall be the Insect Queen!
Big brother...!
I can't! I just can't watch anymore!
Don't you run, Shizuka!
Look at me!
I might lose this, but...
I want you to watch until the end!
No matter what happens,
I can't give up...!
My brother fought fair and square right up to the end of his Duel!
Bug brother, I will continue
until the very end!
Shizuka-chan!
Shizuka...!
Yugi, you sure it's alright to be following Jounouchi?
I have no clue, but all we can do is trust Jounouchi-kun on this for now!
Over there!
I'm sure of it!
SHIZUKA!!
Big brother!
Shizuka!
Yugi-kun!
Anzu-chan!
Otogi-kun!
We finally found each other!
Nice of you to come here.
Perfect timing.
Now you get to watch as your little friends lose to me!
The Big Five!
Shizuka, what are you doing down there?!
Hey, where's Honda?
Wasn't he with you?
He was...
But that guy beat him...!
It can't be...!
No way!
Honda was...?!
You're kidding...!
You're kidding, right...?!
Why...?!
There's no way he did!
It's not possible that he was beaten!
Big brother...
I'm so sorry!
In order to protect me, Honda-san...!
Shizuka...!
Jounouchi-kun!
He still hasn't won the Duel!
If we win the Duel,
maybe Honda-kun...
Yeah, good point.
Shizuka, trade places with me!
That will not happen!
We've already started!
Damn him...!
Shizuka, listen closely.
So long as you're on the Dueling Field, you're a Duelist.
And if you're my little sister, you won't give up until the very end.
I'll...
Your big brother will be watching.
Big brother...!
Right!
Shizuka-chan!
Watch me, big brother!
It's my turn!
Draw!
Shizuka-chan, calm down and think about what Honda-kun taught you!
Right!
What Honda-san taught me...
Honda-san, while we're waiting to arrive in Domino City, teach me how to Duel!
Sure, no prob.
Let's see now...
I'm sure you already know that in a battle, the Monster with higher Attack Power wins.
But you can even trade in weaker Monsters for higher-level and more powerful Monsters.
Each card has a certain number of stars that represent its level.
For example, a Monster with more stars is more powerful.
And to call it out, you need to sacrifice one or two Monsters depending on the number of stars.
The cards all have stars on them?
They must look like a ladybug's! How cute!
A ladybug, eh?
Also, you can take those cards and fuse them together to play an even stronger card.
You'll need the Fusion card to do that.
So sacrificing and fusing are two important points, right?
Yup, you bet.
Okay!
I understand now!
Honda-san...
This has more stars...
To Summon this card, I need a sacrifice!
I do feel bad for her,
but I'll have to take the Lady Panther.
I've got this.
I sacrifice Lady Panther in order to Summon Fallen Angel Mari!
Good.
If we don't make it work this turn, we'll never get the chance to stop him.
Give it all you got, Shizuka-chan!
I'll need Fusion next.
A card capable of polymerization...
But I don't have the Fusion card...
My goddess!
Leave this to me.
In place of the Fusion card,
simply discard one Magic Card,
and I will activate my Deck Master Ability, Fusionic Eye.
And that will let you fuse your Monsters without need of the Fusion card.
This one!
A Magic Card!
I will activate my Deck Master Ability, Fusionic Eye!
By discarding one Magic Card, I fuse Fallen One Mari with Merciful Nun!
Fusionic Eye!
So that's the strongest warrior you can call out, young lady?
But it's still no match
for Perfect Machine King!
What?!
All right!
Command Angel's Special Ability raises the Attack Power of all Angel Fairy-Type Monsters like St. Jeanne by 500 points!
The Command Angel
Honda-san left behind...!
So now St. Jeanne
has 3200 Attack Points.
Perfect Machine King is the Deck Master!
He's got 4200 Attack Points!
It still wasn't enough!
That's...!
Shizuka-chan!
Otogi-kun!
This match isn't determined yet!
You have to use the power
of all three of you!
All three...?
You said "all three of us"...
...but Honda-san is...
Just where the hell do you plan on getting his help from?!
That's it!
Even if Honda-kun is gone, we can still work together!
Alright!
This is our last bet!
I activate my Deck Master Ability!
By discarding two cards from my hand, I can activate Honda-kun's set card!
What did you say?
Honda-kun, we're going to bet on the card you left us!
You better not let us down!
We're counting on you!
Honda-san's card...
"Rin"
"Assistant"
"Hyou"
"Soldier"
"Tou"
"Fighting"
"Sha"
"Person"
"Kai"
"All"
"Jin"
"Ranks"
"Retsu"
"Split"
"Zai"
"Be"
"Zen"
"Before"
Rare Metal Soul?
Great! I activate Rare Metal Soul!
Upon its activation, the Fusion Monster St. Jeanne will gain 1000 Attack Power!
What!?
Their Attack Points are equal!
It's a draw!
No!
Shizuka-chan, let this guy see the power of Honda-kun's feelings with St. Jeanne's attack!
Right!
St. Jeanne,
attack the Perfect Machine King!
DAMN YOU ALL!!
WAS I A FOOL TO
USE MY DECK MASTER!?
You did it, Shizuka!
-Yes!
-They won!
However, although I lost the Duel, I gained a body!
"A body"...?!
Don't tell me Honda-kun...!
I have accomplished
my goal at the very least!
Things are about to get interesting!
Until next time!!
This can't...
Honda-san... didn't come back...!
Shizuka!
Honda-san...!
For my sake...!
Honda-san...!!
Shizuka-chan...
Honda-kun... I'll save you no matter what!
Dammit!
Damn you all, Big Five!
Return Honda right now!!
We beat the Big Five, so why didn't Honda come back?
While we're searching for clues, Mokuba is kidnapped.
By a fake Honda!
What the heck are you doing?!
Does that mean you really had your body taken?!
Meanwhile, the final member of the Big Five appears before Kaiba-kun.
Hey, what's this little toy robot?
Next time!
"Kidnapped Mokuba: Kaiba VS Psycho Shocker"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise