Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Esper Roba:
Terror of the Psychic Deck"
Ah! Finally found one!
Please excuse me~
Dinosaur Ryuzaki-kun!
With my super natural powers, I can see every card in your hand!
Furthermore, I've knocked out your Monster with my Hypnotism card.
W-Why?!
How'd he see my hand?!
It's over now, Ryuzaki!
Psycho Shocker, attack!
Psychic Wave!!
My monster...!
That guy saw through the Ryuzaki's cards.
He really does have psychic powers!
Shit! I couldn't even touch his Life Points...
I lost!
Well, Ryuzaki.
Please hand me your rarest card along with your Puzzle Card.
Here, take it!
Serpent Night Dragon? It's an alright card...
But I can't use it in my Psychic Power Deck.
Well, who's the next challenger?!
I'll pass.
I don't know if he really has super powers, but I don't stand a chance if he can see my hand.
What about you?
Jounouchi! Ya better give up right now!
He's Esper Roba. A Duelist who has super powers!
Super powers?
Right! He read every one a' my strategies with his super powers!
Ya can't win against him!
Is that really true?
Yeah! I highly suggest you give up on him!
I feel like I can't win against this guy either.
No way in hell!
That's why I want to!
What'd ya say?!
I made a deal with Yugi...
To become a True Duelist.
Step one to becoming a True Duelist!
Don't turn your back on an opponent, no matter what!
Step two! Fight opponents that seem stronger than you!
I don't know a thing about his "super powers", but I'm gonna fight him!
Ya dumbass! Don't do it, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi...?
Oh, so you're the runner up of Duelist Kingdom...
Interesting.
I'll take you on.
I didn't know I was that famous.
Doesn't take much to get 'im overconfident...
This guy's a true blue dumbass.
Yes?
It's me, Honda.
Please come in.
I brought something good.
Good?
It's a laptop.
I borrowed it from the nurse center.
With this, we can watch the Domino City contest live on the Internet.
And you can watch your brother's Duels, Shizuka-chan.
But...
I...
That's why I want to be beside you and tell you how the Duel's going.
Please, Honda-san!
I've never seen Big brother's Duels before!
I see. Alright! Just wait a moment!
What's wrong?
Oh crap... I forgot to ask them how you use this thing...
Where did Yugi run off to?
A Rare Hunter holding one of the God Cards is hiding somewhere in this town.
Oi, is it true? That there's a Duelist with super powers?!
Let's go watch!
Super powers?
Wait for me, Yugi!
I will win.
Then head towards the battle field where you're waiting.
Let's go!
Duel!!
My turn!
Alright! I drew good cards.
Jounouchi, Jounouchi...
Ah, there, there! It's connected.
Thank you!
Where, where? You must be trying hard out there, Jounouchi.
Found it, found it.
It's Jounouchi's first turn.
It's just getting started now.
First, this card...
I feel the energy of the universe...
Flowing through my body...
Becoming one with me!
At this time, at this space...
I will win this Duel, as prophecized by the great force of the cosmos!
"Force of the cosmos"? What's this guy talking about?
I'll win!
Don't be talkin'! You don't got any powers, ya "beep beep" bastard!
Go, Mage Knight Giltia!
Useless!
W-what? My Monster didn't appear.
Don't tell me! His super powers?!
Simply the law of the cosmos.
Ah? Is he a beginner?
What is he doing?
Are ya stupid, Jounouchi?
What?!
That wasn't super powers just now!
It was the card ya used.
Who the heck plays a Level 5 Monster Card right off the bat?
If you wanna Summon it, you gotta sacrifice a Level 4 or lower Monster first.
Didn't you even read the new contest rules?!
Dammit.. I forgot that stuff already...
Really, you just completely wasted your turn.
That was just an error on my part!
But thank god it's not super powers...
I'd like to give you some advice.
Let's see...
The card on the very left of your hand...
I think you should play the Swordsman of Landstar.
H-How can he look at my hand cards?
It's telepathy.
Telepathy?
My heart and the universe have already become one,
That's why I can see through everything.
As long as you and I are in the same space,
Then I can get all the information.
That's impossible!
My turn!
Summon Cyber Raider!
Direct Attack the player!
Cyber Knuckle!!
It's quite scary.
In the Battle City rules,
If there's no monster on the field,
Then you can Direct Attack the player.
Turn End.
He already messed up the first step.
What's Jounouchi doing?
Honda-san.
You didn't say anything since just now,
Is something wrong with Big brother?
N-No...
No way.
The opponent has no ability to counter attack.
Then, Big brother's winning?
Y-Yeah! Of course!
I think he'll be victorious soon!
That's good.
Help me out, Jounouchi.
Don't make me lie.
Is this "psychic powers" duelist one of Ghoul's Rare Hunter?
I can see the left side card beside Swordsman of Landstar is Angel Dice.
OK, Big bro, I see Angel Dice.
It seems I was wrong.
Well, what's wrong? It's you turn!
Shit. I need to hurry up and summon a monster,
Or else I'll take another Direct Attack.
It's another Angel Dice card.
OK, Big bro, can you hear?
The opponent drew another Angel Dice.
Transmitting!
That guy's starting again.
I can feel that you just drew a second Angel Dice.
Saying his card correctly, he's shocked!
Jounouchi-kun is a true duelist.
That's why he can break through the opponent's trick.
Are you surprised?
My telepathy ability has gained from the universe.
It's your turn!
Call a card out!
His psychic powers could be real or fake,
But he really said my hand cards.
Against a psychic person,
what kind of plan should I use?
Wait!
He said I had two Angel Dice.
I see. Could it be...
My turn!
Go, Swordsman of Landstar!
Next, I set two cards. Turn End.
He set two Angel Dice?
Angel Dice is once a 500 Attack or below monster appears,
He can roll a dice and increase it's Attack times the number rolled.
I see.
I already know, Jounouchi-kun!
You're thinking when I attack with my monster you'll activate that Magic Card's effect,
To roll a dice and increase Swordsman of Landstar's Attack Points.
Maybe.
I'm right. If he really did have psychic powers, then he won't see the wrong cards.
But setting 2 of the same cards is pointless.
Angel Dice can only be used once per turn.
I think you should study the rules a bit more.
My turn!
I sacrifice Cyber Raider to summon Magic Gigacyber!
Now!
Activate Magic Card!
Angel Dice!
The enemy's monster has 2200 Attack Points.
My monster only has 500 Attack Points.
If the dice roles a 5 or above then I win.
Hmph! You can't win a duel by using luck.
Please!
That's too bad. Your monster only has 1500 Attack Points.
He's no match for my monster!
Go, Gigacyber! Attack!
Hehe, you fell into my trap!
Open one more set card!
Oi! Didn't you hear what I said?!
Angel Dice can only be used once per turn!
Who said I had two Angel Dice?
Magic Card...?
Devil Dice?!
How could this happen!
According to Devil Dice's dice number,
It can decrease your monster's Attack Points.
This is bad!
Who told you I had two Angel Dice?
The other card is Devil Dice.
Why would you mix up Angel Dice and Devil Dice?
That's because my other hand card was covered and only revealed the word Dice.
In other words,
You don't have any psychic powers to see through hand cards.
It's someone from somewhere looking at my cards,
and then telling you.
What did you say?!
This is bad, it's been seen through!
So you did realize, Jounouchi-kun?
Warning!
Run!
Wait!
I finally caught you guys.
S-Sorry. Can you let us go?
As Battle City's Chief I can't allow this to happen!
This duel must be immediately stopped.
Stop?
Don't do this!
Big bro is fighting just for us.
Big bro's doing this all for us,
So we don't get bullied!
Protecting you guys who are always bullied...
If Big bro wins this duel,
Everyone won't dare to bully us anymore!
That's why Big bro...
Yugi?!
No! No!
As the Contest's Chief, I can't allow such an unfair duel!
Please!
Let Big bro continue the duel!
Big bro is very strong.
Using his true powers he can win this duel.
Yugi...
Please.
Allow the duel to continue!
Then let it continue.
But next time I won't allow you guys to do this again.
Thank you!
Yay!
Heh, I still can't stop the feeling between brothers.
I can't find them anywhere.
The other Yugi is moving ahead in battles.
In order to find his lost memory.
Have you not awaken your psychic powers yet?
Saying such crazy things.
I'll tell you I have the ability to 100% predict the future.
Predict the future?
In this duel, the one who will win is me.
The one who will lose is, Jounouchi-kun, you!
What did you say?
I have my proof,
Because up until now I still haven't lost a duel yet.
Compared with an uninitiated person like you,
in the future, of course it is I who wins.
I don't know what the future is,
But I know,
Somewhere in this city, there's someone waiting for me.
I will continue to move forward and appear in front of him.
I will.
Jounouchi-kun.
Because I believe in that future,
I have come here. That's all!
Hmph, allow me to break your future.
A duelist at your level,
I don't need to use universe's communication and can still win.
I won't lose!
Right now I'll make you understand the power of Psychic Cards.
Alright, let's continue the duel!
My turn! I set one card down.
Turn over!
Alright, there's no monster on the enemy's field.
I'll direct attack the player and wipe out his Life.
Please! Give me a good card.
Alright!
It's Wyvern Swordsman!
Summon Wyvern Warrior!
I have two monsters.
Their Attack Points added together is 3000.
I'll win!
Here I go, my Battle Phase!
Both monsters attack together!
Wyvern!
Dragon Sword!!
Damage the player!
Good going! Shizuka-chan,
One more and Jounouchi's going to win!
Do your best, Big brother!
Do your best, Big bro!
You have to be stable, Jounouchi-kun.
Go, Swordsman of Landstar!
After this the winner and loser will be determined!
I won't let you move on!
Trap Card Open!
Activate Mind Control!
Trap Card?
Monsters that have fallen into this Trap Card will become mine for two turns.
Why? Why didn't he activate it on the first monster's attack?
It's true if he used it at the start,
Roba's Life Points wouldn't have been as damaged.
And Jounouchi-kun's monster will both be destroyed.
Since he's using it now,
He must be planning to sacrifice it!
Come then.
I'll use this Trap Card to deal with you.
I set one card on the field.
Turn over.
My turn!
I use Swordsman of Landstar as a sacrifice to summon Android Psycho Shocker!
Psycho Shocker
Come and attack.
At that time I'll use a trap to deal with you.
You had set one Trap Card right?
Psycho Shocker's Special Ability will now take effect.
Trap Crush!!
What?!
That's too bad.
My Psycho Shocker can destroy all the Trap Cards on the field.
Come at me then!
Although Esper Roba's trick was broken, he summoned Psycho Shocker, and Jounouchi is in a huge pinch!
In this match he drew his trump card, Baby Dragon again, and played his combo.
Will he be victorious against Psycho Shocker in the end?
Don't give up, Jounouchi!
This duel, Shizuka-chan is rooting for you!
Next Time: The Courageous Bet: Spinning Roulette Spider
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...