Here I go, Kaiba!
Reverse card open!
Hand Obliteration!
Card Destruction
What?!
Hand Obliteration?!
You need a sacrifice in order to Summon High-Level Monsters.
But in this specific case, there's another way to Summon a High-Level Monster onto the field without sacrificing.
My turn!
Reverse card open!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Monster Reborn
That's...!
Kaiba!
Thanks to Hand Obliteration, I was able to Summon Blue-Eyes from the Graveyard!
Cooperate!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon returns!
Blue-Eyes...!
Kaiba!
Did you finally understand the importance of cooperation?!
Shit...!
To think these guys actually worked together to pull off a Hand Obliteration\Resurrection of the Dead Reverse Combo...
Yugi and Kaiba...!
They weren't supposed to have any teamwork...!
So you you realized it, Yugi?
To win this Tag Match, we needed this one thing!
Kaiba...
Did Kaiba finally gain the heart to cooperate?
Like this, we can win!
So is this what they call "using your partner to win"?
In order to allow me to Summon a High-Level Monster onto the field, you played your Hand Obliteration.
Just as I planned.
So don't go misunderstanding that I've gained some ridiculous willing to "cooperate" with you.
Your one easy-to-please guy.
Now I don't owe you!
Yugi, aside from the next attack on these idiots,
don't you think my Blue-Eyes will be helping you out.
Kaiba...
Just as I thought originally, these guys don't have an ounce of teamwork!
Kaiba!
It's yo' Battle Phase!
Even though you Summoned Blue-Eyes,
my Masked Beast - Masked Hell Raiser still holds 3200 Attack Points!
So its 200 points stronger than yo' Blue-Eyes!
Attack, Kaiba!
What?!
Your Blue-Eyes can beat The Masked Beast right now!
Will you believe what I said?
Or will you let the Blue-Eyes you Summoned this turn go to waste?
If I lose Blue-Eyes now...
We can't win...
Show me your courage, Kaiba!
Interesting!
Yugi, I never thought I'd have to listen to what you say!
I won't back down!
Blue-Eyes, attack!
What!?
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
The Masked Beast is pulverized!
What?!
Impossible!
I beat it...
Why...?
Why'd The Masked Beast...?
When I used Hand Obliteration,
my entire hand was sent to the Graveyard.
Among those in my Graveyard,
I activated the Special Ability of a Monster Card!
When Red Lord of Hell - Gilfor Demon is sent to the Graveyard,
It becomes an Equipment Card,
and can Equip itself with any Monster on the field!
When that happens, the Equipped Monster loses 500 Attack Points!
So that card decreased The Masked Beast's Attack Points by 500?!
So Yugi allowed me to play Blue-Eyes and managed to defeat the enemy all at the same time?!
So his plan to use Hand Obliteration went this far...?
Kaiba...
This is the power of cooperation!
Cooperation is such a dumb word!
Isn't it exactly the same as me taking orders from Yugi?!
Turn over!
We don't have a Mask Monster on the field...!
It'll be bad if Blue-Eyes hits us with an attack next turn...!
My turn!
A Monster face-down in Defense Mode!
I'll also place these 2 reverse cards face-down and end my turn!
Reverse cards?
These reverse cards'll stop ol' Blue-Eyes!
Now Yugi!
It's your turn!
Don't forget!
Because of Mask of the Accursed and Mask of Dispell's Effects,
your Life will be slashed by 1000 points!
My turn!
Because of the Hand Obliteration strategy, they don't have any other Monsters this turn!
I set 1 card!
Also, I Summon Magnet Warrior Alpha!
Now attack!
I can't waste my reverse card on this weakling!
Sword Strike!!
Four-Faced Beast is beaten!
I need to use that on Blue-Eyes!
Turn over!
Partner, if we don't beat that troubling Blue-Eyes...
we won't even be able to worry about it any longer.
Relax, Partner.
We'll beat Blue-Eyes!
In any case, use the Monster Card in your hand.
And attack Blue-Eyes.
Understood.
We gotta get out of here somehow...
If we don't, even the power of Kaiba Corporation can't crush the Ghouls.
We may be able to.
At least you, anyway.
You're one of the Ghouls, aren't you?!
What are you after?!
It would be best if you did not know such matters.
We'll have good use for you either way.
That's just great!
You gotta be after Yugi's rare cards, am I right?
It's useless to hold me hostage!
Any good Duelist wouldn't waver just because of that!
Not the Yugi I know!
Wh-What're you up to?!
What're you gonna do to me?!
Heavy~
Hurry!
They're coming!
R-Right...!
What about you, Anzu?
I'm fine.
Just hurry and tell the others about this!
You bastards!
Hurry up!
I know...!
Anzu!
Don't worry about me!
Hurry and get out of here!
I'm definitely coming back to save you when I get help!
That brat!
Go find the kid!
Right!
I'm counting on you, Mokuba-kun.
Is he over there?!
He ain't here!
Shit...
Keep searching!
Right!
I'm gonna to save you no matter what, Anzu!
My turn!
I Summon Holy Doll!
Rogue Doll
It only has 1600 Attack Points.
So all you had was a weakling Monster?
It's not even qualified to be Blue-Eyes's enemy!
Even so, what's this bad feeling I have...?
We'll see about that, Kaiba.
Go, Holy Doll!
Attack Blue-Eyes!
Know your place!
I open my reverse card this very moment!
Mask of Weakness!
"Weakness"...?!
I place the Mask of Weakness on Blue-Eyes!
With the Mask of Weakness,
Blue-Eyes loses 700 Life Points!
And next...!
Mask of Brutality!
The Monster wearing this Mask gains 1000 Attack Points!
Disappear, Blue-Eyes!
I won't let that happen!
Reverse Trap activate!
Spirit Mirror!
Mystical Refpanel
This card will take your power!
Reverse Trap activate!
Spirit Mirror!
This card will take your power!
Holy Doll's Mask of Brutality was...!
Overtaking the Mask of Weakness,
it now wears the Mask of Brutality instead!
The decreased power of Blue-Eyes now increases by 1000 points!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
What is power?
I've lived up till now by one thing only...
The thing I've always believed in is power...!
In a fight, everyone is your enemy...
Power is the weapon used to crush your enemies in combat.
It's something to be used by yourself and no one else!
The power of cooperation...
Can this power overcome my beliefs?
My Life...!
Partner, you alright?
You're the one who told me it was fine to attack him!
But look what happened!
What?!
You sayin' it's my fault?!
You're the one who got careless!
Shut up!
Their teamwork is crumbling.
If we use that to our advantage...
But... in order to win, me and Kaiba need to cooperate...
My turn's not done yet!
I don't have a Wall Monster on my field...
If I'm hit by Blue-Eyes's attack next turn, I'll be blown up!
If that's the case, I can't depend on Partner.
I'll protect myself on my own!
I set 1 reverse card!
Turn over!
Are you alright?
Yes.
We should make it to Domino City in about half an hour.
Something wrong?
Are you not feeling well?
Nope...
I'm happy!
I'll finally be able to see big brother Duel!
Yeah.
I'll handle it.
My turn!
Power...!
Power!
POWER!
That's right! This is my invincible Blue-Eyes!
Isn't this my power?!
Blue-Eyes, rip the enemy to pieces!
Burst Stream!!
Your attack will be used to Direct Attack Mask of Darkness!
It's true that if this attack works, Mask of Darkness will be defeated!
But this attack was launched without thinking!
Kaiba's more than Duelist enough to know this...!
What the hell is Kaiba doing?!
Reverse card open!
Mask of Impregnability!
When this mask is played, the player is protected from the opponent's attacks for one turn!
Blue-Eyes's attack failed!
Too bad for you, Kaiba!
I read right through your attack!
Just your life though!
Wh-What?!
I could have easily attacked either one of you guys this turn with my Blue-Eyes.
I simply chose not to go after you.
And if I had, would that "Partner" of yours have activated the Magic Card to save your life as well?
No, I'm sure he wouldn't!
What?!
What nonsense is that?!
You damn well know I'd have activated the Magic Card to protect you!
No doubt I would have!
Believe me!
I see!
Kaiba did that to break their teamwork.
Kaiba may be right...
Mask of Darkness's usually the type ta think only a' himself...!
Shit...!
Damn you, Kaiba!
You didn't have to go and say all that!
It's my turn!
I'm still nervous about taking off the bandages...
Though I'm probably just acting dumb...
It's too bad, since I came all this way to give my big brother courage...
If I take you to where he's Dueling, you'll take them off, right?
Yes.
Seeing my big brother will give me the courage I need.
You have a good brother, don't you, Shizuka-chan?
Yes.
He's always giving me courage.
He's the most important person to me in this world.
I want someone to say that about me~!
Jounouchi! You're so lucky!
Jounouchi...?
Jounouchi!
So you're safe!
What are you doing?
Didn't you come here to save me?
Come on, what're you waiting for?
Jounouchi...?
Jounouchi...!
Pot of Greed...?
With the Magic Card Pot of Greed,
I draw 2 cards from my Deck!
This card is...!
They have Blue-Eyes on their field...
And we have squat shit!
I got no choice but to play this.
I'll first set this face-down!
Then...!
Magic Card activate!
Hand Exchange!
Card Exchange
This Magic Card lets me switch hands with any other player on the field!
In a Tag Match only, of course!
So my Tag Partner!
I hate my current
hand so I'm gonna
take yours!
What shit are you pulling?!
Now!
And I'll activate my set Magic Card!
Chosen One!
Chosen One?!
I'll then set 3 cards in reverse!
One of these cards is a Monster Card!
The Mask Spinner will select 1 out of the 3 cards,
and if it picks the Monster Card,
I can instantly play it on the field!
I see, so that's what you were after?
I ain't gonna let your hand go to waste.
If this fails, I won't have mercy on you!
Here I come!
Mask Spinner, do your thing!
If this works, they'll be able to Summon a High-Level Monster in one turn...!
Two of the cards are Magic Cards...
And the other is...
The strongest Monster Card our Decks can produce!
The mask's beginning to stop...
The card was chosen...!
I did it! I'm really lucky!
The Masked Beast Death Guardias!
The Masked Beast Des Gardius
It has 3300 Attack Points...!
It's stronger than Blue-Eyes?!
Alright! You really are the best partner!
Believe me, we have no chance of losing!
You should know that!
So this was the true strongest card they've been hiding all this time...?
Blue-Eyes can't stand up to The Masked Beast!
What should I do...?!
I have 1 card in my hand that might work...
But if I attack him now...
Now then...
Who should I attack with Death Guardias?
Should I wipe Yugi out in one attack?
Or...
Should I exterminate that annoying Blue-Eyes?
Preview
Yugi and Kaiba-kun are once again in a pinch when the Rare Hunters counterattack.
Ah! That Kaiba-kun sacrificed his Blue-Eyes so Yugi could attack!
But because of his grave error, even though Kaiba-kun tried to help, Yugi is left unable to attack!
The true play is put into motion!
Is it possible the final trump card will allow Kaiba-kun to play that card...?!
Next Time
Obelisk the Giant War God
Next time!
Duel standby!