Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Akhenaden turned into the High Priest of Darkness after obtaining Zorc's powers
and he tried to convince his son, Seto, to take over the throne.
Seto, don't listen to him!
Stand with us and protect the country against this threat called Zorc!
On the other hand, my partner and the others arrived at the place that carries my name.
And Bakura, who should have been destroyed, reappeared once more.
"Countdown to the Revival of the Great Wicked God"
Hey Holy Pharaoh, I'm back!
How can that be?!
Did this man arise from the dead?!
Bakura!
Take a break for now,
High Priest of Darkness.
I have no interest at all in listening to your grievances.
Seriously...
It's troublesome having a pawn that has too much of a self-conscious.
You are...
Must you be so surprised?
You should know fully well the powers Lord Zorc has.
I managed to revive, all thanks to him.
The Great Wicked God Zorc... To think that his powers are so high...
Mister High Priest of Darkness...
I didn't think you were so free that you could talk about all your past grievances.
You should have a mission
to accomplish, right?
Like him over there!
Lord Seto...
Seto...
That's right, your mission is to make him obtain the powers of Blue-Eyes.
Did you say Blue-Eyes?
Since young, he's had a strange affinity with a girl that has the powers of the White Dragon.
Fate is such a cruel thing.
Kisara...
Could it be the girl from back then...?
You know here, Shada?
Yes. We found a foreign woman with tremendous powers.
Seto kept her hidden in the palace.
What's wrong, Seto?
Wh-What is this...!?
Th-This woman's Heka... is far too much for the Ankh to measure!
It's an enormous Heka!
That woman's Heka is too strong.
If I may be so bold,
it is on par with the Gods.
Do not tell you you planned to take...!
You said it! He wanted Seto to use that power for Lord Zorc's sake.
By doing so, he vowed to grant your wish and make Seto into the new Pharaoh.
Mister High Priest of Darkness here wanted a
new Pharaoh with far greater powers for the new era!
And you had best not forget those words!
Seto. My son...
Now. Come bask in this glory and become the new Pharaoh!
I...
Wait, Akhenaden!
Hold it! Have you guys forgotten I'm here?!
Diabound!
How can that be!? Diabound's stone tablet was destroyed!
So sorry about that.
But as all the Millennium Items are gathered here,
the seal to the
Underworld has weakened.
All the dark energy seeping out from this door has made Diabound more powerful.
Now Seto, you must become the Pharaoh!
You must obtain powers that exceed that of the Gods!
Do not do it, Seto!
You mustn't follow him!
Seto, you are one of us High Priests who have sworn loyalty to the Pharaoh!
Do you intend to betray the Pharaoh?
Wake up, Seto!
Do not get sucked into that dark energy and become like Akhenaden!
Seto, don't go!
Don't stand in the way!
Seto!
Wait!
You guys will be sticking around for a while.
Bakura!
It's time we enter the next play!
What's going on?!
The stone tablet is...!
Now you can't touch the stone tablet until the sand in the hourglass runs out.
Bakura!
Now then, if we just sit and wait quietly,
when the time comes, the Great Wicked God Zorc will come back to life.
While we wait for him, I shall grant Akhenaden's wish in the meantime.
Whoa there! I haven't forgotten about you guys.
What are you up to?
Well, let's start!
What is this?!
Now, let's start a game of hide-and-seek!
What... happened...
This is...
That's right... Back then...
What?!
Is this another
occult-themed hallucination...?
What happened to me back then?
Quick, quick!
Wait for me!
You're so slow!
Come on!
Wait up!
Is this world a hallucination...?
Or am I one?
Lord Seto!
No...
You are...
You're..!
From that vision...!
How mysterious...
You give off the
same feeling as Lord Seto.
What do you know?
Where is this place?
What is going on? Tell me!
A calamity is going to happen.
If that happens, everything will be destroyed.
What?
I have to go there right now.
But I have a feeling that
we will meet again.
Bakura, where are the others?
Don't get all worked up.
Look... It's clearing up.
Master! Prince! Where are you?!
Are you alright, Lord Shimon?
Yes...
But where are we?
What... are you intending to do?
Well, I figured it would be boring to sit around and wait.
I thought it would be nice if I showed you a small portion
of the dark power about to revive.
You'd better be thankful.
You bastard..!
Oh, here it goes!
I wonder where everyone went...
Wh-What!?
Bobasa must have appeared in order to bring us here.
Let's go, Yugi.
The name of the other me lies inside here.
Just a while more...
I'll definitely find your name!
Mahado, where are the rest?
Yes. They are not around here.
Is that so?
I hope everyone is alright...
Yes. Bakura probably wanted to separate us and kill us off one by one.
There's a very strong force backing him up.
We must quickly reunite with the others and track down where Seto is.
Is this the era where Kaiba... No, where Seto met the Blue-Eyes?
Just like how I met Mahado, who became the Black Magician?
What's wrong, you two?
That is...!
What's going on?
I-It's here!
Isis...
Kalim, are you awake now?
Don't bother about me... Go and protect the Pharaoh.
I cannot leave you behind.
Look... I don't even have enough Ba to summon my Ka.
My Millennium Scales
have been taken away.
Don't let me become your burden.
Kalim...
Now...
Let me enjoy this...
Magic Blast!!
Pharaoh!
Hasan! Mahado!
Thousand Magic Blasts!!
Surely they didn't think that their powers alone can defeat those bugs?
Bakura!
I took just a little Ba from Kaiba, so now I still have quite some energy to spare.
What are you going to do, "Great Pharaoh"?
During this commotion, the sand in the hourglass is continuing to fall.
If this continues to happen, no matter what happens after, I'm bound to lose.
I'd better retreat for the time being...
Hey now... Do you really think you can get away from my Ka?
You seem to have forgotten something...
That an NPC's death
means the end of them.
They won't get revived the way I did.
Mana!
C'mon! Run along, little girl!
You'll be squashed flat if you don't.
I won't admit defeat so easily!
Mana...
She's quite nimble
despite her appearance...
But how long can she hold out for?
What are you going to do now, my King?
Are you planning to leave your Priests behind to go search for the Tablet to the Underworld?
Or are you planning to save those useless fools?
Or perhaps you're planning to go after Seto and the High Priest of Darkness?
That's a nice expression you have there.
Continue agonizing!
Two-Headed Jackal Warrior!
Are you alright, Shada?
I'm fine.
More importantly, we must find the Pharaoh.
I pray that he is fine.
Hmph. How persistent.
Your pieces aren't too shabby.
Did you... call them pieces?
That's right.
Right. In the end, these people are nothing more than the pieces of this game.
All they have to do is fulfill their role.
They're meant to be thrown out when they outlive their usefulness.
You're wrong!
They are my important companions!
You're getting pretty fired up for someone who hasn't regained his memories as Pharaoh.
Besides, they are only living inside this game.
In actual fact, they are long gone and covered in dust...
Just like your memories!
It's true that I've got no recollection of my days together with them.
I can't recall a single conversation I had with them...
Or what we wanted to do...
Spiria!
But...!
I-Isis...
Two-Headed Jackal Warrior...
Isis!
Are you alright?
Shada! Lord Shimon!
Where's Kalim?
Shada... The Pharaoh...
Kalim, leave this to us.
Shada...
Shada, take my Ba...
Kalim!
I want to give you the last bit of my energy...
Please use that to protect the Pharaoh!
I promise to.
Kalim, I have accepted your life.
Go, Two-Headed Jackal Warrior!
Shada!
Pharaoh!
Pharaoh...
Seto... Please stop Seto...
We mustn't let him make the same mistake as Lord Akhenaden...
Ah... I know.
Pharaoh...
I'm so happy... to have been able to serve you...
Kalim...
Kalim!
Pharaoh!
I won't let any more people die!
Hasan, can you stay here and protect everyone?
I'm going after Seto!
But...
They are all my important companions.
Please!
Pharaoh...
I understand. If that is the Pharaoh's wishes...
Thank you.
Pharaoh...
I can touch this wall...
I think this place is the one that Grandpa mentioned...
The place where the Millennium Puzzle was kept.
Say what?
The Millennium Puzzle was kept here?
Okay! Let's get moving then!
Jounouchi-kun!
Don't touch anything!
My Grandpa said that there are many traps in here.
You should have said that first!
Then your grandfather should have told you how to proceed forward in here right?
Yes.
There will be no problem if everything is the same from when my Grandpa last came.
Hey, man... Are we really inside a tomb?
All this must have been set up to protect the thing hidden in its deepest chambers.
So, how do we proceed?
"The Gods shall punish you, o ye who dares disturb the great Pharaoh resting here."
In Ancient Egypt, the Pharaoh is regarded as a God.
In order to show respect to these statues representing the Pharaoh,
we must present our left feet forward at all times.
This means putting the heart out towards the godly Pharaoh.
A display of ultimate loyalty.
That means...
We must walk with our
left feet forward, right?
What the heck? Isn't this simple?
This is the second room.
What should we do now?
"The Ka sealed in the stone slabs shall judge you...
The cowardly will have their souls eaten by demons...
The courageous will be shown the way..."
Does it mean...
That we will get eaten if we have even the slightest fear?
Yugi!
Be careful!
My other self's name
lies within this tomb.
If I'm able to save the other me if I find this name...
I have no fear.
Yugi...
That's right! How can we be afraid now?!
You're right!
This was where the box that contained the Millennium Puzzle was.
But there's nothing here.
Where exactly can the name of the other Yugi be?
Yeah...
There appears to be nothing similar carved on this wall...
Yugi...
There must be a place inside here that not even my Grandpa entered.
Even if you say so, Yugi...
W-What's going on?!
There's a door...
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Even though we've reached the deepest area of the King's Tomb...
We aren't able to find the Pharaoh's name anywhere.
Suddenly the wall opens...
And a hidden room is revealed!
The name of the other Yugi
must be inside!
But Honda... Haven't you been acting weird for a while now?
On the other hand, the Pharaoh has gone in search for Seto.
Will he be able to save Seto from the Dark Priest?
Next time!
"The White Dragon"
Please look forward to it!