Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Ghost Deck VS
Occult Deck"
Finally... the Battle City finals are about to start.
The fight for the God Cards.
And the fight to regain
my other self's lost memory.
Shizuka... There's something I can finally say to you.
Watch me, Shizuka.
With the courage you gave me, I'll be sure to get my glory.
Uh-huh!
However, Shizuka-chan...
Reality can be rather cruel sometimes.
I've got to be completely honest with you here!
If your dear big brother loses to me disgracefully, you mustn't look away.
Huh!? What'd you say?! I won't lose, Mai!
Well, I also have something to tell Yugi.
You'd better not underestimate
my Amazoness Deck.
Amazoness Deck...?
Yugi, I didn't forget our promise to fight each other in this tournament.
This time we'll fight each other fair and square, as True Duelists.
Alright! Let's confirm the location of the finals!
This is the stage of the finals?
But where is it?
Is there even a place like that in this city?
It looks like this area that's under construction by Kaiba Corporation.
"Domino City Hospital"
Oi oi, I finally found it.
Why are you in my host?
That's it...!
Was it back then?
Correct.
I've implanted a part of myself inside your host, Bakura.
You'll suffer a horrible death someday...
What happened to our promise, you bastard?
I helped you with your plan to kill Yugi.
You're supposed to hand me your Millennium Rod.
There's been a slight change of plans.
What?
Yugi and I have both gotten into the finals.
If you desire this Millennium Rod so badly...
you'll have to get yourself into the finals.
So your little plan failed you, huh?
I don't listen to the bloating of an over-arrogant fool.
Say whatever you want!
The finals will begin shortly.
Before then, you have
to earn enough Puzzle Cards!
And you'll have to lend me your host a little longer.
That brat...
Oi, are you alright, Bakura-kun?
Bakura-kun...! Bakura-kun...! Oi, Bakura-kun!
You're finally awake, Bakura-kun?
You've been moaning in your sleep.
It's alright. Just a bad dream...
I see. Thank goodness.
They did it, Bakura-kun!
Yugi and Jounouchi gathered 5 Puzzle Cards!
They just called!
R-really...? That's great...
So... where will the finals take place?
Crap, I forgot to ask about that.
I'm not surprised that Yugi made it... but that his friend Jounouchi did too...
It means my training was a success.
What's wrong?
I.... want to go find them...
No way, no way! You still are yet to recover!
I don't have the time to waste sitting around here.
You... you are...
Behave and stay sleeping here, old man.
A blood-soaked millennium battle is about to begin.
And I don't wanna be left out of the fun.
Give it back~!
Now this surprised me!
Now there's one less hack Duelist who didn't even Duel once!
I-I didn't buy that for the tournament! It's a memento!
Now that I have a Puzzle Card, I'm qualified to Duel.
I guess even a hack like you deserves some thanks.
These cards are so bad it's stupid.
Here!
My... my cards...!
Oi, I heard there's already four people who've earned enough Puzzle Cards.
I heard there's six.
Only eight slots for the finals are available.
I don't have time to screw around.
Cool. I'll check the billboard again to make sure.
Hey, bastard! Do you know where I can find a Duelist around here?
Who the hell're you?!
Just answer my question!
What's up?! Wanna fight?!
Answer me.
I-I heard there's some Duelists wandering around the cemetery...
Cemetery, you said?
Are there really Duelists
in a place like this? Geez...
Wh-what the? A crow?
Don't scare people like that!
Drop the Disk~
The plan was a huge success.
Now I have five Puzzle Cards.
All we need is one more
and we can enter the tournament finals.
This time at least one of us will make it into the tournament finals.
We'll make Bandit Keith regret what he did!
Oi, someone's coming.
That's just perfect. Let's make our final offering.
Who the hell are you fools?
If it isn't a Duel Disk?
I see.
So you scumbags have been hiding out stealing others' cards!
What now? We just need one more Puzzle Card.
Oh? You guys got five Puzzle Cards already?
Now I remember!
You're one of the guys who was tagging along with Yugi in the Duelist Kingdom!
Ah, yeah... Him...
But we've never seen him Duel before...
A beginner, eh?
Okay, I'll challenge you to a Duel!
Oi oi, is that okay?
Making such a quick decision!
I'm the Duelist they call "Ghost Kotsuzuka"!
I won't lose to a beginner like you!
It won't be hard to take these guys out...
It's perfect warm up for my Occult Deck.
Fine! The condition is that you hand me all your Puzzle Cards!
I've got one.
What did you say?!
This is ridiculous! We won't listen to you anymore!
Don't you guys know?
The amount of spaces open for the finals was just cut in half.
What?
There's no time to waste.
No matter how many cards you get, you won't make it in time.
The winner of this match goes to the finals!
I got it!
I'll show you the terrible power of my Ghost Deck!
I'll let you guys taste true fear in this battle...
Now! Let the Dark Game begin!
Somehow, the atmosphere feels really weird all of a sudden...
Here I go! My turn!
Draw card!
Do you know about the legend in this cemetery?
Legend...?
Yeah, it's said that the spirit of a knight who lost his head haunts this place.
What?
See? Can't you hear it?
The steps of the spirit searching for his head.
Y-you're lying, right?
I Summon the Headless Knight!
IDIOT! How are ya gonna handle this if you're scared by that?!
Y-you're right...!
Also, I set a reverse card on the field.
Now my turn is finished.
Now it's your turn!
Scaring me like that...
My turn!
My Monster is Medusa's Ghost!
It has 1500 Attack Points!
Whoever looks at Medusa will be turned to stone!
Go, Medusa!
Stone Blizzard!!
Now your monster is dead.
The more cards I draw,
the closer you are to death.
Magic Card, open!
The Shallow Grave!
The Shallow Grave allows us to choose one monster from our Graveyards
and play it on the field in Defense Mode.
Thus, I revive Headless Knight!
Kotsuzuka, you don't have a Monster Card in your Graveyard!
Calm down!
Though his monster revived,
Kotsuzuka has more Attack Points on his side!
So you think!
I'll sacrifice Headless Knight and summon a stronger monster in its place.
Show up, Death Duke!
What? It has 2000 Attack Points!?
TAKE THIS!
Ancient Sword!
Lightning Tornado!!
Shit...!
What's wrong with that fake "cursed" deck of yours?!
"Fake", you said?!
I won't forgive anyone who makes fun of my deck!
My turn!
Come on, Dragon Zombie!
Also...
Early Burial!
This card pays 800 of my Life Points as a cost
and allows me to revive a monster from the Graveyard to the field!
Also, the Magic Card Fusion!
Come forth! The strongest Monster of the realm of the dead!
The Golden Elephant!
According to the tournament rules for Fusion Monsters
you can't attack in the
same turn they're summoned.
I set this one card and I'm done.
You still haven't seen the true terror of my Ghost Deck...
The moment you take your next turn, it'll start.
Now! It's your turn!
My turn.
Alright! Trap Card, activate!
Skull Invitation!
Every time when a card is sent to the Graveyard,
Skull Invitation deals the card owner 300 Life Points of damage.
That means when I destroy your Monster next turn,
you'll also receive 300 points of damage from my Ghost Combo!
How's that?! This is payback for making fun of my Ghost Deck.
What's up with this guy?
Did he go insane 'cause he knows he can't win?
Since you want my cards to go the Graveyard so badly
I'll grant your wish!
I'll discard my entire hand to the Graveyard!
What?
Insane bastard.
He really must a' gone insane!
It's fine like this.He's destroying himself!
Good.
Go! Skull Invitation!
Now this bastard's as good as dead!
What's so funny?
I'm getting chills...
Just picturing the scared looks on your faces...
...makes my body tremble with excitement!
Have you not realized yet?
Look carefully at my feet!
I activated a Magic Card the second I discarded my hand!
That is...
This Magic Card is Spiritualistic Medium!
For every card discarded during the players' turn
a monster on the field increases its Attack by 500 points for one turn!
What?!
I've just discarded four cards from my hand.
Therefore, Death Duke receives a total of 2000 Attack Points for each card.
Now its Attack Power will go up!
4000 Attack Points!?
TAKE THIS!!
Big Lightning Tornado!!
My... Golden Elephant was...
Also, you lose another 300 Life Points due to your own trap Skull Invitation!
Hang in there!
Otherwise you three won't return home alive!
What... are you talking about...?
Whoops! Didn't I tell you?
Take a good look around you!
What... what is that?
The Death God awaits your arrival!
I thought I told you this was a Dark Game?
The loser of this Duel shall be swallowed by the World of Darkness!
That's impossible!
That's right. Fear more!
I can't get enough of people cowering for their lives!
I-I DON'T WANNA DIE!
Takeido!!
Huh?! Why am I back here?!
It's useless to run.
No one can run from the dimension of a Dark Game.
If you wanna live, the only way is to defeat me.
KOTSUZUKA! IF YOU LOSE, WE'LL DIE!!
Yeah! You mustn't lose!
M-my turn...
Y-Yes...
A Magic Card! Demon's Iron Cage!
This card seals your monsters and stops them from attacking for two whole turns!
Also, a monster in Defense Mode!
Kotsuzuka! Use this chance to take the lead!
I-I know...!
It's my turn.
The bastard... probably got a bad draw.
I wanted to see more of you fools struggling against death, but...
It appears the end has come for you guys.
What are you talking about!?
As long as Demon's Iron Cage is in play,
no matter what monster you use, it can't attack for two more turns!
That worthless trick won't work against my Occult Deck!
Ectoplasmer, activate!
This card transfers half the Attack Power of a monster into Ectoplasmer
and attacks the opposing player directly.
What?!
ECTOPLASMER, FIRE!!
What a shame it is...
Now then... it's time for you all to descend into Hell.
You can wander the afterlife for all eternity.
WH-WHAT IS THIS!?
WHAT THE HEEELLL..!?
Just you wait...
Yugi...
Malik...
I wonder if there's any other strong players who've won and gone to the finals before us.
Dunno. We won't know until we get there.
That's... Kaiba-kun's helicopter.
So, you're following in my footsteps along the road of battle!
Hurry it up, you weaklings!
Oi, Kaiba got ahead of us!
Idiot! There's no way we can beat a helicopter!
We're finally heading there...
Up ahead...
...is the location of the Battle City finals.
"Preview"
Just when the tournament finals' location is right in front of us,
Out of nowhere comes a Hollywood star, Jean-Claude Magnum.
You were waiting here to propose to Mai-san?
Claude wants to Duel Mai-san to get her.
If she loses she has to accept the proposal!
Who'd except such a challenge?
EH? "I'll take you on"?! Mai-san!
Next time: "Ninja Master Magnum Arrives"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...