Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
This is...
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Throbs of a New Darkness"
In other news, some new ruins have been discovered in the Atlantic Ocean.
They say it is older than anything we've discovered so far.
It's said to be part of an ancient civilization from long ago...
-OWWW~!!
Be more careful!
Ya walked right into me!
Right back at you!
Y-You're...
-Insector Haga!
-Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Ya can't be here for Battle City since it ended...
What're ya doin' in a place like this?
N-Nothing much, really...
A-Anyhow, what are you doing here then?!
J-Just a walk...
What the hell?! Don't follow me!
Same to you!
I have to get those God Cards!
No matter what I have to do, I will get them!
I ain't about to be outdone!
Even if I have ta trade all my rare cards, I'm gonna add those God Cards to my collection!
-Whoa! Outta da way!
-Look out!
M-Move it...!
What the hell are ya standin' there for?!
That's dangerous, you know!
Are ye Sir Dinosaur Ryuzaki and Sir Insector Haga?
W-What the hell...?
Do ya want somethin' wit' us?
I come to claim thine souls!
W-What do you mean?!
Words are pointless!
DUEL!
What's wrong, Anzu?
What are you doing all the way up here?
Just doing some thinking.
About Yugi?
Sort of...
Hey, Other Me!
Where are we going?
Partner, did you bring
the God Cards today?
Yeah...
You can't be...!
Let's go.
Let's head to the art museum!
But this is so sudden...
You didn't tell the others about it!
It's better this way.
It's too painful to bid farewell...
I'm fine with just
you seeing me off, Partner.
Other Me...
YUGI!
OIIIII!
Yugi!
We made it in time!
You guys...
You were acting odd this morning and then you just rushed off by yourself, so we hurried over here.
That's harsh, Yugi!
Going by yourself like that!
You're about to start a new journey, Other Yugi.
But we'd be sad if
we couldn't bid you farewell!
Yugi, no matter how apart we are...
...our hearts will always be together.
Yeah.
Thank you, everyone!
So this is that palette everyone keeps talking about, eh?
That really does look just like Yugi!
The time has come at last...!
Once I show these three God Cards to the Palette,
...my lost memories will be opened, along with a new path.
And then what will happen...?
The answer is here!
Other me...
The stone tablet...!
What's happening?
Yugi!
What's wrong?!
W-What the...?!
I.... feel a different and powerful energy interfering...!
What do you mean?
Did you regain your memory or something?
What happened to the slate?
W-What's all this?!
Duel Monsters!
Did someone's Duel Disk break or something?
They don't look like they're being controlled...
Jounouchi, all the data on the different Monsters is stored in Kaiba Corporation's main computer, right?
Then let's head over to Kaiba Corporation
and see if they know anything.
Yeah, let's give it a shot.
Yes, this is Kaiba Corporation.
So you're saying it suddenly
appeared in your back yard...
Our computers are functioning normally...
Please hold.
The Monsters are all over the city!
Th-Those guys are...
Isn't that Ryuzaki and Haga?
Oi, what are you doing at a time like this, you guys?
The omen has begun~
Soon this world's gonna be destroyed~
Omen?
What do you mean by, "this world will be destroyed?"
What's with this creepy feeling?
Just forget about these guys. Let's go!
Yeah.
Please tell us about the current situation.
Are the rumors that the Solid Vision System is the cause of all this really true?!
The system is working fine.
I assure you, there is no relation to this situation!
If not, then what exactly is causing this?!
Have President Kaiba comment!
President Kaiba is currently in America on important business.
Please leave here now!
He'll be holding a press conference later this evening!
We won't take this as a proper response!
Are you even speaking the truth?
Are you really here, President Kaiba?!
It's so crowded here.
Will Kaiba-kun be okay?
In other news, many sightings of Duel Monsters Solid Vision holograms have been spotted around the world.
As of current, there is no real explanation for these events and the panic they are causing.
So this event is all around the world?
I guess Domino City
isn't the only one affected.
Now we take you live to a press conference with Kaiba Corporation's president in America.
Kaiba!
Our system has absolutely nothing to do with the crisis that has been occurring.
Immediately after these sightings were reported, we shut down all of our systems to test them.
During the time the systems were down, Monsters were still appearing.
In other words, something other than our system is causing the Monsters to materialize.
What's the deal? If it's not Kaiba's system causing this, then what is...?
Could this all be related to what
happened at the palette today?
Yeah, I've been thinking it's a possibility as well.
At that time, a strong power disrupted the palette and my memory returning to me.
Right after, these Monsters started coming...
And what puzzles me most is what Haga and Ryuzaki said...
The omens have begun~
Soon this world's gonna be destroyed~
Now that you mention it, those guys were acting funny...
What did they mean by "the world will be destroyed"...?
GRANDPA!
Grandpa, hang on!
Are you alright, gramps?!
Yu-Yugi, I'm sorry...!
What's wrong, Grandpa?
The....the God Cards...!
You can't mean...!
They were stolen?
Sorry...
Damn it!
You won't get away!
The Great War God... Obelisk...?!
That's...!
The Great War God Obelisk!
It's not just Obelisk...
Ra and Osiris, too!
Only Millennium Item Possessors should be able to Summon the three God Cards...!
Just who could have-
What?!
Shit!
Who's there?!
When the forbidden door is opened...
...the light of Orichalcos shall punish this sinful world!
We are The Musketeers of Doma!
Musketeers?!
You guys were the ones who stole the God Cards!?
That's correct!
Indeed, we have taken these cards, O Great Nameless Pharaoh!
These guys know about my other self?!
We issue a challenge to you.
If you want the cards back,
come to the unfinished building!
We'll be waiting!
The Three Musketeers of Doma?
"Safety first"
Where are you?! Come out!
Welcome. We have been
awaiting thy arrival.
Sir Yugi Mutou...
Or rather, should I address thee as "Nameless Pharaoh"?
Hey, you! Are you in cahoots with those motorcycle-riding bastards from before?!
Thou be correct!
My name is Gurimo.
Among the Musketeers of Doma,
as well as Master Raphael's servant.
Now! Will thee accept my Duel challenge?
Fine. But before that, I have one thing to say.
The God Cards are cards that won't allow anyone but the chosen ones to wield them.
If you try to use them, God's anger will consume you.
Will I be able to use them or not?
You will have to confirm that with your own two eyes!
Interesting. I'll accept this Duel!
Become our offering!
Sir Yugi Mutou!
-DUEL!!
-LET'S DUEL!!
I'll go first!
Draw!
I Summon Magnet Warrior Beta in Defense Mode!
Also, I set one reverse card!
I can't attack on the first turn.
Turn over!
Nameless Pharaoh.
Allow us to test your power.
It is now my turn! Draw!
Do you think he really has the God Cards?
If he does use them, Yugi...
Don't worry! Yugi's the King of Duelists now, you know!
He won't lose that easily.
I Summon Marauding Captain.
And I activate Marauding Captain's Special Effect!
He lets me Special Summon another Monster of Level 4 or below.
I Summon Demon Tamer!
In just one turn, two Monsters...
Sir Yugi, the time has now come for me to show you our true power.
Behold! A Magic Card born from the very darkness itself!
This age old power has
become our power!
I shall seal my enemy within a sacred barrier of divine justice!
I activate the Barrier of Orichalcos!
What?!
Ow!
Guys!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...
So long as this boundary exists on the field, all distractions are forcefully removed so we can focus entirely on the Duel.
Until the Duel's outcome has been determined,
not a single being shall be granted passage within this barrier.
And vice versa, neither I nor thee shall be permitted to leave.
The only one capable
of exiting this bound...
...is none other than
the winner of the Duel!
And the loser's soul shall forever be sealed within the sacred boundary for all eternity!
What was that?
This guy is able to
control the Dark Games?
Then...
What?!
How futile!
So long as we remain within this boundary, the power of the Millennium Items are nullified!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...?
Not the power of the Millennium Items,
but a whole different power...?!
I've only just begun showing you the true power of the Barrier of Orichalcos!
It turns my Monsters into Dark Monsters and raises their Attack Power by 500 points!
What?!
Go, Marauding Captain!
Attack Magnet Warrior Beta!
Trap Card, activate!
Soul Rope!
This card's effect starts when one of my Monsters are destroyed.
At the cost of 1000 Life Points, I can Special Summon a Four-Star Monster from my deck!
Magnet Warrior Gamma in Defense Mode!
And here I thought I got rid of all your Monsters.
I set one card.
My turn is over.
Owww~
That bastard... ever since that boundary was activated, his character changed.
All his Monsters became Dark Monsters?
And most importantly, when he said, "the loser's soul will be sealed within the boundary," what did he mean?
That's your subordinate all right.
Rafael, does this Yugi
really stand a chance?
If he's defeated by him here, that means the Nameless Pharaoh isn't worthy of being our enemy.
Nothing more, nothing less.
Then that leaves Katsuya Jounouchi.
And Seto Kaiba.
We must obtain all three of their souls.
Our plan must not fail.
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Magnet Warrior Alpha in Attack Mode!
At this moment, my Trap Card activates!
Hidden Soldiers!
This card activates when the opponent successfully Summons a Monster.
It lets me Summon a Dark-Attribute Monster from my hand.
Come forth, Executioner Makuyura!
I'm going to activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Shallow Grave, activate!
It lets both players Summon a Monster from their Graveyards in Defense Mode!
The Monster I'm reviving is... Magnet Warrior Beta!
Alpha, Beta, Gamma! Now all three of the
Magnet Warriors have gathered!
Here I come! Join together!
Magnet Valkyrian!
But you have no Monster you can Summon in your Graveyard.
Not bad, Yugi Mutou!
Looks like the rumors are true.
But Gurimo still has that card...
Go! Magnet Valkyrian!
Magnet Sword!!
Turn end!
Yeah!
You did it!
His Life Points fell significantly from this!
That is the King of Duelists for you!
You are very good!
But I'm about to Summon a much more powerful Monster!
Indeed, Magnet Warrior Valkyrian's Attack Points are higher than almost all Monsters.
But mine is different from the others!
Stop trying to act cool!
Listen up, pal!
The only Monsters with more than 3500 Attack Points are the God Cards, and--
You wouldn't...!
Yes! The card I'm about to play
is the God Card, The Great War God Obelisk!
I activate the Magic Card Resurrection of the Dead
to revive Marauding Captain!
Wait! If you're unable to handle God, you...!
I sacrifice all 3 of my Monsters in play!
Stop it!
Now, appear before us in your greatest form!
GREAT WAR GOD, OBELISK!!
Obelisik...!
What?! Impossible!
It's Attack went up?!
Obelisk became a Dark Monster...!
And you said those who aren't the "chosen ones" couldn't play the gods!
But I did!
Anything is possible within the holy bounds of the Orichalcos!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...!
He's doesn't even have a Millennium Item, yet this Duelist can control God...!
What in the world is he?!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
PREVIEW
Yugi faces off against the God Card under Doma's control.
But is there a way for Yugi to defeat the God Card?
Even worse, the Barrier of Orichalcos's effect powers up the opponents Monsters greatly!
Will the loser of this Duel really have their soul taken?
But the opponent is acting kind of weird...
Next time!
"The Barrier of Orichalcos"
Duel Standby!