Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Now it's your turn, Malik!
Card draw.
Come on! Hurry it up!
No matter what you do, the outcome of this match is within sight!
On my next turn, you're gonna be killed by your own Winged Sun Dragon of Ra! Thus bringing this farce to its end!
You're not the only one who can read the Hieratic Text!
I'll bury you in darkness next turn with the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
That's quite bold of you, Dominant Half...
No, I don't think I can even call you "Dominant Half" anymore!
What?!
I took the Millennium Rod from the Ishtar family, who guarded it for centuries.
It now lies in my hands.
This is mine from now on.
The Rod accepted me.
In order to allow me to help you with your revenge.
So it just might be me
who's the dominant half!
Screw you!
I am Malik Ishtar!
Very well, forget it...
If you're gonna Summon Ra,
go on and do it!
Our answer will be here soon...
I activate the Magic Card,
Vengeful Bog Spirit!
Thanks to this card's effect, all Monsters on the field cannot attack within the turn they are Summoned.
Turn over!
Whether I attack with Ra in the first turn or the second, the result's still the same!
Draw!
Go, Bakura!
Go on and Summon Ra!
Don't bother me!
Prepare yourself, Malik.
I'm gonna play your
beloved Ra right now!
I sacrifice every Monster I have on the field, totaling three tributes!
Come forth! Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
You fell for it!
I activate the Trap Card, Joyful Doom!
What?!
Thanks to the effect of Joyful Doom,
The Attack Points of the Monsters you tributed are added to my Life Points!
And the Attack Power of every Monster you just sacrificed...
...drops to 0!
Impossible!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra has 0 Attack Points?!
Ra's Attack Power is determined by the total Attack Points of the Monsters sacrificed.
If the Monsters sacrificed to Summon it have 0 Attack Points, then Ra's Attack Power...
will be 0!
What the hell do you mean?!
That's different from
what you told me before!
I never had a
card like that in my deck!
Shit...
He planned on us stealing the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...
So he baited us with it!
Even more, his Life Points rose all the way up to 8550!
Shit...!
I switch both the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra and the Puppet Master into Defense Position!
Huh? I...
...was in Mai-san's room before, the last I remember.
Where is...?
Who is it?
It's me! Anzu!
Anzu...?
What is it?
So late at night...
Bakura-kun... Bakura-kun's gone!
My turn.
Card draw.
Here I come, Bakura...
Drillago, attack the Puppet Master!
Puppet Master is beaten!
I end my turn!
My turn!
Card draw!
All you've got left
is that 0 Attack Power Ra!
What do you plan to do now, Bakura?
This isn't a joke...
I don't need a god
with 0 Attack Points!
I sacrifice the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
To Summon
Hades, Ruler of the Realm of the Dead!
I can't believe you
cast God aside so easily...
You must have the Resurrection of the Dead
you stole from me in your hand.
But...
Ra's Attack and Defense Points are determined by the total Attack and Defense Points of the three Monsters used to Summon it.
In other words, if God is Summoned using Resurrection of the Dead without any sacrifices, its Attack Points will be 0!
So Ra's better off in the Graveyard!
It's true that the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra should now be sealed off entirely.
But why do I feel like he's got something up his sleeve?
Why is he standing there unfazed?
I failed in Summoning Ra,
but my turn is far from over!
I'll tribute 3 Demon-type Monsters in my Graveyard from play!
To Summon Dark Necrofear!
And then, the Magic Card Early Burial!
I pay 800 of my Life...
...to revive Ghost Duke
from the Graveyard!
My deck only gets stronger when you send Monsters to the Graveyard!
Knock it off! If we lose any more Life Points, we're in trouble!
Shut up! I thought I told you you not to bother me!
If we want to reduce his Life at all, it's necessary to take risks!
Just calm down, Bakura!
He's still planning something.
I know myself all too well!
What the hell do you know?!
And now that I think about it, Malik, it's your fault our previous strategy didn't work!
What'd you say?!
Get the hell outta me!
Fighting amongst one another...?
Not that I mind it,
but let's continue the game.
Any Monster Summoned this turn...
...cannot attack due to the effect of Vengeful Bog Spirit.
I know that without
you needing to tell me!
Turn end!
Let's just continue this already!
Really?
Then allow me to
get things moving again.
My turn!
Draw!
I wonder where Bakura-kun ran off to...
He couldn't walk alone with his body like that...
Maybe Malik did something to Bakura-kun again...!
I'll create a simulation depicting the outcome of my Virus Combo's success...
There's only a 13% chance of the Virus Combo working on the Ra Deck!
What the hell are you laughing at?!
One Turn Kill...
What?!
You're going to die
in just one turn, Bakura!
What'd you say?!
Even my dominant half doesn't know about this...
I'll show you the second hidden Special Ability of Ra!
Ra's Special Ability that
I don't know about?
One Turn Kill?
One Turn Kill...
When the conditions are
right for the Ra card,
in one turn, it can crush all its enemies and reduce the player's Life Points to 0...
The three God Cards...
The one I hold,
Great War God Obelisk...
Yugi's Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
And Malik's Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...
The one thing they have in common is that they are Summoned to the field with three sacrifices.
And most Trap Cards
have no effect on them...
Magic Cards used on them are only effective for one turn.
But there is one Ability Ra has that the others don't.
The power of quickness!
Magic Cards only affect a God Card for one turn, whether the cards are yours or your enemy's...
Therefore, the effects of Resurrection of the Dead will expire after just one turn,
and will once again
return to the Graveyard...
And thanks to the effects of my Vengeful Bog Spirit Magic Card, it won't be able to attack in the turn I Summon it.
But... Ra has the power
to attack instantly!
One turn is more than enough!
If I activate Ra's Hidden Special Ability,
you'll be finished in an instant!
If the Ra card goes to the Graveyard...
...and you have the Resurrection of the Dead in your hand...
The One Turn Kill is complete!
Look, Yugi!
That's...!
That's not just fog!
It's the Void of Darkness where Dark Games are played!
Then that means Bakura-kun...
Bakura must be playing a Dark Game inside there.
And his opponent has to be Malik.
Anzu, don't get too close.
You'd be best off
returning to your room.
No!
Anzu!
You're always excluding me when there's an emergency!
It's not like I don't know anything about the Millennium Items, you know!
And I also know all about your lost memories, other Yugi...
Anzu...
I want to help you out, too!
Playtime's over.
I'm about to send you both to the World of Darkness!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Resurrection of the Dead!
And of course, the one I Special Summon to the field...
...is the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
But because it wasn't a Sacrifice Summon, its Attack and Defense Points should be 0!
Plus, Resurrection of the Dead only works for one turn!
If we can survive this turn, God should disappear!
We'll see about that...
You don't understand the true power of Ra!
Wh-What the hell...?
What's he doing...?!
I'm not sure.
This is the first time I've heard this Hieratic Text...
My dominant half never received the full revelation of the Millennium Rod...
Only I can decipher God's Special Ability!
What?!
Malik's body is disappearing!
I'll tell you...
Ra's Special Ability...
As written on the card
in Hieratic Text:
"He who chants the third litany...
...may keep 1 Life Point and transfer the remainder
unto Ra's Attack Points for one turn!"
The player's Life Points change into Ra's Attack and Defense Points?!
That's right...
And it doesn't take any time at all...
It's been a fun little Duel, Bakura.
This is the last time you'll see me.
But once you disappear into darkness, my body will go back to normal.
What...?!
This is Ra's Special Ability!
Ra and I become one!!
He fused with Ra?!
Ra, attack!
God Blaze Cannon!!
Destroy every Monster!
And kill the player!!
Now die, my residual thoughts!!
My lost memory as the Pharaoh...
There's not much I know about it myself...
But I must obtain it at all costs!
No matter what
kind of memory it may be.
But I no longer want to put everyone in danger because of it.
Yugi...
I'll let you win this time...
Those are some brave words...
But remember this!
I'll be resurrected in due time!
To kill you!
I originated from the darkness anyway!
The darkness, eh?
Then I'll enjoy taming the darkness...
Malik!
So you came here, Yugi?
Where did you send Bakura?!
Bakura, you mean...?
Who knows?!
Nobody knows where those who lose a Dark Game are sent!
Bakura lost?!
Yugi! It'll be your turn very soon!
Then you can reunite with Bakura in the next world!
Sister!!
Malik...!
You're...?
My sister...
Big sister!
Rishid...!
Malik!
Save Rishid from that man!
I can't believe the Parasite Mind I used a while back would come in handy now...
The Millennium Ring's power lets one seal part of their own soul within an object!
That includes this piece of the Puzzle!
Parasite Mind!
Seal complete!
The moment Malik's attack killed me...
...I suddenly woke up inside of here.
Can't be helped.
I'll sit tight and wait for the Millennium Items to be gathered,
and begin my search for the "Door of Truth" which lies somewhere inside of here...
Where the hell did he go?!
An invincible God Card that decides the match in just one turn.
Is there any way to stand up to Ra?
Big brother...
You're still up?
You should go to bed.
Tomorrow's the Finals!
Yeah...
I know...
Big brother...
The place we're headed for is Alcatraz.
Our stepfather, Gozaburo Kaiba, spent a fortune building that island.
It was full of high-tech
military equipment.
After he died,
my brother destroyed
all of the facilities,
and built the
Duel Tower atop the ruins.
Mokuba...
I will win the Finals
on Alcatraz Island!
And when I earn
the title of Duel King,
I will finally obtain true victory!
Only when that happens will I be freed of his curse!
If my hunch is right...
...there is a way to overcome Ra!
Wait for me, final stage of our last battle! Alcatraz!
I will become the true Duel King,
and conquer the future!
"Preview"
Oh no!
The Battle Ship suddenly changes its route on the way to the destination of the Finals!
Some unknown person seizes control of the ship,
but who could even do that?!
Then out of nowhere, a giant mobile fortress submerges from the water!
What the heck is that thing?!
And who are they?
I've never heard of such a thing!
Next time!
"The Unknown Challenger:
The Huge Mobile Fortress Submerges!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise