Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Unseen Enemy:
Sea Stealth II"
Jounouchi-kun...!
Where are you?!
Mutou Yugi, am I right?
If you wanna get by us,
you got no choice but to defeat us.
Of course, in a Duel!
Rare Hunters?
Move it, you bastards!
No way.
If we let you go, Malik-sama'll have our heads.
And besides...
If you refuse to Duel us,
your friends will pay a high price.
So then, which one of us should go first?
You go first.
No, no. That won't do.
But it will.
Then you wanna roshambo for it?
Okay.
Rock...
Paper...
Scissors!
Shoot!
Oi, ain't it a bit dumb to keep playing paper?
Yeah, you're right.
Then, next is...
Rock, paper, scissors!
Shoot!
Rock!
Will you bastards cut it out!
Sorry, Yugi!
But there's no helping it!
We have to play you one at a time!
Then come at us as a tag!
You weaklings!
Kaiba!
I'll pair with Yugi.
A Tag Match, you say?
We certainly have the right number of people...
But don't misunderstand, Yugi.
I have held the Battle City tournament for the sole purpose of gathering the God Cards and eliminating the Ghouls.
I cannot allow such an evil group who counterfeits cards continue to prosper.
I'm not lending a hand for that nobody of yours.
Or, since you you just obtained a God Card...
Maybe you don't need my help?
Kaiba...
This is better than our original plan.
Indeed, if we get rid of you both right here, Malik-sama will be overjoyed.
Let's go!
DUEL!
Now this'll be fast.
We'll take you guys apart.
You aren't going to win by spouting such meaningless threats.
My turn.
The Magic Card Pot of Greed.
Its effect allows me to draw 2 cards from my Deck.
I will then Summon The Dragon Ruler - Lord of Dragons, to the field!
Also, the Magic Card The Flute of Summoning Dragon.
2 The Flute of Summoning Dragons?!
When The Flute of Summoning Dragon
is activated while Lord of Dragons is face-up on the field,
this Magic Card lets me play up to 2 Dragons from my hand!
Let's see... Meaning...
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Diamond Dragon!
Impossible!
4 Dragons right off the bat?!
The first player can't attack.
My turn will come to an end here.
Now come at me.
Even if I'm up against weaklings, I won't hold back.
Shit!
A Monster in Defense Mode!
My turn's over!
My turn!
I place 2 set cards.
Mind your own business, Yugi!
I have no intentions of asking you for your help.
What did you say?
Me alone is more than enough for these weaklings.
Then why don't I just sit back and watch?
I place Kuriboh in Defense Mode.
Now it's your turn guys!
We're in deep trouble...
Leave it to me.
Even if he gathered those Dragons right off the bat,
I hold a Trap in my hands that will destroy those Monsters in an instant.
No matter how rare the card is, the Ghouls can make them.
I place 1 set card.
I also Summon a Monster in Defense Mode and end my turn!
Trap?
Magic?
No matter which it is, it's useless.
Be careful, Kaiba.
They may be aiming for something.
Yugi, I thought I told you to stay out of this!
Kaiba!
I'll show mine to you now.
I also wield one, just as you.
Blue-Eyes!
Become God's power!
Behold, Yugi!
Come froth, Obelisk!
Wh-What?!
This is...!
This is the first God Card!
Obelisk the Giant War God!
I sacrifice my two remaining Monsters!
I activate his Special Effect!
Our Wall Monsters...!
Obelisk, attack!
God Hand Crusher!!
You fell for it! Trap activate!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Mirror Force
Such a trick won't work against God!
GO!
Did you see, Yugi?!
My god!
This is Kaiba's God Card...?
Obelisk the Giant War God...!
Where's Jounouchi-kun?!
Shit...!
So these weaklings only had 1 Puzzle Card each?
This is for your collection.
I'm going to look for Jounouchi-kun!
Wait!
You're persistent, Kaiba!
Right now...!
Mokuba, contact Head Quarters.
So you're gonna look for Jounouchi and the others?
Using our system, we'll be able to locate that nobody the moment he starts a Duel, no matter where he is.
Kaiba!
But the moment we locate them, be prepared.
For the conclusion between me and you!
So that's the rumored Obelisk...
We found it!
The God Card!
TAKE THIS!
Alright! Not bad!
What do you think you're doing?!
That's my line!
This giant whale attacked me just because I was catching my food!
What "catching my food"?!
This is an aquarium!
An aquarium?!
I see! So it's a fish tank for public feed!
It's not feed! That's stealing!
Wh-What's wrong?
What a high fever!
But today's an important chow for the Ocean World...
If I don't do it...
It's impossible with the shape your body's in.
But everyone is looking forward to the show...
Alright! I'll show them the best show of their lives!
Yugi's Osiris and Kaiba's Obelisk, eh?
Interesting.
I will take back both of the cards!
This presence...!
This is the Dark Power that was controlling Keith!
It seems that person has come.
Another person who stands before me within this Battle City.
Bakura-kun!
You came to see Battle City too?
I-I guess.
Speaking of which, are you winning, Jounouchi-kun?
Yeah.
I got 4 Puzzle Cards now.
Just 2 more and I can enter the Tournament Finals!
Wow~ Amazing~!
Huh? Where's Yugi-kun?
We're looking for him.
I'm sure Yugi's winning, though.
Yeah!
We decided we'd meet in the Tournament Finals, after all!
You can't waste time standing around.
Yeah!
But I need someone fitting for my last opponent...
What's wrong?
Wh-What the hell's this?!
It's Ryouta!
Kajiki!
That bastard...!
Alright!
I found my last opponent!
Jounouchi!
O-Oi...!
Oi, wait up!
Now then, I have to greet our new guest.
Where'd you go, Kajiki?!
Jounouchi! That's...!
Yahoo~!
What's he doing?
Yahooo~!
There~!
What are you doing?!
Yo, Jounouchi!
It's been a while, Jounouchi.
Since Duelist Kingdom, I believe.
Kajiki-kun, the Duels aren't in the aquarium, but in the streets!
What?
Just takin' a bit of a break.
I decided to help out with the show.
What the?
And I came all this way to Duel you!
You Duel me?
Forget about it!
You're no match against my Sea Deck!
What'd you say?!
I just need 2 more and I can enter the Finals.
Me too. See?
Wow! Not bad!
Then how 'bout we Duel so we can see which one of us' stronger!
Interesting!
Let's do it!
Wow, something's starting!
Those guys're from Battle City!
YAY~!
Sorry to butt in on your act.
Jounouchi, I'll bet 2 Puzzle Cards!
Who'll win and get into the Championship?!
Alright! Then let's bet 2 Rare Cards!
Let's go!
Yeah!
DUEL!
Good luck, Jounouchi!
If I win this Duel, I can fulfill my promise with Yugi.
It's true you made it quite far in Duelist Kingdom...
but how much of that was just sheer luck?
I'll test you!
I go first!
DRAW~!
What the hell's that?
That idiot's giving me the creeps!
It's decided.
Parasite Paracide?!
Damnit~! I forgot to take it out!
Hey...
That's right.
Maybe getting this wasn't such a bad thing...
This thing causes a real mess if used against you...
This time I'll use it to cause Kajiki to suffer.
Let's see...
What have we here?
"Set as a Reverse Card and then place it in your opponent's Deck when flipped."
Hey, what the hell are you waiting for?!
Just hurry up and end your turn!
I know!
Don't tell me you don't even know the cards in your own Deck?
N-No way that's true!
It's a strategy!
Strategy!
Anyway, it's okay if I just do this.
I play this card in Defense Mode!
You got no guts.
I Summon Flying Fish!
I don't know what your so-called "strategy" is, but I'm gonna attack ya!
Alright!
Parasite Paracide!
Huh?
Why didn't it do anything?
Dumbass!
In order to activate Paracide's Reverse Effect,
you gotta offer an offering from your filed!
So that means...
In other words...
Ya gotta send somethin' to the Graveyard in order to activate it.
WHAT~!?
Geez~
He's got no brains just like always~
Shit~
My turn~
A Monster in Defense Mode!
It must be a Defense Monster for sacrifice...
in order to Summon a High-Level Monster.
That ain't gonna work, Jounouchi!
In that case...!
My turn! I set 1 Set Card!
My turn's over!
Alright!
My turn!
With good posture, I dra-
Just hurry up
and freaking draw!
Goodness!
You're one bastard with no showmanship!
Draw card!
Prepare yourself, Kajiki!
I sacrifice my one Monster!
I Summon Garoozis!
Trap Card activate!
Torrential Burial!
Torrential Tribute
This is the first time I've met a Duelist like this~
Yugi...
Right now, I'll take your friends and cause you great suffering!
Who are you?!
The Millennium Ring!
Won't you behave and hand me your Millennium Item?
I'll kill anyone standing in my way!
I see.
So you're after them?
The Millennium Items.
For what purpose.
Isn't it obvious?
The moment the 7 Items are gathered atop the Pharaoh's Memory Tablet in Egypt,
The Door of Darkness will open.
It's for the purpose of obtaining the Dark Power!
Why doesn't this guy know about the truth of the Tomb Keepers?
But without the 7 Millennium Items, the Door of Darkness can't be opened.
He knows nothing more...
Those secrets are engraved upon my back.
My name is Malik.
Name's Bakura.
Bakura, I'm not interested in the Millennium Items.
What I'm after is the nameless Pharaoh's life and nothing more.
Once I destroy him,
this Millennium Rod is nothing more than garbage to me.
This guy...!
But there's a condition.
If you help me eliminate Yugi,
I'll hand this to you when all ends.
Condition, you said?!
I believe I told you to behave and hand me the Millennium Item!
It seems you won't accept my offer.
Until I take out Yugi, I can't hand this to anyone.
In that case, how about we compete with our Power of Darkness with the Millennium Rod and Millennium Ring at stake.
If you really insist.
My turn!
Flying Fish, Direct Attack!
You got nothin' to block ya!
Jounouchi!
I place 1 Set Card!
Turn over!
I'm disappointed in you, Jounouchi!
You're not taking this Duel seriously!
What?!
Not taking it seriously, you said?!
That's right.
I challenge my opponent in a match with all I have, no matter who it is.
That's a fisherman's courtesy to one another!
Out on the sea is no different.
No matter what the fish, I give it my all!
If I go about this, one day I can overcome my own fear!
I entered the previous competition in order to obtain a fishing boat with the prize money and accomplish just that!
That's why I won't hold back against anyone!
I vow to enjoy myself to the fullest as my battle against the sea continues!
The one I want to fight...?
My sea is...
Kajiki!
I have someone to fight against, just like you do!
Indeed, I get a bit nervous.
But I'll fight this Duel with everything I have!
Then come at me, Jounouchi!
You can do it, Jounouchi!
Stay calm.
My turn!
Draw!
Wyvern Warrior! Attack Mode!
Alligator Sword
Also, I set 2 Reverse Cards!
Turn over!
Indeed, he let his guard down before.
But Jounouchi, I can truly feel the aura of a Duelist from you now!
But I'll be coming at you with everything I have as well!
My turn!
I sacrifice Flying Fish!
I Summon Amphibian Beast - Fisher Beast!
Amphibian Beast
2400 Attack Points?!
Here I go! Fisher Beast, attack!
Sea Claw
Reverse activate!
What the?
The Monster entered the box...!
Now. Do you know where he's hiding?
You're naive, Jounouchi!
Did you forget I have this card?!
The Field Card Sea!
Monster Box was completely submerged!
Wyvern has no choice but to come up for air.
Found ya! He's right there!
Magic Card, activate!
Devil Dice!
Your Monster's Attack goes down according to the number I roll on the die!
Alright!
Now your Life falls!
Not bad.
You're no
longer boring me!
But Jounouchi...
You don't know the true terror of the sea.
To enter the territory of a fisherman...
It takes more than skill!
Jounouchi...
You've already fallen deep within my sea...
I'll show you!
The ultimate fisherman!
Sea Stealth II!
Within the Sea Field,
Kajiki-kun completely takes the advantage with the Monsters he Summons!
And then Kajiki-kun Direct Attacks!
Ah! The situation has changed!
The attack fails!
But be careful, Jounouchi!
Something's waiting to attack you from the sea!
That Monster is a clone of Kajiki-kun's father?
Next time!
The Legendary Fisherman
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...