The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Friendship Power!
Barbarian #1 & #2
Mokuba-kun!
Mokuba!
Mokuba, where are you?!
I can't find that damn Mokuba anywhere!
He surely was taken to Pegasus's castle.
The only way to get in Pegasus's castle is collecting ten star chips.
Yeah.
Jounouchi - 2 Star chips
Yugi - 6 Star chips
I found some cards!
Those are mine.
Huh? You play Duel Monsters too, Honda-kun?
Yeah, I became interested in it, so I bought some cards.
And then brought them with me.
This is...
What is it, Jounouchi-kun?
Barbarian?
I think I saw something like it...
This one!
Number one and number two? Having them both would be good.
All right! It's a pain to have this card, but I'll keep it.
Who gave it to you?
It's all right, isn't it? You won't use it anyway.
Well... can't help it. I'll lend this card for a while.
Really... It's a great duo.
Idiot number one and idiot number two, isn't it?
Yugi!
Sorry!
Harpie Queens, attack!
Triangle Ecstasy Spark!
Yeah... It's my win. Leave your star chips and disappear.
Damn!
Somehow this is boring...
I can't stand it! How could I lose to someone like him?!
Finally found ya, Mai Kujaku!
It's me, Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
I didn't forget what happened on da ship!
Go away, you freak!
Ah, you're talking about that, aren't you?
I challenge ya to a new match here and now!
I'm not interested in men that already have lost!
Get lost!
I-I got the strength of da National Championship, ya know!
I already got five star chips!
E-Eight star chips?
Did you understand? I only need two star chips to get in Pegasus's castle.
Besides, I've already decided the opponent that will give me the remaining star chips.
Yugi?
I'm gonna beat 'im!
You win against Yugi?
That's right!
Okay. I'll duel you. But there's one condition.
These people over there don't
seem very strong but they are suitable to Jounouchi, aren't they?
What?
No, no. Haga looked weak but was really strong.
You're right.
Ah, but I don't think that there's someone in this island weaker than Jounouchi.
That's true too.
You jerks! You've been laughing at me for a while now!
T-This loud voice is...
We meet again, Jounouchi.
M-Mai Kujaku!
You guys are tagging along with each other, as usual.
Were you ducks in a former life?
Ducks?!
Yugi, don't you think it's troublesome?
If Jounouchi weren't slowing you down, you would already be at Pegasus's castle.
This is not...
I'm not here now to fight you.
My target is Jounouchi!
That time I lost to you, but this time my servant will defeat you!
Servant?
It's been a while, Yugi, Jounouchi-han.
Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Are you Mai Kujaku's servant?
I'm a little envious...
What foolishness are you saying?! Hurry up and refuse her!
Well, well, you'll run away?
Okay! I accept it!
Jounouchi...
Stop it! You can't win!
This's good. I should be grateful to Mai Kujaku.
Actually I want revenge, but that would be immature.
If I defeat Ryuzaki after Jounouchi loses to him,
then it would be like I defeated you.
This woman... is doing this because she lost to Jounouchi...
But just watch! This time again, with Yugi's support...
Oh Yeah! This duel will have a condition.
The public can't give advice to the duelists!
If someone gives advice, the duel won't be considered as a real one, right, Jounouchi?
No way! That is...
I'm okay with this condition!
Maybe I'm really reckless.
If I lose my star chips in this duel, I'll be forced off of this island.
But... I want to win with my own power.
I don't want to always be depending on Yugi!
Are you serious?
Even if you were in the city's tournament best eight, you can't win against him!
I'm sorry. He's a little out of himself now...
Just forget what he said about the duel.
I didn't ask for your opinion!
What're you doing, jerk?!
What that woman said is true. Surely if I wasn't here, Yugi would already be...
Jounouchi-kun, I never thought that you...
If I can't even defend myself, it would be better for me to lose now.
Bastard... think a little about it!
If you lose, what will happen to your little sister?
Stop that, both of you!
I will not cheer for an idiot like that!
Honda-kun...
Let him go, Yugi!
What a joke...
What did you say?!
So, what will you do? If you want to give up, we can cancel this duel.
Of course, I will accept it!
Yugi, in this duel, don't give me any advice, got it?
All right! Duel Standby!
Good luck, Jounouchi!
Having to fight without Yugi's advice leaves me a bit scared...
Servant, you have to win, or you won't receive your reward!
You... what reward will you receive if you win?
That ain't yer business!
How many star chips will you bet?
Of course, two! All my star chips!
All right! My field is wasteland.
Yours is grassland.
Ryuzaki...
It's true that he was a competitor in the national tournament
and his dinosaur cards are strong....
But I too have my powerful combo that defeated Mai Kujaku!
With the Time Magician,
Baby Dragon can transform into the powerful Thousand Dragon.
Let's go!
Duel!
Anzu, I'll leave Jounouchi-kun with you. I'll be right back!
Yugi!
Lucky!
I already drew Baby Dragon and the Time Magician!
Huh? Yugi?
Well... it's alright. Even without Yugi, I already won this duel.
Let's Go!
Baby Dragon in defense mode!
Now, play a monster...
In the next turn, my killer combo will destroy it.
Now it's my card.
Two-headed King Rex in attack mode!
King Rex destroyed Baby Dragon with one movement.
My Baby Dragon...
Ya freakin' numb?!
There's someone that would start with a monster in defense mode?
Why dont'cha use yer head a little? Yer head!
What are you doing, Jounouchi?
I knew it, it's useless...
AS expected from an amateur...
With this, his plan to use Time Magician
to transform Baby Dragon into Thousand Dragon has failed.
Now, draw and play the next card.
Doesn't matter what card it is, my dinosaur card will destroy it!
He really looks powerful, but I have some powerful cards in my hand.
Go, Leogun! Defeat King Rex!
Ya really are numb!
My King Rex gets stronger with da wasteland field power source! It receives a power up!
Shit! I forgot!
Dinosaur Foot Stomp!
Damn...
My true objective is ta defeat Mai Kujaku, so I gotta hurry an' beat Jounouchi.
Now, I'll leave as it is. Hurry up and play your next card!
My field is grassland... It must favor my knight and warrior cards.
All right, this card!
Axe Raider! With the field power source he powers up!
Air Cutter!
Then I play this card! Sword Dragon!
Dragon Tail Sword!
I knew it. Can't I win?
What are you doing Jounouchi? Hang in there!
Yugi...
That idiot...
Are you alright, Honda-kun?
Yugi... why are you here?
I promised I wouldn't give any advice, so whether I'm there or not it's the same.
Yugi, how can you say it like that?
"Whether I'm there or not it's the same".
You're wrong. You don't have to keep that promise.
If you don't help him, then what you have is not a true friendship.
Until this duel's finished, I won't talk to Jounouchi.
Yugi!
I'm sure Jounouchi-kun believes that if he can win by his own power,
Shizuka-chan can do the same.
But... That is...
Jounouchi-kun probably was worried when he accepted the battle.
Watch this battle of his until the end. It's the best way to show your friendship.
I'm sure Jounouchi-kun understands your feelings.
Yugi...
Damn! Where are you, Yugi?
This is pathetic...
I'm still counting on Yugi...
I have to win with my own power! I decided to do that for Shizuka!
In my hand, I don't have any card that can beat his dinosaur card...
This... Time Magician!
But I don't know any other way to use it, but to create the Thousand Dragon.
What other power does it have?
Anyway, I'll set this card in the field.
That card... I have no doubts that it is the Time Magician.
Servant!
I got it.
That is, without a doubt, the Time Magician.
But, an amateur like him can't use it properly.
Time Magician is a card that possesses a great power.
My Harpie Ladies were defeated by it.
I put a monster in defense mode!
Whatever card it is, it'll be crushed!
Megasaurus!
Megasaurus's charge attack!
Did you already give up?
In that case, this card...
Finally, you played a powerful card...
But the Flame Swordsman's attack power is less than the Megasaurus'.
Megasaurus! Charge Attack!
Idiot! Ryuzaki!
Burning Sword of Fighting Spirit!
What? My Megasaurus...
I won?
The Flame Swordsman is a fire monster... That happens to be dinosaurs' weakness.
But I think it was luck.
It's your turn, dinosaur bastard!
Flame Swordsman... Being a fire monster really sucks...
Defense mode!
Go, Flame Swordsman!
It's strong! Jounouchi will win! He'll win!
Damn! What a problem...
It seems the game has turned to my side.
Don't underestimate me! I still have rare cards in my deck!
All right!
Appear! Evil Night Dragon!
This's a premium-card given to the ones who passed
the second round in the national tournament!
Jounouchi! You'll always be a loser!
Go!
Nightmare Shadow Sonic!
Flame Swordsman was...
Jounouchi!
I don't have any card that can beat that powerful monster...
This is... Honda's...
You... want to take us alone...
Are you an idiot?
People like you that bully the weak really piss me off!
You...
I'll beat you so you can't even stand!
Jounouchi!
Get them!
Hey! Are you alright, Jounouchi?
Coming here alone was madness...
I didn't ask for your help!
What?
It was my fight! I could've taken them on alone!
I didn't need your help!
I've never noticed before but...
Honda... you always have been by my side since then.
What are you doing, Jounouchi?
Hang in there!
Honda! Yugi!
That idiot! If I'm not around, he can't do anything...
All right, Honda! Let's fight together!
Oh, that's my...
Useless! Here's the attack!
Nightmare Shadow Sonic!
Attack the Barbarian Number 2!
W-What happened? The Shadow Sonic was reflected!
My Barbarian Number 1!
Honda's card helped me!
I got it! When these monsters are together on the field, they help each other!
Honda-kun's friendship saved Jounouchi-kun!
I'm grateful, Honda!
Damn!
All right! Now, let's continue!
Let's fight together, Jounouchi!
Well... no problem...
Be happy while ya still can...
Preview
The friendship power has manifested and saved Jounouchi from a pinch!
But with the arrival of Dinosaur Ryuzaki's best monster, he will be in a second pinch.
Notice it, Jounouchi! What can change everything!
Then, a new person joins us...
Huh? Bakura-kun? I knew you were here!
Next time: Dark Fire! Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship