Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
All right, man!
It's my turn now!
I Summon Buster Blader!
Nice move!
Get 'im! Get 'im!
Anzu-san!
S-Shizuka-chan?
Good afternoon!
"A Sign"
Sorry to bother you like this...
But I really want to see this
town again before I leave.
After all, this is the town
my brother and the guys fought
really hard in during Battle City.
I wanted to see
this town properly.
It's fine. Don't worry about it.
C'mon!
Let's go!
Is that...?
He looks just like Yugi-san!
Right...
The other Yugi began the search
for his memory on that day...
Right in this same spot,
after seeing this stone slab,
it all began...
That's...
The Ancient Egyptian king carved here...
There's no doubt in my mind that this person is me!
Why? Why is there a carving of Yugi on that stone tablet?
The Millennium Puzzle?!
Anzu, I have just realized who I really am.
The soul of an Ancient Egyptian king who was trapped inside the Millennium Puzzle for thousands of years.
That is who I really am.
Can it be? Does Yugi's other soul really live inside of the Millennium Puzzle...?
After all this time, it's no wonder I've forgotten everything.
We have been waiting for you.
Who are you?
I am Ishizu Ishtar.
For 3000 years...
I have protected a piece of the Pharaoh's memories.
That's... a Millennium Item!
This is also where we met
Ishizu-san for the first time.
And Ishizu-san
told us about the existence
of another Millennium Item...
Also, one other...
The person standing beside Yugi...
The resemblance is too great. Could it be?
The carving on this stone slab...
predicted our present-day battle!
Is the only way I can find the answers to find my lost memories?
That palette... surprised me a bit.
I know, right?
I was shocked when
I saw it for the first time.
It was around here.
This is the spot Jounouchi had
his first Duel of Battle City.
What about you?
Jounouchi! Ya better give up right now!
He's Esper Roba. A Duelist who has super powers!
Super powers?
Right! He read every one a' my strategies with his super powers!
Ya can't win against him!
I don't know a thing about his "super powers", but I'm gonna fight him!
Ya dumbass! Don't do it, Jounouchi!
I was cheering for him
in the hospital!
Over the Internet!
I couldn't see it myself,
but Honda-san guided me through it!
Mmm! That's true, isn't it?
Let's see Jounouchi's condition.
Don't miss the moment of victory.
It's okay.
Thank you, Honda-san.
But, you don't need to comfort me.
The nurse told me the truth.
Big brother is losing, right?
I'm sorry, I didn't want you
to get you worried, Shizuka-chan.
Yes, I know.
But I want to know the truth.
Big brother is playing hard.
I want to support him, too.
I am bound to win.
It's useless to struggle more.
Just surrender now.
Yugi, I am sorry.
I may not be able to keep my promise.
Shizuka-chan is watching you.
Jounouchi!
Anzu...
Honda called, they are watching your duel through the Internet.
Honda and Shizuka-chan are cheering for you.
Honda...
You must work hard, Jounouchi.
The wind feels nice.
Domino Port, huh...?
There's no way I could
ever forget what happened here.
That's for sure.
Watch closely.
There's a bomb set up atop this container.
What?!
Try anything and I'll press this switch,
dropping the container right on top of that girl!
Anzu!
Where...?
Yugi, you get to go first!
How can I fight...
...knowing one of us will die when our Life hits 0?
What a sadistic Duel!
Hey c'mon! What's wrong, Yugi?!
Hurry up and play a Monster!
Back then, Jounouchi and I
were being controlled by Malik...
And just when I things were
getting sticky, you arrived at the scene.
I made up my mind that I wanted
my brother's face to be the first thing
I saw when I took off my bandages.
But I never would have imagined
I'd see him like that!
I don't have time to grab my own key!
Big brother!
Jounouchi!!
Honda!!
Yugi!
Jounouchi...-kun...
I'm sorry, Yugi...
And thank you...
Yugi!
Shizuka...
We were separated, but now I'm by your side again.
Because your friends supported me.
At last, I found you big brother.
Shizuka-chan, you went and jumped
in the water all of a sudden!
You really scared me!
And then we
boarded the Battle Ship...
Battle Ship, take off!
All three of the God Cards
were gathered on board...
the Three Illusionary Beasts.
The first time we witnessed the
three cards being used was in the sky...
On top of the Aerial Duel Arena...
I sacrifice Black Magician Girl...
...Magnet Warrior Gamma...
...and Big Shield Gardna, totaling three offerings!
The advent of... Osiris!
Ra's changing its form!
This must be...!
Bring me victory!
Awaken, Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
This is the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
I'll show you God!
Come forth! Great War God Obelisk!!
It's getting a bit chilly, isn't it?
Shall we head back?
Yup.
This is my ultimate card!
Go!!
-Bastard!
-Turn over!
I sacrifice Rocket Warrior!
I Summon Android - Psycho Shocker!
Now that the Battle City Tournament
has ended, everyone's started Dueling
a lot more than before.
That's because Kaiba Corporation has
been advertising it more than ever.
And they've started selling
the Duel Disks at a low price!
Then I play two set cards
face-down on the board!
Turn end!
Noah...
Eh?
Ah, nothing...
It's just that I think of Noah when I see
all these kids Dueling like this...
It's my turn!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Noah! You're really sad!
What?!
Your knowledge may have advanced, but your heart has remained frozen!
You're still nothing but a child who knows nothing about the world or the people that inhabit it!
Heh, I shouldn't have expected commoners like yourself to understand my greatness.
But I'm sure someone chosen by victory will understand.
Yugi, I've chosen you!
Now all you have to do
is say you'll serve me!
Using your power to try and sway people's hearts...
How do you expect people to accept you if you do things like this?!
You're acting really stupid, Noah!
Noah...
After having lost his body,
he was forced to live in Virtual Reality...
Such a lonely young boy...
He never had any friends
to play with him...
I Summon the Demon's Summon!
Thinking back on it now,
I feel even sadder for him...
Yes...
Father, let's put an end to all this!
I want you to stay by my side forever!
WHAT DO YOU
THINK YOU'RE DOING, NOAH?!
LET GO OF ME!
I STILL HAVE SOMETHING
I NEED TO DO!
We died a long time ago, Father.
LET ME GO!!
NO!!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE YET!!
If we had met him
in a different way,
I would have liked
to become friends with him.
Yeah...
I lost again!
You're really strong, Bro!
Wanna play me again?
Yeah! I'm not gonna lose this time!
It's kind of nice...
They're all Dueling like this
and enjoying themselves...
But the Duels Yugi and the others
fought weren't like this at all...
Jounouchi-kun...
I'm headed to the Duel Ring
where Kaiba's waiting.
Yugi!
So you stay here and keep fighting!
As a Duelist!
I want you guys to stay here
with Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi!
Wait, Yugi!
Are you saying Dueling is more
important than Jounouchi!?
Why do you have to fight
at a time like this!?
Not just Jounouchi...!
Mai-san...
Bakura-kun...
Even that man named Rishid...
Every one of them have fallen
one after the other!
We've got nothing left to lose!
Anzu...
I fight because I
promised Jounouchi-kun.
Promised...?
As long as people continue
to search for answers...
...they have a reason to live,
a place to return.
Jounouchi-kun will come back!
I'm certain he'll return to us
as his usual, energetic self!
I believe in that future!
Just hold on a moment!
We still have no idea what even
happened to you in the first place!
You still need to be properly tested!
I said I'm fine, pal!
Let's gun it, everyone!
Don't.
The doctor's right...
You have to do what your
medical overseer tells you to!
I get what's goin' on in my body
more than any of you.
You don't know!!
You were practically dead
just minutes ago, you know!
We've all been worried sick over you!
And here you are, making that face
like nothing happened...!
You need to worry about your body
before you start thinking about Dueling!
Anzu...
I'm sorry.
But I have to go do this!
No matter what!
Jounouchi!!
I really am sorry
for worrying you all.
But Yugi's not the only one
concerned about his battles!
I have to fight as well in order
to keep my promise with him!
Your... promise with him...?
Our Battle City isn't over until
I settle things with Yugi!
Both Yugi and me have been fighting
in order to reach the point when we
can call ourselves True Duelists!
It doesn't matter who
it is we're Dueling.
We're connected to each another.
So I want to watch how it ends!
I'm going to watch Yugi's battle!
I have to go!
The mutual feelings of trust and warmth
between Yugi and Jounouchi...
Friendship between men
is really confusing...
But I feel like I've started to
understand it a little better...
Wanna go to our next stop?
Yes!
And after finally overcoming
all of those hardships, Yugi...
The Battle City Finals are over!
The winner is Yugi Mutou!
And Yugi obtained all three
God Cards at long last...
Yugi, here's the God Card!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
The Great War God Obelisk...
Finally, the three God Cards
are in my hands.
Those three cards hold the secret
of the other me's memory...
What could it be...?
And...
The key to the Pharaoh's memories,
which the Tomb Guardian clan
has protected for centuries...
It lies right here!
How awful that
must have been...!
That's horrible...!
This cruel scar...
Is this how the Tomb Guardians
guarded my memory for
so many generations...?!
These hieroglyphs contain a prophecized
message passed down from the first Tomb
Guardian who served under the Royal Family.
"In the future, one will come
who will wield the power of the
three gods depicted on the stone slab."
"This will be proof that the
Pharaoh's soul has been reincarnated."
Yugi, since you now hold the three God Cards, it is proof that you are the Pharaoh.
And thus, you deserve to know the
truth of your long-lost memories.
This is...!
That slate!
Is my memory truly sealed
within that slate?
He's gathered all three
of the God Cards...
When the seal on his memories
is lifted, the other Yugi...
Anzu-san?
Anzu-san?!
What is it?
Um... I realize I took up
a lot of your time today...
You sure this is okay?
You seem like there's something
you're missing out on.
Eh!?
You had something
that important planned!?
Uh, sort of...
Don't "sort of" me!
You should have
told me about this earlier.
I didn't know...
I held you here with me for so long!
Ah c'mon, it's no big deal!
I still have time.
No... In actuality,
I only have a little time left...
Pretty soon, the other Yugi's going to
disappear right before my eyes...
Then please excuse me.
Uh, right...
Make sure you visit
Domino City frequently, okay!
Huh?
"This is... the proof of our friendship!"
My big brother says this a lot!
"We're all connected with
a bond of friendship," is what he says.
A bond of friendship...?
So I've finally become
friends with you guys!
What're you talking about?
You were one of our friends
a long time ago!
We're friends, even if
we're separated, right?!
Of course we are!
Thank goodness!
Then goodbye!
Goodbye, Shizuka-chan!
Friends, even if we're separated...
I may not... have much more time
to spend with the other Yugi...
"We're friends, even if
we're separated," huh...?
But I need to cherish the
little time I have left with him!
Yugi!
At last, the other Yugi begins the journey to find his lost memories.
But before that, Haga and Ryuzaki are suddenly attacked by someone!
And something strange happens when the three God Cards are faced towards the stone slab.
And to add to the strangeness, Duel Monsters begin appearing all over the town!
Just what is going on here?
Next time!
"Throbs of a New Darkness"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other