Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The KC Grand Prix Semi-Finals have begun.
It appears that Sieg stormed his way right into the Finals as soon as the match began,
but Rebecca and Leon are locked in a fierce Duel,
both sides not moving an inch and using all of their strategies.
We'd like to go cheer for her right away, but my grandpa went missing...
It's like he was kidnapped by someone!
Wait for me, Grandpa!
I'm on my way to save you!
"Leon In Fairy Tale Land"
That looks freakin' delicious!
Yeah! That's steamed shrimp tofu!
They've even got Peking duck!
-The hell?!
That person...!
Vivian?!
The hell's goin' on?
Over there!
Upsie-daisy...
Grandpa!
Grandpa Sugoroku!
What are you doing, Grandpa?!
W-Well... You see...
Hey, you! That hurts, Grandfather!
I-I'm sorry, my precious Vivi-chan.
Vivi-chan?!
Grandpa, what's the meaning of this?! Explain yourself!
We were really worried about you, you know!
Well, the thing is...
The truth is...
Don't you say anything more, Grandfather!
This is between Yugi and I.
What the hell?
Huh?
We are going to hold the true Final Match of the KC Grand Prix here!
On this holy ground where Yugi and I will share a passionate battle!
What are you, stupid?
You lost to Rebecca in the first round!
Only the winner of the KC Grand Prix gets to fight against Yugi-kun!
Shut up, will you?!
In Dueling, as long as both mutual parties want to do it, it can happen anywhere, anytime!
Isn't that right, Yugi~?
I'm sorry, but I can't fight against you.
Eh~!?
D-Don't be like that, Yugi!
Go on and Duel against Vivi-chan!
Eh?!
Could it be, Gramps?!
Is she holding your life hostage?!
N-No, there's an explanation for this.
Ow, ow, ow, ow...
Rock-Xiansheng~
No, Sugoroku Mutou-Xiansheng?
You're...
Wei, Sugoroku-Xiansheng, you're...
...the grandfather of the infamous Yugi, am I right?
Y-Yes I am.
Terrific!
Hey, will you listen to a request Vivian has of you?
I'll listen to you...
But as you can see, my waist is in a lot of pain...
If I make that waist of yours all better, will you listen to me then?
Whoo! Of course I will!
Really?!
It's a deal~!
Huh?
My waist doesn't hurt anymore.
I was fortune enough to have had Vivi-chan come heal my back for me!
There's definitely more to it than that...
It's pretty obvious she's got the old man on a leash.
What'd you say?!
C'mon, Gramps! That's pathetic!
If this is how it is, I'm not gonna be your student anymore!
Grandpa...
So you won't...? I knew it...
Gimme a break!
You came all this way!
My waist...!
What the hell did you just do?
I just returned him to how he was.
Are you all right, Grandpa?
Yugi! If you want me to heal your grandfather's back again, Duel against me!
That's low, ya creep!
I'm the kind of woman who will do anything in the face of love.
We'll find true love through Dueling.
How about it? Sounds lovely, doesn't it?
You really are dumb!
Give it up, Yugi.
You have no reason to face her.
Grandpa.
Partner.
Other Me.
There's no helping it. Let's help him.
Sorry...
If it's for my grandpa...
I'll take you on!
That's what I'm talking about.
But there will be one additional condition.
If you lose, you will become my slave.
My love slave.
Hold on, you tramp! What kinda "KC Final" is this supposed to be?!
What kinda "slave" is he supposed to be?!
You're not making any sense here!
H-Hey, Anzu...
I'm fine with that.
Because I'm going to win.
Yugi!
He's right.
Let him take care of this quickly so we can go root for Becky.
Stay out of this, all of you!
I'll show you Dueling worth 4,000 years of China's history!
Duel!!
My turn! Draw!
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
And draw two cards from my deck!
Then I Summon Witch of the Black Forest in Attack Mode!
Witch of the Black Forest, get rid of the Pumpkin Carriage!
Now Cinderella lost her ability to Direct Attack.
Turn end!
It's my turn! Draw!
Cinderella, attack Witch of the Black Forest!
I activate Witch of the Black Forest's Special Effect!
When this card is sent to the Graveyard,
I can add a Monster with 1500 Defense Points or less from my deck into my hand.
I'm not done yet!
I Summon Tom Thumb in Defense Mode!
Then I set a card face-down!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Ruby Dragon in Attack Mode!
I then activate a Magic Card from my hand, Dragon's Flame Bullets!
According to the Magic Effect of Dragon's Flame Bullets,
I can destroy one face-up Monster with 800 Defense Points or less!
And using Ruby Dragon, I attack Tom Thumb!
Reverse card, open!
Attack Nullification!
It negates your attack and ends the Battle Phase!
I set two cards face-down and end my turn.
As I thought, this boy is strong!
Why, Yugi...?
Don't lose, Rebecca!
You can do it!
-Fight!
That's right. I'm not alone out here.
They're all cheering for me.
Keep at it, Rebecca.
Mm-hm.
I won't lose!
It's my turn! Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand! Giant's Training!
As long as he's been on the field for one turn, I can tribute Tom Thumb!
I can then Summon Globberman in Attack Mode!
Globberman, attack Ruby Dragon!
Reverse card, open!
Rope of Life!
When a Monster is sent to the Graveyard as a result of battle,
I can discard my entire hand to activate this!
I can Special Summon the Monsters with an increase of 800 Attack and Defense Points!
I have no cards in my hand!
So I can Special Summon Ruby Dragon without doing anything!
Furthermore, I open my other reverse card!
Resurrection of Adamantine Sword!
It lets me sacrifice a Special Summoned Dragon-Type Monster...
...and Special Summon Diamond Head Dragon from my deck!
Diamond Head Dragon's Attack Power
is determined by the total Attack Power of the sacrificed Monster plus 1000 points!
It's got 3400 Attack Points...
Well?
I'll end my turn.
I won't lose!
Damn is this good!
What a unique flavor this dish has!
What the heck are you two doing?
Go cheer for Yugi!
Like we need to! It's obvious Yugi's gonna win!
You should eat some, too! It's really good!
Is it?
-Yup!
Vivian just pulled out some kinda trump card!
I sacrifice Master Kyonshee and Kung-Fu Nyan Nyan...
...in order to activate the Magic Card, Luminous Cloud!
I Special Summon Dragon Lady in Attack Position!
I cannot Special Summon any other Monsters this turn.
But, you see...
I activate the Equipment Magic from my hand, Lightning Saber!
Dragon Lady's Attack Power increases by 300 points!
And then, Dragon Lady will attack Black Magician!
What?!
It can attack twice?!
The Monster equipped with Lightning Saber, you see,
can halve its own Attack Power in order to attack a second time.
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Big Shield Gardna in Defense Mode!
I place a card face-down and end my turn.
You doin' okay, Yugi?
You scared or somethin'?
What are you saying?!
Like he'd be scared of her!
My turn! Draw!
Dragon Lady attacks Big Shield Gardna!
Reverse card, open!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Quick-Play Magic! Snowfall Sword!
It's an Equipment Magic that only activates with a Warrior-Type Monster!
It negates the opponent's Magic or Trap Card!
And it destroys the card!
Isn't this getting pretty bad?
She's able to Direct Attack with two strikes!
And then I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Flying Dragon Whirl!
By sending four Dragon-Type Monsters from my deck into the Graveyard,
I can raise Dragon Lady's Attack Power up by 1200 points!
Oh, shit!
No way!
Dragon Lady, attack Yugi directly!
Oh my~! I'm gonna win~!
You sure about that?
By discarding the Kuriboh card from my hand,
the player's damage can be reduced to zero!
No~! I was sooo close~!
Guess we'll have to end it next turn~
Turn end~!
There won't be a next time.
On this turn, Vivian, I'm going to defeat you!
Th-There's no way you could do that...!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Skilled Dark Magician in Attack Mode!
And I activate Pot of Greed.
I draw two cards from my deck.
Then, I activate Emblem of Dragon Destroyer from my hand!
I add Buster Blader from the Graveyard into my hand!
That light is...!
Spell Counters. They are tallies for the activation of a magical spell.
I've still got more.
I activate Reincarnation of the Dead from my hand!
It allows me to add a Monster from the Graveyard into my hand.
I choose the Black Magician!
Then the Spell Counter tallies at three,
I can tribute Skilled Dark Magician...
...and Special Summon Black Magician in Attack Mode!
Moreover, I'm fusing the Black Magician on my field with the Buster Blader in my hand!
Come forth!
The Mighty Magic Swordsman - Black Paladin!
Black Paladin's Attack Power
increases by 500 points for every Dragon-Type Monster on the field and in the Graveyard!
That can't be...!
I have four Dragons in my Graveyard...!
Black Paladin, attack Dragon Lady!
Beyond Magic! Fierce Slashing Wave!!
-Awright!
Naturally!
You promised me.
Please heal my grandpa's waist.
Okay...
Yugi~
Rebecca!
Darling!
We're here, too!
-Go for it!
-You can do it, Rebecca!
Becky!
You guys!
Yugi-san!
But are you alright, Rebecca?
You only have 100 Life left!
It'll be okay! Because Darling came to cheer for me!
Do your best!
Mm-hm!
My turn! Draw!
Diamond Head Dragon, attack Globberman!
-She did it!
It's not one-sided anymore!
Rebecca!
I set one card face-down and end my turn!
My reverse card is Dragon's Imperial Wrath.
Even if my opponent uses Defense Position,
if my Monster's Attack Power surpasses that Monster's Defense Power,
the difference in damage will be inflicted on my opponent.
Unless he plays a Monster holding more than 2500 Defense Points...
...I'm going to win.
My turn! Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Gold Moon Coin!
I'm giving these to you.
When I activate Gold Moon Coin, I give all the remaining cards in my hand to my opponent.
I then draw the same number of cards from my deck.
Spinning Wheel Spindle?
If you had used this, you would have been able to destroy a Monster on my field?
If you Summon a Monster with 900 or more Attack Points on the next turn,
I'll be finished.
So I'm betting on the future!
Leon...
Leon-kun...
He's very quiet, but I can sense a lot of vigor from this boy.
Here I go, Rebecca!
I activate the Magic Card, One Hundred Year Awakening, from my hand!
What?
I sacrifice Curse of Thorns!
In order to Special Summon Thorn Princess from my deck!
Thorn Princess?
Wh-What's going to happen?
I activate Thorn Princess' Special Effect!
When Summoned, I can take control over one of the opponent's Monsters!
No way!
Using Diamond Head Dragon...
...I attack you directly!
-Rebecca!
Seto-sama, we have completed the background check on Sieg Lloyd.
I knew it.
So you're the rat?
Um... I'm sorry, Rebecca.
Why are you apologizing?
Eh?
Congratulations. You better win the Final Match so you can face Yugi.
Right!
Rebecca...
Guess even Rebecca says good things here and there.
She's a hell of a better sport than you are.
That was a great Duel!
You did a great job, Rebecca.
Darling!
I lost because you didn't get here earlier!
Sorry.
Rebecca sure has a long way to go.
-Like you can say that!
I-I'm sorry.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Not only Jounouchi, but even Rebecca lost!
It looks like Leon-kun will end up fighting against Sieg in the Final Match.
What an unexpected development.
Naturally, we'll be rooting for Leon-kun.
Try your best for the others and win the championship!
Huh?
Kaiba-kun suddenly stopped the two of them!
Don't tell me that Kaiba-kun is going to Duel?!
Next time!
"Kaiba's Intrusion!
The Grand Prix Final"
Duel standby!