Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
We received the power of the Legendary Dragon from the Duel Monsters World.
I can't believe it, but that wasn't a dream!
A powerful Monster has revealed itself.
That's what is trying to destroy the world?
Even though the Legendary Dragon, Timaeus's power was able to stop it,
the fight has just begun!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Invitation From Pegasus"
After the Duel Monsters sightings that occurred yesterday,
there have been many abnormal incidents, like auroras or massive tornadoes, happening around the world.
We experienced auroras
and large tornadoes ourselves last night.
Some even claim to have witnessed "Monsters" in the area.
So what happened last night wasn't just a dream.
Because we still have the card you got from the Duel Monsters World.
But no matter how you look at it, it's just like any normal card.
I don't see any great power
in it or anything.
You'd better be careful with this!
This is an important card given to the True Duelists.
Right, Yugi?
Mhm-hmm. I got something unbelievable.
The power to
save the world from despair...
The Monocle of Timaeus...
So, what are you gonna do now?
"What," you say?
We have no clues
about the enemies at all.
We don't know where the ones who stole Yugi's God Cards,
those "Musketeers of Doma" guys have gone.
Come on~!
I don't get any of this~
Other Me...
Is there anything
we can use as clues?
Like, say, you rub the thing and it goes "PUFF!" all of a sudden!
Can you tell us
where the enemies went?!
Ow!
Didn't you say
we need to be careful with it?!
Shut up!
I'm just trying it out!
What do you want?
You bastard!
Knock it off!
What the hell...?
It's so loud up here.
Grandpa!
What's up?
Hey Yugi, a parcel came for you today from America.
America?
Could it be from Otogi-kun?
Now that you mention it, he's in America right now, isn't he?
What's wrong, Yugi?
Let's see... "Industrial Illusions"...
WHAT DID YOU SAY?!
Industrial Illusions is the company that Pegasus owns, right?
Yeah...
Besides this card..
There's a video letter along with it...!
Didn't the same thing happen before Duelist Kingdom?!
Grandpa!
Jounouchi-kun!
Honda-kun!
Anzu!
No one can get in the way now.
Shall we begin...
Yugi boy?
Is this a Dark Game?
My power is the Dark Power of the Millennium Eye.
Millennium Eye?
I'll see you again at the Kingdom.
If you want back your most valuable treasure.
Yugi...!
Wouldn't we be better off
throwing this out?
But Pegasus doesn't have
the Millennium Eye anymore.
Doesn't that make it alright?
Now that you mention it...
It was stolen by someone.
Still...
The other me...
Although he doesn't have it now,
Pegasus was the one chosen by the Millennium Eye.
And he's also the one who created Duel Monsters.
Maybe this tape
has something to do with this...
Yes.
That's very likely.
Why don't we check it out?
Oi, Yugi!
I'm not ready to die yet, ya know!
Long time no see... Yugi boy.
He appeared!
Pegasus...
I know this is abrupt,
but you should know what's happening around the world right now.
What the hell?
It's like an ordinary video.
Yeah...
Duel Monsters is the game I created.
And now these Monsters
are being substantiated,
and have caused a lot or panic around the world.
Just what has happened?
I've done some research.
And I realized one thing.
What has he realized?
About this thing...
I have to talk to Yugi boy personally.
Eh?
However, I cannot leave this building.
I am being watched by someone.
What?
To be completely honest, I am taking a gamble on whether or not this letter even reaches you.
But if you safely get it,
please take the card with you and come to America!
America?
I will arrange for a plane to pick you up.
So please make haste!
I will wait for you!
What's going on here?
Yugi.
We have no choice but to go.
We don't have any other clues or leads.
Yeah. You're right.
I'm going to America.
Yugi!
Right.
You can't waste your time here.
I'll go with you!
Jounouchi-kun!
I won't let you go alone!
He's right.
I'll go too.
Good!
Since you've made up your mind,
let's get ready to leave!
Everyone...
Okay!
And seriously,
if Pegasus is gonna pick us up,
we get to go to America for free!
Yeah, that's right!
You guys are too much...
Let's go~!
Yeah!
America, they said?!
Speaking a' Pegasus,
he's the creator a' Duel Monsters!
And he invited those yahoos?!
Hang on.
Industrial Illusions is a company well known for selling cards.
They must have a ton of rare cards!
Rare cards?
Alrighty then!
Take all the rare cards
you like, kiddies!
Wow, amazing~!
Thank you, Pegasus!
Rare cards...
Ain't fair, ain't fair!
It ain't cool that those bumpkins are gettin' all the rare cards to themselves!
That's right!
We can't stand by and let them hog all the cards to themselves!
Right!
We gotta get the
rare cards for ourselves!
But... how?
We plan ahead.
By capturing the souls of countless Duelists and obtaining the power of the three God Cards...
...the door has been opened.
However...
Lend us your power, Timaeus!
I cannot believe the nameless Pharaoh has obtained the power of that dragon...
Our God has only just been awoken.
A great deal of offerings shall be required if we wish to keep its strength alive.
Nameless Pharaoh...
You shall not get
in our way any longer!
Rafael!
Yes.
As you command.
I'll present the soul of the nameless Pharaoh to our God this time for sure.
That alone shall not be suffice!
If we desire to fully revive our God,
we require the souls of as many talented Duelists as we can possibly obtain!
Please let me handle taking the soul of Seto Kaiba.
And I'll be taking Katsuya Jounouchi.
I'll beat him to a bloody pulp.
And then I'll steal his soul!
All for the sake of that woman?
That's none of your business!
But why do you insist
on sticking with Kaiba so much?
And that would be
none of your business.
What?!
Will you two give it a rest?!
We stand before Lord Dartz.
Leaving the nameless Pharaoh aside, we desire the soul of another powerful Duelist.
I want you to head towards where Pegasus J. Crawford resides.
Pegasus?
I have already made arrangements for another person to take care of it.
All you three need do is pick her up!
Yes!
Yugi boy...
Please hurry and get here!
Something terrible has happened.
You are..
NO~!!
Let me see...
I wonder how long we're going to stay there for.
America, huh?
I never expected to return there in a way like this...
What the hell should I bring with me to America!?
Yeah.
I'll be out of the country for a while.
So don't worry about me.
And don't you go
catching a cold, Shizuka.
Better not forget to bring this.
"Key of Illusion"...
I wonder what the key card is this time...
What do you think, Other Me?
Other Me?
What's up, Partner?
What are you thinking about?
No, it's nothing.
Liar.
Something is troubling you, but you're trying to hide it. Right?
Partner...
I can't keep anything from you, can I?
Other Me...
I'm thinking about
how to deal with the enemy this time.
Just who are they?
It's possible... that I already know who they are... in my lost memories, anyway...
Look, there you go again.
I hope you'll not conceal
what's on your mind.
This time, there's so much we don't know.
Partner...
I guess... I guess I have a bad feeling about all this!
Something we're not
aware of is approaching.
It makes me really nervous!
Partner...
I'm sorry...
For saying something strange.
Alright... let's hurry and get some rest!
Good night, my other self.
Well, Grandpa.
Yeah.
If I learn any new information
from Arthur,
I'll be sure to inform you.
Okay.
We're off!
We're off.
We'll leave now.
See ya.
Be careful.
Amazing!
We're going on that?!
Rich people sure go all out on everything they do!
Whether it's Pegasus or Kaiba.
Speaking of which, Kaiba-kun is in America too, isn't he, Yugi?
Yeah.
But with the Duel Monsters
appearing everywhere in the world,
he's probably totally exhausted.
I like the sound of that!
You must be Master Yugi Mutou.
Y-Yes.
We're here to pick you up.
Please come this way.
Okay.
We'll get your luggage.
Please come with us.
Eh?
Awesome!
It's like a reception room!
This plane is exclusively reserved just for us?
Yahoo!
This is the best thing I've ever sat on!
Hey Yugi, come and sit down.
Okay.
Hey... give me a hand.
Hey, what are you doing?
Ahh, no...
Alright!
Off we go to America!
Good! We succeeded!
We're gonna go to America!
But should we stay inside the cockpit 'til arrival?
We have no choice.
We can't get the rare cards
if they find us.
Yes~! It looks delicious~!
F-Freezing~!
Endure it.
This is all for the rare cards.
I-I'll die~!
Who the hell came up
with this horrible plan?!
E-Endure it...
Rare cards...
We're here at last!
That was a great plane!
Yeah.
Please get into this car.
EH~
This time it's a limousine?!
Huh?
Did we have a bag like this?
Hey, whose bag is this?
It's not mine.
That's not mine.
Maybe someone mistakenly took the wrong bag?
Is that so?
Then I'll handle it.
America~
Rare cards~
Just as we announced earlier!
Whatever this current situation is, it has nothing to do with our Kaiba Corporation's Solid Vision!
Just answer them like that!
Yes.
What the hell is happening...?
Is this some kind of elaborate takeover plot being orchestrated by one of Kaiba Corporation's competitors?
Has there been an answer from Industrial Illusions yet?!
Right. We haven't heard anything yet.
Then try and contact them again!
Yes, sir.
This is a very important time for Kaiba Corporation and our plan to build Kaiba Land around the world...
Big brother!
It's terrible!
Someone's bought a huge amount of Kaiba Corporation's stocks!
What?!
There's just no way...!
How could anyone buy this many of our stocks without us finding out about it?
Just how did they...?
Big brother... What should we do?
I won't let them do us any more harm!
I'll find anyone who
dares to get in my way!
And I'll make them regret it!
What is it!?
Hi, Kaiba boy!
Pegasus!
Did you receive
the message I sent you?
This is your doing?!
It was just a friendly greeting!
I take it you didn't like it?
You bastard!
You're even more
persistent than I thought!
You're still planning to take over Kaiba Corporation?!
Oh! Please don't make such a scary face!
This was merely a demonstration.
Demonstration, you say?!
Right.
A little tease before our Duel.
It's been far too long since we last Dueled one another!
Will you accept this challenge?
Who the hell would come visit you?!
No!
Kaiba boy, you cannot simply ignore me!
Because if you do not come, I will sell all of the stocks I purchased from Kaiba Corporation!
And if I were to do that...
Your company will nosedive!
And your dream will fade away.
You scumbag...!
Still not going to come, Kaiba boy?
Big brother...
I'll accept your challenge!
Then I invite you to the ever-so nostalgic Duelist Kingdom.
I'll be waiting for you, Kaiba boy.
Big brother...
After Battle City ended,
my brother sealed away his cards in order to focus on the plan for Kaiba Land production.
Now he has no choice but to go against his word...
Pegasus...
Yugi is the only man I've truly lost to.
If you plan to
stand in my way once again...
I'll beat you down until you move!
What's wrong?
Big brother...
Pegasus may once again...
Don't be afraid, Mokuba!
The same strategy won't work on me!
Right!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
We have been invited by Pegasus
to come to America.
At the same time, in order to fight that same Pegasus,
Kaiba-kun is headed for Duelist Kingdom.
Kaiba-kun keeps asking about the Duel Monsters incident,
But Pegasus claims it's the fault of him and Kaiba Corporation.
But isn't there something strange about Pegasus...?
Next time!
"The Nightmare of Toon World"
Duel standby!