Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
So you finally went and played your trump card, Blue-Eyes, Kaiba!
But I won't be done in so easily!
Thanks to my Graverobber/Resurrection of the Dead combo, Blue-Eyes belongs to me now!
What?!
You Summoned your own Blue-Eyes and had 'em destroy each other?!
Now you're getting desperate!
Oh shit! He got his Blue-Eyes back with Resurrection of the Dead!
"The Path of a True Duelist"
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
Faced with the Blue-Eyes that has been reunited with his true master, there's not a thing you can do now.
And yet you still won't accept defeat?!
Heh! Ya think I'd accept
something like that?!
I already told you!
I don't give up until the end!
Here goes! I draw!
None of my Monsters can beat a Blue-Eyes with 3000 Attack Points...
But if I had that...
I need it for times like this!
I Summon Baby Dragon in Defense Mode!
I end my turn!
That's the best he's got? Does that mean Jounouchi-kun's run out of options?!
No, he may still have another trick left.
Isn't that right, Yugi?
Huh? Where the heck did Yugi run off to?
Now that you mention it, Anzu-chan hasn't come back yet either.
I realize that it is
unreasonable to ask of you.
Even so, I ask you to save
my little brother, Malik!
Malik organized the Ghouls.
And there is no way he can
simply be forgiven for the
countless people he has harmed.
But he did it because he was
a victim of the fate the Ishtar clan
has endured for years!
I just want to save that boy!
The only little brother I have!
The one I cherish!
Ishizu...
You're the only one who can defeat Malik's
dark side and rescue him from himself!
I beg of you! Please save the boy!
Other me...
I know.
The Tomb Guardians have been
protecting the Millennium Items
along with the Pharaoh's
forgotten memories for centuries.
All for the memories I've lost.
Malik hates me for this same reason.
If that's so, I'm just as responsible!
When I fight him in the upcoming Final,
I'll defeat his dark half!
I'll save Malik from his dark curse,
and rescue those who fell to the
Dark Games, Mai and Bakura, as well.
I am grateful.
Huh?
Anzu!
What was... I doing?
What am I doing here?
You don't remember?
Uhh...
All I remember is Jounouchi about to start his Duel with Kaiba-kun...
He's got nothing left!
Yeah, but all Jounouchi's Monsters are in Defense Mode.
If they're beaten, he won't lose Life Points, but he won't be able to strike back either!
My turn! Draw!
It looks like your luck
has just about run dry!
Whah?!
[Sounds like "lucky"]
Magic Card!
Defense Seal!
Not good! He's done for!
Sweet! Big brother's gonna win!
Pulverize this deadbeat!
Blue-Eyes! Attack the Falcon Knight!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
You're finished!
Now's my chance!
Reverse card, open!
What!?
Strength Increasing Medicine Super Z!
When I take 2000 points
of damage or more,
this card automatically increases my Life Points by 4000!
Wow! Jounouchi's pretty stubborn!
Tough persistence is one of Jounouchi-kun's strong points!
Heh! I won't be beaten that easily!
This annoying bastard just doesn't know when to accept defeat...!
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
No matter what you do, you can't escape your eventual defeat!
I'm going to put an end
to it all on this turn!
It's true that if this attack hits, I have no hope of dodging...
Even so...!
There's tons of
possibilities lying in my deck...
Please draw it!
My turn! Draw!
Oh man!
Let's do this, Time Magician!
Time Magician, you said?
Kaiba! This is our final fight!
Let's test whether my luck's really run out or not!
Time Magic!
Activate!
Hit it! Hit it!!
If it hits, Jounouchi-kun wins!
Big brother!
Booyah! It hit!
A thousand years passes us by!
And the Baby Dragon on my field...
...evolves into the Thousand Dragon!
As for you, Kaiba, all the Monsters on your field are destroyed!
Vanish into the thousand-year time wrap!
Blue-Eyes!!
So your last dying effort
scored a hit, did it...?
However...
That's not going to work against me!
It... worked?
Good going!
The Blue-Eyes should have vanished into the time warp!
You fools!
Return to me once again, my Blue-Eyes!
By my side!
What?!
Impossible!
No way!
That's...!
I activated
Sub-Space Matter Transfer Device.
This card transfers one Monster on my field to a safe location.
I guess you could call it
another dimension!
That's my big brother for ya!
Dammit! He almost had this won!
It's impossible for you to defeat me relying on luck with that Gamble Deck of yours!
That's just what I expected
from you, Kaiba!
Still refuse to accept your loss?
No, I meant that!
Kaiba, you're really strong!
Dueling with strong guys makes my chest throb with excitement!
It's really fun!
"Fun," you said?
What the heck, man?
Why the hell are you Dueling if you don't think it's fun?
A mediocre deadbeat like you could never understand!
I Duel in order to win and obtain everything I've ever wanted!
Victory is my everything!
But...!
Ya know, there's no way I could understand any of that.
I don't have any cards left to play!
Turn end!
It's about time we end this farce...!
It's my turn! Draw!
By discarding this
Thunder Dragon from my hand...
I am able to add two more Thunder Dragons from my deck to my hand!
And then the Magic Card, Fusion!
I fuse together my
two Thunder Dragons!
Twin-Headed Thunder Dragon!
Furthermore...!
I activate Quick Attack!
It allows Fusion Monsters to attack on the same turn they are Summoned!
Thanks, Yugi.
Are you sure you're alright?
Yeah... I seem fine.
But not remembering what happened
creeps me out a little.
Other me, why would
Malik go after Anzu?
I'm not sure about that...
Oh yeah, how's the Duel with
Jounouchi and Kaiba-kun going?
Right...
They should be settling it
any minute now.
Twin-Headed Thunder Dragon,
attack Thousand Dragon!
Thousand Dragon!
Blue-Eyes!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
My brother won!
You gave it your all Jounouchi, but you're still no match for big brother!
Challenging someone to a Duel
knowing they were going to win
from the start was frivolous.
A big waste of time.
Hold it, Kaiba!
Jounouchi!
What now?
I don't want to hear the howl
of a loser dog.
It's true I just lost...
But that's only for the time being!
One of these days
I'm gonna beat you.
Until then, I'll fight you
as many times as it takes.
No matter how many times I lose
to you, I'll stand back up again!
That's my path to
becoming a True Duelist!
I guess death really is the only
thing that can cure stupidity.
Wh-What was that, ya jerk?!
Give it a rest, Jounouchi!
Le'go!
C'mon! Yugi-kun's
final match is about to start!
Oh yeah, that's right.
What the heck? Yugi and Anzu went on ahead without even watching the end of my fight?
Let's get moving.
Man! What heartless people they are!
And I'll be sure to tell 'em that!
Let's go, Mokuba.
My Battle City is over.
But brother...!
We still have the Final...!
There's no longer any meaning in it.
Ishizu...!
Seto...
Do you believe Yugi can defeat
Malik's Ra Deck, even after having
won a second God Card from you?
No... The probability is very low.
That's how strong the
hidden powers within Ra are.
But all of this no longer has
anything to do with me.
It's not really any of my business, regardless of which one of them ends up winning.
In order for Yugi to win, Seto,
he needs your help!
What nonsense are you
going on about now?
Did your ridiculous occult garbage
give you another "revelation"?
Mokuba, we're going.
R-Right...
Pert kertu.
You've read it, have you not?
Seto, have you translated
the meaning behind the carvings
on that stone slab palette?
The 3,000 year old palette discovered
in the Pharaoh's mortuary temple...
...bears a prayer for the dead in Hieratic
writing, known as the pert kertu.
A dedication to the late Pharaoh, signed by his "true friend".
Hmph, what nonsense!
Those words, that proof of friendship,
were left to the world...
...by none other than
the second being carved on
the palette, the priest himself!
"The corpse sinks to the floor."
"The vessel becomes sand,
becomes dust..."
"Even the brightest gold,
even the sharpest sword..."
"...is wrapped in the sheath of time."
"Woe to the Pharaoh,
for his body lacks even his name..."
"Time is a battlefield of souls."
"I cry the song of battle,
the song of a friend..."
"To the place far away where
souls meet... Guide me."
What are you trying to say, Ishizu?!
I have no interest in some words
inscribed on a 3,000 year old relic!
Seto... The God Cards guided
you to start Battle City.
And to put an end to these battles
atop the Duel Tower.
Your battle with the soul of your friend,
the Pharaoh, that is.
Humph! Pharaoh, you say?!
What a load of shit!
You're going to regret it if you don't stop
muttering this annoying gibberish!
Face your heart!
Seto, this Duel Tower you built
is the place where souls meet!
This sanctuary of battle
built by your spirit!
"Sanctuary" my ass!
That very same Duel Tower
represents my hatred for Gozaburo!
And I was supposed to become
the Duel King atop it and prove
that I'm better than it all!
But it's all meaningless now!
Then I'll sink this place to the bottom of the sea with my own two hands!
Mokuba, activate the detonator's time
switch in the underground facility!
What's wrong? Get going!
Big brother... Just because you're angry
and hateful because of how it
was for us while growing up...
There's no reason to make
Yugi and the others suffer because of it!
Mokuba...!
When I first met them,
I hated them!
But they fought hard
for me on Pegasus's island...
And they rescued me when
I was captured by the Ghouls!
They viewed me as one of their
friends and tried to help me...
Mokuba...
I think what Yugi
and Jounouchi said was true!
The Monsters drawn on the cards
we Duelists wield in battle aren't
the only demons in a Duel!
The anger in our hearts...
Hatred...
Desires...
Our worst enemies are inside us!
Only when you overcome all of that...
...can you walk the road to
becoming a True Duelist!
That's just what I expected
from you, Kaiba!
Still refuse to accept your loss?
No, I meant that!
Kaiba, you're really strong!
Dueling with strong guys makes my chest throb with excitement!
It's really fun!
You used to think
like that before as well!
You enjoyed games from the
bottom of your heart back then!
I loved the smile you used
to show me back then!
Mokuba...
Please! I want you to
promise me, big brother!
That when this Duel Tower sinks,
you'll forget all about your hatred!
I want you to go back to the old brother
I knew before all of this happened!
Will I be able to let go of my hatred?
Even if I sink
this Duel Tower into the sea?
Jounouchi! Is your Duel over already?
You guys're really mean!
Abandoning me in the middle
of my Duel like that!
Sorry, Jounouchi-kun.
Don't sweat it!
We can't have you watching
this dummy lose when your important
final match is about to start!
What'd you say?!
Eh? So Jounouchi lost?
You bet!
But he did put up a pretty good fight.
But he was still
no match for Kaiba-kun!
Well, it couldn't be helped.
Jounouchi's still got a ways to go.
Shut up! You shouldn't be talkin',
since you weren't even there
to see my brave fight!
I knew without watching.
Oh, you little...!
C'mon guys! I'll remember that!
Now it's my turn!
Malik!
I look forward to this, Yugi...
The Ultimate Dark Game
awaits us in our Duel!
I will tear you apart and give you
a taste of the pleasures of death...
Yugi, this bastard is more dangerous
than any one else.
He's a freak who likes torturing his
opponents before defeating them
in his Duels, and he enjoys it!
Just like he did to Mai...
If only I was stronger, I might have
been able to save Mai...!
So please, Yugi!
Beat Malik and save Mai!
I will! For sure!
Yugi probably thinks he's got the
advantage since he beat Kaiba
and won his God Card..
But they are worthless against my Ra!
One Turn Kill...
I can destroy you in
an instant if I choose to!
Yugi has about a 3% chance
of victory against Ra.
One Turn Kill...
The other gods don't even compare
to the hidden powers of Ra.
There's only one way.
A key card that I own.
The only card that can
seal the power of Ra...
Even with the card in Yugi's hands,
his chances will only go up
to about 20%.
Big brother, where are you going?
The Sky Duel Arena!
This should be entertaining!
It's a game with
only a 20% chance of victory!
He said, "I won through the
power of my friends."
In that case, I'll take this card, with the
little possibility is holds of winning...
...and Yugi, I'll entrust it to you!
Can you perform a miracle?!
There's no such thing as miracles!
There's no such thing
as the power of a friend!
Take this, Yugi!
Your defeat
will be the proof of that!
What's the big idea?
Kaiba-kun gave Yugi a card!
What's he up to?
But Yugi places the card in his deck without a moment's hesitation!
And the final match of the Battle City Tournament begins!
Is there any way to fight against the hidden abilities of Malik's God Card, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra?
Please! You can do it, Yugi!
Next time!
"Final: Yugi VS Malik"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other