Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Oujia Board's Death Call"
So by destroying Dark Necrofear,
the Field Magic Dark Sanctuary is activated...
Just what could Bakura be planning?
The moment Dark Sanctuary is activated,
the Hateful Spirit, known as the Onryou, is automatically Special Summoned.
That vengeful soul, knowing only hatred, will wander your field in search of its next host...
But Yugi...
You won't see which Monster is possesses until it's too late...
Something's up...
But I have no clue what it is...!
Currently, Bakura has no Monsters on the field.
If I directly attack Bakura with Magnet Warrior Gamma,
I'll win.
I've just got to give it a shot!
I direct attack with Magnet Warrior Gamma!
What?!
Spirit Burn!!
Something came out of Magnet Warrior Gamma and attacked me!
You must be really shocked!
He's been possessed by the Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary, the Onryou!
Onryou?
The Onryou becomes an Equipment Card
and attached itself to one of the opponent's Monsters.
So it's inside of my Magnet Warrior?
The Onryou is more than happy to attack when you order it to,
although you're the one who takes the damage.
Furthermore, the player who is attacked loses half of the possessed Monster's Attack Points.
What!?
In other words, that's half of Magnet Warrior Gamma's 1500 Attack Points,
totaling at 750 points that will be drained from your Life Points!
And the 750 points you lost will be added to my Life Points!
You absorbed my Life?!
It's too early to get surprised, Yugi...
This is but the start of my Occult Deck's terror!
My turn!
Draw card!
I then play my Permanent Trap!
Ouija Board, activate!
What the heck is that weird looking board?
That's a tool they use in Western spiritualism!
S-Spiritualism?!
I've heard about it.
So it's similar to a planchette, right?
It really... creeps me out...
Ouija Board...!
I'll explain!
An Ouija board is a tool to communicate with spirits...
The planchette will point to letters on the board, and spell out the spirit's wishes...
Look.
This turn, the spirits will send you a letter!
The letter "D" appeared on the field!
There'll be much more than just "D"!
Starting next turn, the letters "E", "A", "T" and "H"...
...will appear one by one!
"D-E-A-T-H"...
"Death"!
That's right.
when all the letters of "death" mark the message of demise,
even if you still have Life remaining,
you'll be eliminated right on the spot!
So that means I only have four turns left...!
So he let me beat Dark Necrofear on purpose so he could play this combo?!
No way!
Does that mean Yugi only has four turns left?!
Big brother...
Using the Onryou to possess Yugi's Monsters...
...stealing his Life...
...and using the Ouija Board to put a time limit on this match with a message of death?
I guess he did have a strategy.
Yugi!
The countdown to your doom has begun!
You only have four turns left to live!
But there's much more to the Occult Combo!
Magic Card! The Dark Door!
Now you can only attack with one Monster each turn!
And now I'm about to play another terrifying card!
I set this.
I then Summon Earthbound Spirit!
I plan to sacrifice this guy.
The Permanent Field Magic Dark Sanctuary requires a sacrifice each and every turn!
Turn over!
My turn!
Because of the Effect of the The Dark Door Magic Card,
I can only attack with one Monster per turn.
Magnet Warrior Gamma is possessed by the Onryou, so it can't attack.
But...
Bakura doesn't have a wall Monster on his field.
If I attack him directly with the Black Magician Girl...
...since Bakura only has 900 Life Points, he'll be finished!
But there's a good chance he's realized that...
And if he has... there's no doubt in my mind his Reverse Card is a Trap!
What's wrong?!
But I can't waste this turn!
Even if it is a trap...
...I've got to try!
I'll place Kuriboh on the field in Defense Mode!
And I attack with Black Magician Girl!
Black Burning!!
Spirit Burn!!
Th-This time...
...he got the Black Magician Girl?!
And half of the Black Magician Girl's 2500 Attack Points
will come out of your Life, Yugi,
and be added to my Life.
I forgot to tell you.
The Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary changes its host on every turn...
If you don't choose your attack Monster carefully,
...your own army will slowly tear your body to ribbons!
Turn... over...
I activate the Ouija Board's Effect!
The Death Message card...
"D" and "E"...
He's gathered two now!
Finally get it now?
Every time your turn comes to an end,
the Ouija Board automatically adds another letter to your message of death!
Bakura...
Before you gather the "Death" letters,
you still require three more of the Death Message cards.
But you only have one open slot on your Disk open!
Thanks for the warning!
But don't go thinking you found a weakness in my strategy!
Let me explain!
Dark Sanctuary doesn't just have the Onryou as its Special Ability!
I can now play both Magic and Trap Cards in the Monster Zone slots on the Disk!
What?!
So you're saying you can play up to ten Magic and Trap Cards at once?!
My Occult Combo is perfect!
Yugi! Your life ends in three turns!
You can't escape this fate!
Yugi!
Shit! He's been completely cornered!
In any case, he's got to do something about that Ouija Board!
But Yugi has no clue what Monster on his field is being controlled by the Onryou!
If he carelessly attacks, he'll only damage himself!
But if he doesn't do anything about this,
Yugi-kun will lose in three turns!
Big brother, is Yugi-san going to lose?
Nope, it's Yugi we're talking about.
He's sure to find a way out of this!
Here I go!
My turn!
Even if I do nothing, you're bound to lose in three turns!
I Summon Critter!
And I sacrifice Critter to the Dark Sanctuary!
And due to Critter's Special Effect,
I draw one card from my deck!
And it's turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
Now then... who's next?
Alright...
I'll pick the Magician girl again.
And you can't see it, Yugi!
Which one of my Monsters did he possess this turn?
It can't be Kuriboh...
He knows it's not an offensive-type Monster...
Is it Magnet Warrior...?
Or is it the Black Magician Girl?
But because of the Permanent Magic Card on his field, The Dark Door...
I can only attack with one Monster!
Just once!
Since all I've drawn is a bunch of useless cards,
I've got no way to stop the Onryou.
But with Big Shield Gardna as my Wall Monster,
there would be no point in possessing it, as it has only 100 Attack Points.
Big Shield Gardna in Defense Position!
Haven't you realized it yet, Yugi?!
There's no point in trying to defend yourself!
I hate to admit it, but he's right...
I've only got a few turns left...
I've got to pick one of these two...
If I hesitate now, I have no chance of beating Bakura!
This is a gamble!
I attack with Magnet Warrior Gamma!
That's just like him to make a wise move like that...
But that won't work against me!
Trap Card, activate!
Dark Spirit of the Silent!
It possesses a Monster in Attack Mode, silences it,
and forces another Monster to take it's place, despite what the player orders!
Dark Spirit! Possess the Magnet Warrior Gamma!
Magnet Warrior Gamma can't attack or move,
so instead, my command to "attack" will be carried out by Black Magician Girl!
But the Black Magician girl is possessed by the spirit of Dark Sanctuary!
Spirit Burn!!
There is no flaw in my Occult Combo!
Bakura-kun's Occult Combo is perfect!
There's no way to beat it!
No way!
So Yugi-san is really going to...
Oh crap...!
Otogi!
Stop saying Yugi is gonna lose over and over again!
Stop worrying Shizuka-chan!
N-No, I just...
Big brother!
Yugi... show me the form of a True Duelist!
This is bad, big brother...
If this keeps up, Yugi's in real trouble!
So Yugi's Battle Phase has been completely sealed away...
Will he have to waste his remaining turns,
and simply wait for "death" to come?!
No! Yugi will turn this situation around!
This isn't enough to break his Duelist's fighting spirit!
Yugi, you're finished!
My Occult Combo has no weaknesses!
Think...!
There must be something I can do...
My problem is the Onryou that keeps possessing my Monsters...
Unless I can get rid of the Onryou, I can't stop his Occult Combo.
But how do I fight an enemy I can't see?
What's wrong, Yugi?
You can surrender if you want to!
The Onryou becomes an Equipment Card on its opponent's Monsters...
Equipment Card...!
There's still a way!
I set two Reverse Cards!
So you still continue on with your futile strategies,
even when the certainty of death awaits you?!
Yeah!
No matter what happens in a Duel, I will always survive that one turn!
And I believe that the next turn always brings new possibilities!
Don't make me laugh!
There are no "new possibilities"!
Turn over!!
I activate the Oujia Board's Effect!
The third letter...!
Now, what're you gonna do, Yugi?
You won't be laughing anymore after I'm done with you!
My turn!
I Summon Souls of the Forgotten!
I sacrifice you in order to maintain Dark Sanctuary!
Look at you, still standing on the brink of death...
In just two turns, I'll see the distorted look of fear on your face!
Turn end!
You sure have gotten full of yourself.
But don't you think you'd be safer keeping that superego of yours in check?
What'd you just say?!
Bakura... In my next two turns,
I will crush your Occult Combo!
So you finally figured out how to strike back, Yugi!
See, look at that!
I knew Yugi'd find a way outta this!
Yugi, I want to witness how you manage to get out of this with my own two eyes!
My turn!
Draw!
You're gonna crush my Occult Combo in just two turns, you said?
Just give the tough-guy act up already.
Aren't you the one who's getting full of himself, Yugi?!
Each new card holds a new possibility!
A Duelist has as many possibilities as they have cards in their hand!
And this is one of them!
Trap Card!
Collected Power!
Every Equipment Card on the field is now equipped with Kuriboh!
Collected Power gathers every single Equipment Card on the field
and equips it to one selected Monster on the field.
So by doing that, the Equipment Magic Card attached to Black Magician Girl,
Spellbook of Black Magic, is transfered to Kuriboh...
But that's not all!
You said this yourself, right?
That when the Onryou possesses a Monster, it becomes an Equipment Card.
Although I myself cannot see the form of this hateful spirit,
the Effect of Collected Power forces the Onryou to possess Kuriboh!
So he could do that...?!
And the Magic Card...
Exorcism!
It targets all Demon-type Monsters on the field and destroys them!
And the Onryou attached to my Kuriboh is a Demon-type!
Both the Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary
and the Kuriboh it possesses are destroyed simultaneously!
I wouldn't get too cocky if I were you, Yugi!
It's not as if you've completely broken my Occult Combo or anything!
Don't you worry, Bakura!
My turn isn't done yet!
He's still got one reverse card on the field!
Great! Go get 'im, Yugi!
Yugi! You can do it!
It seems he's found a major weak point in your Occult Combo.
Weak point?
I know what Yugi's reverse card is.
Get lost.
Or I'll kill you!
Go for it.
It's true your Occult Combo is close to flawless,
and you've done quite well covering up Dark Sanctuary's major draw back.
But the problem at hand is the activation conditions of Dark Sanctuary itself.
What did you say?
In order to activate Dark Sanctuary,
Dark Necrofear must be in the Graveyard at all costs.
So, if Dark Sanctuary were to suddenly return to the field,
Dark Sanctuary's Effect would disappear!
I'm pretty sure I need not say more for you to realize what his reverse card is.
Resurrection of the Dead.
Right.
It's Resurrection of the Dead!
Bakura!
I'm going to destroy your Occult Combo!
The Magic Card Resurrection of the Dead!
Dark Necrofear revives!
Now that Dark Necrofear has been brought back from the dead,
the Effect of Dark Sanctuary disappears!
Shit...!
Now you are no longer permitted extra spaces on your Duel Disk,
and you return to the normal rules of only being allowed five Magic or Trap Cards on the field!
I've only got one space left...!
And now I can directly attack you with this guy!
Dark Necrofear!
"Prey for Death" Gaze!!
Now my turn is over!
Ouija Board's Effect activates!
"D-E-A-T..."
You've gathered four letters of the word "death".
But you'll never get to play the last letter!
I've got no spot left to play the final piece!
In order to complete the message of "death",
you've got no other choice than to remove The Dark Door!
But the moment you even try,
I'll attack you with all of my Monsters at once!
Your Occult Combo will be destroyed in one turn!
I don't have any Monsters on the field...
If Yugi attacks me with all three of his Monsters right now...
I'll lose!
Not... possible...!
Looks like this match is decided.
Damn right!
Big brother?
Ryo Bakura...
You're qualified to be Yugi's opponent.
Looks like you're at your rope's end.
Silence.
Well, I may have a trick or two left up my sleeves...
Shut up!
I don't need your advice anymore!
Disappear already!!
There's no way I am gonna lose!
I'll just have to draw a card that'll turn this situation around!
Card draw!
That's far enough, Yugi!
So long as I have this card, you can't stop my Occult Combo!
What?!
Does Bakura really still have a strategy left?!
He just doesn't know when to give up!
Is he just bluffing?!
Just what card did he draw...?
"Preview"
Yugi has succeeded in sealing Bakura-kun's Occult Combo.
But Bakura-kun uses another strategy to bring Dark Sanctuary back to the field!
So that means the final letter to the "Death" message can be completed,
and Yugi'll lose!
In that case, he's got no choice but to draw out that card this turn!
Please come!
God Card!
Next time!
"Smash the Darkness - God Attacks!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise