Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Despite Kaiba's heartless attack against my Partner and the other Mirror Knights,
we just ended up facing Orichalcos Shunoros in their place!
And now that Kaiba has fallen...
...I am fighting this battle all alone...
With all three Barriers of Orichalcos on the field,
as well as Orichalcos Shunoros...!
I'm not sure how I should fight them!
What?!
I'm a cursed king?!
"Revive!
The Three Legendary Warriors"
You're saying that my existence is what will destroy the world?!
Nameless Pharaoh, your cursed spirit has already gained control over the darkness in your heart.
You are an abominable king whom has resurrected in order to lead this world to its demise!
Wh-What is this place?!
The last thing I remember is...
I was being used as Dartz's Monster...
Then Kaiba's Mirror Force Dragon...
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi!
That you, Yugi?!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi boy!
Jounouchi boy!
-Pegasus!
I certainly never imagined we would reunite in such a way as this!
If you're here, then that means...
Hey! Get it together, you gu-
The heck? It's like all the strength's leavin' my body.
It's that thing!
That thing's been draining our strength!
What is it?
Maybe... it is the god Dartz spoke of offering us to.
C-Come again?!
We gotta get outta here somehow!
The only way we'll make it out of here is if Dartz is defeated.
Oh yeah, Kaiba...
What the heck's he doing here, anyway?
He didn't...!
Kaiba-kun arrived here shortly after we did.
That means my other self is fighting Dartz alone.
He's facing Dartz all alone?
But I believe in him!
That my other self will beat Dartz.
And that he'll rescue us.
But before we disappeared from the Duel, he had close to 20000 Life Points.
And he had the three barriers of the Orichalcos.
There is still hope!
He has the nameless card I entrusted to him.
If he were to use that power...
Nameless card...?
Correct.
In the past, in order to create a variety of Duel Monsters cards...
...I traveled all around the world.
Wherein, I heard tale of the three dragons said to exist among the Duel Monsters.
These dragons, whose names were lost ages ago after a massive conflict,
now sleep among the Duel Monsters undisturbed.
Oh, what a transient yet mysterious existence they hold!
I tried tapping into my imagination...
And I came up with a hypothesis.
A hypothesis?
Yes indeed!
These dragons are merely their temporary forms.
Their true forms were sealed away by the King of Darkness,
and they took on the form of dragons.
The nameless dragons are their temporary forms?
It is certainly inconceivable for those who view life through the facts of our world's history.
However, the microscopic world exists unseen by the naked eye.
As does the dark void of the universe.
And with it, existence mankind can only fathom.
When it is impossible to truly see,
humans are capable of creating an entire world of possibility through their imaginations!
This unlimited potential that can alter the future...
That is what we call imagination!
I get it! Using our imaginations...
...we can create our own world within our souls that will cast away the darkness in our hearts!
The nameless Pharaoh is one of the Chosen Duelists.
I have faith that he will discover the power of that card!
Dartz! I won't be fooled by your words!
I swore to Black Magician Girl and my partner...
Ironheart and Kris also gave me a mission!
"Mission," you say?
Such a thing never existed from the beginning!
Your only mission is to become
one of the gears of destiny!
Gears of destiny?
Yes. The Duel Monsters and your comrades...
As well as my father and my daughter.
None of them realized that you are the reason behind the world's destruction.
And they blindly put their hopes in you!
The vision you saw!
You are the only one who could recall the conflict that took place 10,000 years ago.
Similarly, disaster struck once more 3,000 years ago in Ancient Egypt.
So you're saying the events I saw were caused by my very existence?!
I'm saying you held no meaning from the very start.
It's a lie... It's a lie!
I won't believe such nonsense!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
I draw two cards from my deck!
I Summon Retrained Elf Swordsman in Defense Position!
For now, I have to withstand his attacks...
I can't come even close to striking Orichalcos Shunoros!
I place an additional reverse card!
That finishes my turn!
Then it is my turn!
I activate the effects of Orichalcos Deuteros!
He's got 20000 Life!
Orichalcos Dexia's Attack Power will always rise 300 points higher than the opponent.
If this attack is able to pass through your Wall Monsters...
...you will lose all the Life you possess!
Orichalcos Dexia!
Attack the Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Trap, activate! Soul Shield!
By cutting my Life Points in half with this card,
I am able to negate the Monster's attack and end the battle!
Such reluctance, Nameless Pharaoh.
However, you had best look around you.
All the comrades that support you have fallen.
The bond you believe in so much no longer exists!
What point is there in suffering so much by yourself?
And it would be in your best interest to carefully examine the situation of this Duel!
Do you really believe you hold any hope of victory the way you are now?
He's got 20000 Life...
He's got the invincible Orichalcos Shunoros on the field...
Along with the three Barriers of Orichalcos...
My hope of victory has already...
Face reality.
You are nothing more than a cursed soul.
That is the truth.
What merit could getting back such unsightly memories possibly hold?
The labyrinth in your heart...
Even if you were to open that meaningless door and regain your lost memories...
...all that would await you is horror and tragedy!
Nameless Pharaoh... Your pain and your worries...
Feelings that you have felt over the span of endless time...
I alone am the only one capable of understanding your suffering.
The very least you can do is put an end to your fate with your very own hands.
Now...
If I just raise my hand, that fate...
Put an end to all of it.
Bring your existence back to nil!
I'm... nil?
Do you not wish to join your friends?
Kaiba...
Jounouchi-kun...
Partner...
That's right... I used to be nil...
Simply trapped within the Millennium Puzzle...
I am nothing...
Null, from the very beginning...
And if I lose them, I have nothing left...
That is why I have to vanish...
O Nameless Pharaoh...
Disappear!
Surround him, Barrier of Orichalcos!
It is over.
Disappear...?
I'm going to...?
I've got nothing... left within me...
What in the...?!
Impossible...!
Past memories... My body...
Does someone like me who holds no existence have it...?
Something in my heart that can never be erased...
You have something like that...?
I see... I never noticed it...
Deep within my heart...
Among the bonds I've woven with my friends...
There's a vessel of memories....
That is my everything...
I am not nil...
As long as I still have the vessel inside of me...
No matter how many times it takes... I can still be reborn!
Dartz, allow me to answer you...
Why is it that I...
After losing everything, why did I cross over 3,000 years of time?
Why was I brought back into this world?
It's because... I was revived in order to protect my friends...
...as well as to defeat you and change the future of the world in the process!
What did you just say?!
My turn! Draw!!
This is the nameless card...!
I can feel it... In my current state, I can feel the hidden powers of this card!
I believe!
From now on, I believe in the vision of the future I hold with my friends!
Grant me your strength!
Legend of Hearts!!
I pay 1000 Life Points and offer up a Warrior-Type Monster I have on the field!
Who has called us?
Us souls still a slumber.
You call us into battle?
My name is Timaeus!
My name is Critias!
My name is Hermos!
Let our power fill this place with light!
That is the true form
of the nameless dragons?!
This cannot be! The Barrier of Orichalcos was...!
Our bonds are absolute!
A barrier of darkness shall not work!
You are the one who gave me this wound!
I am going to pay you back!
Dartz!
I have now eliminated your untouchable barrier!
Timaeus! Attack Orichalcos Aristeros!
The Legendary Knights!
Critias!
Hermos!
And I'll now end my turn.
Willingly injuring your own Life...
In order to lower Shunoros' Attack Power.
However, your Life is nothing but a flickering light in the wind.
This does not change the fact that my next attack will kill you.
My turn!
Draw!
Orichalcos Shunoros! Advance and attack Critias!
Photon Ring!
I activate the Special Effect of Critias!
He can absorb the effects of every Trap Card used throughout this Duel!
What?!
The card Critias has absorbed is...
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Critias will reflect the attack sent at him towards every one of the opponent's Monsters!
Wisdom Sword!!
To think you would manage to defeat Shunoros...
However...
What?!
Evil God Gē.
This is the strongest servant I have.
The very moment Orichalcos Shunoros' Attack Power reaches zero...
I can give up 10000 of my Life Points as well as every card in my hand in order to Special Summon it.
Your Life Points...
My Life is in turn eliminated.
And as soon as my servant is destroyed, I automatically accept defeat.
However, its Attack Power is...
Its Attack Power... reached infinity!
There was never any hope for the likes of yourself to defeat me from the very start.
So, Nameless Pharaoh...
Draw your final card!
Is there... even a way to defeat that Monster?
But...
My deck... My Monsters... I will believe in you all!
It's my turn! Draw!
Black Magician Girl...
Master!
Both us Duel Monster's world and your world...
Master, you are the only one capable of saving both of our worlds!
The promise I made that day... I will uphold it no matter what!
I set one card face-down!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I discard the first ten cards in my deck in order to invoke the Evil God Gē's attack!
Infinity End!!
Timaeus!
This puts an end to everything.
And the beginning of a new history.
Your cursed soul... now belongs to my God!
What?!
Not possible! Your Life...!
A pity for you. I just activated a Trap Card in that attack just now.
Activated Relay Soul, to be more precise.
When my Life Points reach zero, Relay Soul Summons a Monster from my hand.
It's a card that pits the end of this Duel with the selected Monster.
If Black Magician Girl is destroyed, I automatically lose.
Now the both of us are in the same situation in this Duel.
Black Magician Girl...
My soul is now a part of yours!
Dartz! This begins the real battle!
Humph. Nameless Pharaoh...
Do you truly believe such a level of strength is capable of besting me?
The power of infinity lies within my Serpent God Gē, after all.
I won't be affected by your words any longer!
I believe in the bonds I hold with my Monsters!
That bold front of yours shall end there, Nameless Pharaoh.
Magic Card, activate!
Impact Revive!
This card revives a Monster destroyed this turn and increases their Attack Power by 500 points.
I shall choose to place it on the opponent's field!
You... revived Timaeus?
The Legendary Knights are nothing more than meaningless beings when faced with infinite Attack Power.
And as the cost of this effect, I am permitted to enter the Battle Phase once again this turn!
What!?
I send ten cards from the top of my deck into the Cemetery!
Grant me your power one more time!
Serpent God Gē!!
Infinity End!!
Vanish from this realm, Black Magician Girl!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
The three nameless dragons...
So their true forms were the Legendary Knights, huh?
Shunoros was beaten. So this is as far as Dartz-
So we thought, but he still had a hidden trump!
Plus, it's a Monster with infinite Attack Points!
How can he defeat it?
Yugi left his Life with Black Magician Girl against the Serpent God Gē!
What will be Yugi and the world's fate?!
Next time!
"Infinite Attack Power: Serpent God Gē"
Duel standby!