Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Trap of Revenge:
Reckless! Paracide"
Jounouchi-kun!
Yo, Yugi!
Mai's here too?
Hi~!
Yo!
Still pressing on, right?
Of course!
If you have time to worry about others, worry about yourself!
Don't say that to me.
You got 4 already?!
As expected of Mai-san!
I've got 3.
So Jounouchi-kun's got 2?
Out of the three of us, I'm still the lowest~
Many of the duelists should have been weeded out by now.
We're down to half now, huh?
We've got a ways until the Finals, so we can't just sit around here wasting time.
I know that!
Then I'm gonna go search for more prey!
Guys, don't disappear before the Finals now.
Yeah!
Let's meet in the Finals!
Malik holds one of the God Cards...
I'm sure to run into him...
Eh?! Yugi's gone already?!
Ah! He was in a rush!
Geez! It's your fault we missed him Honda!
No~ I just was talking to Shizuka-chan on the phone~
I was just trying to make her feel comfortable!
Ain't it the opposite?
Now I'll have to search all over again~
Alright! It'll be easier if I come along and help you look.
Now then, if I wanna become a true duelist,
I have to battle the right person...
I should search for...
There's no one good I can think of...
Um, Big brother!
What's up?
Um, please give me your autograph!
You're a Battle City duelist, right?
I see! He must think I'm famous!
You really want my autograph?
Yeah! I'm gathering signatures from everyone all over the streets!
That way, if one of them wins, it'll be worth a lot!
Oh well~ So I mistook him as one of my fans~?
That duel disk is so cool!
Ain't it?
This is for special ranking duelists only.
Hey Big brother, can you let me try it on for a few minutes?
Isn't it fine?
I beg you!
No helping it.
Consider this fanservice.
Here.
Cool~!
Take good care of it~
That's more important than my life,
a duelist's soul!
Oi! Hey!
You jerk!
Wait~!
Where'd he go?
We've been looking for a while,
but Domino City is rather large.
But of course.
Hey!
Jounouchi!
Why's he chasing someone?
Wait!
The duel disk?!
Hold it!
Let me go!
Honda!
What the hell were you doing?!
That's what I'd like to hear from this brat!
I'm very sorry.
In truth, I was trying to qualify.
Qualify?
I was ready to duel in this tournament, but I lost my rare card.
What'd ya say?
It was taken from me.
So I was trying to qualify in order to duel him.
Even with just reasons, you can't just go and steal someone's duel disk.
That makes you the same as him.
I'm very sorry.
But who did such a rotten thing?
Uh, he had a head shaped like a beetle...
was short...
had bug-like eyes...
and had a weird laugh like "hya hya hya!".
Insector Haga?!
That scum's still doing stuff like this?!
Unforgivable...!
I've decided!
My next opponent is Insector Haga!
I'm gonna go look for him!
Yeah!
Jounouchi!
Wait!
See ya!
You can do it, Big brother!
So everything went according to plan?
Yes!
He's completely fallen for my lies!
Now Jounouchi will fall into my web.
His deck...
Now then, Haga-san, please give me the rare card you promised me!
Ah! That's right~!
Here.
Thanks!
Isn't this just Roachball?!
This isn't a rare card!
I wouldn't waste a rare card on the likes of you.
N-No way...!
Then...
I'll give you this instead!
I'll defeat Jounouchi first and then head to Yugi.
I'll be sure to pay you back for what you did to me at Duelist Kingdom!
With my Super Insect Deck!
Kenta-kun! Where'd you go?!
Shizuka-chan, did anyone come in here just now?
What's wrong?
Kenta-kun refused to go to school and is running away from everyone.
Refused to go to school?
I don't know the details, but he sure is a troublesome kid.
It's okay to come out now.
You found me?
I could hear your breathing.
But why didn't you say anything?
We should help each other in times of pain, right?
And besides, I'm not too fond of that nurse myself.
Then I'll do anything for my Big sister!
What'd ya need?
Let's see...
Then can you read to me what it says on the screen over there?
This is the Battle City homepage?
My Big brother is participating in it.
Shit! Where the hell did that Haga bastard go?!
He's not here?
It's been a while, Jounouchi-kun.
So you finally showed yourself, Insector Haga!
I was looking forward to meeting with you.
You jerk! You stole that kid's rare card, didn't you?!
He went and said that...?
If you aren't sorry about it, I'll make you feel sorry.
Wait Honda!
I'll settle this with a duel!
Hold it, Jounouchi!
Don't fight with this guy!
This guy's a cheater who threw Yugi's cards into the sea!
It's an honor to be remembered by such a cute girl like you.
How 'bout it Jounouchi?
We fight betting 2 Puzzle Cards and our rare cards.
2?
So if Jounouchi loses, he'll be disqualified...?
Don't do it, Jounouchi!
What's wrong?
You gonna run?
I know!
Jounouchi!
This guy lost to Yugi in Duelist Kingdom.
But the fact that he's the Japan National Champion hasn't changed.
He's not a bad opponent at all!
No matter!
Your deck has already been manipulated!
If a duelist should meet another in this city...
They must fight in Battle City!
Duel!
My turn first!
Swordsman of Landstar in Attack Mode!
I'll also set 1 card!
Turn end!
What's up with that weak-looking monster?
He's more than enough to deal with an insect like you!
Then it's my turn.
Come out, Dragonfly!
Take apart Jounouchi's monster!
Set Card activate!
Shield in the Left Hand, Sword in the Right Hand!
This reverses the situation!
Dragonfly is beaten!
How's that?!
Just kidding!
When Dragonfly is sent to the Graveyard,
his Effect allows me to Special
Summon a WIND-type monster with 1500 Attack or less!
Even with my Life reduced, it's far too early to think you've beaten me.
Uh, his name's Jounouchi Katusya, right?
That's right.
He's dueling with Japan's National Champion right now!
But I'm sure he'll be fine.
Big brother was the second place runner-up in Duelist Kingdom.
Really?
Weird...
It says here he's only a Level 2 and a nobody...
My turn!
If I don't do something, Swordsman of Landstar will be done in next turn...
What's wrong?
Don't tell me you've played all your hand's best already.
Jounouchi...
Just kidding!
I sacrifice Swordsman of Landstar...
in order to Summon Android - Psycho Shocker!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
2400 Attack Points...?!
Not bad, Jounouchi!
Alright!
That's the way!
My turn.
A monster in Defense Mode!
Turn over.
Alright, let's end this!
Psycho Shocker, annihilate that card!
What?!
You fell for it!
Any monster leeched by Kiseitai
will cause my Life Points to increase by half your monster's Attack each turn!
What'd you say?!
Disgusting!
I'll show you the terror of my Super Insect Deck!
On my turn I'll place a monster in Defense Mode and end my turn.
My turn!
I'll take 1200 points!
Shit!
Psycho Shocker, attack!
Thanks!
What?!
Haga's Life just...!
When Skull-Mark Ladybug is sent to the Graveyard,
I receive 500 of my Life!
Now my Life is higher than yours!
His Insects are sure tricky monsters when used right...
It seems Insector Haga has brought out their true strength.
My turn!
A monster in Defense Mode!
Now, with that it's your turn.
My Life goes up!
Defense Mode again...?!
If I fall victim to another weird Effect,
I'll just waste this turn and Haga's Life may increase even further...!
Hey, who's winning?
Well.... it looks like Big brother is losing.
I see...
Big brother sure is brave, fighting against such an opponent...
But I'm certain Big brother chose this match on purpose.
Why?
Big brother's just like that.
He enjoys a new challenge and pushing his limits.
It's useless.
There's no use in trying to face something you can't succeed in.
No use.
But Big brother believes in a fair and square fight.
Believe in your own power.
My turn!
I Summon Jet Black Soldier Panther Warrior!
Panther Warrior can't attack unless I sacrifice a monster on the field!
So then I'll do this!
Panther Warrior!
Sacrifice Psycho Shocker and attack!
Alright!
Now Haga's Life is wide open!
I see, good thinking Jounouchi.
So you've got quite the warriors now, do you?
But that was hardly enough to reduce my Life.
And the monster you rejoiced in defeating
has the Effect to let me play another monster from my hand.
I'll Summon Larvae Moth!
Shit...! Now he's got a monster on his field again...!
You can squash them and squash them again, but they'll continue to come back!
That's the strongest aspect of an Insect-based deck!
I Equip Larvae Moth with Cocoon of Evolution!
This thing...!
That's right!
I failed to evolve it to its final level back in Duelist Kingdom,
but this time I'll show you!
The fully evolved and most powerful stage of the Ultimate Great Moth!
I knew it was useless!
This National Champ is too strong!
His card is no doubt stronger than all of big brother's cards!
But he hasn't lost yet.
Big sister, you don't know a thing about cards, do you?!
There's no way he can win!
Jounouchi, you have just 5 turns until the birth of Ultimate Great Moth.
I have to do something before that...!
It's a shame, Jounouchi.
You can do nothing to stop it from evolving.
You lost before the duel even started!
What?!
Take this!
The Magic Card Reckless Parasite!
This card brings out the Parasite Paracide card that lies in your deck.
W-What are you talking about?!
I don't have a card like that in my deck...!
What?!
Parasite Paracide will leech onto every monster you Summon,
and transform them.
What's that?!
Jounouchi!
Why do you have a card in your deck that helps the opponent?!
Impossible!
I'd remember putting a card like that in my deck...!
It couldn't be...!
You jerk! You used that kid!
A good strategist prepares for a fight long before it begins.
That's foul play!
That's dirty!
Is it?
Isn't it a duelist's job to check their deck before entering a duel?
You jerk...!
Now every monster on your field will become Insect monsters!
I'll then set another card face-down and complete my turn!
I'll pay you back for that cheap move!
My card may be infected, but its Attack and Defense haven't changed!
Oh right!
I forgot to mention this, but you can't sacrifice infected monsters.
What!?
You can no longer Summon high-level monsters,
and Panther Warrior can't attack without having a sacrifice first!
Then I Summon Little-Winguard!
You've just increased the number of infected creatures on your field!
No!
I'll use Little-Winguard to attack Cocoon of Evolution!
You're gonna try and attack the 2000 Defense Cocoon of Evolution with that monster?
Take a closer look at your field!
D-Damn it...!
I left Cocoon of Evolution in Attack Mode!
That's right!
Go on and attack the 0 Attack Cocoon of Evolution, Little-Winguard!
Stop it!
Kidding again!
Reverse card open!
The Continuous Magic Card Insect Barrier!
I told you!
All of your monsters have become Insect-type monsters!
In other words, as long as this card is in play, you can't attack me!
What did you say?!
That means even if Jounouchi can play high-level monsters, they can't attack!
Now Jounouchi's been completely cut off from attacking.
What incredible strategies that young boy has...
Jounouchi, the Ultimate Great Moth fully evolves in just 4 turns...
Amazing...
He's really gonna Summon the Great Moth!
Is this Great Moth really that strong?
It's not just strong, it's probably one of the strongest monsters there is!
I see...
I knew it was no use.
But...
It's not that easy to just believe in yourself...
Big brother...
Now then, let's not just sit and wait for the evolution to be complete.
Maybe I should work on reducing your Life while I wait for the Great Moth to appear?
Alright!
Even if he reduces my Life, the infected monsters on my field will be destroyed...!
If Paracide disappears, I may still have a chance...
Leghul in Attack Mode!
Direct Attack!
A direct hit...?!
Leghul can directly attack the players.
For you to think I would actually destroy my own parasite...
There's no way I'd do such a thing.
I switch all my monsters to Defense Mode and end my turn!
What a useless struggle!
Now let's begin the final count down!
Great Moth will evolve in just 3 more turns!
But before that...!
Leghul!
Direct Attack!
Just 2 turns!
Leghul, Direct Attack!
Does it hurt you?
Wanna stop now before the Great Moth is Summoned?
Hey you!
Stop trying to discourage him!
Knock it off, Honda!
Yugi taught me something in his fight...
That no matter what kind of strategy his opponent uses,
A true duelist must play fairly...
And he win fairly!
Yugi!
I'll show you I can become a true duelist in this Battle City!
I play a monster in Defense Mode!
And I then place a set card, finishing it!
Wyvern Paracide, eh?
So you gonna run?
It doesn't matter!
I'll continue onward until my Life hits 0!
I haven't lost to you yet!
You sure don't know when to quit!
I'll show you that you have no hope left!
Now it's my turn!
Come forth, Ultimate Great Moth!
Witness this ultimate form!
This is the Ultimate...?
Great Moth...!
The Ultimate Great Moth finally makes an appearance!
But Jounouchi can't Summon a new powerful monster because of Paracide!
Just how can he fight?
Ah! The Dice Cards!
So those still work? Annihilate Great Moth!
We want to celebrate but...
But suddenly a new strong Insect monster, Insect Queen appears...!
Don't give up, Jounouchi!
Don't give up until you fulfill your promise with Yugi!
Next time!
Gearfried the Iron Knight
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...