Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Capturing the God Card"
Hey, Mai's acting really weird up there...
Mai-san! Hang in there!
Mai-san, you can do it!
I hear someone calling me...!
Who...?! Who are you...?!
Mai-san...
Is Mai seeing some kind of illusion?
There's no way you fools could understand what this woman is suffering from.
I'll make her suffer a terrifying loneliness beyond anything she's ever felt!
My turn!
I set a card on the field!
Come forth, Executioner Makyura!
Attack Mode!
Furthermore...
I play a Magic Card
with Executioner Makyura!
I attach the Black Pendant to it!
This card increases my Monster's Attack Power by 500 points...
Now Malik's Monster has higher Attack Points...!
He's going to attack me...!
The Dark Games are a world of illusions and phantasms...
And only those chosen can see it...
Mai Kujaku...
I'll let you enjoy the World of Darkness!
Executioner Makyura attacks!
Trap Card, open!
Amazoness Archers!
This Trap Card keeps your enemy's Monsters from moving,
and lowers its Attack Value by 500 points!
Very smart...
Now the Ally-Slaying Swordmistress counterattacks!
Dance of Betrayal!!
You, huh...?
What's wrong?
Who... was that just now...?
That's right.
He just vanished from my memory.
Now I do wonder
who he could have been...
But whoever it was that disappeared,
I could care less either way.
I've loved only the
darkness since I was a child.
He's...
Oh yeah.
The Black Pendant's Effect states that when the Monster it is attached to is sent to the Graveyard,
the opposing player receives 500 points worth of damage.
My turn has indeed come to an end,
but Executioner Makyura
has a Special Ability.
When it's defeated,
I can instantly activate a Trap Card from my hand.
I shall activate this
Trap Card from my hand!
Rope of Life!
This card selects one of my Monsters destroyed this turn.
It revives it with 800 extra Attack Points
and allows it to attack again!
Wh-What did you just say?!
Go, Executioner Makyura!
Swords of Judgment!!
A befitting end for someone who betrays her allies.
Jounouchi!!
I sure nailed a nice card.
She contained the memories of one of your friends, didn't she?
Jounouchi's going to
disappear from my mind...
From within me...
My parents died when I was young.
So I lived alone
in my deceased parents' house.
That's right...
I ended up associating
with terrible people...
No matter how much I wished for it, there was always something I couldn't achieve.
It was something I longed for ever since I was a child.
And then I met the Harpies.
The Harpies made themselves stronger
by wearing armor and wielding weapons.
I lived in a similar way.
I screamed this
from the depths of my soul.
But deep down, I lived alone and cried deep within my heart.
And eventually those guys appeared before me.
After meeting them...
After meeting Jounouchi...
I slowly began to trust people.
I was no longer alone...!
I had friends that believed in me!
And now all of that...
...is disappearing right in front of me!
I'll... be lonely again...
That's it!
You won't be able to remember a thing!
You'll wonder the dark in loneliness and descend into true darkness!
Now disappear!!
Mai!
What's wrong?!
Yugi, just what the
hell is happening to Mai?!
Most likely... Malik is erasing the memory of Mai's friends.
That's impossible!
Mai! Can you hear me, Mai?!
Mai! You forgot me?!
Once a Dark Game begins...
...you usually can't interfere with it.
But I can!
Mai!
Yu...gi...?
Yugi! You bastard!!
Don't be confused by Malik's illusions!
Illusions?
So I'm... just imaging this loneliness?
That's right.
In a Dark Game, willpower is the key to success!
These illusions are created by the fear and terror in your heart!
Y-Yugi...!
I feel... like I've lost something important to me...
Something I cherished... deep within my heart...
Mai!
Mai! Don't give up!
That voice...!
I'm not sure who it belongs to,
but it warms my heart...
It's so warm...
Mai, you have to win!
If you win this Dark Game, Malik's illusion will disappear!
Don't ever let
the light in your heart go out!
Take back the memories you've lost!
Yugi...!
Mai, the rest is up to you.
Yugi...
Keep trying, Mai!
We're with you!
That voice again...
It's supporting me...
It's... important to me...
Damn that Yugi...
Using his Millennium Puzzle to interfere with the Dark Game...
Has this woman
regained all of her memories?
Either way, having the spirit to fight against me like this...
Thanks, Yugi...
Don't worry...
My fighting spirit
doesn't break that easily!
I'll be taking back what you've stolen from me in this Duel!
That's if you defeat me...
My turn!
I won't let you
touch my memories again!
I play the Amazoness Chain Master in Attack Mode!
Then I play a reverse card
and end my turn!
His Executioner Makyura has enough Attack Points to beat my Amazoness Chain Master...
He should attack right away...
Unless he's afraid of my reverse card...
It's my turn...
But the Trap I've set
isn't my reverse card...
It's the Amazoness Chain Master's Special Ability!
When Amazoness Chain Master goes to the Graveyard while in Attack Mode,
her "Brink of Death Chain Dance" ability is activated.
And by paying 1000 of my Life Points,
I can steal one card
from my opponent's deck!
I'll teach you over and over...
...that loneliness is not an illusion!
He's coming...!
My card is...
Holding Arms!
I'll use this to attack your Amazoness Chain Master!
500 Attack Points?!
And he's attacking me
with that Monster?!
Holding Arms captured the Amazoness?!
But why didn't it lose, since it has less Attack Points, big brother?
That Monster must have some sort of Special Ability...
This thing has the "Power of Invincibility" ability that renders it
unkillable against all opposing Monster's attacks for three turns.
Holding Arms doesn't hold enough Attack Points to defeat the Amazoness...
But...
It's more than enough
to keep it from moving!
And it'll be slowly tortured to death for three turns...
I wonder just how long it'll take before it passes on~?
Malik...!
Don't panic, Mai...
Otherwise your heart will fall into Malik's Power of Darkness again!
Malik! Stop this meaningless fight already!
No one can stop this now...
This game, that is...
Yugi, the moment this woman loses to me in this game,
she shall fall into a deep slumber!
It is not "meaningless"!
Torturing those little friends of yours...!
Lousy scum...!
Very nice, Yugi...!
Hate me! Say more!
I've been waiting to fight you for 1,000 years!
Let your anger reach out
and touch mine, Yugi!
You won't get away with this, Malik...!
Yugi!
Yugi, this is my fight!
Stay out of it!
I'm a Duelist!
I'll fight him till the end!
Yugi!
What does he mean Mai will fall into a deep slumber?!
That's... what a Dark Game is.
Dark... Game?
Reverse Card, open!
Magic Card! Burial Arm!
I'll bury one Monster with this Magic Card!
Isn't that a shame?
My Holding Arms is currently in Invincible State.
That Effect won't work on it.
Who said anything about
burying your Monster?
You aren't...
Amazoness Chain Master!
And since it wasn't beaten by you, my memory won't disappear!
Sending your own Monster to the grave...
However, the Amazoness Chain Master has a Special Ability!
Brink of Death Chain Dance!
I give up 1000 points from my Life!
To take one Monster from your deck!
What?
Right...
And the one I'm taking...
...is your God Card, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Yes!
You rule, Mai!
It's mine now!
Your God Card, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
You really think it'll go like you plan?
Your suffering will be legendary.
Now that sounds fun...
But before that,
you'll be dancing in Hell!
Yeah! You're awesome, Mai!
She must've been planning to steal Malik's God Card from his deck all along!
Good job, Mai!
Now that you've taken his God Card, Malik should be considerably weaker!
But can you really control the God Card you've so effortlessly stolen from me?
So God has switched sides?
Big brother, now we can't tell who'll win this Duel!
Malik said only those connected to the Millennium Items can control God Cards...
Will God obey this woman?
I guess we'll find the answer soon!
My turn!
Three sacrifices are required to Summon a god...
Malik has two Monsters on his field...
I don't have anything on my field...
So all I have to do is evade my enemy's attacks until I get three Monsters on the field!
That's the key to winning this!
Well then... Let's see what you can do.
Go, Mai!
If you Summon the god, you win!
Don't rush...
Be careful, Mai!
Show me God, Mai Kujaku!
I'll set two reverse cards on my field!
As well as Amazoness Hands-On Warrior!
Attack Position!
My turn's over!
Now just try and attack me!
This time I've got a trap waiting for you!
My turn!
Draw!
Malik discarded his entire hand earlier, so when he draws a card, he'll only have one.
This is your chance, Mai!
I'll attack Amazoness Hands-On Warrior with Executioner Makyura!
Go, Makyura!!
You fell for it!!
Magic Card, activate!
Amazoness Curse Master!
Thanks to this Magic Effect, our Monsters will switch Attack Points!
Amazoness Hands-On Warrior!
Counterattack Makyura!
Pandora, eh?
Be gone already.
Executioner Makyura goes down!
Alright!
Malik only has a little remaining Life, Mai!
It feels good...
...when an enemy falls into your trap!
Trap...?
That's right!
Trap Card!
Card of Last Will!
Card of Last Will?
Right!
When one of your Monster's Attack Points is increased,
you are permitted to draw from your deck until you hold five cards.
So Malik used this timing to replenish his hand...!
One more thing...
Executioner Makyura's Special Ability.
When Makyura is destroyed,
I can activate a Trap Card from my hand.
Dammit...!
I destroyed it thinking he didn't have a hand...!
I shall let you taste
even greater pain...
Trap Card, activate!
Torture Wheel!
Now I'll torture your Amazoness Hands-On Warrior to death!
The Torture Wheel will strip away 500 of your Life Points every turn.
I should thank you for trying to trap me!
What?!
I'll match Trap with Trap!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Dramatic Rescue!
This card allows me to take one trapped Monster back to my hand...
...and play another Monster Card from my hand in its place!
Is she going to use that card to...?!
You plan to call the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra to the field?
No! I know the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra's Attack Points are based on the total Attack Points
of the Monster used to Summon it.
So if I called it out using that method, Ra's Attack Power would be zero!
You're pretty clever...
But... there is a way!
For me to Summon the God Card!
How's Mai gonna get three sacrifices?
I rescue Amazoness Hands-On Warrior from the Torture Wheel,
and return her to my hand!
And I'll play this Monster based on Dramatic Rescue's Effect!
Harpie Lady Cyber Bondage!
This is it!
Mai's best trick!
And now it's my turn.
Please... let me Summon God!
I play the Magic Card Angel's Charity!
This card lets me draw three cards from my deck and discard two from my hand!
Now everything's all set.
I'll let you see it!
Me controlling God!
At last, God is...!
I see!
The combo Mai is after!
God now obeys me!
This is my trump card!
Magic Card, activate!
Kaleidoscope!
The Three Harpie Lady Sisters!
I forgot about that!
Way to go, Mai!
I then sacrifice my three Harpies...
...and Summon the
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Come forth, Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
Did you think you, of all people, could control God?
You don't realize...
That the god is
already controlling you!
Th-That's...!
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...?
What?!
Just what...?!
This... isn't possible...!
"Preview"
A huge sphere hovers over the ring.
Is that really Ra?
Then suddenly, the card set on Mai-san's disk
becomes covered with strange symbols...!
Only those who can read the text are able to control Ra?!
Malik begins to read the text...
...and Ra's control shifts to Malik!
It's changing form!
Next time!
"The Secret of the Hieratic Text"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise