Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
The effects of the Swords of Sealing Light have vanished!
Are you ready for this?!
I can feel it...
God's pulse being
emitted from my deck!
Draw!
God is in my hand!
Obelisk...
Death Gremlin! Direct Attack the player!
The future is infinite!
The past is merely a string of footsteps!
The stuff that happened long before my time in the past has nothing to do with me!
Ishizu, the same goes for the fact that you gave me a God Card!
But God's hand will
not bring you a path of victory...!
Listen carefully, Ishizu!
I won't be controlled by the future!
The road I walk myself...
That is what determines my future!
"One Attack Changes the Future"
Ishizu, remember this!
I didn't choose God...
God chose me!!
No, you are not chosen.
Your future states that you shall fall by Obelisk's hands.
That woman's in the
worst possible position,
But she looks like she doesn't care.
Maybe she does see the future
and that's why she's so calm?
How can that be?
I can't tell what Ishizu-san is planning...
Her strongest cards were dumped into the Graveyard!
Graveyard...
If Malik and Ishizu
are brother and sister...
Then Ishizu is also one
of the Tomb Guardians...
They protect the grave... protect...!
If this key word...
is also hidden in Ishizu's deck...
This turn, I'll push you even further into my trap!
Kaiba has dug his own grave...
And he'll suffer in that deep grave he's dug...
I'm going up
Reverse card, open!
Anti-Magic Virus Cannon, activate!
It can't be...!
Send her Magic Cards to the grave!
Ishizu, choose 10 of your Magic Cards
and put them in the Cemetery!
Now your deck has been completely destroyed!
Monsters and Magic...
You've lost nearly every basic requirement needed to Duel!
And yet you still try to claim I am destined to lose?!
I shall not take back my words.
I have already seen a vision of this happening.
What did you say?
You still intend to put up a bold front?
It's you who fell into a trap!
The trap of the Tomb Guardians!
What? The trap... of the Tomb Guardians...?
I shall reveal it right now...
Reverse card, open!
I activate the Trap Card,
Reversal of the Worlds of the Living and Dead!
Reversal of the Worlds of the Living and Dead?
I sacrifice 1000 points of my Life
to exchange the living cards in our decks with the deceased cards in our Cemeteries.
Exchange with the deceased cards in our Cemeteries...?
Nice. It's working great.
No way...! Big brother...!
Damn! Brother!
So this is what Ishizu was aiming for!
Kaiba's deck will die and go to the Graveyard...
and Ishizu's deck will revive!
For this purpose
Ishizu sent her cards to grave
one after another.
So scary...!
Now you know, Kaiba...
It's your deck
that was destroyed and killed!
Ishizu's Graveyard was filled with cards due to Kaiba's Deck Destruction...
And they were mostly
her main cards.
On the contrary, Kaiba only had six cards in the Graveyard...
In seven turns, Kaiba won't be able to draw a card and he'll lose!
It seems to be my turn again.
You lousy bitch...!
I draw a card and Summon Kelbek!
Kaiba's finished!
He can't turn this around with just six cards!
Ishizu-san really can see the future!
Otherwise, he wouldn't have lost this easily...
Kaiba...
I won't believe it...
Are you telling me
it's my future to lose?!
I set one card on the field.
I then end my turn.
Brother!
Mokuba!
Mokuba, has the analysis of
the card been completed?
Not yet...
but I was worried about you, big brother!
It's my turn!
That's Anti-Magic Virus Cannon!
I am not simply guessing right.
To me it's a future I experienced already.
You are free to use that card as you please.
Damn right I am!
Anti-Magic Virus Cannon!
At this moment, my Counter Trap activates!
Trap Card! Muko!!
Please throw away
the Virus Cannon.
She knows my entire deck...!
Brother...
Kaiba...
Next you'll draw the Deck Destruction Virus.
And of course, I won't allow you to add it to your hand.
This woman...
Turn end...
On the turn just now,
Kaiba's Death Gremlin
had higher Attack Points than Ishizu's Monster.
Why didn't he attack, Yugi?
Kaiba's trying to Summon Obelisk...
What did you say?
His God Card?
If he is, he must have that in his hand.
As long as she
gathers three monsters on her field...
I know what you're thinking, Seto...
The only means you have left...
...is the Magic Card, Cross Sacrifice.
You're waiting for me
to gather three monsters on the field.
To Summon the god that will lead to the road of destruction,
The Great War God Obelisk.
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Zolga!
Everything will lead
to your predestined loss.
Seto, you cannot defeat me.
So she's seeing the future after all...
Seeing the future of my failure...
Kaiba!!
I can see it!
Yugi...
I can see us battling one another on the road of battle!
Use our cards to explore that future!
That's a Duelist!
I can see it!
A future where me and you fight each other in Battle City!
Then wait for me, Yugi!
My turn is not over.
Zolga attacks the Death Gremlin!
Cape of Deadly Wind!!
Death Gremlin is beaten!
I'll then use Kelbek
to launch a direct attack on the player!
Damn you...!
I set a reverse card on the field! Turn end!
Ishizu's set card...
It must be a sure-kill Trap to destroy the Deck Destruction Virus!
I have to step in, knowing it's a trap...!
I'll endure this
humiliation and pay you back
by trampling you with my Obelisk!
My turn! Draw!
Trap Card activate! Muko!!
I knew it...!
Every method Kaiba-kun had has been completely ruined!
Because his deck was completely broken by Ishizu!
I guess this is what you call the worst-case scenario...
Kaiba, don't give up on your future!
My brother... My brother won't lose!
I still believe you can win, big brother!
Mokuba...
Cross Sacrifice...
It lets me sacrifice Monsters on the other player's side of the field.
Ishizu has two Monsters on the field...
On her next turn, the moment Ishizu Summons a third Monster...
I can let Obelisk descend via Cross Sacrifice!
I set a reverse card! Turn over!
Kaiba doesn't have any Wall Monsters on the field!
If Ishizu attacks again, he's done for!
That set card has to be Cross Sacrifice!
But Ishizu knows it's coming...
Cross Sacrifice...
This game will end on your next turn.
It is exactly the same as the vision I saw.
It's my turn!
Draw!
I set a reverse card on the field!
It doesn't matter what you play...
You better just put out a Monster!
Seto, this is the greatest trap you will ever fall in...
The Trap Card,
Bomb Held By a Tribute.
The moment this card
is placed on the field,
A bomb is planted inside the body of one of my Monsters...
A Monster that is Summoned using it as a sacrifice...
...will be destroyed
the moment it attacks!
Even if it is a god!
I'll then Summon another Monster!
Now there are enough sacrifices on Ishizu's field!
She sure is frightening...
My dear sister's morale has gotten even stronger...
Well, she'd haft to to get this far!
What if this is a trap as well?
If Ishizu already knew about Cross Sacrifice...
But I have to just depend on Obelisk!
Reverse card, activate!
Kelbek! Agido! Zolga!
Ishizu, I'll sacrifice your Monsters!
Reverse card, open!
Cross Sacrifice!
He fell for it!
I'll show you God!
Come forth! Great War God Obelisk!!
So you finally played it...
Good job! Brother!
Th-This is Kaiba's God Card?
The Great War God Obelisk?
On my next turn, God's fist will shatter your future!
Turn end...
Seto, when the Giant War God moves...
...your task is over...
It's my turn!
Now attack me!
Well, Ishizu?
Obelisk, the God of Destruction,
will crush you
and bring me victory!
My last reverse card is already in the Graveyard... It's an unseen trap...
A Trap that will activate when it's too late to stop it...
Seto, the Trap has already been activated.
Seto, when you sacrificed Kelbek, Agido and Zolga...
When you sacrificed
these three Monsters...
the unseen Trap is triggered!
And the destroyed Monster's Attack Power will strike you as well.
I caught a small glimpse...
...of what will happen the moment the trapped Obelisk attacks...
At that moment, just as the Millennium Tauk predicted,
you will be guided
to the path of failure.
Ishizu, you don't have a Wall Monster on the field to defend you.
You can surrender now
Yugi, will Kaiba-kun really win like that?
Yugi?
Can he really beat Ishizu with this attack?
Why did the Millennium Tauk Ishizu holds
show her a vision of Kaiba losing, then?
Yugi...
I have a bad feeling about this...
So how about it, Ishizu?
You ready to feel God's attack?
Right, there's no other way but to attack me with God.
Like the future I saw.
Go, God!!
Bomb Held By a Tribute...
This Trap will trigger the moment he attacks with Obelisk.
Great War God Obelisk! Attack!!
What?!
That's your future.
Now hurry and pull down the curtain of this act with your very own hands!
This match is over...
The moment
Kaiba declares an attack...
"Boom!" ...right?
My older sister truly is a fearsome opponent to be reckoned with...
Here goes! Great War God Obelisk!!
It's over...
Wh-What is this...?!
The Millennium Rod...!
Atta...
Kaiba stopped his attack!
What's wrong, Kaiba?!
Big brother?!
What... is this...?
This vision...!
What is this sadness
pounding in my chest...?
Why didn't he attack...?!
Is it possible that his memory is sealed within the Millennium Rod?!
Kaiba...!
It looked like... the Blue-Eyes White Dragon was on that palette!
Why...? Why did I see this vision?
What the hell do you want?!
Blue-Eyes...! What are you trying to tell me...?!
I-I'll... believe that vision I saw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Silent Death!
I revive a Monster from the Graveyard in Defense Mode!
I Summon Gadget Soldier!
Impossible! This isn't the future I saw!
In order to Summon the Blue-Eyes from my hand,
I require two sacrifices!
In which case...
You can't...!
That's right! I'll sacrifice God!!
What did he say?!
Is this guy serious?
Obelisk?!
He's sacrificing it...?!
My pride!
And my soul!!
I decide my future!
Obelisk! Gadget Soldier!
For my loyal servant,
you shall be sacrificed!
He sacrificed Obelisk...? God?!
Ishizu, I'll show you!
The embodiment of both my pride and soul, my loyal servant!
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
He changed... the future...!
Kaiba, what the hell did you see?!
Seto...
You really are the White Beast Handler!
Ishizu, in the vision of the future you supposedly saw....
...did the Blue-Eyes show up?!
It seems it didn't...
I lose.
It's my future!
Go! Blue-Eyes!!
Tear open the future!!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
I win! Ishizu!
The winner is
Seto-sama!!
Amazing...
I always knew you were the big brother I believed in!
You showed us all, Kaiba!
There's no engraved future for a Duelist!
But the one called the White Beast Handler on the stone tablet...
And that moment when the Millennium Rod began to glow...
Do the God Cards
really choose their wielders?
Just who are you...?
That was outstanding, Seto.
You have just proved you truly are a wielder of the God Cards.
But, why...?
Everyone has something they believe in... even deeper than in gods.
All I did was trust that.
Seto... I took something important from this Duel.
And that is the light of hope.
One not predicted in the future shown by the Millennium Tauk.
Even if I won, I only had a slight chance of saving Malik...
I bet that hope
and planned to step up with my life on the line...
To win in order to save my little brother...
Things have become interesting...
I lost, but I now believe that the future can be changed.
And the people gathered here
have to power to save Malik.
Seto, people can change the future.
People who allow themselves to be chained by the future will never see that light.
Brother!
The next time we meet, it'll be time to settle the score in our fight.
Yes.
The unseen future...
I would like to believe in this!
"Preview"
With Kaiba-kun's victory,
The four people rising to Semi-Finals
have gathered.
The Battle Ship is flying to the location of the net Dueling ground,
but this tournament has had way too many sacrifices!
Please tell us, Ishizu-san!
Why does Malik want
to take everyone's lives?
Ishizu-san starts to talk about
Malik's past
and the tragedy of the Ishtars.
Next time!
"The Truth of the Ishtars Revealed"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise