Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
It's finally the Final Match of the KC Grand Prix.
The match was supposed to be between Leon-kun and Sieg...
But Kaiba-kun suddenly appeared and disqualified Sieg!
And he arranged for himself to play in the Final instead.
Sieg attacks Kaiba-kun with a heart full of rivalry...
Just how will this Duel end?
"The Valkyries VS Blue-Eyes White Dragon"
Kaiba...
The curse of the Valkyries has just yet begun.
Due to the effects of Nibelung's Ring...
You can draw two cards.
If any Monster Cards are drawn, one must be discarded to the Cemetery.
Humph! What kind of curse is that?
My turn! Draw!
No Monster Card.
I place one reverse card and end my turn.
Hmph. Still, you cannot control the XYZ-Dragon Cannon you have on the field
due to the effect of Nibelung's Ring...
Is he going to Direct Attack again?
It is my turn! I draw!
Here I come, Kaiba!
I use Valkyrie Zwei to Direct Attack the player!
Reverse card, open! Attack Guidance Armor!
Your attack will be guided to the Monster equipped with this armor!
Reverse card, open!
Wotan's Judgment!
This card can be activated when a Monster attacks.
By exchanging a Magic Card in my hand with the topmost card on the deck,
the Battle Phase will be forced to end.
Such a pathetic tactic.
But thanks to you, I now have all the Goddesses of Fate in my hand.
Watch this!
Continuous Magic...
Goddess Urd's Verdict!
Goddess Verdandi's Guidance!
Goddess Skuld's Oracle!
Those three goddesses have appeared!
It's the Monster Erasing Combo that caused Jounouchi-kun to squirm...
A small trick to seal the opponent's hand...
A move fitting for a rat like you.
And you would be mistaken there.
As I am favored ever-so by fate, I am able to forgive your petty insults.
Goddess Skuld, the one that controls the future...
Show me the future that is to come!
Three Blue-Eyes White Dragons?!
Why are you looking so nervous?
Have you seen the fate that will destroy you?
That will be all for the moment! Do not attack him!
Due to the effect of Goddess Verdandi's Guidance,
I can know the present.
I'll guess the topmost card of your deck.
It's a Monster Card!
If I am right, please Summon the Monster in face-down Defense Position.
Worthless trick.
Then, Goddess Urd, the one who controls the past, will pass judgment on the card!
If guessed correctly, the card will be removed from the game.
Vorher! Begin your journey towards Valhalla!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Blue-Eyes...!
Disappeared!
Turn end.
Kaiba.
Your superb luck in drawing cards will become your downfall.
When the two Blue-Eyes are drawn later...
One will be sent to the Cemetery due to the effect of Nibelung's Ring.
And then, due to the Special Effect of Erste...
It will take on the same Attack Power of the Blue-Eyes in the Cemetery.
If Erste gets on the Fortune Chariot to attack...
...you will come to meet your end.
My turn!
Draw!
Kaiba, I am well aware.
Due to Nibelung's Ring's effect, the Monster Card you've drawn gets sent to the Cemetery!
Now I simply wait for him to declare his turn's end!
I activate Resurrection of the Dead from my hand!
What?!
Return from the Graveyard!
Come out, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
You did it, Brother!
It's finally appeared!
My Blue-Eyes won't let you do as you please!
Blue-Eyes, attack Valkyrie Zwei!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Fortune Chariot will be sacrificed in order to prevent Valkyrie Zwei's destruction!
You're nothing!
Now their Life Points are equal!
Turn end.
Hmph, what was that about being favored by fate?
If that were true, it would be on the side of Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
It's my turn! Draw!
I activate the Effect of the Three Goddesses!
Place the third card on the top of the deck.
That card is a Monster Card!
Be gone, Emerald Dragon!
Next from my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Gryphon's Feather Duster.
By destroying all the Magic and Trap Cards I have on my field,
I regain 500 Life Points for every card.
Just when Blue-Eyes managed to deal him some damage...
Next, I sacrifice Valkyrie Erste and Valkyrie Zwei...
To Summon Valkyrie Brunnhilde in Defense Position!
Turn end.
Kaiba, I hate to steal away your anticipation of the next card you'll draw...
But the first will be a Monster Card.
Hmph. My turn, draw!
Activate the effect of Nibelung's Ring.
Discard one Monster Card into the Cemetery!
Just one Blue-Eyes will be enough for me.
Go forth, Blue-Eyes!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Brunnhilde's Special Effect has been activated.
By losing 1000 Defense Points, she can avoid getting destroyed in battle.
I set one card and I end my turn.
Quite a pity it is, Kaiba.
But you can't use that effect once her Defense Power reaches zero.
Of course, I am aware of that.
It is my turn! I draw!
I change Valkyrie Brunnhilde into Attack Position!
The Attack Power of Brunnhilde increases by 300 points for every Dragon-Type Monster on the field!
In addition, from my hand, I activate the Equipment Magic, Enchanted Sword Nothung!
When this sword is equipped, all Dragon-Type Monsters on the opponent's field are removed from the game!
In just a second, Blue-Eyes got...!
Brother!
And the Attack Power of the Monster equipped with this card goes up by 400 points!
The power of Nothung does not end there.
It can destroy all Dragon-Type Monsters in battle and not take any damage at all.
Yes, this blade is known as the "Dragon-Slaying Sword"!
In addition, I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
I invoke Pegasus Wings!
This card can be activated when Fortune Chariot lies in the Cemetery.
A Monster with "Valkyrie" in its name
can Direct Attack the opposing player this turn with half its Attack Power!
But you should also know what the set card I've played is.
Even so, I'm still able to decrease your Life by 550 points.
Go, Brunnhilde!
Attack the player directly!
Reverse card, open!
Shrink!
Pay it no mind!
Brother!
The epilogue draws near.
Do you know how long I've waited for this moment?
Ever since the first day I laid my eyes on you.
Yes, I've wanted you to disappear ever since that day.
Even back when your father, Gozaburo Kaiba, was still the CEO...
As both our companies excelled in military trading,
my Schroeder Company was always under your pressure.
To my father, that was the greatest humiliation.
It was unreasonable for the supreme Schroeders
to be beaten by a company like yours.
As the successor, I wanted to surpass Kaiba Corporation...
No, I wanted to surpass the next successor, Seto Kaiba...
I not only wanted to surpass you, but I wanted to hand you a complete and utter defeat!
However, as my father began to compete against Kaiba Corporation again and again...
My Schroeder Company began to drop in performance day after day.
My father went crazy from the shock and fatigue and was consumed by it.
Keeping my father's name intact, I took control of the Schroeder Company as the new CEO.
The first thing I did was get rid of the military department...
And I entered into a new area of the gaming industry.
I was willing to ruin my own life
if it meant getting rid of the hatred I had for Kaiba Corporation.
But...
Herr Siegfried!
Kaiba Corporation made an announcement earlier.
Seto Kaiba has taken over Kaiba Corporation as the new CEO...
He announced that they would dissolve their military department,
and go fully into the game development industry!
Wha-?!
What did you just say?!
After that, in order to walk out of your shadow...
I devoted myself to game development day after day.
Finally, the Duel Monsters Duel Box System I had most confidence in
was developed successfully.
However...
I was too late.
With the funding of your Solid Vision System...
Just a step behind, you stole my chance from me with one shake of your hand!
To think that happened...
But fate is finally smiling down on me now.
Now that the Kaiba Corporation's stock prices have fallen considerably,
and my defeating you during this time where civilians have lost trust in your company...
Even Pegasus himself will give up on you and form a new partnership with us Schroeders.
Is that your aim?
Kaiba, even you cannot deny that
the fate of Kaiba Corporation lies on the success of your competition!
So what if it does?
What?
You keep going on and on about your hatred for me and all...
But that has absolutely nothing to do with me!
Those empty words you muttered didn't move me one bit!
Kaiba...!
Let me show you the difference between us as Duelists!
My turn! Draw!
There's no Monster Card.
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card, Angel's Charity.
I draw three cards from the deck and discard two from my hand.
Nice thinking!
In that way, he doesn't need to discard any Monster Cards that he drew.
Right!
Looks like its starting... Kaiba's retaliation.
I discard these two cards.
What? He's sending Blue-Eyes into the Cemetery?
In addition, by removing the Blue-Eyes and Pitch-Dark Dragon in my Graveyard from play,
I Summon Chaos Emperor Dragon in Attack Position!
That's useless!
There's no dragon that the Enchanted Sword can't conquer!
No, the Special Ability of Chaos Emperor Dragon is that...
It can send all cards in both players' hands and on the field to the Graveyard.
But in order to activate that ability, you need to use 1000 Life Points.
Your Life Points-
I set one more card!
In addition, I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Emergency Provisions.
I get to regain 1000 Life Points by destroying one Magic or Trap Card from on my field.
What?
Then I use 1000 Life Points to activate the Special Effect of Chaos Emperor Dragon!
Destroy everything!
Cemetery of Fire!!
This effect also states that you'll be dealt 300 points of damage
for every card that got sent to the Graveyard.
How's that?
I bet you can't hear fate whispering to you anymore.
My turn, draw!
From my hand, I activate Pot of Greed!
I draw two cards from my deck!
Then I activate the Continuous Magic from my hand, Magical Alms!
This card allows me to regain 1000 Life Points the moment it's activated.
In addition, at every turn, each player must predict how many Magic Cards they will use,
and both players will gain 500 of their Life for each Magic Card that appears.
However, when the number used is less than predicted,
both will suffer 1000 points of damage per card.
I predict that I'll use one card!
I then activate a Magic Card from my hand, Final Light!
By paying 1000 Life Points,
I can Special Summon one Light-Attribute Monster from the Cemetery!
Revive, Brunnhilde!
The opposing player can also Special Summon one Monster with Attack Points of 2000 or less.
Then I'll Special Summon Grand Dragon!
Due to Brunnhilde's Effect,
she gains 300 Attack Points for every Dragon-Type Monster on the field!
Valkyrie Brunnhilde, attack Grand Dragon!
Looks like the tables have turned, Kaiba.
Turn end.
My turn.
Draw!
I predict that I'll use four Magic Cards!
What? Saying that he'll use four when he only has one card on his hand?
That's right. I'll destroy you with those four cards.
You... seriously believe you can?
This will be the first!
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Life-Shaving Card Treasure!
I can then draw until I have five cards in my hand...
And I must discard my entire hand after five turns into the Graveyard!
What?!
The second.
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Soul Release!
Both players can select up to five cards from the Graveyard
and remove them from the game.
I select Chaos Emperor Dragon from the Graveyard and remove it!
The third!
From my hand, I activate Magic Reproduction.
By sending two Magic Cards to the Graveyard,
I get to add one Magic Card from the Graveyard back to my hand.
And the fourth!
I use 2000 Life Points to activate Dimension Fusion from my hand!
With this, both players may Special Summon all their Monsters removed from play!
You fool!
Brunnhilde gains Attack Points for every Dragon you play!
Against Brunnhilde, no Dragon you play stands a chan-
Emerald Dragon, attack Brunnhilde!
He's only got 50 of his Life left!
Brother...
Have you gone mad, Kaiba?!
As the number of Dragons decreased, Brunnhilde's Attack Power went down!
Chaos Emperor Dragon, attack Brunnhilde!
Brunnhilde can avoid being destroyed by reducing her Defense Power by 1000!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon, attack Brunnhilde!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
With that, Brunnhilde can no longer use that Special Ability.
Blue-Eyes White Dragon, attack Brunnhilde!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
My... Valkyrie..!
My last Blue-Eyes...
Play a requiem for this miserable, fallen man!
Direct Attack the player!!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Damn you...
Hmph... In the end, a rat will always be a rat.
There's no way it could ever beat me, the king of all animals!
Well done, Brother!
He's amazing...
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Sieg infiltrated the KC Grand Prix with the intention of ruining it...
But he was utterly defeated by Kaiba-kun's relentless attacks.
As expected!
I'd like to say that...
But I sort of feel sorry for Sieg, seeing him look so dejected.
Anyway, it's time to pit the title of Duel King,
as the final battle between Yugi and Leon-kun begins.
Both of you must do your best!
Next time!
"The Final Battle for Duel King - Yugi VS Leon"
Duel standby!