Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Mai...
I didn't know you were suffering this much...
But still...
It's definitely a huge mistake to risk your life in this Duel!
I won't hold back anymore!
I'll fight you with all my power!
And Mai, I'll find a way to make it so we can live like none of this ever happened between us!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Revive! The Third Dragon"
Come on, man...
If he doesn't figure out a plan this turn,
Jounouchi will lose!
And the one who loses will have their souls sealed!
I don't want to see that
happen to Mai-san or Jounouchi!
Other Me...
Is there really nothing we can do?
The Barrier of Orichalcos won't go away until one of their Life Points hits 0.
However...
That's also the key to saving them both.
As long as Jounouchi-kun realizes it...
And that is...?
No matter how many times he gets back up, it'll end the same.
Just one more attack and Jounouchi's soul will belong to us of Doma!
Right, Rafael?
What's wrong?
Nothing...
I only have 200 Life Points...
Even worse, Mai still has an untouched 4000...
The number of Monsters on the field is also in her favor...
Even so, I can't give up.
As long as there's cards in
my deck, there's a possibility!
There's got to be a way to
save me and Mai in this Duel...
If I could just destroy this boundary...!
Wait! Maybe...
This is all I can do...!
I'll bet everything on this card...!
I Summon Magical Gigacyber to
the field in Attack Mode!
Gigacyber?
He's a Six-Star Monster, but...
If the opponent has at least two more Monsters than I do on the field, I can Special Summon him to the field without sacrificing!
I use Gigacyber to attack Harpy Lady!
Ye-yahh~!
At least he finally made a counterattack!
But...
Does Jounouchi seriously want to fight Mai-san?
No...
Jounouchi-kun has finally realized.
The way to end this Duel...
If both of their Life Points hits 0 at the same time...
...the boundary may just disappear...
Jounouchi-kun has discovered this possibility.
This Jounouchi fella's gotten pretty energetic all of a sudden.
Indeed...
It's because he's a Chosen Duelist.
That doesn't change the fact that Mai will win.
Also, I set one card in reverse! Turn end!
Looks like you're finally serious, Jounouchi...
Yeah.
I'm about as serious as I'll ever be!
This is what I'm talking about...!
I've been waiting for this!
To finally be able to move past this utter nonsense of friendship and fight you with all my might!
And I'll win!
This place is...?
You don't have to worry.
Your wishes will be fulfilled here.
What exactly do you want me to do...?
Welcome, Mai Kujaku.
To our temple of Doma.
And you are...?
I am Dartz.
The one who shall make your wish come true.
My.... wish...?
Your heart is trembling with fear...
Your fear is rooted in the despair and loneliness you tasted after suffering defeat.
I am the only person capable of helping your heart let go of that fear.
D-Don't speak nonsense...!
I...
I'm not...!
...afraid of anything...!
Not afraid... of anything...
Go! Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
God Blaze Cannon!!
Mai Kujaku...
I plan on letting you enjoy the inside of the world in your mind to the fullest!
No...!
I don't want to lose!
I don't want to feel that ever again!
Then all need you do is win.
Those who spoke trivial words of comfort to you in the past no longer stand beside you.
Will you continue to walk this maze all by yourself after having been left behind?
Or will you cease to follow in their tracks and get ahead of them?
This is for you to decide.
You did say you wanted to win, did you not, Mai Kujaku?
I want to win....!
For that purpose, are you prepared to throw everything else away?
I want to win!
I want to win! By any means!
Do you desire power for this purpose?
I do!
Then I shall grant you it.
From this day forward, you will be one of us... of Doma!
My turn! Draw!
With all the power I've mustered, Jounouchi, I'm going to beat you!
Why ya drivin' so fast...?
As I thought, this is strange.
The entire place is empty!
O-Oi! Wait!
Don't leave us behind!
Yugi-kun!
Guys!
Otogi!
Otogi-kun!
Why are you here?
That's what I want to know!
Why are you Dueling in a place like this?!
Isn't that Jounouchi-kun Dueling against Mai-san?
We don't have time to explain!
There's something terrible happening!
We've been locked in here!
Can you open the door from out there?!
Got it!
I'll try!
We're counting on you, Otogi!
Ryuzaki and Haga!
Why are you guys here as well?
No, that....
That's the boundary from that time!
Right!
We couldn't do a thing 'gainst that thing and we were done in!
I sacrifice two Harpy Lady Copies.
I Summon Harpy's Pet Dragon!
Due to the effect of the Barrier of Orichalcos, its Attack goes up by 500!
And for every Harpy Lady on the field,
it goes up another 300 points!
3400 Attack Points?
That woman's horribly powerful!
She's so much different than she was back in the Duel Kingdom!
Where did Mai Kujaku get that barrier card?!
This is the last strike, Jounouchi!
Go! Harpy's Pet Dragon!
Attack Gigacyber!
Reverse card open!
Compensation Mediation!
This card allows me to shuffle it with two cards from the opponent's Graveyard.
If I can pick this card from the three cards,
for this turn, all battles will be forced to a close.
No way!
The chance of getting your own card is one third!
If he doesn't get it, he'll lose!
This guy's seriously strugglin' right to the end.
No.
If he truly is one of the Duelists whose radiance shines brighter than all others,
he just might pull it off.
Now!
Choose two cards from your Graveyard, Mai!
These two.
Cool.
Then you shuffle them.
Now then, ready when you are.
Now then, let me pick.
I choose..... this one!
I'll choose.... this one!
Yippeekayay!!
Bitchin'! He got it right!
Right on!
That's just not possible...!
His cheap good luck keeps getting better and better...!
He really did it....
This turns' battle is over!
Thank goodness...
In any case, he made it through this turn.
But compensation comes with a high price...
As expected of you.
I'll give you a hand for coming up with such a thorough plan.
However....
Yeah I know.
The opposing player gets to add the cards they chose to the top of their deck.
That's not fair!
So that means those cards are back?!
Pharaoh Formation and Phoenix Formation...
No matter which she uses,
they're both powerful cards...
One of the two will be added to Mai's hand when she draws.
The battle may be over,
but my turn isn't over yet!
With the effect of the Orichalcos Barrier,
I move two Harpy Ladies to the back row!
Also, I set two reverse cards face down! Turn over!
Even though I avoided that attack earlier...
My Gigacyber can't stand up to her strength....!
And if Mai draws Phoenix Formation
next turn, I'm finished....!
But I still have a chance!
My turn! Draw!
I set one reverse card!
Also, I Summon a Monster
in face-down Defense Mode!
I switch Gigacyber to Defense Mode!
Hey there!
Running on the defensive again, are we now?
SHUT UP! Shut yer trap!!
Not here either!
No good!
If I don't hurry...!
Shit!
Same here!
No good!
It opened!
You're awfully calm in this desperate situation, Jounouchi...
I guess.
It's one of the many lessons I learned in Battle City.
Never give up until the last second, no matter what happens.
If you do, a chance will come!
That's right...
I was waiting for someone to save me then...
That's why I have to win now!
My turn! Draw!
Reverse card open!
Drop Off!
I won't let you draw!
I won't let you have your way!
Reverse card open over here as well!
Trap Jammer!
I discard a card from my hand to make your Trap Card's activation useless!
Damn it!
Which card did Mai draw...?!
You really have good luck...
I'll set this.
That card isn't Phoenix Formation! It's Pharaoh Formation!
It's too early to relax!
Harpy's Pet Dragon! Attack Gigacyber!
Also, I use Harpy Lady to attack
your Reverse Defense Monster!
Hot diggity damn!
I activate the Reverse Effect of Fiber Pot!
All Monsters on the field, our hands, and the cards in both our Graveyards return to the owners' decks, and then we shuffle them!
Not bad at all, Jounouchi.
But that's useless!
Reverse card open!
Harpy's Feather Snowstorm!
This Card Effect can only be activated if my Harpy attacks! It makes all my enemy's Special Effects invalid!
Jounouchi's Monsters were all destroyed again!
Jounouchi....!
Mai saw through all of Jounouchi-kun's strategies....!
She's strong...!
Turn end!
Now what'll you do next, Jounouchi?
Not yet...!
My Life isn't gone yet...!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon a Monster in Face-down Defense Mode!
Turn over!
Next turn, Mai will draw Phoenix Formation.
No matter what Monster he played, he's done for with only 200 points.
My turn! Draw!
There's only one Monster left on Jounouchi's field...
If all my Harpy Ladies attack at once, I win.
But what if his Reverse Monster has a similar Effect to that Fiber Pot before...?
All I can do is use the magical effects of my Phoenix Formation to seal away his Special Abilities!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Phoenix Formation!
Beat his Reverse Monster!
Now I win!
Yes!
Jounouchi~!
N-Neko Mane King?!
Right!
The Cat Mimicry King's Attack is 0!
So the effect of Phoenix Formation
that deducts half the destroyed Monster's Attack Points from the player's Life Points becomes meaningless!
Also, Neko Mane King's Special Effect is activated!
If you send it to the Graveyard in this turn due to a Magic, Trap, or Monster Card Effect....
the opponent's turn is forced to an end!
Thank God...!
He barely made it by the skin of his teeth...!
There's got to be a limit to his strong good luck...!
This dude just doesn't know when to throw in the towel.
He just delayed his defeat for a single turn.
Knock it off already!
If you're still thinking about "saving me," you're more stupid than I thought!
Sorry!
You know I'm bad at giving up.
But that's Mai for you...
You don't give anyone time for a chance...
If I can't think of a plan on the next draw...
I'll really lose for sure.
Will it end this way?
Will I lose before I save Mai, and before I beat these Doma punks a new one?
No!
I won't accept that!
I can't give up yet!
I'm counting on you.... my deck!
Any sort of miracle is fine!
Please give me a chance!
This is...!
The Monocle of Timaeus!
Could it be...?!
What's up with this light?!
The Fang of Critias?!
It's the same as what happened to me before....!
W-Where is this?
Mai? What happened to the Duel?!
This is the World of Duel Monsters!
The place where the Nameless Dragons sleep.
This sword...
Jounouchi-kun, only you can lift this sword!
You're the only one who can pull this sword.
You're the last one chosen by the Nameless Dragons.
I am?
I feel it!
Something spoke to me through this sword...!
Nameless Dragon...!
I know your name!
Your name is... Hermos!
What was that just now? A dream?
No...
That's right, Jounouchi-kun....
You've certainly been chosen
by the Nameless Dragons...
What was....?
What's wrong, Big Brother?
Mokuba, did you see the light just now?
Eh? What are you talking about?
No, forget it then....
The Orichalcos is reacting....!
Is it the power of the Nameless Dragons?!
Are they trying to interfere again?!
What the hell just happened?
What are you doing?!
It's your turn!
I don't know what just happened...
But I can feel a power flowing through me...
I'll bet everything on this card!
Draw!
This is...!
The Claw of Hermos!
What's wrong with Jounouchi now?
He's acting stranger...
Umm...
Like we thought!
Jounouchi-kun is the last to be chosen!
Yeah!
As long as he has that card...
I'm counting on you.... Hermos!
Please lend me your power!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Jounouchi got a special card when he was in a desperate situation.
What the hell is that?!
Just like Yugi was entrusted with a Legendary Dragon Card from the Duel Monsters world,
Jounouchi was chosen by that card too!
The Nameless Dragon - The Claw of Hermos!
Could this card's hidden power be enough to save Jounouchi and Mai-san from this Duel?!
Next time: "The Miracle of Hermos"
Duel standby!