Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In order to get into the Semi-Finals of the KC Grand Prix, Jounouchi-kun competed with Sieg.
Using his Goddess Combo,
Sieg drove Jounouchi-kun's Monsters out of the game one by one.
But Jounouchi-kun put up a good fight.
Even when faced with danger time and again,
he still managed to drive Sieg into a corner.
Even though he still lost in the end,
it really was a fantastic Duel.
"Rebecca VS Leon:
Genius Girl VS Genius Boy"
Seto-sama.
The investigations on Sieg Lloyd have finished, but the result was not satisfactory.
What do you mean?
Even though the results of all his Duels have been collected...
...along with the data of him as a Duelist, but...
Sieg Lloyd's background...
That is...
Besides his personal particulars amongst the data,
We could not find any connection between him and the Schroeder family that you mentioned.
How can a person with such a dubious background
participate in so many Duel tournaments around the world?
Yes, after contacting the organizers of the various competitions...
...we found out that at the start of each competition...
Sieg would get local influential people to recommend or introduce him,
so that he could take part.
Influential people...
We did try to get in touch with them...
...but they all refused to appear in person.
There's various ways of playing such tricks.
Show me the name list.
Contact this man once again.
Tell him that I still remember what happened back then.
With that, his attitude should change.
Yes, sir!
Damn rat...
I'm going to grab you by the tip of your tail!
Jounouchi lost...
Which means...
Great! Yugi will come and cheer me on!
Yes!
Dammit...
Why'd I have to fail in the end?
How long're you gonna sit there sulking for?
Get off!
I can't accept this!
Stop it, will you?
Let's go cheer Rebecca on.
What's up with that?! Rebecca this and Rebecca that...
I need comforting too!
Dude...
It couldn't be helped.
His deck consisted of limited edition cards that we've never seen before.
You've already done very well, Jounouchi-kun-
Yugi-kun!
B-Bad news, Yugi-kun.
Professor Hopkins.
What's wrong? You look so frantic.
Sugoroku... H-He's missing...
My grandpa?
He's what?!
But wasn't he resting in the infirmary because his waist hurt?
That was the case, but...
I'm so miserable.... this hurts...
Hang in there, Sugoroku.
I'll go get the doctor.
Doctor?
Rebecca!
Good job, Rebecca! That's it!
Great! You've done well, Rebecca!
That's my granddaughter!
Oh right, I need to get a doctor...
What's wrong, Mutou-san?
Sugoroku...
I only took my eyes off him for a while...
Could he have gone to get something to eat?
But his waist hurt so badly, he couldn't possibly have gone alone.
Then... Maybe someone helped him?
Like who?
Maybe he was abducted.
Don't say stupid things like that!
But didn't Mokuba-kun say that some suspicious character snuck in?
You're thinking too much.
What good would kidnapping Gramps do?
It'd be great if that's the case...
Anyway, let's go search for him.
That's right.
There's no helping it.
I'm sorry, everyone.
It's no big deal.
Professor, you go ahead first to cheer for Rebecca.
Once we find his grandfather, we'll go cheer for Becky too.
I'm sorry, everyone.
Please tell Rebecca to do her best on our behalf.
I will.
Right, let's split up to search for him!
Okay!
Where are they?
They're not coming to cheer me on?
Rebecca!
Hey there!
Grandpa!
You've done well, Rebecca.
And now it's the Semi-Finals.
Mm-hm!
But Yugi and the others still aren't here yet.
Are they running late?
Actually, I met them earlier.
Seemed like something popped up and so they might be late.
But they said that they'd definitely come and cheer for you.
Oh no!
Don't make things difficult for them, Rebecca.
They will be here shortly.
But-
Yugi-kun asked me to tell you to do your best.
Really?
Then, I'll tolerate it for a while longer.
Good girl! Come, let's go.
Wow, amazing!
I feel as though I've turned into a giant!
Am I Dueling here?
Gulliver?!
Oh, that's really life-like!
I fell asleep...
Leon-kun...
What are you doing?
I felt as though I entered a fairy tale world...
I got so comfortable that I fell asleep.
You're such a child.
Huh? Where's Yugi-san and the others?
They're not coming to cheer you on?
They will be coming!
Just that they'll be here slightly late.
Leon-kun, do you not have any family or friends coming to cheer for you?
Yeah, they're all very busy.
Besides, I'm used to being alone.
I see.
You're not alone.
Hey, between Rebecca and Leon, who do you think will win?
Rebecca, of course.
No, I think Leon will win.
But Rebecca is a genius.
Go for it, Leon!
Don't you lose, Rebecca!
Rebecca, Leon...
Your Duel has attracted all these people.
Leon-kun.
Look, there are so many people cheering for you.
So, you are not alone.
But it'd be even better if Yugi-san was here to cheer for me.
No way.
Yugi can only cheer for me.
You're so lucky!
Speaking of which, I wonder what happened to Sugoroku...
Grandpa... where are you?
Attention all visitors.
"Old Man Over-Alls"is waiting for you in the ticketing booth.
I repeat.
Over-alls?
Could that be Grandpa?
Yugi!
Guys!
Did you hear that announcement just now?
Yup. But I don't see the old man around.
What's going on?
What's that?
This is...
A map.
Looks like a map of Kaiba Land.
Then what's this place marked with a cross?
Can it be...
That it means Grandpa Sugoroku is there?
Grandpa...
But don't you all find this strange?
Gathering us here on purpose so that we can see this map?
What do you mean?
This must be a trap.
Hey Otogi, what kind of trap?
I wouldn't know even if you asked me.
Now!
It's finally time for the Semi-Finals to begin!
First up, from the A Block!
We have Sieg Lloyd versus Balfry Ginger!
It will be held at the planetarium special stage!
From the B Block!
We have Rebecca Hopkins versus Leon Wilson!
It is taking place in the "Miniature Land" special stage!
Well then, who will be the one to return to this final Duel Ring?
The Semi-Finals will now... start!!
Duel!!
Go on, Leon... come on!
Go Rebecca... do your best!
Here I go, Leon.
My turn! Draw!
From my hand, I activate the Angel's Charity Magic Card!
I draw three cards from my deck...
...and then discard two cards from my hand.
These are the cards I'm discarding.
Fallen Angel Marie...
As long as this card remains in the Graveyard,
my Life Points increase by 200 points during each of my Standby Phases.
Then from my hand, I Summon Big Bang Girl in Attack Position!
I set one card face-down and end my turn.
It's my turn! Draw!
What will Leon-kun show us during this Duel?
I Summon Forest Wolf in Attack Position.
Forest Wolf, attack Big Bang Girl!
Even though Forest Wolf is quite a glutton...
...it needs time to digest the food it eats.
Y-You mean...
In its stomach...
Then from my hand, I activate a Magic Card, Curse of Thorns.
Curse of Thorns...
It is able to seal up effects that are activated when the Monster is in the Cemetery.
You're good, Leon.
I end my turn.
He was able to destroy Rebecca's combo right from the start...
And he even stole Life Points from her...
Leon-kun will be hard to deal with.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Sapphire Dragon in Attack Position!
How's that?
I have various forms of attack.
Allow me to teach them to you.
Sapphire Dragon, attack Forest Wolf!
Sapphire Spark!!
Because Forest Wolf got destroyed...
...the Monster in its stomach is Special Summoned onto the owner's field.
That was great, Rebecca.
That's not all.
Big Bang Girl, attack the player directly!
Turn end.
As expected of the U.S. Champion.
But I won't lose.
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Glife The Phantom Bird in Attack Position!
Glife The Phantom Bird is a Four-Star Monster...
It won't be able to attack if Gravity Bind is activated.
What?!
When Glife The Phantom Bird is Summoned,
I can destroy one of my opponent's Magic or Trap Cards.
Next, I use Glife The Phantom Bird to attack Big Bang Girl!
Next I activate the Continuous Magic, Gingerbread House, from my hand.
Turn end.
Gingerbread House...?
What kind of card is that?
My turn! Draw!
Sapphire Dragon's Attack has increased!
What is going on?
Being too fat is not good for you.
Listen up.
During each of your Standby Phases,
Gingerbread House will add 600 Attack Points.
The thing is, if the Monster's Attack Points exceed 2500, it'll pop!
Then my Life Points will increase by 500.
What card is that?
He has many rare cards that I've never seen before.
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card, The Shallow Grave!
Both of us can select a Monster in our Graveyards
and Special Summon it in Defense Position!
I Special Summon Sapphire Dragon!
Then I...
...shall revive Forest Wolf!
Then I sacrifice Sapphire Dragon...
To Summon Emerald Dragon in Attack Position!
Here I come, Leon!
Emerald Dragon, attack Glife The Phantom Bird!
Emerald Flame!!
Turn end.
You're really strong, Rebecca.
Now I'm getting all excited about this Duel.
It's my turn! Draw!
I switch Forest Wolf to Attack Position!
Then from my hand, I Summon Cinderella in Attack Position.
Due to Cinderella's Special Effect...
I can Special Summon Pumpkin Carriage in Defense Position.
Then from my deck, I activate the Equipment Magic, Glass Slippers.
W-What?
Well you see...
When Pumpkin Carriage is on the field,
Cinderella can attack the opponent directly.
What did you say?!
Cinderella, attack the opponent directly!
The Glass Kick!!
And when Cinderella attacks successfully...
I can equip Glass Slippers on the opponent's Monster.
What do you mean by that?
A Monster equipped with Glass Slippers cannot attack Cinderella.
And its Attack Points will be decreased by 1000.
How can that be?
Next I use Forest Wolf to attack Emerald Dragon.
And you know...
When the Monster equipped with Glass Slippers is destroyed,
Glass Slippers will be equipped back on Cinderella.
And Cinderella's Attack Power will go up by 1000 points.
I set one card.
Turn end!
...What?
These strange cards...
They must all be limited edition cards sold only at certain places...
What a joke.
How can I be defeated here?
My turn! Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Offerings to the Dead!
By discarding one card from my hand, I can destroy one Monster on the opponent's field.
Next I activate the Magic Card, Stamping Crush!
It can destroy one Magic Card and deal 500 points of damage to that player!
And then!
I use Emerald Dragon to attack Cinderella!
Reverse card, open!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
T-That can't...
Turn end.
It's my turn. Draw!
Cinderella, Direct Attack the player!
Dear... me!
This kid...
He's strong!
Yugi...
The winner...
Sieg Lloyd!
How long do you
intend to drag this on, Kaiba?
I am right here.
Right here...
Over here!
You think he's really in a place like this?
Our only clue is that map.
We can only give it a try!
Grandpa Sugoroku, please be safe!
Grandpa...
This is it!
Is Grandpa Sugoroku inside?
Be careful, Yugi.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The Semi-Finals of the KC Grand Prix has finally started.
It looks like Sieg secured an easy ticket into the final round...
...but Rebecca and Leon are locked in a fierce Duel, with neither side moving an inch!
We'd like to go down and cheer for them, too.
But Yugi's grandpa is trapped in a strange place.
What a headache this has become!
And it looks like Yugi will have to Duel someone...
Rebecca, hang on a little longer!
Next time!
"Leon In Fairy Tale Land"
Duel standby!