Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Within the Stone Wilderness, a mysterious Monster suddenly appeared before me.
So it's a follower of the one who destroyed Atlantis years ago?
And Kris... Ironheart...
You two are the souls of warriors who fought against this threat alongside the Duel Monsters in the past!
I swear to you both!
That I will fight with everything I've got to protect those close to me!
"Varon Engages!
The Mysterious Armor Deck"
We finally reached the top!
Yeah!
If we follow this railroad track, we should be able to meet up with Jounouchi-kun and Honda-kun.
I want to tell them both about this as soon as possible.
Eh?
That Yugi's going to be alright now.
That he's gone back to his usual self!
Mhm.
Let's get moving.
Right.
198...
199...
200-
Can't move an inch~
C'mon!
Rock, paper, scissors!
You jerk!!
That's freakin' low! Catching me when my guard was down like that!
Shaddup! Win's a win!
So hurry up an' pick up Ryuzaki!
L-Let me take a quick break~!
Ya sure it's okay to sit around like this?
Don't you wanna meet up with Yugi?
That's right!
Get a move on, Honda!!
Hey- No, wait! Isn't that a little too fast?!
Jounouchi!
You gotta pace yourself properly! Pace yourself, ya moron!
That's as far as we'll
tolerate your disobedience.
Disobedience?
Let me be clear on this. I never once agreed to Duel by anyone's orders!
I only fight the way I want to!
That includes Pegasus as well as Jounouchi!
Watch your tongue, Mai Kujaku.
But in the end, you weren't able to beat Jounouchi, right?
Give me a break!
If this guy didn't get in the way, I would've beat him!
I can't believe you're still saying that...
I'm going to do what I want to do!
Dartz! Even if it's you, I won't let anyone get in the way of my Duels!
Let her do as she pleases.
After all, her fate rests in the hands of our God.
Jounouchi...
Yo, sweety!
That's a hot bike you ridin' there!
Whatd'ya say to comin'
to play around with us?
Beat it.
Huh? Was'sat?
I told you to get lost!!
What're you gonna do with that little computer image a' yours?
Impossible! That's not a hologram!?
Varon?
I'm going to take care of Jounouchi.
It's not your turn to go out.
It's for you!
For your sake, I'll beat Jounouchi to a bloody pulp.
Humph! For "my sake"?!
Please keep your ridiculous jokes to yourself.
The reason behind our actions.
"Reasons"?
What are you talking about?
I mean those eyes.
Those eyes...
You said yourself. You seek victory in order to never allow yourself to suffer the despair of defeat again.
But that wasn't all.
No, you were searching for something beyond mere victory.
Almost like an exceptionally serious addiction.
You're manipulated by your own desires.
Something... beyond winning?
That's right.
Kind of like a vampire.
Like the walking dead in search of blood, you wander aimlessly for victory.
That's how you are.
But even if you manage to win, your desires aren't fulfilled in the least bit.
You only seek a new victory beyond the victory you already felt.
Stop kidding around!
What bullshit are you on about?!
How long will it take for you to realize?
You don't have to shoulder this burden!
No matter how many times you achieve victory, you're becoming nothing but an overflowing vessel!
Jounouchi and the Pharaoh...
They too have their own.
That includes Rafael and Amelda.
Every one of us has our own "container".
Mai, I'm the same.
I can't live on if I can't win.
But I finally found it.
Something to appease my "vessel of victory"!
And that, Mai, is you.
Mai...
Stand by my side.
For your sake, I'll continue winning.
Be it Jounouchi or the Pharaoh...
No, if you wish it so, I'll even defeat Dartz!
You... You have to defeat me first.
But I have already.
I'm not the same as I was back then!
You'd be better off not thinking you can win so easily.
Mai...
How's the professor holding up?
He seems a bit tired.
He's sound asleep in the back.
As I figured, he hasn't recovered from the shock of this whole thing yet.
Yeah... But my grandpa wanted us to set off ASAP.
That's... Mai-san!
He's...
He's one of Doma's men!
Becky!
Otogi...?
You...
You two took Yugi...
You stole Yugi's soul, didn't you?!
And what if we did...?
Unforgivable!
That's it?
I'm going to defeat you!
I challenge you!
Wait, Becky! It's too dangerous!
Don't belittle me!
It may not look like it, but I'm the U.S. Champion!
I'll defeat this guy and win back Yugi's soul!
Oh? Are you now, honey?
The U.S. Champion...?
Rebecca Hopkins...
If you underestimate me, you're in for some pain!
What a mature kid.
I bet you wanna knock some sense into this kiddy, but...
Mai, I'm gonna show you a sample of my strength.
I accept, honey.
Becky! Let me fight too!
With me tagging along, we'll be that much more powerful!
Sure thing. I'll take you both on at the same time!
Bring it!
Becky! Watch out for The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Right!
Duel!!
Guess I'll go first.
Get ready!
Draw!!
I Summon Psychic Armor Head in Attack Mode!
He put a Monster with 0 Attack Points in Attack Position?!
Psychic Armor Head?
That's the first time I've heard of that card.
What kind of powers does it have...?
Turn over!
It's my turn! Draw!
I play a Magic Card from my hand! Summon Dice activates!
I pay 1000 of my Life to roll a die!
If the die rolls a one or a two, I'll be able to call an additional Summon outside of a Normal Summon!
If it lands a three or a four, I can Special Summon a Monster from my Graveyard!
And if it hits a five or a six...
It's a six!
I can tribute in order to Summon a High-Level Monster!
Come out, God Orgoth!
Turn over!
It's my turn!
I draw!
I Summon Sapphire Dragon in Attack Mode!
I then place a card face-down...
...and end my turn!
I'll be able to attack next turn.
What's he going to do?
My turn!
I activate the Effect of Psychic Armor Head!
In exchange for drawing a card this turn,
I can add one Armor Monster from my deck to my hand.
And then, I sacrifice Psychic Armor Head to Summon Double Cross Armor!
Following, I set a card in reverse and end my turn!
What's he up to? He Summoned another Monster with 0 Attack Points...!
I'll tell you.
This Monster can't attack on the turn it's Summoned.
But when it's attacked,
the opposing Monster is destroyed by its Effect...
...and the opposing player takes half the destroyed Monsters' Attack Points as damage!
And after engaging in battle, this card is destroyed.
I see!
If I were to strike with God Orgoth, half of his Attack Power, 1250, would be deducted from my Life Points.
But next turn, he won't have a Monster on the field!
My turn! Draw!
I play two cards on the board!
Take care of the rest, Becky!
God Orgoth! Attack Double Cross Armor!
Destroy it!
Diamond Blade!!
Now's your chance, Becky!
My turn!
Draw!
I set a card on the field.
I sacrifice Sapphire Dragon and Summon Emerald Dragon!
Emerald Dragon, Direct Attack the player!
Reverse card, open!
Magnet Armor!!
This card allows me to Special Summon one Armor Monster from my Graveyard!
And I'll be Summoning...
Double Cross Armor!!
What?!
Not yet...!
Trap Card, activate!
Rope of Life!
When a Monster enters my Cemetery as a result of battle,
I toss my entire hand away...
...and increase that Monster's Attack Strength by 800 points!
And I can Special Summon it to the field!
And that's not all!
Quick-Play Magic!
Resurrection of Diamond Blade!
This card activates only when a Dragon-Type Monster is Special Summoned from the Graveyard!
By sacrificing it, I can Special Summon one Diamond Head Dragon from the deck of the controller in Attack Position!
Use this well, Becky!
Diamond Head Dragon's Attack Points are equal to the Attack Power of the sacrificed Monster, plus an additional 1000 points!
Thank you, Otogi!
So what do you think? Turn end!
W-What is it?
I guess I've had more than enough fun now.
I'm done playing games with the two of you!
It's my turn!
Draw!!
Psychic Armor Head has another Effect!
When this card is in the Graveyard, you can Special Summon it in Attack Mode during your Standby Phase!
Mai, I'm gonna show you the passionate fire of my strength in the blink of an eye!
This can't be!
Are you gonna use a card related to that Barrier of Orichalcos?!
Let's not be conceited now!
I won't be needing the Barrier of Orichalcos against the likes of you!
Here I come!
Magic Card!!
Armored Gravitation!!
What the hell is that thing?!
The armor attached itself directly to the player's body?!
Big Bang Blow!
If this card is destroyed in battle, all cards on the field are destroyed.
Then the players receive damage equal to the Attack Points of their destroyed Monsters!
Absurd! If you did that, even you...!
Wanna test me?!
This... ENDS IT!
Trap Card, activate!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
USELESS!
No way!
"THE END OF" CRUSHER!!
There's just no...
Why...?
Give Jounouchi a message.
Tell him, "You're next."
Mai...
Honda~
That's not fair!
Making me carry Ryuzaki for 5,000 steps...!
Shut it!
Ain't my fault ya can't beat me!
Hey... Honda, look!
Huh? What's that? An aurora?
Aurora? I remember last time...
Yeah, it's the same as before.
Is something about to start...?
Guided by time, my God...
Having absorbed powerful souls, it has begun to act.
Big Brother, you sure about this?
I still don't believe Yugi's lost yet!
It just means he was not the man I thought he was.
He's become a loser dog.
Hey look, Seto!
It's an aurora!
Aurora?
See! It's really pretty!
Why would an aurora occur all the way out here...?
We are about to experience a little turbulence.
For your safety, please be seated and fasten your seatbelts.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
In order to meet up with Jounouchi and Honda, whom we were separated from...
Yugi and I head back the way we came.
Meanwhile, Kaiba-kun heads to Florida in order to find the proof he needs.
But Doma makes another unavoidable move!
Amelda takes Kaiba-kun on in a revenge match aboard a flying plane.
This time's in midair?!
Next time!
"The Revenging Amelda - The Great Airborne Duel"
Duel standby!