Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Damn it! I thought I had this match in the bag!
He's one stubborn guy!
Because of that, my body is at its last breath...
It's really gotten to bad.
But, it's been a while since I've had this kind of passionate Duel.
A game where we pit our full strength in one shot...
I'm getting excited, Varon!
My Duel with you is the best!
It's too bad I had to fight you under these circumstances...
"The End of a Painful Battle"
Wait a sec.
There's no time for this! While we're wasting time, Jounouchi's probably Dueling right now!
If he loses, his soul will be taken!
I know, but the map says it's around here.
What's left is to find a small alley....
Yugi?
What's wrong?
Ah... Some time ago, Jounouchi-kun's Claw of Hermos activated.
I certainly felt it.
This...!
Jounouchi-kun...!
But I can't feel it now at all.
Which means Jounouchi is already....
Honda!
Yugi.
Anyway, let's look for Jounouchi-kun quickly.
Not bad.... Varon.
I thought it was settled now, but...
You're not bad either, Jounouchi!
Nobody's fought me this hard up until now!
You rank number one without a doubt when it comes to stubbornness!
What a Duel!
They're fighting such a fierce battle, yet their fighting spirit hasn't dropped in the least!
This Duel...! This sort of passionate Duel...!
This is what I have been seeking!
I want to fight too!
The cost of activating Aura Armor is paying half of my Life Points.
And I set two cards face-down and end my turn.
My turn, draw.
During my Standby Phase, I Special Summon Psychic Armor Head from the Graveyard!
Then, I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Phoenix Gravitation!
What!? Don't tell me....!
This Magic Card can Special Summon four Armor Monsters from the Graveyard!
Revive!
Burning Knuckle!
Jet Gauntlet!
Overboost!
Active Guard!
PHOENIX GRAVITATION!!
I praise you for fighting this far!
You are a real Duelist.
That's why I will bet on my full power and defeat you!
That's what I'm talking about.
But there's only one getting beat today, Varon. And that's you!
Reverse card open! Graverobber!
I take one card from your Graveyard.
What?!
Big Bang Blow!
Then...! Reverse card, open!
Take One Chance!
With this card, I draw one card from the Graveyard randomly and activate it.
The one I choose is...
Will it come?
I beg you, please come give me power....
All right!!
I knew he'd be able to bring it out again this turn!
Let's go! I activate the effect of the Claw of Hermos!
Fuse with Big Bang Blow!
Big Bang Dragon Blow!!
This time I'm gonna use your own weapon against you!
That's right... This is what I've been searching for.
The best Duel that makes me burn with anticipation!
And the strongest Duelist.
This is the first time I've ever enjoyed a Duel this much!
Let's go! This will be the final turn!
You said it!
Burning Knuckle!!
Big Bang Dragon Blow!!
What is that?!
It was a blast! It was the greatest Duel I ever had!
Same goes for me...!
Jounouchi!
I activate Big Bang Dragon Blow's Special Effect!
By sacrificing one Monster, all of the opponent's Monsters will be destroyed,
and its total Attack Power will be inflicted to the player's Life Points!
I lose.
Mai!
I-I...
Don't make that face.
Regardless of who you're thinking of now, I always believed you'd return to me in the end.
But it's my defeat.
Admittedly, I did show you my uncool side...
But I don't regret it!
Varon...
Jounouchi, I leave Mai to you.
Ah...
VARON!
So you were defeated, Varon?
Your soul shall also become food to our God.
And your turn shall come next, Mai Kujaku.
Show me the darkness of your heart.
Varon...!
Mai, I'm the same. We're similar.
I can't live on if I can't win.
But I finally found it.
Something to appease my "vessel of victory"!
And that, Mai, is you.
Mai...!
What a stupid man...
Dueling is not meant to fight for others.
Fighting is to win for yourself.
Aren't you the one who said so?
That's why you lost.
Mai?!
Varon did his best as a Duelist.
Even if it's you, I won't allow anyone to belittle him!
You're more hot-tempered than you usually are today.
Wasn't Varon an enemy?
Yeah, he definitely was an enemy.
But any Duelist who faces me head on with all he has...
I have respect for them!
Mai, come on over and fight me.
I won't run anymore.
I won't understand your feelings unless I fight you one-on-one.
Let's do it, Mai.
Let's both Duel at full strength so we have no regrets!
If you go easy on me like the last Duel, I won't accept it.
Yes, I know.
Jounouchi, I leave Mai to you.
Mai, hit me with everything you've got!
As a Duelist, I'll also go all out!
That's what I wish for!
Duel!!
That light before must have been coming from Jounouchi!
It should be around here, but where the heck is it?
This way!
Wait, Yugi!
Hey!
Hey, Brother, don't you think it's a little strange?
There hasn't been anyone around here for a while.
It appears that Doma's hand is already reaching out.
Just as I thought.
They don't intend on letting us pass.
Brother!
I don't really have the time to play around with smallfry like yourselves.
But if you won't step back and let us pass quietly...
...I'll forcefully open up a path!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage in Attack Position!
Turn end.
My turn.
The damage I got from that last Duel is still here...
Even so, I have to do it.
Draw!
I Summon Blue Flame Swordsman in Attack Position!
Dammit! I'm not seeing very well anymore...
C'mon, my body... Hang in there a little longer...
Turn... end!
Both my Harpy Lady and your Blue Flame Swordsman have an equal Attack Power of 1800.
Even so, ending without doing anything is not like you.
Don't you worry. I'm not pulling my punches here. I already made up my mind about that.
When I fought seriously with Varon, I understood something.
While Dueling with him, we started to understand each other as we spoke.
I feel like I really understood his feelings.
That's why, Mai, I will fight you seriously.
This time, my feelings will reach you.
Me too. I want to feel what you're feeling!
What are you saying?!
There's no way you could ever understand my feelings!
The desire for victory...
Having no choice but to continue winning...! My feelings....!
I couldn't understand until now.
But I don't want to give up there.
Whatever it is you're planning, I'm just going to crush you along with it!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon one more Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage in Attack Position!
And then, I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Claw of Earo!
By equipping Claw of Earo, the Attack of Harpy increases by 300 points!
Mai's greatest specialty... the Harpy Lady Combo?
My Harpy attacks your Blue Flame Swordsman!
The moment Blue Flame Swordsman is destroyed, his Special Effect is activated!
I can Special Summon Flame Swordsman!
The Flame Swordsman and the other Harpy Lady's Attack Power are both 1800.
How about it? You have the resolve to attack with the same Attack Points, Mai?
I won't do such a meaningless thing!
I'll only attack if I know for sure I'll lower your Life Points!
I place a reverse card face-down and end my turn!
Mai's deck isn't an Attack-Only Deck like Varon's.
It's a much more well-balanced deck.
She has a good variety of both Magic Cards and Trap Cards in her control.
If I'm not careful, I'll lose any advantage I got in a second.
I'll wake you up right now, Mai!
I sacrifice Scapegoat in order to let Panther Warrior attack!
Reverse card, open!
Harpy Lady Pharaoh Formation!
This Trap Card can be activated only when there are two or more Harpy Ladies on the field!
The wings of fire will negate the opponent's attack!
If we had been able to continue before, I could have lost...
Without telling Mai anything...
That won't do. This time I'll tell Mai...
My turn! Draw!
All right! I sacrifice Flame Swordsman and I Summon Cybernetic Wyvern in Attack Position!
Cybernetic Wyvern, attack Harpy Lady!
This is how it should be...
At long last I can have a real Duel!
The Special Ability of the Claw of Earo activates!
When this card goes to the Graveyard, I can equip it to a Harpy Lady on the field!
I set a reverse card face-down and end my turn.
Me too. I will go without holding back.
My turn, draw.
I drew it.
You did...?
Yes.
The Barrier of Orichalcos!!
That's...!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Jounouchi-kun is over there!
If that boundary has appeared...
If we don't hurry...
With this, you can no longer run away.
We're the only ones here.
This time, without anyone interfering, we will fight until one of us falls!
Yeah, I didn't plan on running.
This barrier takes out the darkness of one's heart.
Even Yugi couldn't hold off its power.
But in this Duel, I'll rid you of the darkness in your heart.
Here I come! I Summon Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage in Attack Position!
And my Harpy Ladies gain 500 Attack Points due to the Orichalcos Barrier's effect.
Come on Harpies, attack Cybernetic Wyvern.
Continuing, Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Reverse card open! Scapegoat!
You're stubborn just as always.
But that's just as I planned!
Reverse card open! Nightmare Tri-Mirror!
Whenever my opponent Summons a Monster in any other way than Normal Summoning,
I Special Summon Monster Copy Tokens on my field equal to the amount my opponent has.
Harpy Lady, attack a Scapegoat!
This turn, the Harpy Copy Tokens can't attack, so I end my turn.
You have fallen for the same trick as last time......
It's a little sad that you didn't learn from your previous mistakes, Jounouchi.
Don't say that. It's not like I don't know how to grow up, you know.
I'm not falling for your bluffs!
You have no place to run! This time I will win!
I am not going to run.
This time, Mai, I swear to get you back!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
In a fierce battle of spirits, Jounouchi defeated Varon. But without resting, the Duel with Mai-san started.
He wants to tell his feelings to Mai-san, who doesn't want to accept them.
In these conditions, Jounouchi is standing in the field.
But because of the battle with Varon, Jounouchi has damaged his body to the point where he can fall anytime.
Will Jounouchi's feelings reach Mai-san?
Next time!
"Bitter Victory"
Duel Standby!