Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
The Eternal Wall - God Slime!
It sent my Obelisk's attack
right back at me!
Malik's Wall Monster has taken on the ability of immortality!
He plans to use
the God Slime as a wall,
and wait for a card that can allow him to resurrect Ra!
And every attack I send his way only damages me instead!
And in turn causes my partner to be consumed by the darkness!
But we won't give up!
Chances are born
from the depths of a pinch!
"Obelisk's Anger -
Soul Energy MAX"
Take a close look!
Resurrection of the Dead
has returned to my hand!
And I'm pretty sure you know
what that means by now...
I can Special Summon Ra
on my next turn...
The darkness of Hell is finally
here to take you away, Yugi...
As long as Malik has the God Slime protecting him on the field, I can't beat any of his Monsters...
No...
The real wall
blocking my path right now...
...is the one being held as a sacrifice,
Malik's dominant personality!
If I defeat Malik's dark personality,
his original personality will die...!
It's still my turn!
I place a reverse card...
And then I Summon this guy...
Granadora in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
As long as this creature stays
on my field in Defense Position,
my Life will increase by
1000 points every turn.
That will cover the cost.
And next turn, God will rise as a phoenix
and burn Obelisk to ashes!
And once Obelisk is gone, Yugi...
you have no chance of winning...
My... turn.
Yugi-kun!
If he doesn't stop him this turn, he's going to Summon Ra next turn!
But Yugi's acting like there's something
holding him back in this Duel...
Holding him back?
Yeah. It's like he's pulling his punches and holding back his attacks.
That's right.
You guys can't see it, can you?
Are you Malik again?!
Malik!
You aren't aware that these two are
fighting a Dark Game with one another
up atop that Duel Ring?
Tell us!
What kind of fight is it this time?!
Is it like when he played me and I felt
the pain my Monsters felt, Malik?!
The two of them have another self.
They fight with both myself and Yugi,
their other personalities,
as human sacrifices.
What?!
The other Yugi's
being held as the sacrifice?!
When one of their
Life Points reaches zero,
the sacrifice will fall
into eternal darkness...
That includes the fragment of myself
I placed inside of Anzu...
Eternal darkness?!
Just what do you mean by,
"fall into eternal darkness"?!
Yugi!
Huh? Was I saying something just now?
What's wrong?
It's your turn, Yugi.
Yugi acts like he doesn't
want to take my life...
But why?!
Long before any of this,
I was trying to take the lives
of you and your friends!
Me, not him!
So why?!
Other me!
Our real enemy is Malik's evil side!
There has to be a way to
defeat him and him alone!
Right...
But how should we fight then...?
Even if his Life Points reach zero,
Malik's good side is
the one that will die...
His evil side will stay alive!
Maybe...
Maybe his weakness
is tied to Ra's power!
Ra's power?
Yeah. Ra has three modes
of battle, right?
And one of those is the ability
of Ra to fuse with the player!
But even "God" is merely a Monster!
And that means, if they fuse,
the player becomes a Monster too, right?
The player becomes a Monster...?
That's it!
Thank you, Partner!
Draw!
There may still be a way!
Yup!
I set two reverse cards!
And Summon Illusion Beast Gazelle
in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
Whoa there! Don't forget
that this guy gets an attack
on the end of your turn!
Bowganian!
Release the Crossbow of Pain on Yugi!
Other me!
Partner!
Please do it!
Defeat Malik's evil heart!
Partner, I won't let you die!
Keep talking!
No matter what you say,
this is going to be the last turn!
On this turn, he'll bring back Ra
with Resurrection of the Dead.
Yugi, do you have
any way to stop him?
You can do it!
Don't lose, Yugi!
Yugi!
Yugi-kun!
I draw!
The darkness is
my ally 'till the very end!
With this card, I'm guaranteed
to offer you to the darkness!
Come, Malik!
And on my Standby Phase,
Granadora's Effect activates and
increases my Life Points by 1000!
Get ready!
You'll burn to death in one sweep
of the Sun God's wings!
Magic Card, activate!
Resurrection of the Dead!!
God Phoenix...!
I give up 1000 of my Life Points
in order to activate Ra's third Ability!
Go!!
Burn Obelisk to ashes!!
God Phoenix!!
Reverse card, open!
Nothing you do will matter!
Obelisk is dea-
What!?
Osiris the Heaven Dragon?!
Osiris is shielding Obelisk
from the God Phoenix?!
The moment you attacked,
I used my reverse card!
Magic Card!
Resurrection of the Dead,
one you know well!
So on this turn...
Obelisk is unharmed!
Oh yeah! It's not like Malik's
the only one who has
Resurrection of the Dead!
So Osiris acted as a Monster shield!
To challenge Ra with Obelisk as
a sword and Osiris as a shield...
Look at that, brother!
Obelisk... is mad...
Yugi... You know...?
That anger is what unleashes
Obelisk's true power...?
The phoenix... shall return to
the Graveyard once more...
Do you think
this means you've won, Yugi?
My Battle Phase is over!
What?!
He ended his Battle Phase
without attacking? What's he thinking?
But that doesn't mean my turn is over.
I told you before!
That this turn will be the last turn!
Magic Card, activate!
Surprise Attack from the Darkness!
Surprise Attack from the Darkness?!
With this,
I get an entire second Battle Phase!
And I can revive the Monster
Summoned in this turn!
What?!
Another Battle Phase?!
That card can't be legal!
Malik, you fiend...
Are you going to Special Summon Ra
all over again and finish Yugi off?
Lord... Malik...
Come forth!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
Here it comes...!
Now then...
Ra is still not in Battle Mode.
What form shall I attack you with?
Of course, I'll use this.
That's Ra's second form!
Malik's going to fuse
with Ra for a One Turn Kill!
Malik is left with one Life Point,
and all the rest...
...are transferred to
Ra's Attack Power!
Other me!
Yes, Partner! I know!
It's now or never!
It's our last chance!
Watch as I become one with Ra!!
This moment...
In this one moment, we can beat Malik's
dark side and Ra at the same time!
Yugi... If I sacrifice all the
Monsters on my field,
Ra's Attack Points will rise to 6899!
Far beyond your Obelisk's
mere 4000 Attack Power!
I can blast your Life Points
to 0 in one shot!
Brace yourself...
Heh... We'll see about that.
What?!
I've been waiting for this!
For the moment your evil heart
manifests in the form of a beast!
Reverse card, open!
Soul Taker!
Big brother, what's that card?
Soul Taker...
It's a Magic Card that lets you
sacrifice one Monster on the
opponent's side of the field.
At the same time,
the opponent gains 1000 Life Points.
Don't tell me, Yugi...!
Magical effects only work for
one turn against gods...
Are you trying to
sacrifice me along with Ra?!
Big brother!
I knew it! He's sacrificing Ra!
With this method,
because the player
has one Life Point left...
The real Malik, the human sacrifice,
won't have to die!
Did you really think you could
destroy me by sacrificing Ra!?
Heh! And who said
I was sacrificing Ra?
What?
What's he mean?
Then who's he sacrificing?
The sacrifice...
...is right there!
You're sacrificing... God Slime?!
That's right... Your God Slime is
merely a fusion of Revival Slime
and Reflect Slime.
Meaning...
I'm able to count it as two sacrifices
for the price of one!
You bastard! What do you
hope to accomplish by
sacrificing my Slime?!
I'll tell you!
It's to activate
Obelisk's greatest Ability!
Obelisk's greatest Ability?!
Soul Energy MAX!!
Soul Energy MAX...
God's pent up anger
will create a miracle!
That is Obelisk's greatest Special Ability!
But will it work against Ra?!
Impossible...!
It's Attack Power is infinite?!
Here I go, Malik!!
God Hand Impact!!
Hold it!!
This moment, I take the
Monsters on my field...
Bowganian and Granadora!
And offer them up to Ra!
When Soul Taker was activated, Malik received 1000 Life Points, which were in turn added to Ra's Attack Points.
So Ra has 1699 Attack Points!
Additionally, adding the Attack Points
of the Monsters he sacrificed...
Ra will grow even more powerful...!
Ra now has 4899 Attack Points!
But Obelisk has infinite Attack Points!
He should be able to beat Ra!
Did it work...?!
What!?
Why is he still standing?!
Because I activated this Magic Card...
Class System?!
When our Monsters engage in battle,
if the Level of my opponent's Monster
is equal to or less than my own,
that Monster's Attack Power
and Effects are negated!
Ra and Obelisk both
have a Level of ten!
And there you have it!
Obelisk's Effect has been
rendered useless!
Too bad for you!
Once the Effect wears off,
Obelisk's Attack Points return to 4000.
Yugi, you lose.
Yugi's... going to lose...
And now!
Surprise Attack from the Darkness!!
This is the final Battle Phase!
Yugi!!
Lord... Malik...
You mustn't... make this mistake...
Here I come!
Ra attacks you!
God Blaze Cannon!
I win!
You sure about that?
Huh?!
Reverse Magic, activate!
Magical Dimension!
This Magic activates when my opponent
attacks while I control a
Spellcaster on the field!
Magical Dimension sacrifices two
of the Monsters on my field!
What?! You're sacrificing God?!
By sacrificing Obelisk and Gazelle,
Ra's attack has been evaded!
Sacrifice Escape!!
I heard it back there...
The voice of Lord Malik's soul...
Rishid...
Soon I'll be
headed to the Dark World...
Before I do, there's something
I want to tell you.
I disobeyed the laws of my clan
and committed a terrible sin...
Eternal darkness isn't enough to
punish me for what I did to Father.
But now that you've lost God,
do you really think you have
any hope of defeating me?
Yugi!?
I have my friends!
I have the servants, my comrades,
who have been fighting
alongside me in my deck!
And now for
Magical Dimension's other effect!
I am able to Special Summon one
Spellcaster-Type Monster from my hand!
What!?
Come forth!
Black Magician!
I see...
So Obelisk was just a decoy...
This turn, we will counterattack Ra!
Magic Card, open!
Ragnarok!
This card can only be activated if I have
at least two Magician Monsters on the field!
I remove all the Monsters in my deck,
Graveyard and on the field from play!
By doing so, I can destroy every
Monster my opponent controls!
Malik!
That includes you,  a fusion between
God and yourself, as well!
However, Yugi...
If you destroy Ra, you will leave me
with only 1 Life Point!
And I can tell you right now that my dominant personality
hardly has enough life energy
to live on one measly Life Point!
By destroying Ra...
...you'd be snuffing the life
of my dominant half in the process!
Is he saying that even if
I leave one Life Point,
I can't save Malik!?
Rishid...
When I went through
the Ritual of the Tomb Guardians,
you endured the same pain I did...
You made a choice then to
share my sin and share my destiny...
You decided to live
with me in the darkness.
And yet, you've done enough.
But there's no need for you
to suffer anymore...
Alright! If you're prepared to
kill him, go ahead and try it!
No way!
Now my other self can't attack!
So long as I have this sacrifice,
I can't lose!!
Whether I live or die...
Whatever the outcome,
you need to keep heading toward the light.
That is... not right... Lord Malik...!
Thank you... Rishid.
Lord Malik!!
Rishid!
R-Rishid...!
Isn't that man Rishid-san?
He was lying
in the Battle Ship unconscious!
What's he doing here?
But when Rishid-san begins speaking, Malik's face begins to change.
Malik's dominant personality
is beginning to awaken!
Betting his life on one point, Yugi goes on the attack.
Battle City finally reaches its climax!
Can Yugi beat Malik's dark personality and save everyone?!
Next time!
"The End of Battle City!"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other