Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"The Cruel Duel:
Yugi VS Jounouchi"
Those two should be on their way shortly.
To save their precious friends, that is.
Jounouchi and this girl have become my pawns.
I'm looking forward to the show that's about to unfold.
Lord Malik.
That you, Rishid?
Just as you ordered, I have secured 12 Puzzle Cards for the Battle City Finals.
Good work.
That's just like you.
You took on enough Battle City Duels for two, and won every one of them.
With that Trap Strategy of yours.
There's no need to take control of you.
Because I know you'd never betray me.
Now... please accept these Puzzle Cards.
Now I'm qualified to enter the Battle City Finals.
Rishid, along with you.
Yes, Lord Malik.
Give Jounouchi the Deck of 40 cards we've prepared for him.
Right away.
And now Jounouchi's deck has been transformed into a Banned Deck that can be used to assassin a player.
The time has come for you to feel the furry of our clan.
By the hands of your dear friend, you'll be sent to another world, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun... Please be safe...
How naïve.
If he truly has the power to control people,
then Malik probably already turned Jounouchi into a wild animal with its fangs drawn at you.
If I were him, that's what I'd do.
Kaiba! I don't know what he's up to,
but if it means saving Jounouchi-kun,
I'll gladly put my life on the line!
Yugi, I'm already aware.
You made a serious self-contradiction
when you decided to follow that self-righteous path you're always preaching about.
Self-contradiction?
That's right, Yugi.
In our Tag Duel with those Rare Hunters,
you showed me the power of cooperation.
If we don't combine our power in this Duel, we have no chance of defeating the Ghouls!
But if you and Jounouchi are forced to fight one another this time around...
Then tell me where this "power of cooperation" lies then!
Answer me, Yugi.
There's someone down there! Is that...?
It's Jounouchi!
Kill Yugi!
Kill him! KILL HIM!
Kaiba! The answer lies right ahead of us!
Interesting.
He's coming!
Kill him...
Kill him...!
Kill him!
Jounouchi-kun!
I've been waiting for you to show up, Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun...!
So he really is being controlled by Malik...?
Jounouchi... Almost seems like a different person!
So this is Malik's power of controlling people?
Jounouchi-kun! You've got to wake up!
Wake up?
I'm wide awake!
I'm more than awake enough to beat you to a pulp!
It's no use...! His mind's being completely controlled by Malik...!
Yugi! You can't run away from me or this Duel!
A Duel with our very lives on the line, fighting till our last breaths!
Jounouchi-kun!
Big brother, just what...?
A Duelist must be prepared to crush all challengers
standing before them, even if they're his friend.
That is the way of a Duelist.
If you go against it, you'll never get anywhere.
The way... of a Duelist?
The only way he'll win is if he tosses his usual "friendship"
sentimentality garbage aside, and just fights him.
This is one matchup that may be too much for Yugi to handle...
Now, what'll you do, Yugi?
Show me your answer!
Jounouchi-kun, listen to me.
I want to Duel you in Battle City from the bottom of my heart!
But as True Duelists!
With our pride on the line!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
Those words touched me.
I think the reason we've gotten this far...
...was so I could keep that promise with you.
I truly believe that.
But this battle is a trap set by Malik!
This isn't the true Duel we promised each other!
Follow me, Yugi!
The stage for our Duel of Death is over here.
Jounouchi-kun!
It's no use, Yugi!
No matter what you say,
you can't escape this Duel with Jounouchi!
Anzu!
Jounouchi has become my puppet,
and his emotions and memory are being controlled by my anger!
Anzu's under his spell, too...?!
Now then, Yugi!
Jounouchi is waiting for you at the stage of your Death Duel!
Anzu!
This is our Duel stage...?
Before the Duel begins, you will each attach these handcuffs to your ankles.
That's...! Mine and Jounouchi-kun's handcuffs are attached to an anchor!
That's right!
The anchor weighs 300 kilograms [600 pounds]!
When either of the player's Life Points drop to 0,
the bomb will explode within 30 seconds, and it will fall!
And take a look at your feet.
That box shows your opponent's Life.
The key to your handcuffs lies inside.
The box will open when you take your opponent's Life Points down to 0.
That means...
Before the anchor drags us to our watery graves, one of us can escape!
So the loser of this Duel will be dragged to his death...!
That's right.
Either me or you!
You can't!
There's no way I can have such a dangerous Duel with Jounouchi-kun!
You can't escape this!
The explosive device attached to the anchor has just been activated.
Even if you do nothing, it'll explode in 40 minutes!
In that scenario, you'll both sink into the sea!
What?
It's very simple.
If you wish to save Jounouchi, all you need to do is lose.
Malik! I'll never forgive you for this!
A death match between Yugi and Jounouchi?!
To make them fight such a sick Duel...
Just for Malik's stupid talk of "revenge for 3,000 years of torment"...!
He's seriously trying to kill Yugi...!
We have to stop them, brother!
We can't accept this Duel!
It's a battle where no matter what they do, one of them dies...!
This isn't even a Duel anymore!
I can't accept this!
I will not let Malik do what he wants in this Battle City!
Wh-What the?
Anzu!
What the hell are you trying to do?!
Watch closely.
There's a bomb set up atop this container.
What?!
Try anything and I'll press this switch,
dropping the container right on top of that girl!
I can't believe he'd go this low...!
Kaiba-kun, I'd love it if you could behave yourself and just watch
as the greatest show in existence begins.
That's right.
I'd like for this girl to see this amazing show as well!
Anzu!
Where...?
Hey...!
What the heck is this?!
Yugi...!
Jounouchi?!
That's really dirty, Malik!
Let Anzu go!
That's it!
Suffer more!
But this isn't even close to the suffering my clan and I have endured!
Suffer more and more, Pharaoh!
Then die!
Oh yeah, I almost forgot about that...
Yugi, I could care less if you drown in the sea.
But you better not take the Osiris card along with you!
So take Osiris out of your deck!
I keep the God Card in here!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon...
Yugi...
Right now I can't take Red-Eyes back.
The way I am now, Red-Eyes wouldn't let me.
So anyway, Yugi...
I'll leave that card with you.
I've got no choice but to fight him.
If I put his Red-Eyes in my deck...
I'll use it to regain Jounouchi-kun's Duelist heart!
Put the Osiris card on the floor!
So only the one who lives gets their hands on the God Card.
Now everything is in place!
Now, Jounouchi!
Assassinate Yugi!
Yugi...
Jounouchi...
Let's fight, Jounouchi-kun!
Shuffle your deck!
Duel!!
We're here now, Shizuka-chan.
Right.
It sure is nostalgic...
This town's smell...
My big brother and I always came here when we were little.
I want to hurry up and see my big brother!
Because it's my turn to give him courage!
That's right, alright.
So let's hurry and find Jounouchi.
Right!
Okay... I wonder where the guys are...
Wait right here, okay?
Huh? That's weird.
The phone can't get through.
What the heck is Anzu doing?
Yugi, you get to go first!
How can I fight...
...knowing one of us will die when our Life hits 0?
What a sadistic Duel!
Hey c'mon! What's wrong, Yugi?!
Hurry up and play a Monster!
Illusion Beast King Gazelle!
Defense Position!
Turn... over...!
My turn.
Here goes.
My card is...
Thunder Bolt!!
Then...!
I play Wyvern Warrior on the field!
Directly attack the player!
What's wrong, Yugi?
You're not so tough after all, eh?!
But it's way too early to start fearing me!
Now bring it, Yugi!
My turn.
Draw!
Big Shield Gardna in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
It's no use pulling out a Wall Monster...
My turn!
I'm gonna use this against you!
Fireball!!
Yugi!!
What?!
Magic Cards that directly damage the player are banned from this tournament!
I added tons of illegal cards printed by the Ghouls to Jounouchi's deck.
No one using a store-made deck can hope to beat his deck!
You're about to be burnt to death by your friend!
Die, hateful Pharaoh!
Lord Malik, I just learned that Yugi's friend has brought Jounouchi's little sister to the town.
Jounouchi's little sister?
She could be of great use to my avenging of the clan.
Interesting!
Bring her to me at once!
Yes, sir!
How's it feel?
The power of the illegal player assaulting banned card, Fireball, that is!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Very good.
Kill him.
Kill your friend, Jounouchi!
You're just a puppet, a vessel of my desire for revenge!
I really don't want to fight you...
This isn't the Duel we wished for...!
But I have to fight him!
I know Jounouchi-kun's Duelist heart still hasn't disappeared from within him!
It's your turn.
Yugi!
I will call it back!
Your Duelist's heart!
Card draw!
I'm really sorry, Shizuka-chan...
I should've asked where we were meeting before I left...
No... it's fine!
Don't worry about it, Honda-san.
Shizuka-chan.
I know my brother's somewhere in the town.
And I'm sure the others are as well.
So don't worry, we'll find them.
Who the hell are you guys?!
What do you want with us?!
Honda-san...?
You guys are Ghouls, aren't you?!
Shit... I'd have no trouble kicking their asses...
But protecting Shizuka-chan comes first!
Shizuka-chan, climb on!
Okay!
Hang on tight!
After them!
Stop this!
What the hell are you doing, Jounouchi?!
What's going on here?!
Are you telling me Jounouchi joined up with the Ghouls?!
Jounouchi... seems to be under the control of this Malik guy in charge of the Ghouls.
Under Malik's control?
He said he's avenging his clan for 3,000 years of suffering...
I... don't get any of it at all!
Revenge for 3,000 years of suffering...?
So, this is...!
...a battle related to the other Yugi and his lost memories?!
Don't make a fuss over there, my dear.
Keep runnin' your mouth and I'm gonna send that container right down on ya!
If you think you can do it, why don't you go and try it?!
What was that?!
Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun!
Forget about me!
Stop Jounouchi and Yugi!
No way...
We can't!
Yugi...!
No matter what happens, you've got to endure it!
Hang on to your pride through this dishonorable Duel!
Come on now, Yugi!
How long are you gonna buy time for?!
Hurry up and put out a Monster!
Jounouchi-kun has Wyvern Warrior with 1500 Attack Points on the field...
And I have Big Shield Gardna with 2600 Defense Points...
And I don't have any cards right now strong enough to fight the Wyvern Warrior...
I'll have to strengthen my defense and try and buy some more time...
I set a reverse card!
And then...
I call Kuriboh to the field in Attack Position!
Turn over!
Kuriboh in Attack Position?
Are you kidding me?!
If my Wyvern attacks your Kuriboh,
Yugi, your Life Points are gonna take a serious hit!
I get it.
So to save my life, you're gonna die instead?!
Jounouchi-kun.
I won't die!
And I won't let you die either!
This Duel only ends when one of us dies!
Here goes!
Wyvern Warrior!
Attack Kuriboh!
Reverse card, open!
A Trap Card!
Kuriboh is shielded by the Hexagram Curse!
And the Hexagram Curse stops the Wyvern Warrior from attacking!
That's no use, Yugi!
That won't work against his Banned Deck!
Please!
Stop this already!
And so what of it?
It doesn't matter whether I play a Monster or not...
All I need to do is drain your Life Points!
So why don't you...
...eat this once again?!
FIREBALL!!
"Preview"
When Jounouchi still isn't waking up from Malik's control,
the other Yugi allows Yugi to take over the Duel in his place.
Believing in their friendship, he Summons the Red-Eyes to remind Jounouchi of their bond together!
I beg you, Red-Eyes!
Bring back Jounouchi's heart!
Next time!
"Take It Back! The Red-Eyes Black Dragon of Friendship"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...