The leader of the priests...
Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Just when I thought defeating Bakura was as good as done,
time suddenly started to reverse.
My Millennium Puzzle was also taken and I was thrown down into the valley.
While I was unconscious, I started dreaming about memories of my father.
When I opened my eyes, a man called "Hasan" was in front of me.
The Great Wicked God, Zorc?
Is that my true enemy?
"The Village of Dead Spirits"
Looks as though all of you
knew I was coming.
But I didn't come to look for you guys.
I've come for the thing inside.
I'm sorry...
But what you're looking for is not inside.
What?
The stone palette that is displayed here is a mere replica.
The real tablet has been returned to its proper place.
Where is it?
What are you planning to
do after hearing it?
That's...!
The Millennium Eye!
Bakura handed this to me and gave me some ridiculous challenge.
I accepted his challenge.
Bakura?
Apart from us, he's only one who knows the secrets of the Millennium Items.
I see!
Maybe he's also...
Sister!
Go to where the stone tablet is, Seto!
You will know the truth when you are there.
Amazing!
Bobasa is amazing~!
What're they doing?
She's too relaxed for such a critical time.
Wait up!
Other Me...
Was your Millennium Puzzle taken by Bakura-kun?
Yeah, but I'll make sure I get it back.
That's an important thing that my father left for me.
Your father?
Have you regained your memories?
But a little bit... It may have been just a dream, though.
Although... I do remember my father's warmth as he held me.
My father left behind
the Millennium Items to protect the people of this country.
My father dreamed of a peaceful country.
Eh? Your father was the one who created the Millennium Items?
Yeah. That's why I can't let them be used for Bakura's ambition.
Other Me...
Speaking of which, what's your name?
You still don't know, huh...?
No one calls me by my name here.
Nobody tells me the answer
even when I ask.
Prince, let's play in the water together!
Come on!
The White Dragon resides in Kisara...
That Ka is different from any other!
It is most likely that
the White Dragon is a Ba!
Seto! You must steal
the Ka from that woman!
Kill that woman and extract the White Dragon from within her!
You will wield a God!
Lord Akhenaden always showed mercy, even to the worst sinners...
He's the highest of all priests...
Aren't you the one....
...who imparted a lot of knowledge to me When I was still a greenhorn?
Why would you...
say something like that?
Lord Seto!
We've managed to locate the Pharaoh!
What?!
The Pharaoh is-
Yes, sir!
Move the woman to
another room at once.
Don't tell anyone her location,
except for me!
Yes sir!
Isis' spirit, Spiria,
has sighted the Pharaoh!
The Pharaoh is hurt, but he's alive!
Shada is the closest to his position.
I've asked him to head
to where the Pharaoh is.
Finally we can breathe a sigh of relief.
The Pharaoh... is alive?
But...
However... It is possible that Bakura has stolen the Pharaoh's Millennium Item.
Bobasa...
Oh yes, so you're the Pharaoh?
You are...
I'm so glad that I could meet you!
His name is Bobasa, and he's like us.
The people of this world can't see him.
Apart from his name, We know nothing else about him...
But we became friends nonetheless.
That's right!
Bobasa, your friend!
I see. Nice to meet you.
The Pharaoh is my friend!
Pharaoh!
Pharaoh, are you alright?
Yes, sorry to have made you all worried.
This guy can't see us...
Hey! Where are you going, Mana?
*Shock*
Well... Um...
Since you were together with the Pharaoh, why didn't you inform us?
I'm very sorry!
This guy is scary~!
More importantly, Pharaoh, we've located Bakura's whereabouts.
What?
Upon tracking down the hoof prints,
the troops found out that he is heading for the village of Kul Elna.
Come on, let's head
to the Kul Elna village!
Yes!
Hey, wait!
We're going too!
This is the Dark Game that Bakura set up.
The Bakura in this world is not the Bakura that you know.
He's a very dangerous man whom we can't figure out.
I don't want you to put you guys at any further risk.
I will settle my scores with Bakura.
All of you must return to your world safely.
I'm very happy to see you all.
Other Me!
I'm going too!
What's with Yugi all of a sudden?
Being so distant...
But... Even though we're here, we're like ghosts.
How can we be of help?
Well...
There must be something that we can be of help with!
You're right, Yugi.
Yeah, we shouldn't give up so soon.
You're right.
Yes, I'm hungry!
So... Bakura is in Kul Elna village?
Yes.
The Pharaoh and Shada are already on their way there.
Priests, prepare to set off!
Yes!
Kul... Elna village, you said?
So this is Kul Elna village...
What a sinister aura this place has...
Since I came to this village, I feel like I can't breathe...
...like something's tearing out my heart...
What happened to this village?
Something... seems to be here...
Th-They appeared!
What in Ra's name are these things?!
The Millennium Ring is responding.
You are indeed alive, Your Highness.
Welcome to my birthplace.
This is my home field.
Pharaoh!
Master...!
Don't be afraid! Protect the Pharaoh!
Mana, I entrust the Pharaoh to you.
Prince, please leave this place first!
I, too, have been training hard!
I can fight properly!
But...
Go on, quick!
If Master was around, he would have done the same thing.
That's why I am doing this!
Please believe in me!
Mana...
I summon forth the Two-Headed Jackal Warrior!
We will stop these things here.
Please go ahead!
I'll leave this to you, Mana! Shada!
The spirits are restless.
Have they sensed the vile Pharaoh is heading this way?
Soon, you can exact your revenge!
Come on in, "Great Pharaoh"!
The Millennium Puzzle I took from you is right here around my neck!
Mana!
Mana, you...
Welcome back from the brink of death, Your Highness.
Bakura!
Hold your horses and
look on over at this thing!
Seven holes shaped like the Millennium Items...!
It's the Stone Tablet
of the Underworld!
This is the cursed tablet which connects this world to the next...
Yes! The vengeful spirits of those who were killed still linger in this place.
The soldiers used the residents of this village as living sacrifices
in order to create
the Millennium Items!
Living... sacrifices?
You should be able to see them as well...
These vengeful spirits that won't leave until they exact revenge on the royal family.
My father, Akhenamkhanen, created the Millennium Items in the name of peace...
You can't mean...!
A Pharaoh with his Millennium Puzzle stolen doesn't have the power to summon the Gods!
Dead spirits, go get him!
How's that?
Can you hear their vengeful voices?!
Tell me, Father...!
Were the Millennium Items really...?
You will pay for your father's sins with your death!
That's...!
My spirit is always with the Pharaoh!
Mahado...
You again?
So worried about this unreliable Pharaoh that you couldn't even cross over?
Please stand up, my Pharaoh.
Mahado, is that really you?
I exist together with your consciousness.
If you lose your will to fight, I would also cease to exist.
Will to fight...?
I've always believed that the Millennium Items were created in the name of justice.
Justice? Don't make me laugh!
Your father is a total sinner!
I witnessed the whole tragedy... from start to end.
I say this because I was the only survivor of this village.
There's no mistake.
Everyone was killed in order to create the Millennium Items.
My father... actually did
such a terrible thing...
It's true that the Millennium Items were created using the lives of many.
You knew it!?
I could feel the evil residing in the Millennium Ring.
And subsequently, I learned the truth of how the Millennium Items were created.
I already knew of this... atrocity.
But the former King, Akhenamkhanen, knew nothing about this.
Are you speaking the truth...?
To think that such a thing happened...
How could it have happened?
I have made a grave mistake.
But I do not want my son to bear my sins.
I beg you, Mahado.
Please protect my son.
Yes, my lord.
My father...!
The former King had wanted peace for all.
There's no mistake about that.
And you have inherited
his will as the Pharaoh!
I have...?
Stop all that talking!
Go on, dead souls! Tear both the Pharaoh and magician to shreds!
I have committed an unforgivable sin...!
This thousand-year sin...
No....! Please put the blame of the creation of seven the Millennium Items on me!
My father has always been in pain and suffered over this.
But still he taught me...
To think for the country, and to protect this country!
I believe in my father!
And I will inherit his determination and continue to fight on as the Pharaoh!
Have you regained a little of your memories?
But well, I don't give a damn about exacting revenge for these dead souls.
I'll show you my Ka!
It's coming!
Come forth, Diabound!
It's evolved even further since it fought the Gods!
I've used the resentment and vengeance in the Millennium Items to make Diabound evolve!
I have the Millennium Ring and Millennium Puzzle in my hands now!
Be careful, Mahado!
Take this! Thunder Force!!
Afterworld Warp!!
What?!
Bakura, I've been honing my skills as well while I was in the Afterworld!
My Heka has increased!
What?!
The pillar is going to land on the stone tablet!
Diabound, protect the stone tablet!
That was a close call.
Magic Blast!!
I didn't expect you
to target the stone slab...
But it's an essential tool for the resurrection of the Great Wicked God, Zorc.
The Great Wicked God, Zorc...!
It's what that man said...
That's right... My true powers are sleeping behind this door.
I summon a new Ka
to protect the stone tablet!
Bone Snapper!
A second Ka?!
Now I can concentrate on defeating the both of you.
I activate Diabound's Special Ability!
Dark Camouflage!!
Don't let it get away, Mahado!
Thousand Magic Blasts!!
There's no point in randomly lashing out at the darkness!
You're dead with this strike!
You think so...?
You missed on purpose!?
Your Diabound has nowhere to hide now!
Thousand Black Magic Blasts!!
Did we get it...?
I see...
Your level has gone up quite a bit...
Your magician as well...
But that is not enough to defeat me!
Dead spirits, come into me and grant me your powers!
All the evil vengeful thoughts that are residing in my body...
...will increase Diabound's powers!
Thousand Magic Blasts!!
What?!
Spiral Wave!!
Mahado!
I'll crush you into pieces so small, you'll never be able to enter this world again!
Thunder Summon Shot!!
Did I get him?
Mahado...!
Mana!
Master, get a grip on yourself!
I got here on time!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Yugi went after Bakura and came to an underground palace in the village of Kul Elna.
But Diabound has powered up so much because of the Millennium Items and the Dead Spirits
that even the revived Mahado couldn't do anything to it.
But Mana's spirit saved them in the nick of time.
The Priests got there as well.
The deathly duel between Bakura and the Priests starts.
Next time!
"Final Moments of the Thief Bakura"
Please look forward to it!