Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In Bakura's battle against the priests,
Bakura held an overwhelming advantage,
aiding Diabound with power from the dead spirits.
Just as Kalim fell and we thought we had no chance of victory,
the soul of my father, Akhenamkhanen,
manifested and lead the spirits into the World of the Dead.
Now, Mahado!
Finish Diabound off!
This match is over, Bakura!
"A New Stage"
After all that, we still can't enter...
If there are any clues about the other me's name, they have to be within this palace!
Other Me...
If you want to win this game, you have to obtain your lost name!
We finally understand that now.
We came to this world so we could find your true name that's been lost.
So please...
Let us enter the palace, Other... Me...
We can enter!
It's okay! We can enter!
Really?
There's gotta be a toooon of food to eat in there~!
Bobasa's gonna eat 'till he bursts!
Let's go look for the other me's name!
- Let's!
Hold up, Yugi!
Yugi!
Bobasa's coming too~!
Awesome~!
So this is the palace!
But it's so large. There's no telling where it could be around here.
Let's all split up and search!
Good idea!
Yugi... Damn you...!
Just you wait...
I'll rip all of your lives right out of you...
I'll steal all the Millennium Items and obtain the Power of Darkness for myself!
Damn it...!
It's no use, Bakura!
As long as we're holding the remaining Millennium Items,
you won't be able to break the seal on Zorc!
Shut up...!
Just give up, Bakura. You've lost.
Are you sure about that?
Lord Akhenaden!
Now everything required for the revival ritual has been gathered together!
What?!
Th-That is...!
That's Shada's Millennium Ankh!
What is the meaning of this, Lord Akehnaden?!
The time has finally come!
Wh-Where am I...?!
Just what... am I doing...?
Wh-What the...?!
What?!
Good work.
I no longer have any use for you.
That voice...!
What's going on here?!
H-Help me...!
Help m-
The rules state that when a pawn
is no longer needed, it disappears, Yugi...
Pawn?!
Lord... Akhenaden...!
Shada!
Let's see...
The Pharaoh's name...
It's no use.
Even if the other me's name is written here,
I can't read it at all!
Er...
Hey, I gotta question for you!
About the Pharaoh's-
O-Oh yeah...
We're about the equivalent of ghosts here...
It's got to be around this place somewhere...
But I can't touch any of the books...
Geez!
How am I supposed to search like this?!
Bobasa likes eating more than he likes searching!
Lemme dig in!
The "Bo" in...
Where is it?
The Eighth Key... The Pharaoh's name!
Shada!
Lord Akhenaden...! That's my Millennium Ankh...!
Please return it, Lord Akehnaden!
Let go of me!
Shada!
You half-dead worm!
Sir Akehnaden! Why are you doing this?!
Have you gone mad?!
What's the meaning of this, Akehnaden?!
Tell us your reason!
Hmph. How arrogant you are.
Lord Akhenaden! Talking to the Pharaoh with such dirty words...!
Even if it is you, Lord Akehnaden, I will not allow for it!
Shut your mouth!!
What's wrong, Seto?
I believe I said "the time has come"...
My body...
How does it feel being unable to move, Pharaoh?
What have you done, Akehnaden?!
By the power of the almighty Zorc, controller of time...
...time has been stopped.
At this moment, the only one permitted to move...
...is myself, and myself alone!
Hmph. You are an heir hardly qualified to be Pharaoh!
The Millennium Rod!
The Millennium Tauk!
And...
...the final piece lies right here!
Sir Akhenaden!
Lord Akhenaden!
Stop this!
All of the Millennium Items have now been gathered!!
Akhenaden! Place all the Millennium Items within the stone tablet!
Why...?
Why has the Dark Game not ended when Bakura is dead?
And why am I still hearing Bakura's voice,
despite him turning to sand and disappearing?!
Become or key to victory...
Resurrect the Great Evil God, Zorc!
Why?!
Why have I not won, even after defeating Bakura?!
Why has time stopped?
Just how long is this Dark Game going to continue?!
Game...?!
This is the last one.
That's it! This is...
I see you've finally awoken as the Game Master...
...Yugi.
Bakura?
What is this place?!
"This place"...?
Oh, right...
I guess you could call this
"Domain of the Gods".
This before you is the true form of the Ultimate Dark Game.
The Dark R.P.G.!
Dark R.P.G.?!
Correct.
The setting of the game is Ancient Egypt.
Yugi, this field is a reproduction of the world you lived in 3,000 years ago...
Where you ruled as Pharaoh.
As the Game Masters, we control the characters.
If you clear the conditions required for victory, you win.
Then that makes my character the Pharaoh.
And you are Thief King Bakura.
But now that Bakura has been defeated,
I should have cleared my required conditions for victory!
So then, why?
Too bad, Yugi...
Now that the seven Millennium Items
have been placed in the Stone Tablet of the Underworld,
the game has welcomed a new stage!
Naturally, the conditions for victory have changed!
My soul rests with the Stone Tablet of the Underworld!
And shall be resurrected along with the Great Wicked God, Zorc!
So in short, if I don't defeat Zorc,
I'm going to lose?
You won't just lose!
What?
All of your little precious partners who
transcended the labyrinth within the Millennium Puzzle
and snuck into the game without permission in order to find you...
...will die right where they stand.
They will die.
Curse you, Bakura!
If you want to save your little precious partners,
your only option is to beat me.
But currently, none of your characters can move.
Because of this thing's effect.
That's...
My Master Item.
The Time Controlling Hourglass.
A Master Item, you said?!
That's right.
While this item sits out on the field,
all characters I don't recognize are robbed of their movement!
Time Controlling Hourglass?
And my other item is this!
Don't you remember, Yugi?!
I used this to turn time backwards and force your little friends away from you!
That was you?!
Yes. That was the result of my Time Reversing Hourglass.
And Yugi...
I have something else to tell you.
I can activate its special effects up to three times.
Meaning I can once again...
...use my Master Item another time.
What's going on here?
Why won't my body move?!
Does this mean...
...something big is
going on with my other self?
Shit...! What the hell's going on?!
What's the deal?
Right now, the only ones allowed to move are those I acknowledge.
How is he able to move!?
No matter how much I eat, my stomach won't fill up at all!
Almighty Wicked God Zorc!
Please hear the wish I beseech of thee!
He's contacting something enormous, something terrifying...!
I feel a wave of wickedness!
You must not resurrect it!
High Priest Akhenaden...
I knew you would come here to complete the Dark Contract with me...
Because you are the one who brought the Millennium Items into this world!
Akhenaden... Rule the world!
Become the slave of my soul... and I shall grant your wish!
Yes! I have but one wish!
I wish to make my son, Seto,
into the king!
What did he...!?
Seto is...
I'm... I am...?
Lord Akhenaden's... son?
I have heard your wish!
Take my power within you, Akhenaden!
Akhenaden!
At this moment,
Akhenaden has gained the skills of a Dark Magician
and he levels up!
He's become the High Priest of Darkness!
What?!
The High Priest of Darkness?!
Yugi, you may not remember it,
but history is repeating itself exactly as it did before!
Although, some minor details have changed slightly...
But that doesn't change the fact that the history
of what happened 3,000 years ago is repeating itself once again!
Yes. Back then, you gave your own life in order to seal Zorc away.
But that won't be happening this time...
The Great Wicked God Zorc will revive...
And he shall turn this world into a paradise
of destruction and ruin!
Behold!
At my third Master Item!
What is...?!
Now that the seven Millennium Items have
been placed into the Stone Tablet of the Underworld,
the third hourglass, the Hourglass of Isolated Desperation,
can now be activated!
What?!
What's the Hourglass of Isolated Desperation?!
The last spec of sand that falls from this hourglass...
...will usher in the moment
of Zorc's revival!
I found the hidden room which holds the secrets of
all generations of the Pharaohs.
The previous Pharaoh, Akhenamkhanen.
The name of the current Pharaoh should be listed after his.
What?!
Wh-What is going on?!
His name's not written here!
Now, my Priest of Darkness.
If you eliminate the Pharaoh right now, your wish shall be granted!
H-He said my father...?
Lord Akhenaden... is my... Dad?
My father never came home after that day.
And you're telling me Lord Akhenaden
turns out to be that very same dad?!
Let me tell you, my son, Seto.
The truth that the former king, Akhenamkhanen, is my brother!
What?!
Akhenaden is the little brother of my father, Akhenamkhanen?!
That...
...is the truth that only myself and Sir Akhenaden knows of currently!
It's a secret the two of us swore to keep to ourselves!
And why now, of all times...
Why are you breaking that promise?!
Because you, my son, Seto,
are the most fitting to rule as a rightful king!
Meaning that if you rid yourself of all the obstacles,
you can steal the throne and reign over this country!
Weep as, right here and now,
Seto becomes the new king of this country!
The attack was repelled before it could make contact!
What?! He's protecting the Pharaoh!
Who is this guy?!
Bakura...
You aren't the only one
holding a Master Item, you know.
That's...!
Who are you, fiend?!
You, who dares to repel my attack and protect the Pharaoh!
My name is Hasan.
The former Pharaoh has given me the duty to protect this land of Egypt
and the great Pharaoh.
As the late Akhenamkhanen wished, I shall protect you!
Hasan...!
It's you from before...!
Who are you?
My name is Hasan.
Hasan?
Pharaoh, the Great Wicked God Zorc is about to revive.
Only you can defeat Zorc!
Hasan, or whoever you are...
If an insect like you truly has the ability to communicate
with my brother, the late Akhenamkhanen...
Tell my brother this!
That the only one deserving of having the glory to rule as king
is my son, Seto!
I shall not listen to the ramblings of someone
who heeds to the soul of the Great Wicked God Zorc to satisfy
his own desires!
What!?
The Time Controlling Hourglass...!
Now I am free to move as I please!
My friends, I mean!
M-My body...!
Why are you able to move?!
Only those I permit are supposed to be able to move!
High Priest of Darkness...
Time has begun to move once again!!
Curse you... Hasan!!
You sure did screw me over there!
But it's a little too early
to rest at ease, Yugi.
Take a look at the gauges of your pieces!
What? What do you mean, gauges?!
It's the gauge of their souls which lies on the DiaDhanks.
My piece, High Priest of Darkness,
is operating at full power level right now.
Your pieces, however...
Anyone whose gauge reaches zero crosses over...
And if the Pharaoh is injured in battle, his Ba gauge depleted...
...you yourself will die alongside him.
And not only you...
Your friends as well!
Listen up!
This includes all the people in this world!
They all have a Ba gauge!
But since most of them don't have a DiaDhank...
...it's impossible to know how much Ba they have remaining...
...and they blindly wander the city,
believing tomorrow will
come as it always does.
Goodness, what ignorant people they are.
They don't even know that the two of us are
deciding whether they live or die!
Say, Yugi...
How many civilians do you suppose
have been killed during our previous battles?
Bakura! You monster!!
Whoa, there!
Don't try to act like you're innocent!
And don't try to tell me you aren't just as responsible.
Since you were, you know, in the battles as well.
Listen well! This is a battle of Gods!
As far is this game is concerned,
the two of us are divine Gods!
And he who dominates this R.P.G....
...will become the God of all Gods!
Bakura, don't lump me together with you!
I have no intentions of becoming a god!
I just want to protect my friends and this world...
...from everything,
no matter what happens!
Prattle as much as you like, Yugi!
I plan to become the Wicked God of this world...
...and become the key that unlocks destruction and terror!
And I plan to show you...
...the end of this world as we know it!
You scum!
Too little, too late!
Because the countdown to Armageddon has begun!!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Still within the Pharaoh's Lost Memory World,
it's been revealed that the place is really a game world.
So that makes the priests and us all pieces of the game?
Now that the countdown to the release of the Great Wicked God Zorc has begun,
having become the High Priest of Darkness,
Akhenaden plans to make Seto into the next Pharaoh.
That aside, Bobasa, you say you have a purpose to fulfill in this world?
Next time!
"The High Priest of Darkness"
Please look forward to it!