A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Time's Up!
Red-Eyes Black Metal Dragon"
Alright. Their Life Points are pretty close,
but Jounouchi-kun scored a lead!
You can win, Jounouchi!
You better, for Shizuka-chan's sake!
Jounouchi! You better stay at the top!
Of course!
The game has shifted to Jounouchi boy's favor...
Based on experience, deck strength and strategy,
Jounouchi boy is nowhere near close to Keith's level.
So then, what is making up for the difference?
Oh... I see.
After Keith lost that Duel to me,
he became obsessed with alcohol and drugs,
and fell into an untouchable world of the underground gambling unit.
And...
Look! This is the proof of our friendship!
Even if we're separated...
We're always connected by this bond.
How amusing.
One side is driven by despair and revenge.
While the other is lead by hope and trust.
Seeing both of their minds, this is almost a battle of light and darkness.
But in the end, who will the Goddess of Victory smile on?
What the hell's so funny, bastard?!
Hey kid, have you ever been pushed to the far edge of sanity...
The point where you risk everything to win?
Pushed to the far edge?
I'm asking if you've ever seen hell?!
Risking everything to save yourself, no matter what the cost!
The only escape from my hell...
...is right through Pegasus!
I'll do anything I have to do to get there.
Even if it means going to hell and back!!
That's worthless.
What'd you just say?
Don't talk so big and bad.
Despair...
Revenge...
I know all about it.
But you forgot something really important!
What!?
And it's a shame, really.
You ain't gonna reach Pegasus.
Cuz I'm gonna beat you right here and now.
Now it's your turn!
What blasphemy!
I set a card face-down on the field!
And I play this guy!
I'll let you know what it feels like to gamble in hell!
Revolver Dragon is equipped with three guns, each holding three bullets.
So you have a 50/50 chance of survival!
50/50 chance...?
Here I go.
Revolver Dragon...
Gun Cannon Shot!!
My Monsters were wiped out...?
Each of the Revolver Dragon Heads has 2600 Attack Points!
Kid, the chambers will reload on my next turn, and it'll start over again!
It can attack up to three times per turn...
What a powerful card...!
He's in trouble, no matter how many Monsters he plays!
Now ain't that interesting?
In that case, I'll use this card!
Time Magician!
I'll fight a gamble with a gamble!
The Time Magician...?
Here it is! Jounouchi's trump card!
If the Time Roulette works, his Machine Monsters will all rust!
Oops... That wasn't the only card I was gonna play on the field.
It's your show time now, Baby Dragon!
With the Time Magician Combo,
he can transform into Thousand Dragon...
...and he'll blow a huge hole in your Machine Monsters!
Here goes!
Time Roulette!!
If this roulette fails, Jounouchi-kun's Monster will be wiped out...
...and he'll lose half its Attack Points out of his Life Points.
A huge gamble on luck...
Please make it!
It's slowing down!
Please...
Time Magician...
It's about to stop...
It's stopping...
Alright!
Go!
Time Magic!!
Jounouchi-kun!
Now's your chance! Attack!
Okay!
Go!!
Thousand Nose Breath!!
Alrighty!!
I annihilated that Revolver Dragon!
We'll see about that...
I told you...
That my Machine Cards are invincible!
Trap Card activate!
Trap, you said?!
Time Machine!!
W-What's that?
That capsule...!
The door's opening...
Wh-What the hell?
It's Attack and Defense went back to normal!
Go!
Gun Cannon Shot!!
Impossible...
What the hell just happened?
When one of my Monsters gets killed in combat,
I can use this Trap Card, Time Machine, to call back the Monster from a previous turn,
with its original Attack and Defense Power.
A Monster from one turn back...?
As soon as he killed the Revolver Dragon, a new undamaged one from the previous turn appeared.
I can't believe Jounouchi-kun's trump card combo was beaten this easily...
Keith really is a powerful opponent.
I memorized that pathetic deck of yours back when you fought against Kotsuzuka!
Although it's just the worthless deck of an amateur with no true strategy!
So he read right through my plan...?
Now get another Monster out.
I'm gonna show you just how worthless your cards are against my ultimate deck!
A Monster in Defense Mode...
And my turn is over.
If that's what you're gonna do, I'll also play another...
...Monster in Attack Position.
I'll then take out your Defense Monster with Revolver Dragon!
Get lost, ya weaklin'!
I still have the Red-Eyes in my hand...
But if I use it to attack that machine of his...
Revolver Dragon will just wipe it out next turn...!
Can I really play Red-Eyes that easily...?
Jounouchi...!
One after another...
Endure it, Jounouchi-kun!
There's got to be a way to turn this around.
I place a card face-down.
Then...
Red-Eyes Black Dragon in Attack Mode!
Turn over.
That card may be the strongest card in your deck with the highest Attack Power,
but it ain't no match against my Revolver Dragon!
As you wish, I'll be glad to take it out!
Revolver Dragon!
Attack the Red-Eyes!
Alright!
Set card, open!
What...?
The card I set earlier was the Mimic Illusionist card!
This guy can copy any one of your cards!
And the card I'm copying...
...is Metal Force!
Red-Eyes Black Metal Dragon!
Yes!
Thanks to the copy card, he came back from the brinks of defeat!
Counter Attack!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Revolver Dragon is beaten!
Bandit Keith!
Whether you think it's just luck or a miracle that I'm beating you,
I could care less either way!
As long as I win, I can save Shizuka's eyes...
I strongly believe that!
You'd better enjoy your gloating while you can.
I have a ton of different ways to beat you!
I'll show you that a worthless amateur's no-strategy deck
don't stand a chance against a pro!
The key to victory is the difference in our skill level!
Huh?!
"Difference in our skill level", heh?
But your Life's been falling lower than mine~
Don't bullshit me!
It's my turn!
One card face-down on the field!
Slot Machine goes to Defense Mode...
...and my turn's over!
That Machine Monster only has 2300 Defense Points...
My Red-Eyes can take it down!
My turn!
I set a card face-down!
Attack the Slot Machine!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Then I'll use this face-down card!
7 Card!!
What?
The number seven just appeared on the Slot Machine...
What in the world?
This card is a power unit that increases the Slot Machine's Defense Power.
It raises Slot Machine's Defense Power by 700 points, up to 3000!
So Red-Eyes' attack won't work!
The attack bounced back, and my Life Points...!
Jounouchi!
Now he can't lay a hand on the Slot Machine!
Now it's my turn again.
The Slot Machine's Attack or Defense...
I can choose to power up either one with the 7 Card!
That's a total of 2100 points in damage!
I'm gonna show you the true difference in our skill level.
I'm gonna use another 7 Card this turn!
I use this to raise its Attack Power by 700 points!
This asshole...
So he's just gonna keep on increasing its Attack Power while it's in Defense Mode...?
Not good...
If he uses one more of those 7 Cards on the Slot Machine,
it'll have 3400 Attack Points!
Even the Red-Eyes stands no chance!
I'm gonna play another card as well!
Sphere Bomb!!
Wh-What the hell is this thing?
It's a time bomb, set to go off on your next turn,
that'll inflict 2900 points of damage!
What'd you say?!
If this thing self-destructs...
Red-Eyes will be...!
Turn over!
Time's up, kid!!
Blow to hell!
IDIOT!!
Huh?
What the frig?!
That sure was a close one.
This thing really saved me back there.
"Dark Claws of the Dragon-Types"
An Equipment Card...!
His Attack goes up by 600 points?!
He likes to make people worry about him...
I can't believe my Life gets slashed instead!
Turn over!
This damn brat...!
In that case...
I'm gonna use another 7 Card on my turn...
...to bring up its Attack Power!
Both Monsters have the same Attack Points...
And both Jounouchi and Keith have practically the same amount of Life Points...!
The match will be decided this turn.
I have a card in my hand that could turn the tables...
But if I use that now, it'll only further my disadvantage...
If you ain't gonna make a move, I'll take my turn now.
Kid, I praise you for makin' it this far against me.
But this is as far as you go!
Take a look at this card!
Bandit!!
Wh-What?!
The Bandit card allows me to look at the opponent's hand and take any card I want.
Now which one...?
Shield and Sword, eh...?
Now ain't this a nice card?!
I'll be takin' it!
It's over for ya, kid.
Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand!
Slot Machine goes to Attack Mode!
Plasma Laser Cannon!!
Set Card, open!!
No use!!
FIRE!!
I wi-
What!?
The Graverobber card...?!
There's no way...!
He stole the Time Machine card from my Graveyard?!
I'm not exactly proud of beating you by stealing, but...
The Time Machine card can bring back a Monster from the previous turn...
Which means...!
That's right!
Meaning one turn back...
The offense and defensive switch didn't happen yet!
So the Red-Eyes Black Metal Dragon revives at full strength!
Eat this!!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Impossible...!
As great as I am...
I lost to that kid...?!
In this battle of hope and despair...
...the Goddess of Victory has smiled on the side of hope.
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Jounouchi!
And the winner is... Jounouchi!
I DID IT~!!
You did it, Jounouchi!!
I did it, Shizuka...
I really did it, Mai!
This Duel is invalid!!
What'd you say?!
There's a limit to how low you can go!
The entry card he showed wasn't even his!
He wasn't even permitted to participate in this Duel from the start!
You're right.
I couldn't find my card anywhere.
So Mai gave me her card in its place!
But, you know...
How the heck did you know this wasn't my card in the first place?
Ain't it a bit strange?
Hey! How the hell'd you know that?!
The answer is simple.
Bandit Keith...
You stole Jounouchi boy's card!
Wh-What?!
You bastard!
Is that true?!
In that case, you're the unforgivable one here!
I personally could care less whose card it is.
What I can't forgive is you cheating during the Duel just now.
He cheated?!
Keith...
You added the 7 Card you kept hidden in your wristband to your hand.
Unfortunately for you, no one can fool my eyes.
Keith, you lousy scumbag!
And you shall be ejected from the kingdom!
Let go of me!!
Get the hell off me!
Dammit!
Pegasus!
You won't get away with this!
That was an excellent Duel.
Jounouchi boy.
PEGASUS!!
You sure are a persistent one.
Hand over the prize money!
Otherwise I'll take your life right here!
To see the once renowned "Prize King" like this...
You have clearly lost the mind necessary for a Duelist,
as I witnessed first hand in the match just now.
Don't you bullshit me!
Where the hell's the prize money!?
I would like the small fry to disappear!
Now then, excusing the interruption that just occurred,
we shall now begin the final round of the tournament...
...featuring Yugi Mutou versus Katsuya Jounouchi.
So the time has finally come...
Yugi.
The time for me and Jounouchi-kun to fight each other.
"Preview"
They did it!
Yugi and Jounouchi made it to the final round!
Wait, hold on a second!
That means the two have to fight each other?!
We can't allow that!
Aren't they best friends?!
Jounouchi, just leave it to Yugi!
Eh?
Because you're best friends, you'll fight at your best?
You can't!
Next time!
The Final Game of Friendship! Yugi VS Jounouchi.
Part 1.
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship