With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Gods of Thunder, Water, and Wind!
Now's the time to gather your power and revive!
That's...!
Come forth, Triple Demon God!
GATE GUARDIAN!
You guys will have to fight our combined power first!
Here I go!
COME!
"Dragon of the Devil:
Black Demon's Dragon"
Shit! There's nowhere to run!
What should I do, Yugi?
THUNDER SHOT!
He's done for!
Alright. We defeated Flame Swordsman.
Is that so?
What?
The Trap Card Mirror Force!
This protects the Flame Swordsman!
Yugi!
Gate Guardian!
Reflection!!
Storm Barricade!!
Gate Guardian is...
...untouchable!
But the other Monsters on your board aren't safe from the attack.
Monster Tamer is beaten!
Damn you...!
Great job you two!
Yes!
Keep it up, Jounouchi!
Got it!
Did you find him?
No, he's nowhere in sight!
He's got to be hiding somewhere down here.
Anyway, just wait at guard in front of Mokuba's cell.
and you keep searching for Kaiba!
Roger!
Yes! It's my turn!
Jounouchi-kun, focus on the enemy's body.
The 3 parts of thunder, water, and wind that make up
the Triple Demon has three separate parts each holding their own Attack Points.
If we destroy it section by section, we can defeat it!
I saw that too.
My turn!
Flame Swordsman! Use Salamandra's fire and attack the Demon Wind God!
Go!
what?!
Fool. Don't underestimate the power
of the Triple Demon God!
It's my turn!
Launch a counter-attack against Flame Swordsman!
Aqua Wave!
This is bad!
Black Magician can avoid the attack
by hiding in the hat...
But that's impossible for Flame Swordsman.
Because it's a water-based attack,
the Fire-type will receive a 300 point penalty.
Flame Swordsman is beaten!
Shit!
We almost made it out of the labyrinth too...!
No, this turn wasn't a waste.
My turn.
I set a card on the board.
I'll play Demon's Summon and follow in the Flame Swordsman's footsteps.
But that attack...
did not even get close to Gate Guardian's....
...side!
Is that so?
Didn't I tell you?
The footsteps have already been placed in the maze.
That's...!
The ground of the maze was flooded!
That means....!
Here I go!
Demon Lightning!!
Alright! We did it!
It's useless! It's impossible for you
to break through Gate Guardian's Defense!
Let me re-introduce you to the Water Wall!
Reflection!!
Wh-what's wrong?
It's a pity.
Didn't the Black Magician get attacked while inside the Magic Silk Hat?
That second this Trap Card was activated!
What?!
The Hexagram Curse was attached to the Black Magician all this time!
Tr-Trap Card!?
Hexagram Curse!
And their Attack is lowered by 700 points!
The water section is destroyed!
Look at that! Thunder, water and wind were all no match for Yugi!
ALRIGHT!
Alright!
In order to beat it, we need to do it from the bottom up!
My turn!
The Remove Trap card!
The Hexagram Curse is canceled!
The Gate Guardian is back!
Your turn now!
My turn!
Jounouchi-kun, it's time to play our trump card.
This is my card!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Also, I play the Fusion Magic Card I had hidden on the board!
Fuse with Demon!
Th-that is...!
The Devil Dragon...
Black Demon's Dragon!
This is our team's ultimate Monster!
Right. What will you do, Labyrinth Brothers?
Why are you guys laughing!?
You fools. What can that monster possibly do to us?
That's right.
The flying type Black Demon's Dragon
can't move around in the maze!
Oh no!
You can't mean...!
Yes. Only walking units can move
about in the Maze Field.
Yugi, it looks like I screwed up big time!
What should I do?
Don't worry. I've got a plan!
I knew you'd find a way...
My turn is finished!
My turn.
I just drew a scary card.
The Magic Card Force!
You said Force?!
Oi, what's that?
It's a legendary ultra-rare
Magic Card...!
Right!
This card steals half of the
opponent's Life Points
and adds them to the Attack Points
of any Monster you choose!
What'd you say?!
Half our Life Points?!
This is bad!
And...
the Attack Points of Gate Guardian go up!
No way!
This isn't good!
I am unable to attack in the same
turn I played this Magic Card.
But next turn
if I combine the power of thunder and wind, the result will be devastating!
No matter what you do,
next turn you're finished.
Jounouchi-kun, I told you that we still have a chance!
It's my turn!
Alright. This turn I'll move Black Magician
into the labyrinth.
Black Magician, advance 7 spaces!
Foolish. Don't forget that the second you exit this maze
our Gate Guardian is waiting there to attack you.
Listen up! We'll continue to press on no matter
what obstacles stand in our way!
As long as there's a shred of chance!
And with that we've left the maze!
Also...
I play this card on the board!
Resurrection of the Dead!
No matter what monster you've revived,
It's too late...
My turn!
Gate Guardian, attack Black Magician!
Combo attack!
MAGIC SHOCK WAVE!!
Alright. Once we defeat Black Magician,
Yugi's Life Points will drop to 0.
Then we win!
Your attack is useless!
Demon Water God, Reflection!
What?!
The Water Wall we created makes your Magic Whirlwind invalid!
He used his Resurrection of the Dead card to revive the Demon Water God, Suuga!
He's become their ally?!
Amazing, Yugi!
Great move man!
They made it through this round...
But...
Though they made it through this turn...
You bastards... our attacks did nothing against them....
Alright! It's Jounouchi-kun's turn!
There has to be...
There has to be a way to defeat it...!
Next turn, they'll definitely destroy Suuga....
Well, there's no way for me to stop their attack.
Everything depends on
Jounouchi-kun's next card!
Mimic Illusionist?
It copies any card played on the board...?
I got a great idea!
I use this card to give you pay back from that Force earlier!
I'm gonna take half your Life Points
and add them to our guy's Attack!
To Black Demon's Dragon's!
Jounouchi-kun!
Fool! How many times must I say it?!
Black Demon's Dragon is not allowed to cross the maze!
My turn!
I'll use Demon Wind God Hyuga's wind to attack the Water Demon Suuga!
Water Demon!
Reflection!
I knew you'd use that trick...!
Take this!
Thunder Shot!!
Why?
Suuga can only use its Reflection once per turn...
Yugi, you've got no way to block our attacks.
Next turn, we win!
Didn't you realize it?
Don't you know the real reason
I brought Black Magician out of the maze?
What did you say?!
The Monster Replace Magic Card.
This card switches my Monsters,
placing the ones with the highest Attack Points in front.
I-It can't be...!
If he gets even one monster out of the maze...
he can switch that one with any other monster he has?!
Here I go!
Without the Attack Points of Suuga added
it can't stand up to the powered up Black Demon's Dragon!
Meteor Flare!!
What now?!
We win!
YAHOO!
They did it!
Which means...!
Yugi and Jounouchi...
have...
10 STAR CHIPS!
Yes!
We earned the right to the castle!
The game is still not...
FINISHED YET!
What did you say?!
What's wrong?
Big brother? Is that you, big brother?
Mokuba, are you okay?
Big brother!
I always believed you'd save me...!
Always...!
We'll always be together?
I promise.
Mokuba...
Brother, I didn't give anyone the key!
Mokuba!
I protected Kaiba Corporation!
Wait, I'll get you out!
Bravo!
It's touching to see you two together!
Pegasus...!
If you told me you were coming, I would have arranged for a better welcome.
I don't need you to worry about me.
What's with the cold treatment?
What do you mean?
You can have as many Star Chips as you want!
But, are you forgetting something?
Only if you actually walk out of this labyrinth have you actually obtained victory.
I didn't forget!
Now, why don't you tell us which door leads out of the labyrinth?
We'll tell you only one thing...
Only one of these is the real door!
That's not fair. You two lost! You should tell us which is the real one!
Now! Which is the real door!?
I knew you'd be like this...
Jounouchi, what do you think?
You think I'd know?
No...
Oi, Yugi. What do we do?
We'll use these to decide.
So he depends on God in the end?
I'll hold a coin in both my right and left hands.
The coin that remains in my hand
will decide what door we pick.
Pegasus... I don't know what you're planning...
but I won't let you have Kaiba Corporation!
You tell me this now?
What do you mean?
Here I go!
So that's the 'Ze' coin.
So the one in your hand is 'Ma'.
So you've chosen 'Ma'.
Shit... Which one's the right one?
'Ma'.... Or...
'Ze'?
The right answer is....
the 'ze' door!
How come?
As I thought.
What are you talking about?
There is no right answer.
If I picked 'Ma', you'd say 'ze'.
If I chose 'ze', you'd say 'Ma'!
So that was it.
Stop screwing around!
Unfortunately for you, you could not say the right answer!
We win the game!
What a pity.
What I chose...
is 'Ze!
The coin in my hand wasn't just marked 'Ma'.
only 'Ze' is a single-sided coin.
From the start, this coin was marked as
both 'Ma' and 'ze'.
You just got screwed!
I forgot to tell you.
I wasn't honest about which hand
held the double-sided coin.
YES! Everyone onto Pegasus's castle!
Mokuba!
That's...!
What the hell did you do?!
It's just a small trick.
Tell me! What did you do to Mokuba?!
This is a Soul Sealing Card.
I'll be looking after Mokuba boy's soul for a bit.
What did you say?
If you want Mokuba boy back,
you'll have to defeat me in a Duel.
Fine! I challenge you right now!
You can't fight me right now.
First you must fight with Yugi boy.
You can only face me
if you defeat Yugi boy.
"Preview"
We defeated the Maze Brothers' trap and finally
got out of the maze.
When Yugi's in a Duel, he's always so confident.
But normally, he's not very reliable.
We must hurry to Pegasus's castle.
There's not much time left!
Huh? Is that Kaiba-kun blocking the castle's gate?
You want to duel on top of the castle?!
Next time! "The Destined Duel! Yugi VS Kaiba"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship