Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Truth of the Ishtars Revealed"
Has the Ra card been translated yet?
Yeah...
I linked to Industrial Illusion's central computer,
and it's in the process of deciphering it.
Wh-What the...?
Big brother?
Impossible...!
I can understand what this text says!
And it tells about Ra's Special Abilities!
It's terrifying...!
Those letters are Hieratic Text!
The chosen ones can
read it with their hearts!
And the one standing beside the king, the Pharaoh...
The "White Beast Handler" Priest.
And the creature above him...
The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
This can't be...
That vision I saw before...
Was it a memory?!
Wh-What's wrong?!
Big brother?!
What... is happening to me...?!
Big brother...?
Today's Battle Tournament has come to a close with four Duelists advancing to the Semi-Finals!
The Semi-Finals will take place tomorrow morning at the third and final Dueling arena, as we leave the Battle Ship!
Over and out!
"The third Duel arena"?
I get it.
I guess we're leaving
Domino City altogether.
I wonder what the third arena is like!
I could care less where the Semi-Finals take place!
Yugi! Let's make it to the Finals!
Yeah!
Yugi... You and the
other Yugi must be tired.
Yeah... A lot has happened today, after all.
Too many people have gotten hurt from this tournament...
I didn't know this
fight would be so hard...
Anyway, let's head to Mai's room.
Mmm!
Ishizu-san...
I, too, am worried
about this poor woman.
May I join you...?
Shizuka...
How's Mai?
Mai...
Hang in there, Mai!
I'll beat Malik for you!
Big brother...
I know you tell me to be stronger,
but I can't take much more of this!
Mai-san...! Bakura-san...!
Everyone who has fought...!
Shizuka...
This isn't... the world I wanted to see!
Shizuka-chan...
I'm sorry, Shizuka...
No matter what happens...
...we mustn't turn away from anything.
Miss...
Even if our world is full of sadness,
there are those who who reach out with open arms with hopes of merely catching a glimpse of it.
Dating all the way back to Ancient Egyptian times,
us Tomb Guardians have
had countless losses
in order to protect our mission.
The Tomb Guardians...
To protect the great power kept within the Millennium Items!
Ishizu-san, you're Malik's sister,
aren't you?
Please tell me...
Why does Malik want to kill me?
Why does Malik's dark side want to take everyone's lives?
Yugi...
The chosen one, who houses the Pharaoh's soul...
Ishizu-san!
All right.
I will tell you...
The tragic past of the Ishtar family!
We, the Ishtar clan, are descendants of the Tomb Guardians
who protected two Millennium Items and the location of the Pharaoh's memories.
We lived deep underground,
away from the rest of the world...
The eldest sons of the clans had to undergo the Rite of the Tomb Guardians,
and have the Glyphs of the Pharaoh's memory carved into their backs.
That was the life imposed on my younger brother Malik.
The tragedy took place five years ago...
One year after Malik
underwent the ritual.
I said I'm going!
Big sister!
Malik! Lower your voice!
Don't worry!
Father should be
asleep about now.
Haven't we been planning this day for a while now?!
If I pretend like I'm sleeping,
Father will never notice I left the tunnels!
But if Father finds out,
we're in big trouble!
That will mean you
broke the law of the clan...
He will never forgive us...
Don't worry!
If anything happens,
Rishid will take care of it!
Right?
Sister... I... want to see what it's like out there...
No matter what...
Please!
Just this once!
Lady Ishizu... I will cover for him.
Please make Lord Malik's
wish come true.
Big sister...
All right.
Let's leave in the morning.
Alright!
But, hear me out...
After one hour, we will come back immediately.
Right!
For the first time in his entire life, Malik felt the light of the sun wrap around his entire body.
Wow!
So this is what the town is like!
There's so many people!
Malik, don't go
touching anything of this world.
I know!
How terrible...
Stepping on a book like that...
These pictures look so real!
How interesting!
What's that... thing?
Malik?
Hey boy, is seeing a television that rare for you?
Come along, Malik!
That's awesome!
There were people walking and talking in that box!
It's a TV.
I see!
The guy in the TV was riding some strange machine!
What was it?
A motorcycle.
A motorcycle!
That's awesome!
Even if I go on living,
there's no way I can ride a motorcycle...
Sister?
Malik, it's time!
Let's go back!
Already?
We can't stay here any longer!
That was our agreement!
I know...
Then at least...
Let me keep this
page with the motorcycle!
No way!
What'll we do if Father finds it?!
Please?
Guess I've got no choice...
Just don't let Father find it!
Now let's go!
The nameless Pharaoh's soul is about to be revived.
The Pharaoh?!
Who are you?!
Tomb Guardians... A fate of bloodshed and tragedy awaits you.
And this tragedy is the Pharaoh's will.
Seek out the Pharaoh.
Just who...?!
Wait!
Tragedy...
The Pharaoh's will?
That man has to be Shadi!
There's no doubt.
This man appears before anyone tied to the Millennium Items.
I broke the laws of my clan...
By exposing Malik to the outside world,
our family was fated to walk on a road of destruction.
He's gone...!
That guy had an ankh around his neck...
It looked a lot like the Rod and Tauk our family keeps secret...
Malik!
Never speak of what you saw here!
S-Sorry...
Just forget that today ever happened!
Everything you saw in this world...
And that man just now as well!
So we really have to go back down, don't we...?
Malik, follow right behind me.
Sister, just a second!
Malik!
Okay...
Don't make a sound.
Big sister, what's... that?
There's a contraption
on the back of the door!
It was dark when we left,
so I didn't notice it...
What's wrong, Sister?
Rishid!
Sister!
What's wrong with you?!
Forgive us, Father!
Rishid!
Lord Mal-
Malik!
Ishizu!
Watch closely!
This is punishment for breaking the law of our tribe!
This pitiful servant has suffered first because of you!
Rishid...
Malik?
And Malik, it's your turn next!
Malik...! You lousy...!
You intend to defy me?!
I thank you for killing off Rishid...
My dear father!
I feel so much better!
M-Malik?!
Malik... What's gotten into you...?
This is mine from now on.
You mustn't! I forbid you to touch the Millennium Items!
I think this thing accepts me...
Put that down immediately!
SHUT UP ALREADY!
Malik, you bastard!
I can't move...!
Malik! What are you trying to do?!
You stay out of this!
You... aren't Malik...
Let's start with your bloodbath,
my dear father.
Stop it...!
Now then...
That girl's the only one left, eh?
Lord Malik...!
He's still alive...!
Won't you stay dead?!
Lord Malik!
Rishid...
Just what...?
You mustn't look!
Father...?
Father!!
Lord Malik!
You're...!
The one who caused this destiny was the soul of the great Pharaoh.
The Pharaoh will revive soon.
Go search for the Pharaoh, Malik!
Pharaoh?!
My soul...
...caused Malik and his family's tragedy?
But even so...!
No matter what
reason he has for doing it,
I can't forgive him!
Mai's... fighting for her life as we speak because of Malik's Power of Darkness!
And if Malik isn't beaten...
Mai's life will...
If I entrust the cleansing of Malik's dark side to you people...
...there may still be a chance to save Malik from a future shrouded in darkness!
So please use your
strength to help Malik...!
The shipboard lights will be turned off at twelve.
Will all tournament participants please return to their rooms by that time...
Big brother.
We'll watch over Mai-san.
That's right.
We should get to sleep.
"Get to sleep"...?
And where are
you guys goin' to do that?
Well, we can't stay here.
That leaves us with your room.
Ya freakin' serious...?
No helping it, I guess...
We'll leave her to you. Shizuka, Anzu.
Yup!
Yugi, I haven't forgotten our promise!
When the time
to fight you again comes,
I'll go at you with everything I got, and I'll beat ya!
Oh yeah!
Can't you ask Ishizu-san if you and Yugi-san will battle each other in the Final match?
D-Don't ask such outrageous things!
I no longer hold the
power to see the future.
From the moment the future changed when I fought Seto Kaiba.
So Kaiba-kun...
To restore the Pharaoh's memories,
you will need the remaining five Millennium Items and the three God Cards.
This belonged to you originally.
With this, part of my mission as a Tomb Guardian has been fulfilled.
Let's head back to
your room before lights out.
Yeah.
Good night everyone.
Sleep well!
-Night!
Now I have two Millennium Items...
Ishizu-san!
Wait!
Please tell me...
When all seven Millennium Items are fitted into the slab in the hidden temple in Egypt...
Will Yugi...?
What will happen to the other Yugi?!
Miss...
All souls have a place to return.
A place... to return...?
Can't sleep?
Other me!
What were you thinking about?
When all the Millennium Items
are gathered,
I'll have to go to Egypt.
I was wondering if your memory would return after we did that?
It's my duty as your vessel to help you get your memory back, after all!
When that time comes...
Let's get some rest!
The Finals will be held tomorrow!
Right...
Partner...
Rishid... The darkness of death has come for you...
As long as you are alive, it is an inconvenience to me.
Bakura...?
I brought a friend.
This is your other half.
A piece of Malik!
I forgot that he implanted a part of himself in Bakura
when he brainwashed Bakura's vessel with the Millennium Rod's powers.
I won't let you kill Rishid!
I expect you to keep up your end of the bargain.
I'll be taking that Millennium Rod!
Oh yeah. You're a Millennium Item collector, right?
If you hand it over quietly, I won't make you a part of my collection of souls.
Well now... Shall I tear you apart like the puzzle you are?
Just try it.
Die!
Why don't you stick around a while?
I'm going to kill Rishid.
Then it's your turn.
My arm...!
Bastard!
Your power is nothing!
Those who were chosen by the Millennium Items...
...must settle things in a Dark Game.
My pleasure...
The rule is, whoever loses disappears!
Nothing more.
Bring it on!
"Preview"
In order to beat Malik's dark half,
Bakura-kun works together with the part of Malik within Bakura-kun's vessel, in a Tag Duel.
And as always, the two wielders of a Millennium Item fight with a Dark Game.
But the loser's body is eaten!
Just what kind of Duel is this?
When Bakura-kun's Life dropped, his body began to disappear...!
Next time!
"(Dark) Malik VS (Dark) Bakura"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise