Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
"The Blue-Eyed Kisara"
Mahado!
Master!
Master~!!
Mana...
Prince!
You can call the spirits from the stone slabs, can't you?!
Please...!
Please let me see my master again!
Mana...
Until Mahado is able to heal his wounded soul from the previous battle,
no one will be able to call for him.
Besides, even if we could call Mahado...
your Heka isn't great enough for you to see spirits yet!
Lady Isis...!
You must train harder, Mana.
So you can inherit Mahado's will!
Master...!
I swear to become a great magician!
I swear!
I swear!!
This is the Other Me's...
...Memory World!
So you've finally found it?
The True Door.
This is as far as I can guide you.
Beyond this point lies a vigorous world where only the Pharaoh
can recall its memories
from within his heart.
Now, he who has been chosen by the Millennium Puzzle!
Be courageous and go on ahead!
Right!
But by "go on", you mean...
How do we?
What!?
Yugi!
Dammit!
Here goes!
The most important thing is whether or not Mahado killed Bakura.
If he got away, there's a good chance he's stolen the Millennium Ring.
However, if we wish to confirm the truth of this matter, based on the scale of that cave-in,
it could take several weeks to remove all the rubble.
If Bakura takes hold of the Millennium Ring during that time frame...
Miss Isis... Can you see Bakura's future with the Millennium Tauk?
No... I can see nothing.
This is all because of
Mahado's incompetence.
Isis, I am most certain you saw Mahado's actions in the future before this happened.
I am terribly sorry.
The fact that you cannot see Bakura's future is rather questionable...
I'll send my Ka, Spiria, to the valley and use her Clear Voyance
to search while I stay here.
I leave it to you, Isis!
Great Pharaoh.
This has become quite an urgent matter after what we have experienced.
As such, I would like to take my troops so we can scour the city.
My Pharaoh!
If we let this continue, we will continue to let our tears of sadness flow into the Nile!
We must act!
Please allow me to head a search for Bakura!
Certainly, since we do not know if Bakura is alive or dead,
a search would be for the best.
Understood.
But whatever you do, you must not threaten the people!
Yes sir!
Hey!
We really went to Ancient Egypt!
Yeah...
Say, don't you think we stand out in these get-ups?
You're probably right...
But no one seems to have taken notice of us.
No way that's true.
I'm sure they're all staring at us like we're suspicious or something...
Or not...!
See...
Miss!
You don't think we look suspicious or anything, do yo-
Wh-What?!
She walked right through me!
The Millennium Puzzle's gone!
I see. This is my other self's
Memory World.
In this world, no one knows who we are.
In other words, to the people of this world, we don't even exist.
So that means even the other Yugi can't see us?!
I'm not really sure...
But as long as we still remember him...
I'm sure he still...
Seto, do you truly believe that Bakura is still alive?
What a foolish question.
His Ka had enough power within it to fight against a God on equal ground.
Did you not witness that yourself back there?
Mahado died in vain.
The situation has gotten even worse.
You mean the Millennium Ring was...
I do.
If he puts on the Millennium Ring, I have no doubt that his evil will grow.
If we do not reinforce our alignment of Ka,
he will eventually become something we cannot handle.
Shada...
Your Millennium Ankh has the power to search people's souls.
Among the commoners, there must be some who have powerful Ka within their souls.
There's no way!
Even if we are Holy Priests, we are not permitted
to look into the souls of the innocent!
Then tell me this...
If we were to fight Bakura again now that he holds the Millennium Ring in our present state,
do you believe we could oppose him?
Or do you instead intend to put the Pharaoh in danger once again
by relying on the power of the Gods?!
Stop!
Shada, Mahado's actions were foolish.
Even so, we cannot allow the will he had to fight against Bakura's God-like powers
by himself go to waste!
Search anyone and everyone!
Those dressed suspiciously, those unprecedented, insubordination...
I want you to round up anyone who seems questionable, regardless of their age...
...and bring them here on the double!
...increasing...
It's increasing!
At this rate, the fear and despair will continue to increase!
Ah, Lord Priest!
Just what crime am I being suspected of?!
You have yet to commit any sin.
But the chances of you doing so eventually are very high.
Th-That can't be!
Lemme go, goddamn you all!
Lord Seto, we have captured an escaped criminal in the local bar.
I can't believe you
actually found a criminal...
Shada, search this man's Ka.
Millennium Ankh!
Show me this man's soul!
An evil Ka has been created within this man's wicked mind.
It's not at a very high Heka...
But if we leave it be, it could cause trouble again.
So it's trash then...?
But if there's any chance for it to grow stronger...
Lock him up!
Yes, sir!
Pl-Please wait!
I just made it out of the desert alive!
I swear I haven't committed any crimes after doing so!
The very fact we confirmed an evil Ka resides within you,
more or less confirms that you've committed crimes.
That's freakin' outrageous!
If y'all do this to me,
you're gonna be cursed!
I seen it wit' my own eyes!
I seen a God flyin' 'round right smack in the middle of the desert!
It was thanks to it that I was able to survive and make it back to the city!
That's right!
I was guided here by the White Dragon!
What?! Did you just say the White Dragon?!
I wasn't mistaken, no sir!
The White Dragon is in this city!
I know for a fact that it's 'round here watchin' over me this very minute!
The White Dragon's... in this city?
Let's go!
Seto!
Hold on!
You're really gonna be punished for this!
You're gonna be punished by the White Dragon!!
Wait for me!
Hey! H-Hold it...
Wait up!
Geez, what's wrong with you, Jounouchi?!
I'm so hungry I can't even move!
Eh?! We're like ghosts
right now, you know!
You can't be hungry!
Even if you put it like that...
I'm starving, too!
Honda! Not you, too!
But we can't touch anything here.
So that means we can't eat anything either.
What?! You serious?!
Huh?
Ain't that guy pretty weird?
How so?
He's sitting there stuffing his face like a pig,
but no one even notices.
Oh! You're right!
Then that means...
- Hey!
- Let us eat those~!
Wait up!
So you really can see us!
No way!
- Why, you...!
-Why, you...!
- Damn you!
Gotcha now!
- C'mon!
- The heck?
Just get out of this city!
Got no doubt this woman's a witch!
Yeah! Yeah!
Hey, you jerks! Whad'daya mean, ganging up on her?!
We can't stand guys...
- ...who pick on the weak!
Are you alright?!
Damn, I forgot these guys can't see us!
The stones are going right through us!
Damn! Ain't there anything we can do?!
What's gong on here?!
You gotta be kidding!
Kaiba?!
Kaiba-kun!
What's wrong, Seto?
Wh-What is this...!?
Th-This woman's Heka... is far too much for the Ankh to measure!
It's an enormous Heka!
Shada!
I-I never would have imagined she would be holding so much Heka...!
What?!
There's an enormous...
...Heka inside of this woman?
Take this woman into custody immediately!
Give her sufficient water and food!
Then nurse her back to good health!
Yes, sir!
Scurry along, vicious beasts!
Otherwise, I will arrest every single one of you remaining here!
Nice one, Dude-Who-Looks-Like-Kaiba!
Yugi, look!
Mm-hmm!
Those two are holding the Millennium Rod and the Millennium Ankh!
That must mean...
That man is the same priest carved onto the Stone Slab of Memories.
No one is to speak of this to the Pharaoh!
We don't have the luxury to be merciful and lenient as in the past.
Shada, let's return to the palace.
Hey...! He just said "palace"!
So if we follow those two...!
We should be able to see the other me!
Okay! Then let's get going to the palace!
Mhm!
Sweet!
This place is too much!
Come on and hurry up, guys!
Look, the doors are...!
The hell're we gonna do now?!
They closed the doors!
Don't get your undies in a twist!
'Cause we're ghosts here, you see!
A measly little door ain't stoppin' nobo-
Jounouchi-kun!
What in the hell's going on here?!
I smashed right into the thing!
He's right.
So that means we can't enter the palace?
Bobasa and friends can't go in there!
- It's you!
I'm Bobasa!
I was a wee bit surprised back there,
but now I see you people aren't bad guys!
Bobasa saw you guys trying to help that woman that collapsed back there!
You guys're good people!
That's why~
- The hell?!
I'ma giving you these!
- FOOD~!
Say, why can you touch things in this world?
That's because... Uhhh...
Bobasa don't know!
- He ate it!
Hey, how do we enter the palace?
Bobasa's got no idea!
- He ate it again!
Hey, how-
- Don't ask him anything, Anzu!
Bobasa gets really hungry whenever he has to think!
- S-See?!
- So don't ask him anything right now!
Then what do you propose we do about this then?!
Bobasa hasn't a clue!
- He's gonna eat them!
Other Me...
I want to see you right away!
A voice called out to me just now!
Is it midnight yet?
Yeah, the moonlight has spread far.
If something happens,
we'll notice immediately.
Very true.
This time I attack at night.
Like a thief should.
In our Ultimate Dark Game,
something big that happened 3,000 years ago is about to happen in a few days.
He's already called out one of the three God Cards
that were not able
to be summoned prior.
I need to have him call out the others right away.
But I have one more
thing I must prepare...
After getting the Millennium Ring and furthering the evolution of Diabound...
...I can now erase my very presence right under your noses!
Lord Akhenaden!
Seto...
I bring you my report.
The Ka hunt in the city went much better than expected.
As I thought, there were many people in the city hiding superior Ka.
Don't tell me, Seto...
You mean you arrested those people?!
You mean to say I shouldn't have?
Seto... It's not too late.
Let those innocent people go free!
Sin creates fear in one's heart!
Fear leads one to endless darkness!
Lord Akhenaden.
When you compare us to the commoners...
What do you propose is the difference between us?
Faced with the fall of the dynasty, we, too, are faced with immeasurable fear!
All that I do is for Pharaoh and our great country of Egypt!
I do not believe I have done anything wrong.
Seto...
I still have work left to complete.
Excuse me.
Oh, Seto...! You're...
...trying to walk down the same mistaken path I once did?!
Y-You are...
Bakura!
What is the woman's condition?
Yes, sir! She is still asleep.
I see.
The White God with blue eyes...
No, that's not all it is...
The being that lies within her heart...
I know this woman...!
We picked up somethin' nice!
It's pretty rare for this country!
Havin' white hair and blue eyes like that!
We'll follow ya!
Who are you?!
Sssh!
I'll let you out.
Come!
You little-
Now!
They got away!
The girl ran away!
Are they following us?!
No!
Good. I'll give you this horse.
Go on alone from here on out.
If you keep straight on this path, you'll reach the nearest town shortly.
Then you'll have to do
what you can to escape!
Go!
What is your name?!
Seto!
Thank you, Seto!
Thank you!!
That's...
...my village!
Damn them...!
Damn them!
Mother!!
Keep looking!
Hey!!
Where's that blue-eyed brat?!
I-I don't know...!
Mother!
Mother!!
You're the kid from before!
Where'd that girl go?!
Move!
Wait!
Let go of me!
Let go!
Mother!
Wh-What the hell's that?!
It's a monster!
Run!
That's right...
This is the same girl from that time...
And I've seen the White Dragon myself...
Hey, geezer!
When you're that slow, the match'll be over before you even summon our your Ka!
All right, old man!
Ripping the Millennium Eye right from you would be a simple task, but...
...I have a little job
I'd like you to do for me...
Just like you did 3,000 years ago!
I know all about it!
What you did to the Kul Elna village in order to create the Millennium Items.
And that you abandoned your only son, Seto, in order to do it!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
We managed to get into the other Yugi's Lost Memory World,
but to the people of this world, we don't even exist!
We can't even enter the royal palace, so what'll we do now?!
At the same time, there's Akhenaden who was attacked by Bakura.
What's the horrible memory of the creation of the Millennium Items?
Next time!
"The Secret Behind the Birth of the Millennium Items"
Please look forward to it!