A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Toon Demon! Attack Black Magician!
The Trap Card, Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
NO!!
All right! All the Toons were destroyed!
Yeah! It was your courage
that defeated the Toons!
Exactly what I would expect from
one chosen by the Millennium Items.
It seems I was
playing around far too much.
Yugi boy, from now on,
this will be
a fight between two people chosen by the Millennium Items.
Let's settle this in a Dark Game!
Dark Game?!
"The Evil Eye is Activated:
Sacrifice"
Bakura... you...
I'm not the Bakura you know.
I'm an ancient soul resting deep within one of the Millennium Items, the Millennium Ring.
Millennium Ring...?
All I require is the key to the contracts for Kaiba ﻿Corporation that Mokuba has cleverly hidden away.
If you're a good boy and hand me Mokuba,
I'll turn everything back to normal.
Right now, no matter what I say to Bakura, it's useless.
Is he really being controlled by that Millennium Ring?
Ah, I got it.
I'll hand this brat over to you.
Here, catch!
Forgive me, Bakura.
It's this thing's fault!
Now, the Dark Game shall begin.
The whole arena... is being taken over by darkness...!
Dark Game...?
What's about to start?
Oi!
Honda!
Those two...!
I was able to rescue Mokuba...
What's wrong with Bakura-kun?
It's alright. He's just unconscious.
It's here too?!
Here too...?
To be honest, I don't believe it either...
What happened? Tell us!
A Dark Game!
I can't tell anything from up here.
Let's go down and take a look.
Sorry, but these guys'll just have to wait here for now.
Yeah.
What is this?
Yugi...
Dark Game?
From this point on, this is a wizard's battle
that no normal being can endure.
Yugi boy, I wonder how your other mind will hold up.
My other self can't handle this Dark Game!
Other I! I'll draw the cards from now on.
But if we don't fight together, Pegasus' Millennium ﻿Eye will be able to see through you again.
I'll be alright! Let me fight with you again!
Alright.
My turn.
Dark Eyes Illusionist in Attack Mode!
This guy...!
In a Dark Game, the Duel Rings Kaiba Corporation created are no longer active.
The players' willpower literally brings the Monsters to life!
And if that willpower should run out, the player's life might run out as well!
Dark Eyes Illusionist...
An Illusion Monster
with 0 Attack and Defense?
I can't just charge in and attack...
It has to have some sort of Special Ability...!
I call Curse of Dragon to the field!
Turn over!
I'll take over and let you think of a plan.
Mind Shuffle...
So you switched souls again, keeping me from reading your mind..?
However...
The other Yugi boy lacks the mentality ﻿needed to fight in this battle.
What's going on?
My chest... hurts...!
The burden of maintaining the Monsters' real form is draining the other me's willpower...
Hang in there, other me!
As I thought, the other Yugi is merely a normal human.
He'll soon run out of power...
What's wrong, Anzu?
I can't explain it, but... I feel like Yugi's in pain inside that black dark bubble.
It's not your imagination.
A second ago, my chest just hurt...
Me too.
You too, Honda?
Not long ago, I saw Bakura bring the Monsters on his cards to ﻿life using what he called "the Power of Darkness"
Could it be...?
I'm sure we've experienced this "Power of Darkness" before...
I will set a card face-down on the field.
Turn over.
There's a limit to my other self's mental strength...!
I can't let this battle
drag on any longer!
On my turn, I'll attack with Curse of Dragon!
You have fallen for it.
You rushed into battle to protect the other Yugi.
That was my aim!
I activate
Dark Eyes Illusionist's Special Ability!
Dark Eyes Magic!!
What the?!
In exchange for having no Attack or Defense Points, it is given a Special Ability.
Using the power of its Evil Eye, Dark Eyes Illusionist can steal away its opponent's abilities!
But the true terror of my Illusion Monsters has just begun!
What?!
Illusion Ritual! I will activate this card with Dark Eyes Illusionist!
I Summon the Illusion Monster, Sacrifice!
A Ritual Summon Monster?! Sacrifice?!
I activate Sacrifice's Special Ability!
What?! Curse of Dragon is...!
My turn is over.
Black Magician, attack Sacrifice!
Sacrifice Shield!!
What?! It's using the absorbed Curse of Dragon as a shield to block the attack?!
Black Magician's attack has taken out Curse of Dragon!
And I took damage to my Life instead...!
Sacrifice gains the Attack and Defense of any of the opponent's Monsters it absorbs.
And of course, when the player attacks the shield of Sacrifice, they take damage to their own Life.
Sacrifice...! ﻿What a terrible Monster!
My turn.
I use Sacrifice's Special Ability!
I activate Dark Eyes Magic!!
Control Black Magician
with the Evil Eye's spell!
Be absorbed by Sacrifice!
Black Magician!
He's using Black Magician as a shield...!
Sacrifice now gains the Attack and Defense points of your Black Magician.
If you attack him, your own Life will be
reduced. What will you do, Yugi boy?
This is my invincible Illusion Combo!
What should I do?
How do I defeat Sacrifice?
I can't think of anything to do...!
You can't give up!
If you don't take action, Pegasus will just read your mind.
I'll buy you some time to think of a plan.
Your mental strength is already at its limit.
You can't risk it!
No... I want to fight!
To the end!
If your menial strength should reach its limit, your soul will eternally...
Yugi... you...
It's my turn...
Your mind is fading away!
Please.... let me draw one final card...
A card that can defeat Pegasus...!
Come on!
I... set a card face-down...
Gremlin in Defense Mode!
Other me...!
Use this card... to defeat... Pegasus!
It seems this is the end of the line for other mind...
Sacrifice, ﻿attack!
Illusion Black Magic!!
Hang in there, my other self!
You have to defeat Pegasus...
Goodbye, other Yugi boy.
What...? I just felt something really bad just now...
Yeah, me too.
Could it be something happened to Yugi...?
No way!
Hang in there! Pull yourself together!
Wake up! Please!
Other me!
I beg you... snap out of it!
It seems the other mind of Yugi boy just wasn't
up to the right level to play in a Dark Game.
Now your other mind has perished.
Yugi...
Are we really not able to get into that field of darkness?
Can all we do is just stand here and do nothing?!
All we're good for is standing here staring...!
Yugi!
Anzu!
An...zu...?
What's going on?
What's the big deal?
Alright, I'll go next!
Move!
Oi! Honda!
Hey Honda, are you alright?!
Dammit! What's going on here?!
Huh?
Honda!
No good?
I went through to the other side.
So we can't interfere with those playing a Dark Game?
Our friend's in a really bad situation...!
And we can't even go in and support him?!
Maybe... if our hearts are able to somehow reach him...
Pegasus.
I'll... ﻿
...never forgive you!
However, Yugi boy... now that your
other mind has disappeared...
The only thing stopping my Millennium Eye,
your Mind Shuffle, has been sealed away.
Even so, do you still intend on continuing to Duel?
Of course!
Until my heart breaks in two...
...there's no "game over"!
Continue the game!
It's your turn, Yugi boy!
Mind Scan!!
The card you have just drawn is Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress!
A Normal Monster Card with 1400 Attack Points.
Every card in my hand has been read by Pegasus...
The only one Pegasus doesn't know is the set card my other self placed on the field...
I have no choice but to bet everything on this card!
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress In Defense Mode!
Turn over!
In that case, it's my turn!
Sacrifice Illusion: Black Magic!!
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the
Fortress has been defeated!
And the Time Bomber card!
Time Bomber!
The Time Bomb Monster!
Yes.
Time Bomber is a self destructing Monster that cannot be attacked.
In two turns, its Special Ability will destroy
every Monster on my side of the field.
In other words...
In two turns, Sacrifice will be destroyed by Time Bomber.
Yugi boy, your Monster as well.
Sacrifice has 0 Attack Points...!
So if it's destroyed, Pegasus' Life Points won't be harmed.
But if Black Magician is destroyed along with Sacrifice...
...those points... will be deducted from my Life...
If this Sacrifice Combo works, I'll lose!
Yugi boy, can you stop this combo?
You walk the path of destruction!
That is the Sacrifice Combo!
Two turns left...
There's no cards in my hand that can stop him...
Even if there were, Pegasus read them all!
I'll have to draw a card.
But Pegasus' Millennium Eye will see it at the same time I do.
What do I do?
As long as I have the Mind Scan,
you can't do a single thing.
You lose! It's game over!
What should I do?!
Within the Dark Game, Yugi fights alone in great pain.
We won't take just not being able to do anything!
Our hearts are strongly connected through friendship!
Yugi, connect your heart with ours!
We'll lend you the strength to defeat Pegasus!
Next time!
"The Fusion of Light and Darkness:
Black Chaos Descends"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship