The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"The Terrifying
Blue-Eyes White Dragon"
Go on, it's your turn, Jounouchi-kun.
What'cha doin' Jounouchi?
What, you don't know?
It's Duel Monsters!
What's that?
You're so noisy, just shut up and watch!
A fighting game where you use Monster and Magic Cards against the opponent.
Alright, here I go! Battle this!
There's two types of card positions, Attack and Defense. The first to hit 0 Life Points loses.
It's your turn now, Yugi.
Yup, it's my turn.
I'll attack with this.
You use such a powerful card without even a hint of a warning!
I lost right out of the blue!
Jounouchi, you're so weak!
It's not that I'm powerful, it's just my grandpa's a serious game maniac. I get great cards from him.
Alright! We'll stop by Yugi's after school!
Yup, maybe I'll convince him to show you his super-rare card.
Super-rare card? It couldn't be, could it...?
Grandpa, I'm home!
Ah, everyone's together today?
Hey, can you show everyone your amazing card?
What?
That card?
Please?
Please!
Can't be helped!
I'll make an exception, since this is my most valuable possession.
Here it is.
This is called the Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
This is a Super-Ultra-Rare Card.
Amazing...
Huh? What's so special...
There are only four of these in the entire world! This card isn't even for sale.
Alright! Can I hold the card, gramps?
This is mine!
Ah, come on! Then how about showing me some other strong cards?
Welcome!
You're...
Kaiba-kun?
What could the heir of Kaiba Corporation want?
I heard that Yugi-kun's grandpa was a card maniac.
Oh, you play Duel Monsters, too?
You came at the perfect time!
Let's be pals!
No thanks, I'd rather pass.
I don't think you guys are in my league.
What?
I was the only one to win the Duel Monsters National Championships.
In other words, we're at completely different levels.
What did you say? Shut up and play me!
Stop it, Jounouchi-kun!
But he...
He's really irritating!
So, does a shop like this even have any decent cards?
Wh-What?!
Why is the legendary Blue-Eyes White Dragon in a dump like this?
I can't believe he has the real card...!
Alrighty, that's enough.
This isn't for sale.
Old man, if you give me that Blue-Eyes White Dragon, I'll trade you every single one of these cards in return!
Amazing!
No way.
If you aren't gonna trade it, I can buy it!
Name your price!
Just tell me anything, and I can pay it!
Kaiba-kun, wasn't it?
The reason I'm not selling you this card...
Isn't because it's such a strong card.
But because this card is a gift from my most precious friend.
And I treasure this card just the same as I do that precious friend.
Nothing you pay me could possibly measure up to that.
What did you say?!
You would feel the same even if it were a weak card, right?
That's right.
This card has the same heart as that precious friend.
Please excuse me.
Cards have a heart?
What a load of bullshit!
Cards are power!
Just you see. I'll make sure to get that card.
Kaiba-sama, we have obtained the 3 cards...
So that just leaves that old geezer's card, huh?
Yes.
Wel-
I invite you to a Duel on behalf of Kaiba-sama.
Sugoroku Mutou-sama.
And if I were to refuse?
Then we will use force.
That boy misunderstood.
I'll teach him the heart of the cards.
My god, Anzu!
What're ya talking about?
Gramps, we've come again to get more cards today!
Oi, Gramps?
Grandpa, I'm home!
Not in?
Rather careless of him to leave the door unlocked...
Yes, hello?
Yugi-kun.
Kaiba-kun?
Your grandfather is currently under my care.
Won't you come pick him up at my office?
What do you mean?!
Kaiba-kun!
Grandpa!
Grandpa, hang in there!
Yu-Yugi...
I'm sorry...
I tried to show that boy the heart of the cards, but...!
Grandpa!
Well aren't you slow.
Bastard! What did you do to Gramps?!
All we did was Duel.
The bet was the other person's most treasured card.
But I think he may have been a bit shocked by my Virtual Simulator.
You must have pulled some cheap tricks!
No way!
I'll prove it with the card I won.
That's my grandpa's most cherished card!
Only three cards of the same name are permitted in a deck.
A fourth would be in the hands of an opponent.
Fourth?
M-My Blue-Eyes White Dragon...!
Grandpa, hang in there!
How could you do such a thing?!
Yu-Yugi... take these...
Grandpa!
These cards hold the heart I pit against him and lost miserably with!
You can beat that boy...
Teach that boy the true meaning of the heart of the cards...!
But I can't just leave you here, Grandpa!
Interesting.
You want revenge for your grandfather?
I'll take you on.
Yugi, fight him!
Just leave Gramps to us!
Go on and teach him what the heart of the cards is all about, just like Gramps said!
Fight him, Yugi!
Guys...
Yugi, you're the one who changed a person like me who was obsessed with fighting!
You can do it!
I understand, Grandpa!
I'm counting on you, Yugi...!
Now put your hands out, everyone.
Look! This is the proof of our friendship!
What's... this?
The magic marker ink will eventually fade away...
...but our hearts and our friendship will never disappear!
Right!
Jounouchi, Honda and I will take Grandpa to the hospital.
You stay and support Yugi.
Got it!
Take care of him, Anzu!
The rules are the Kaiba Special Rules.
We both have 2000 Life Points!
The first one of us to hit 0 Life Points loses.
Virtual System, start up!
What?!
Kaiba, with my grandpa's soul hanging on the line, I will defeat you.
Now, begin the Duel!
My turn first.
I'll use Cyclops to attack.
The Monster came to life!
This is the Virtual Simulation System!
So this is how he weakened Grandpa?
I'll take you on.
My turn.
I attack you with
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress.
What the?
Awesome!
Just what in the-
Desperate Fireball Strike!
Big brother!
Yippee!
You did it!
The game isn't as interesting if the players don't play multiple Monsters.
I use this card to attack!
The Dark Clown?
But, his Attack Points...
I realize the Attack Points of Winged Dragon are 1400.
This guy only has 600 Attack Points, so he can't win in the way he is now.
But if I add this card...!
A Magic Card...
Exactly!
Generator of Darkness!
This triples the Attack Points of a Dark Attribute Monster!
Saggi the Dark Clown, attack!
Dark Glide!
How's the destructive power of a Combo Attack?!
This damn Kaiba knows the game inside and out...!
But these cards were formed into a Deck by the heart of my grandfather, a game master!
There's got to be something useful in them.
This card can't beat the Dark Clown.
I'll have to hold on and play another Monster in Defense Mode!
Dark Glide!!
What're you doing?!
So this is the same Card Deck made by that dying old geezer?
I can hear his dying breath with each card you draw!
Grandpa lent me these cards because he believes in me!
I can hear the burning, ambitious soul of my Grandpa!
Kaiba, do you hold that kind of belief in your cards?!
I believe in these cards!
The card I drew is Gaia the Dark Knight!
Holding 2300 Attack Points, he attacks the Dark Clown!
What?!
Spiral Shaver!
He's beaten!
Good job, Yugi!
We still don't know the winner yet!
It's already been decided!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
I-Impossible!
Didn't he tear up Gramp's card?
Blue-Eyes White Dragon, attack!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Gaia the Dark Knight is finished!
I'll get what I want, no matter what it takes.
And with two other Blue-Eyes hidden in my Deck, you can't win.
Do you plan to keep using Defense Mode until you run out of cards?
I drew the second Blue-Eyes.
Why don't you just give in and admit defeat, Yugi?!
Yugi...
Yugi...!
Grandpa, I won't give up!
A Magic Card!
Sealing Swords of Light!
It seals the attacks of all Monsters on your side of the field for 3 turns!
What a pointless action!
What could you possibly gain in just 3 turns?
Like Kaiba said, I just have 3 useless Sealed Cards in my hand...!
How can I continue fighting with this?
This isn't like you, Yugi.
Listen, there's nothing useless in this world.
Just like how you put so much effort into the Millennium Puzzle.
The Millennium Puzzle?
That's right!
Cards are just like solving the pieces to a puzzle!
Grandpa!
Like the pieces of a puzzle!
Exodia?!
Exodia is in this Card Deck?
There's a myth in Duel Monsters that states when you gather the 5 needed cards,
you can exchange them for a much greater Monster!
But no one has ever successfully done it.
It's your turn!
Hurry and draw your card!
I'm going now!
This is the fourth piece!
It'll be the same no matter what card you play.
My turn.
I play this Monster to attack your Defense Monster!
Judge Man, with 2200 Attack Points!
Black Magician!
If I put it in Defense Mode, it'll just get done in by Blue-Eyes!
So I'll attack Judge Man!
Black Magic!!
Judge Man is beaten!
That's not nearly enough to harm me.
Just one turn remaining until the seal is broken.
The card I just drew is the third Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Attack the Black Magician!
Go on, Yugi. Draw your final card.
Because next turn, I'll attack you with all three Blue-Eyes!
No matter what card you play, you're finished!
Oi, Yugi!
If I was only able to Summon the legendary Exodia, I'd have a change of winning...!
But the chances of me actually getting the card I need in this last turn are close to zero!
The cards are getting further and further away!
No, I'm just scared to draw the next card...!
The "Magic Circle"...!
This is the mark of our friendship!
Yugi, you aren't alone.
We're all in this together.
Guys, thank you.
I won't be afraid anymore!
Did you find despair by reaching your hand out?
You're wrong!
I just found hope!
The card I just drew...
Is The Sealed One, Exodia!
Wha...
What!?
I just gathered all 5 cards this very moment!
Impossible!
Exodia, you said?!
Did you just create a miracle?!
Light of Hellfire!
Exodo Flame!!
He did it!
It's Yugi's win!
No way!
Big brother lost?!
Now matter how strong a card is...
It's useless if you can't connect your heart with that card.
When you connect your heart with the cards, miracles happen!
I-Impossible...!
How could I lose?!
Kaiba, your heart is being driven by evil!
Mind Crush!!
I've just destroyed the evil within your heart!
You're awake!
Yugi...
Master Pegasus, Seto Kaiba from Kaiba Corporation has been beaten in a Duel.
Preview
Eh?! Jounouchi wants to play Duel Monsters seriously for the first time?
Yugi's grandfather is going to give him special lessons.
That moment, Yugi receives a video tape in the mail.
And the sender is... Pegasus Crawford.
He really wants to play a game through the video?
Eh? A Dark Game?
Next time!
The Illusionist No-Face's Trap
Now!
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship