Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
After we came to Kaiba Land,
someone hijacked the dome and trapped us inside it!
If we don't defeat the Duel Computer, we'll never get back out!
The computer's level has been set to its max,
and my other self can't even use his own deck,
but a terrible Dragon Deck that's all over the place!
"The Conspiracy Begins to Move"
Yugi-san...
It's all right.
Leave it to me.
Even Yugi-kun can't win with that deck...
Yeah... And the computer he's playing against is set to the highest level.
Yugi...
Mama~!
I-It's alright...
The person up there is definitely going to win!
That's right!
That's the Duel King, Yugi Mutou!
There's no way he'll lose to a computer!
You mean it?
Yeah!
He can do it.
Up until now, no matter how impossible the situation was, he still overcame it and won!
That's right.
Let's believe in him.
In Yugi.
My turn!
Draw!
I knew it...
They're all Monster Cards?
I Summon Petit Dragon in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
A Defense of only 700...?
No reverse card face-down either...!
He has no other cards to play!
What's this...?
Mokuba!
The reigning Duel King who defeated Seto Kaiba during Battle City...
Yugi Mutou, is he?
I never expected him to be here...
It is far too amusing to be a mere coincidence.
This will serve as an entertaining vorstellung before the curtain drops on my true performance.
Herr Sieg.
Mhm?
A plane has been prepared for your flight.
I see.
Have a safe trip, Herr Sieg!
My turn.
Draw.
Activate Magic Card from hand.
Cost Down.
Discard one card from hand.
Levels of all Monsters in hand are reduced by two.
Thus, Angel Knight Perseus can be Summoned.
Summon Angel Knight Perseus in Attack Position.
Also activate Permanent Trap.
Thief Goblin.
When Monster inflicts damage to opponent while this card is in play,
you must discard one card from hand.
Angel Knight Perseus. Attack Petit Dragon.
Angel Knight Perseus' Special Ability.
When it attacks Defense Position Monster,
opponent player receives damage equal to difference in points.
Also, I am permitted to draw one card.
And Trap Card.
Thief Goblin's Special Effect. Activate.
Please discard card farthest to the right.
Continuing battle.
Berserk Gorilla. Direct Attack player.
Yugi!
It's useless after all, isn't it?!
No! Yugi hasn't given up yet!
Activate continuous effect of Thief Goblin.
Please discard the second farthest card to the right.
And my turn is then complete.
B-Because I had such an unbalanced Dragon Deck...!
Believe.
In your deck's power.
But...
I believe.
In the strong feelings these Dragons hold within them!
The Dragons' feelings.?
Believe in the warm heart of this deck.
And if I draw the card my partner put in here...
My turn!
Draw!
A Magic Card...!
I Summon Sapphire Dragon in Attack Mode!
Also, an Equipment Magic from my hand!
I activate Dragon's Treasure!
It increases the Attack and Defense of an Equipped Dragon-Type by 300 points!
Go!
Sapphire Dragon!
Attack Angel Knight Perseus!
Alright!
You did it, Yugi!
That deck actually had a Magic Card hiding in it?!
Awesome!
-He did it!
-That's amazing!
I end my turn!
My turn.
Draw.
When Killer Snake is in the Graveyard during the Standby Phase,
I can add another to my hand.
Summon Newt in Attack Position.
What?
It's attacking the 2200 Attack Sapphire Dragon with 1900 Attack Newt?!
Is the computer broken?!
That's not it!
This is...
Activate Newt's Special Effect.
The Monster destroyed by this Monster in battle has its Attack Power and Defense Power lowered by 500 points.
Even reducing its own Life Points...!
Just to lower its Attack Points...!
Furthermore, Berserk Gorilla will attack Sapphire Dragon.
Activate Effect of Permanent Trap, Thief Goblin.
Please discard the card farthest to the left.
This is bad!
As expected of something holding the greatest Duelist level of data!
Otogi, you jerk!
Whose side are you on?!
-Are we gonna get out of here?
-H-Hold it, don't grab me like that! That hurts!
-It'll be all right. Don't worry.
-What're we supposed to do with you being so negative?!
Hold it!
Knock it off. you two!
You're making the kids nervous!
-S-Sorry...
-I-I'm sorry...
I end my turn.
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Lurking Dragon in the Cave in Defense Mode!
Alright!
It can't do anything against 2000 Defense Points!
Turn end!
My turn.
Draw.
I Sacrifice Berserk Gorilla on field.
Summon Android - Psycho Shocker in Attack Position.
That thing...!
He can even Summon Psycho Shocker?!
I thought I told you!
Just about every well-known Duelist's card data around the entire world exists within that computer!
Android - Psycho Shocker will attack Lurking Dragon in the Cave.
I end my turn.
My turn!
Draw!
That card is...!
Your deck's warm feelings answered you!
What card did he get?
Yugi...!
I Summon Baby Dragon in Defense Mode!
Also, from my hand...
The Continuous Magic, Willpower of the Ordinary!
This is my key card!
O-Ordinary?!
That's got a certain ring to it, don't you think?
I see!
That's a good approach!
Not bad.
Turn end!
My turn.
Draw.
Summon Killer Snake in Attack Position.
Android - Psycho Shocker will attack Baby Dragon.
Killer Snake. Direct Attack opponent player.
Turn end.
Let's go.
My turn!
Draw!
This moment, the effects of the Continuous Magic, Willpower of the Ordinary, will activate!
If the card I draw is a Normal Monster,
I show that card to the opponent and I'm permitted to draw another card!
The card I've drawn is this!
Curse of Dragon!
I draw one more!
Devil Dragon!
Draw!
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress!
Diamond Dragon!
Draw!
Earth-Crawling Dragon!
Dragon of Darkness!
Draw!
I Summon Spirit Dragon in Attack Mode!
Spirit Dragon, attack Android - Psycho Shocker!
At this moment, I activate Spirit Dragon's Special Effect!
When it battles, for every Dragon-Type Monster I discard to the Graveyard from my hand,
its Attack and Defense goes up by 1000 points!
I have six Dragon-Type Monster Cards in my hand.
Thus, its Attack goes up by 6000 points!
Continue the battle!
Go!
Spirit Dragon!
Spirit Burst!!
You did it, Yugi!
You're amazing to win with that deck!
As expected of Yugi-san!
We're saved~
You did it!
Rick.
From now on, believe in your Monsters and cherish them.
Yeah!
Thank you!
That was awesome!
Rick's deck is really strong!
Sweet~!
I wanna collect Dragon-Types now!
I would expect nothing less from one who defeated Seto Kaiba.
Fresh air is really great~!
Seriously!
I was wondering if we'd ever breathe it again!
Yugi-san, thank you!
I'll take good care of this!
Yeah.
Goodbye!
Papa! Mama! Something amazing just happened!
Yugi.
What's with that card?
Why'd you have it with you?
Because...
Well...
You handle this!
That's not fair, Other Me!
Yugi~!
It couldn't be that you view me as an ordinary "nothing special" guy, too?
Th-That's not it...
That Magic Effect is quite handy...
It does remind me of you a little though.
Well, it's fine!
Even a deadbeat has his use.
YOU'RE THE LAST ONE I WANNA HEAR THAT FROM!
Mokuba!
Brother!
Are you okay, Mokuba?
Yeah.
Kaiba-kun!
KAIBA!
NOW YOU COME!
That damn Duel Computer you built put us through a lot of crap!
Sorry for the trouble, Deadbeat.
Damn you...!
That wasn't my fault.
Someone hacked our system from another area.
Brother?
Don't worry, Mokuba.
Someone's looking into it.
It's more than likely someone who's trying to stop the opening of KC Grand Prix
and they're using boring tricks to try and stop the revival of Kaiba Corporation...
But anyone who challenges me will soon come to regret it!
To be on the safe side, run a thorough test on Kaiba Land.
Ensure the safety of our guests.
If another disturbance occurs again, they will be displeased.
The KC Grand Prix must be a success!
Yes, sir!
Immediately.
You're all free to do as you please.
Mokuba, I'll leave the rest to you.
Okay!
SO ARROGANT~!
Without us here, your tournament won't even be a success!
There's so many people!
It's a greatly anticipated Kaiba Corporation Duel Tournament, after all!
In order to advertise it successfully, we've invited media from all around the globe!
What?!
Hey~!
Shizuka-chan, I see you~!
Knock it off, Honda!
Shizuka, it's your big brother here!
You two look like little kids.
Looks delicious~!
Hey!
Be more careful!
You should!
You walked right into me!
Rebecca? What's wrong?
This woman is!
Are you Yugi Mutou?!
Y-Yes...
I knew it~!
I'm so happy~!
I wanted to mweet wu~!
I'm Vivian Wong!
A pleasure~
What's her problem?!
I'm so happy to finally meet the legendary Duelist that I dreamed about meeting~!
Although we're rivals in this tournament, in private, we...
...have to get along very well~!
Hey, you!
Get the hell off my Darling!
Oh!
That's Chairman Kaiba~!
SO COOL~!
What was that?
Yugi-san!
You're Leon-kun!
Why are you here?
I'm in the KC Grand Prix too.
You too?!
Yes!
I'm so happy!
To be able to Duel against you, Yugi-san!
Let's both do our best when the time comes!
Haven't all the Duelists arrived yet?!
Well...
There's still one left to show up...
Disqualify him!
Begin, Isono!
B-But...
Pardon me.
I am Sieg Lloyd.
I seem to be slightly tardy.
I thank you for your invitation, Mr. Kaiba.
Now all the Duelists for the tournament are here.
Isono!
Yes!
Sorry to keep you waiting, everyone!
Kaiba Corporation's prestigious event...
...the greatest Dueling Tournament, the KC Grand Prix...
...is at last about to start!
All Duelists, please come onto the stage!
Let's go, Yugi!
Yeah!
To ensure the greatest challenge,
we have chosen the strongest Duelists from around the world!
First up, we have one who has remained untouchable...
...who has never lost a tournament up until now...!
The Invincible Boy Prodigy!
Leon Wilson!
That guy was such a famous Duelist?
The mysterious card prophet of destiny...
Fortune Salim!
His tactics are too smooth for his own good...
The drifting Duelist...
Edsel Johnson!
The assassin from the north...
Sergei Ivanov!
And possessing great intellectual properties and observational skills...
The Duelist Detective...
Paul McGregor!
And the wild gambler...
Abe!
Will his wild nature overcome the Duels?!
And performing an open operation even while Dueling...
Dr. Richard Goat!
And the controller of Magic Cards through time itself...
The Magic Master...
Barry Ginger!
No, we mean this person when we speak of magic tricks...
Someone who Duels while performing using his cards...
The Master of Illusions!
Totani Ialos!
The one who takes all Duels as street fights!
The road-side fighter...
Ethan Shark!
The highly respectful Duelist...
Jafar Hashin!
The beautiful flower of Asia!
Th-That person...!
Vivian Wong!
The highly sociable American Champion...
Rebecca Hopkins!
Straight out of the Battle City Best Four!
The Fiery Duelist...
Yeah, Baby~!
A.K.A. the ordinary "nothing special" guy!
Katsuya Jounouchi!
Since when was I known as "nothing special", huh?!
The man whose birthplace and identity is shrouded in mystery!
The legendary Duelist...!
Mask the Rock!
That's...!
D-Don't tell me...!
Known as the "Untouchable Emperor of Europe"!
Sieg Lloyd!
And finally, the winner of our previous Battle City Tournament...
Yugi Mutou!
As the Defending Champion, the Duel King will
partake in a Duel with the winner of this tournament, betting his title of Duel King on the line!
So only the tournament winner gets to face off against Yugi?
That's disappointing.
Duels in this tournament will be decided at random by the main computer!
So you won't know who you're Dueling until right before?
The outcome's the same, whoever it is.
I'll be the one to win!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
The KC Grand Prix has finally gotten underway!
Looks like Jounouchi will be up fast as he's the first one Dueling in the tournament.
The opponent he's facing is...
Mask the Rock?
Isn't that man... no matter how you look at it...
What's he doing in this tournament?
Jounouchi, what are you standing around for?
If you don't hurry and get to the playing location...!
you'll run out of time!
Next time!
"Jounouchi VS Mask the Rock"
Duel standby!