Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The final trial that will determine my fate... the Rite of the Duel.
My partner accepted this, so in order not to sully his feelings,
I will bet all of my pride on this Duel and fight him with all my might!
Right here and now, Obelisk the Great War God,
Osiris the Heaven Dragon and Ra the Winged Sun Dragon will appear!
I will Summon the three Gods!
Partner, follow suit and fight me with all you've got!
"Defeating the Three Illusionary Beast Gods!"
This means... the Other Me is really serious!
I activate the Pot of Greed Magic Card!
I draw two cards from my deck into my hand and end my turn!
This is incredible, Brother...!
He gathered all three gods onto the field at once?
What a development...!
This is truly a spectacle you'd see only once in a life time!
Sister!
The Pharaoh's power far surpasses our understanding.
This is... Atem's strength?
Yugi's Trap managed to seal away his Special Effect and lower his Attack Points...
Even with that,
Obelisk's Attack Power is 2500.
And Osiris has the Special Ability called Thunder Summon Shot
that deals 2000 points of damage to the opponent's Monster once per turn!
And if he uses Ra's Special Ability
and adds the Attack Power of the Monsters on his field into his Life...
...he can raise its Attack Power all the way up to 14499!
All three gods in the hands of a single Duelist...
Atem's Dueling tactics revolve around Summoning requirements
for this Super Heavy Deck.
It wouldn't be unrealistic to label this battle as a historical Duel.
Though...
The outcome of this Duel has just been determined!
Hold it, Kaiba!
You still don't know that!
That's right!
The match isn't over yet!
What the hell would you fools know of the gods when you've never even wielded one?
Say what now?!
Then let's hear it, Deadbeat!
Do you have a strategy to beat all three gods on the field at once?!
W-Well...
Of course you don't!
Because no such strategy exists!
No! There has to be a way!
Right Malik?!
I'm sure you know Ra's weakness, right?
If you're talking about Ra alone, then yes...
But now that all three gods are together...
This may be an act guided by fate.
After 3,000 years of time has passed,
the Pharaoh's sword has become sturdy and strong.
Seeing as there has been no one to accept it up until now,
this Battle Ceremony may hold no competition for him.
Ishizu-san...
She's right.
The way this match is going, Atem will never return to the Afterlife...
Let's get going, Mokuba.
Brother!
Kaiba!
Atem, it's now evident that you won't be returning to the Afterlife.
I'll settle the score with you one of these days.
But can I defeat all three gods?
Wait, Kaiba-kun!
Kaiba-kun, I want you to watch this until the very end.
Yugi!
The road I'm walking holds no time to watch your defeat!
You're wrong.
That's not what I meant.
There is an unbreakable connection between the souls of Kaiba-kun and my other self.
I want you to watch very closely!
As the Other Me returns to the Afterlife!
Yugi!
You don't really...!
I know that you know exactly what I'm thinking!
I must defeat these three gods!
I will win this Duel!
What did you say...?
Yugi!
I'm standing on this field right now for that purpose!
Well said, Partner!
Absurd!
Yugi, are you serious about this?!
You really intend to defeat all three gods?!
Very well, Yugi.
If you're able to say that much, I'll watch your Duel until the very end!
Now, my Partner!
It's your turn!
My turn!
What's wrong with Yugi-kun?
Yugi! You can d-
He is currently waging a spiritual battle with himself deep within his soul.
Those who have never fought against one of the gods
can't comprehend the fear one feels when standing before one.
It's true.
I can't put the fear I felt that day into words.
They're right...
I'm standing here in order to win.
I came here well aware that the three gods were going to appear.
Despite that...
I'm scared.
I'd really like to run away.
Up until now, I've always worked hard, chasing after you.
And no matter how hard I pushed myself, I just couldn't reach you.
Your back was always too far away...
Partner, now that we've come to this point,
as a Duelist you won't be able to defeat me unless you have complete faith in your deck.
If you're a True Duelist as well as a friend...
...as someone who has walked alongside me,
I have confidence that you've already thought this through!
A method to defeat me!
A method for Yugi to beat the other Yugi...?
That's what it means to be a True Duelist.
When we built this deck,
we both shared the same thoughts of wanting to seriously defeat one another!
You're right.
I've always thought about it.
About you.
That you've always had the courage to stand up during countless ordeals.
It's the same for me, Partner!
I've always thought about you!
You, who always chooses to hurt himself before hurting others.
You, a Duelist who gains his strength through kindness!
Then in both of our decks...
...lies your courage...
And the decks hold your strength as well!
I see now!
Even if our hearts are separated from one another,
we built this deck together!
It was built with your strong desire to return to the Afterlife!
It's my strongest deck!
Yeah!
Thank you, Other Me.
I'm no longer scared.
Because this deck is directly connected to you!
No matter what happens, you never give up the fight!
No matter what happens, you believe in your deck and the Monsters!
A Duelist's courage and pride!
Let's do this, Other Me!
Bring it, Partner!
My turn!
Draw!
Yugi!
You can do this, Yugi!
As I enter into my turn, Silent Swordsman levels up!
Silent Swordsman reaches Level Four!
Now the Silent Swordsman's got 3000 Attack Points!
He can beat Obelisk!
I sacrifice the three Magnet Warriors, Alpha, Beta and Gamma, from my hand!
This lets me Special Summon the Magnetic Warrior - Magnet Valkyrian in Attack Mode!
Now that you've Summoned a new Monster,
I can activate Osiris' Special Ability!
Go, Osiris!
Summon Lightning Shot!!
Endure it, Magnet Valkyrian!
I activate a Quick-Play Magic Card from my hand!
Mirage Magic!
When one of the Monsters on my side are attacked,
the Mirage Magic Card is activated!
It negates the effect and increases my Life by the same amount of Attack Points.
Sweet!
Nice move, Yugi!
Yugi repelled the Summon Lightning Shot!
He actually used Osiris' Special Ability to recover his Life...
But the amount of Life you have doesn't mean a thing in front of the gods!
I set two cards face-down on the field!
Turn end!
Huh? Yugi-kun isn't going to attack?
Not that he doesn't want to. He can't.
Carelessly attacking the gods will only lead to your doom.
Even knowing that, what's really bothering me is that Yugi's Monsters are all in Attack Mode.
That means he can get attacked by all three of the gods.
Show me, Yugi!
Your secret plan!
Are you tempting me, Partner...?
If this were any ordinary opponent, the Silent Swordsman LV. 4,
and Magnet Valkyrian are all very powerful Monsters.
But they're just no match for the three Gods.
It's my turn!
Draw!
I now have four cards in my hand at this moment!
That means Osirs' Attack Power will climb up to 4000!
Here I go, Partner!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon! Attack Silent Swordsman!
Trap Card, activate!
Partner!
Traps won't work against the Gods!
Go, Osiris!
The god's swinging its iron hammer!
Thunder Force!!
What a shockwave!
It's not over!
He's still going to attack with the gods!
Ra the Winged Sun Dragon!
Attack Magnet Valkyrian!
Magnet Valkyrian!
Now Yugi's lost all the Monsters on his field!
But he's still got Obelisk's attack left!
If this attack goes through, Yugi...!
Yugi...!
Brother?!
I guess this is the end of the line.
Partner, this is my final attack!
Here it comes!
Obelisk the Great War God's attack!
Direct Attack my partner!
God Hand Crusher!!
Yugi!
What!?
But why...?
Magnet Valkyrian and Silent Swordsman were...!
Was it... that Trap you played before?!
Yes.
I just activated this card.
Mirage Ruler...?
Yugi's Life was recovered!
When my opponent enters into his Battle Phase,
When all of my Monsters are destroyed,
the Mirage Ruler card's effect activates!
All of the Monsters destroyed during the Battle Phase this turn as well as my Life
are returned after the Battle Phase.
I then pay 1000 of my Life after!
Pretty clever, Partner.
I see.
This time he bet on the Trap he had on his field?
That was probably his reason for reducing Obelisk's Attack Power to 2500 earlier.
Now, no matter which Monster he chooses to attack with, it'll end in a stalemate.
I will now finish out my turn!
That sure was a close call!
He managed to pass through the turn, Gramps!
That's my Yugi!
But this is bad for my heart!
You can say that again! I'm worried about your body's health here!
This Duel's gonna determine the future!
I can't pass away until I see the conclusion!
You've really improved, Yugi.
You've really accomplished a lot in taking on this battle!
Thank goodness...
When did I suddenly start cheering for Yugi...?
Brother, Yugi was able to survive through all three of the gods' attacks!
But he only managed to extend his life a little longer.
Unless he comes up with a conclusive weakness of the gods, Yugi has no hope of winning this.
Oh? Weakness of the gods?
The gods have to have some kind of weakness.
No, they do!
The gods only weaknesses
are that they must require three sacrifices each to be Summoned onto the field.
Truly powerful Monsters worthy of Heaven's title.
But Atem has already cleared those obvious weaknesses
and we've come to this point!
So it really is...
The gods don't have any other weaknesses!
What will you do, Yugi?
Even I couldn't find the gods' weaknesses.
if you want to beat the gods, you'll have to find it!
Show me a Duel that surpasses my own, Yugi!
In the next turn, the match between Yugi and the Pharaoh will be decided.
Sister, could it be...?
I didn't see the future or anything like that.
I simply felt it.
Sister, do you believe Yugi can beat the Gods?
I'm not sure.
But when I look at Yugi now, I feel that it's possible.
The nameless Pharaoh's soul was resurrected.
His strength far transcends our imaginations.
However, we must not think light of the vessel who contained such a powerful soul.
Even if he was a small vessel at the start,
after walking alongside the Pharaoh's soul,
it's possible the vessel has grown much larger than we can even guess.
You mean Yugi?
Yes.
When any human being passes an ordeal, their inner vessel grows in size.
People call this the potential of time.
Time brings with it miracles.
Miracles?
Yugi will create a miracle?
I was able to make it through the gods' attacks.
But when it again goes over to the Other Me's turn,
and I am again attacked by his gods, I won't have anything to counter with.
That's the card he set before I activated Turn Jump.
But I have no idea when my other self plans to activate it.
Knowing him, there's only one possible choice.
I haven't attacked him once since I activated Turn Jump!
If I'm not wrong in my guess, that card is Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
There may only be a tiny sliver of a chance...
but I have one combo in my deck that can defeat the gods.
My hand is at zero.
Everything is riding on my next draw!
My fate!
No, mine and my other self's fate!
My turn!
Draw!
Here I go, Other Me!
Come, Partner!
Are you planning to attack him, Yugi?!
Now that I've entered my turn, Silent Swordsman levels up to Level Five!
Then I activate Magnet Valkyrian's Special Effect!
If I have the Magnet Warriors, Alpha, Beta and Gamma, in my Graveyard,
I can sacrifice my Magnet Warrior on the field
and Special Summon the three onto my field!
Have you gone mad, Yugi?!
You're degrading your powerful Monster to Summon new puny Monsters?!
That's as good as suicide in front of the gods!
Now that you've Summoned new Monsters on the field,
Osiris' Special Effect activates!
What the hell are you doing, Yugi?!
All Monsters with less than 2000 Attack Power will be destroyed!
Go, Osiris!
Thunder Summon Shot!!
I was waiting for you to do that!
Trap Card! Magnet Force!
What?!
When any of my Rock or Machine-Type Monsters
are targeted by my opponent's Card Effect,
the Magnet Force card activates!
I can use the effect I would take in the turn and send it to one of my opponent's Monsters!
This time it's a Trap he bet his own Monsters with?!
The Summon Lightning Shots are going towards the gods!
The gods' Attack Points dropped!
Now it's possible for Yugi's Monsters to beat any of the gods!
Silent Swordsman LV. 5!
Attack Obelisk the Great War God!
You're naive, Partner!
Trap Card, activate!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
What?!
The Monster's on Yugi's field...!
They were all destroyed...!
Yugi~!
It looks like Sister's guess was on the mark.
Atem's gaming tactics are simply at a much higher level...
Damn you, Yugi...! You wasted a ton of my time!
What a pity, Partner!
You couldn't see through my set card.
No, I did see through your set card!
My God Defeating Combo was completed the moment you activated Mirror Force!
This moment, all three gods will vanish before me!
What?
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The three gods stand before Yugi.
We all think Yugi's in a desperate situation,
but what could he mean that his "God Defeating Combo" is finished?
But after Yugi spent so much time together with Atem,
he's truly become really strong!
So show us, Yugi!
A miracle! The defeat of the three gods!
Next time!
"Strong Heart, Kind Heart"
Duel standby!