"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Diamond Blade!!
My only Monster in enemy territory was beaten...
My opponent has four Monsters at his disposal...
And I only have three Monsters.
What can I do?
"The Miracle Dimension:
Summon the Black Magician"
Dice Roll!!
I move Duker of Twin Swords closer to enemy territory!
Then it's my turn.
You won't make it in time, Yugi-kun.
Cuz I'll make it before you!
Dice Roll!!
God Orgoth advances!
God Orgoth is moving towards the Warp Hole!
That's correct!
I'm taking two Warp Route right onto your home turf!
I'm charging right in!
God Orgoth!
Warp!!
He's here!
If I don't do something, God Orgoth will get to my Life!
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
All of my Monsters stand guard in front of me!
Iron Golem, Gorogon! Move forward!
Little Wizard, move forward!
Duker of Twin Swords, move forward!
No wall of Monsters can stop God Orgoth!
Now it's my turn!
God Orgoth, move forward!
God Orgoth's Special Ability!
Using a Magic Crest, I can raise his Attack by 10!
His Attack goes up to 40!
God Orgoth, attack Iron Golem Gorogon!
Diamond Blade!!
Well, at least you've made it this far, Yugi-kun.
Cool~!
Go! Go! Otogi!
That damn Otogi just took the lead again...
Oi, he's running out of Monsters!
Don't you think he can Summon something else, Anzu?
It's impossible.
He's got no room left on the field to Dimension the dice!
You can do it, Yugi!
It's time to show off your true power as a Duelist!
Yugi-kun, you've only got two Monsters left now.
And you can no longer Summon.
You've sure tried hard since the game started.
I praise you for that much.
However, a cheap Duelist who cheated Pegasus stands no chance against me!
I did not cheat him!
And this isn't over yet!
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
Did you forget the Mage's power already?
Little Wizard!
It can attack Monsters from two spaces away!
Lightning Rod!
I use a Defense Crest to increase his Defense against Magic Attacks!
God Orgoth!
Activate your Defense!
Little Wizard's attack was deflected!
God Orgoth takes 10 points of damage.
So his Hit Points drop to 20.
But God Orgoth's Attack is 40!
Little Wizard takes 20 points of damage!
But he still has 20 Hit Points left!
He can still fight!
How naive!
And it's my turn again!
Dice Roll!!
God Orgoth advances forward!
God Orgoth has 40 Attack Points!
And with its Special Ability,
using Magic Crests, his Attack will increase by 30 points!
God Orgoth's Attack Points went from 40 to 70...!
And if he uses his Defense Crests, I can't touch him!
God Orgoth attacks Little Wizard!
Super Diamond Blade!!
I only have one Monster left...
I have no way of stopping the enemy's attacks!
You no longer have any way to turn the tables.
What should I do...?
If this keeps up, the game will be completely in his control.
And the Duel Monsters title me and my other self won will be taken away as well...!
Wanna surrender, Yugi-kun?
Yugi, pick up the dice! I beg you!
Still talking?!
You lousy dog!
You're so cheeky!
Shut it!
Just let me say this!
Fight, Yugi!
I'm sorry, Jounouchi-kun...
I went and promised I'd get your freedom back...
You're not fighting for me anymore!
It's for the hundreds of Duelists out there, Yugi!
For the Duelists...?
Right!
For all the people who fought against you
with all they had, and put their strong feelings on the line!
Same goes for that Pegasus as well!
He gave his all when he fought against you!
And he lost!
And he was the king of Duel Monsters!
Even if the game's different,
you have a responsibility to give it your all,
and fight on until the very end!
That's right!
That's right, Yugi!
You always fight until the end!
Jounouchi! Well said!
Although that ridiculous looking outfit kinda ruined it.
Thanks, Jounouchi-kun.
I came pretty close to losing my sight as a Duelist.
Even if card and dice are different from each other,
a game's still a game!
I'll channel my thoughts in these dice,
and roll on until the very end!
And I'll protect my throne as the King of Duelists!
That's right! Nicely put, Yugi!
That's my grandson for you!
Let's go, Partner!
Okay!
Dice Roll!!
Rice Roll!!
I use a Movement Crest to move Duker of Twin Swords ahead!
And also, with the Attack Crests I just rolled,
I can attack your Monster with his Renzoku attack!
Otogi just used a Defense Crest...
If I use all of my saved Crests, I can beat it!
Duker of Twin Swords!!
Using the remainder of my Attack Crests as the cost,
I'll use his Renzoku attack!
He'll attack God Orgoth six times!
Twin Swords!
Six Renzoku Giri!!
Don't underestimate me!
I activate Yaranzo's Special Ability!
I change my two Trap Crests into Defense Crests!
What?!
He stopped all six of Duker of Twin Swords' Six Rengoku Giri attacks?!
See that?
Yaranzo can change any Crest in my Crest Pool
into any Crest I want them to be!
I didn't even need the unstoppable God Orgoth to put you in your place!
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
God Orgoth!!
Attack the Duker of Twin Swords!!
The God Orgoth's Attack Points are too high!
Even if I raise his Defense, it won't help!
Diamond Blade!!
-Yugi!
I've wiped out the Duker of Twin Swords!
Your Monsters are all wiped out!
Now what'll you do?
I may not have any Monsters, but I still have two of my Life left!
I won't give this game up until the very end!
He doesn't even have any room left to Dimension his dice...
His chances of Summoning a Monster are slim to none.
Even so, his heart hasn't shaken.
Why?!
I can't believe he has such a strong heart...!
There's got to...
There's got to be a way out of this!
There isn't any way!
Just give up hope and fall to my feet!
I move God Orgoth forward yet again!
Towards the Dungeon Master!
God Orgoth!
Attack Dungeon Master Yugi!
If you don't beat God Orgoth next turn, you're gonna lose!
But I'll compliment you for getting God Orgoth's Attack Points down to 20.
This fight's not over yet!
I just have to Summon a Monster strong enough to beat God Orgoth!
What?!
You still won't give up?
And just where do you think...
...you're gonna Summon that Monster?!
Yugi...!
Go! Go! Otogi!
L-O-V-E, OTOGI!
Millions of gaming fans around the world are watching this!
How bout you stop with the tough guy act and accept your loss like a man?
I'll win!
I'll show you a miracle!
For Yugi...
And for all the Duelists in the world!
Dice Roll!!
You have no place to Dimension the dice on this field!
Don't be so sure of that!
What?
Otogi, there are various places left to Dimension the dice.
I can figure that out without you telling me!
Then allow me to show you.
Dimension Dice!
Oh, shit!
That Dimension...!
Here goes.
I Summon the Black Magician!
Black Magician...?
It can't be...!
Otogi boy...
I would like to make a small change to this game upon its publication.
I assume that is okay with you?
Y-Yes.
But what kind of change?
I would like to link it with some of the Monsters from Duel Monsters.
I would like to add a new Monster with its own Effect
to Dungeon Monsters, truly making it the perfect game!
A new Monster?
What does that mean?
That is a secret!
You shall find out through playing the game!
I had no idea the Black Magician was added to my version of the game!
What the hell is the Special Effect of this Monster Pegasus was talking about?!
If it has the same Effects as in Duel Monsters,
I'm seriously screwed here!
Since I was trying to beat an enemy familiar with it,
maybe I should have done more research on his Monsters?!
I made a huge mistake!
I then move Black Magician forward!
Here I go!
I attack God Orgoth with the Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
You did it!
-Yes!
-Oh yeah!
He beat Otogi's best Monster!
-Yes! Nice one! Get 'im, Yugi!
-No~! Otogi-kun got beaten!
In that case, I'll use my remaining Crests to finish this!
I left my trump for that sole purpose!
Dice Roll!!
Dark Assassin, move forward!
And now it's time to open the eagerly-awaited treasure chest!
What's that?
You can look forward to rest later.
It's now your turn.
The Rare Item...
Monster Cannon!!
Monster Cannon?!
What's that?
The Monster Cannon is one of the Rare Items
that uses Monsters as ammo to destroy the enemy's Monsters!
And its target is...
...the Black Magician!!
Monster Cannon! Activate!
Black Magician!
Activate your Special Ability!
What?!
Magical Silk Hats!
Where's the Black Magician hiding?!
Monster Cannon!
Fire!!
Did I get him?!
By activating the one-time use Magical Silk Hats using a Trap Crest,
he can evade the enemy's attack!
Shit!
Yaranzo! Pull back!
I'm certain this isn't the Black Magician's only Special Ability!
I have to protect myself!
You can't get away!
Dice Roll!!
I use two Magic Crests to activate Black Magician's second Special Ability!
Magic Death Box!
Is this the Special Ability Pegasus mentioned?!
Yaranzo!
My Monsters were wiped out!
Impossible!
Go!
Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
He did it!
It's all over!
My dream's gone for good!
I created that game all by myself!
For my dream of making Dungeon Dice Monsters famous!
But if that dream's gone, I have nothing left!
That's not true at all!
Dungeon Dice Monsters is an awesome game!
Mmm-hm!
You're truly amazing competition.
I could be in for some real problems if I'm not careful.
That's right!
Just like Duel Monsters,
Dungeon Dice Monsters is sure to be accepted by everyone around the world!
Really? You really think that's possible?
It is!
I don't like you!
But I like this game!
Yup!
Teach me how to play too!
S-Sure...
So just like you promised, you have to set Jounouchi-kun free.
And I'll be continuing to play Duel Monsters.
Ah, of course, Yugi-kun.
I'm really sorry I put Jounouchi-kun through all of that hardship.
I'm over it now.
No matter who the opponent you face in a game is,
they shouldn't be played to get revenge.
Such a great game should be used to make friends with everyone!
Yugi-kun...
I wonder if I can become your friend?
Of course!
Got mail?
Yeah.
It's from Industrial Illusions INC!
They want to contract Dungeon Dice Monsters!
-You did it, Otogi!
-Awesome!
I'm so glad for you!
I'm glad for you, Otogi-kun!
Thank you, Yugi-kun.
I'm sorry I put you through so much.
Just forget about all that!
You sure are strong.
There's no way someone with a strong heart like you would have cheated against Pegasus.
No, I'm not strong all by myself.
My heart's strong because of the many friends I made...
...and my wonderful partner as well!
"Preview"
This is terrible!
Yugi's Millennium Puzzle was stolen by a suspicious man wearing a cloak!
Yugi vows to believe in his other self, and that he'll definitely get it back!
Yugi finally finds where the Puzzle is,
but winds up in a Duel against the cloaked man!
Just what's he after?
Next time!
"Challenge From the Past: The terrifying Zera"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...