Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Terrifying Revival Combo"
His Deck Master Ability... Reflector Hole?
He redirected my own attack at me,
and I reduced my own Life Points...
An Italian political philosopher
of the Renaissance once said...
"It is more profitable to utilize your enemies than it is your allies."
A universal proverb again?
But because of the Special Ability you used just now,
you don't have a single Monster on the field!
My Battle Phase isn't over yet!
I can use direct attacks, too!
Go! Retrained Elf Swordsman!
That one was a little dangerous...
But I have more Monsters, this holding the advantage!
I won't let you keep any sacrifices you plan to Summon a Monster with!
If you say so...
Thanks to the damage I took just now, I can Special Summon a Monster!
I Summon Ruklamba the Spirit King!
What?
A Monster that you can Summon after receiving damage?!
If the player holding Ruklamba the Spirit King receives 1000 points of damage or more,
you can Summon Ruklamba the Spirit King from your hand!
You'd better remember that...
So he uses a Revival Combo that lets him substitute his Monsters whenever they are destroyed?
We don't have the time to waste on him...!
If you're finished, declare "turn end" already.
I realize that you have a strong defense.
But you can't win if you do nothing but defend.
Defending is an easier and stronger way to fight than attacking.
However, it requires a strong mentality to maintain your status quo and conserve your resources.
Some people out there are not capable of such thought process.
And there is no better strategy out there than simply maintaining your present situation.
You will come to understand this.
Turn end.
Don't waste the chance I gave you.
Now then, what's the rest of the group up to?
And...
Mom was already dead and Dad died from an accident shortly after that...
Our relatives only wanted our Dad's inheritance...
And sent me and my brother to this orphanage.
What?! That's...!
My big brother and me!
It's done! It's done! I built a castle!
You sure did!
Right.. I was remembering the happy times we spent with Mom and Dad...
Mokuba! Mokuba!
Big Brother...
Let's go back, Mokuba.
I'm sorry, Big Brother...
I thought I could turn back time to when Dad was alive
if I went to the park where I used to play.
Mokuba, stop crying. I know how you feel.
We aren't loser dogs or trash.
Don't even think about those who made things like this for us.
Just live happily.
From now on, I'll act as your father.
I'll protect you, no matter what happens.
Big Brother...
So stop crying now.
Listen! Don't let anyone get too close to you.
You're done for if they see your weak side.
Those were the clichéd lines you always said, Big Brother...
Checkmate.
Again...
You're just as good as always, Big Brother!
Seto, the borderline between reality and dreams is imprecisely marked by the vague memories one holds dear.
Even so, human beings struggle...
Using those feelings, those memories, as they aim for better places in life.
When in reality, they are equivalent to electronic signals that insouciantly choose to enter your head.
People lack the foresight to not allow themselves to be controlled by such mentality...
And that is why you are not qualified to be the successor to Kaiba Corporation.
Rather, a person like me who has long surpassed such foolish notions is far more fit for the job.
And I'm going to teach this to you...
And quite thoroughly.
My brother often played with me just like he is now...
But... After that day,
the smile on my brother's face was gone for good.
Yes, since that day...
Since that man came here.
The CEO of Kaiba Corporation, Gozaburo Kaiba, has won the World Chess Championship.
President Kaiba has decided to donate the cash prize of 100,000 yen to charity.
Right...
On that day, up until this very moment even, my plan was put into motion.
It's him...
Gozaburo... Kaiba...
Today is the day I'll keep my promise, Mokuba.
Big Brother...?
That man is Gozaburo Kaiba.
He's the director of Kaiba Corporation.
We should become his adopted children.
Adopted children?
He'll adopt us for sure.
Or rather, I'll make him.
Can I help you?
Please adopt me and my brother!
Say that one more time.
I said, "Please adopt me and my brother."
Naturally, there has to be conditions.
And it will be that you have to adopt us if I beat you in Chess.
What an interesting kid.
But that condition is impossible for you.
You can't become my adopted son like that.
You must not be aware that I beat six world champions in the World Chess Championship...
There's no way you can beat me!
In a match, no outcome is set in stone.
You have absolutely no hope of beating me in Chess.
Yet, knowing this, you still challenge me to Chess anyway.
It doesn't matter either way!
Will you take the challenge? Or will you refuse it?
Which one is it?!
You've got got a nice look in your eyes there.
Very well. I'll accept your challenge.
I'll adopt you if you can beat me.
But I won't hold back!
I don't want you to.
I'll be borrowing one of your classrooms.
Y-Yes! Go right ahead!
Back then, you already had everything planned out, up until this very day.
Of course.
I had done research on every single one of his Chess books
Upon challenging him, I had already memorized his entire strategy, including some additions of my own.
I have to admit that you've made quite a bold impression.
Show me the capacity that surpassed the six world champions in the World Chess Championship.
Shall we start?
This move...
I used the exact same moves he did, putting the game in my favor.
Only I used it as a trap...
He fell into my traps, one after the other...
That moment...
That moment... If my big brother hadn't beaten Gozaburo that moment...
...the smile on my brother's face wouldn't have disappeared!
Wait, Mokuba!
If the past can still be changed,
I wish you'd go back to being the brother I knew who was always smiling!
Calm down, Mokuba.
We're not in the past.
It's imaginary reality Noah's showing us.
It's an illusion!
It's my turn.
Draw!
I Summon Youi in Attack Mode!
The player opposite of whoever Summons Youi
is not permitted to draw a card next turn.
And my turn isn't over yet.
I activate the Magic Card Early Burial from my hand!
I give up 800 of my Life to allow a Monster Card from my Graveyard to revive!
He increases the amount of Monsters on his field so easily...
It's time for me to end this Duel already, or else...
You might be thinking that you'd like to beat me quickly and get to your friends...
...but you're naïve.
I am terribly sorry, but the reality is that won't be happening!
This lineup again?!
Even if I attack with a Monster,
he'll sacrifice two Monsters...
...and activate his Deck Master Ability, Reflector Hole.
Even if I get rid of his Wall Monsters
and successfully attack the player directly...
Go! Retrained Elf Swordsman!
If the player holding Ruklamba the Spirit King receives 1000 points of damage or more,
you can Summon Ruklamba the Spirit King from your hand!
Since he can Special Summon from his hand,
my attacks only strengthen my opponent's line of Wall Monsters!
I have to make sure I don't attack carelessly...
What's wrong with you?
Are you so terrified that you've become frozen with fear?
I'd like to experience what your Deck Master can do at least once...
Although, Kuriboh probably won't do much to prove itself.
Don't let it bother you.
I believe in you.
And I shall now declare "turn end"!
We did it!
Huh?
Yes! We finally got outta there!
But it's still the Virtual World.
No matter how you think about it,
it's too strange for a dungeon like this to be inside a mobile fortress.
What are you going on and on about?!
Come on! Let's go find Shizuka-chan!
-Shizuka-chan!
Anyone, help me!
Shizuka-chan!
Sideways! Run sideways!
No use She can't hear us!
What a pain in the ass!
Hey! This way!
Honda-san!
Shizuka-chan! This way!
Man, I didn't break a sweat!
Thank you very much, Otogi-san!
No! It was a piece of cake!
It was thanks to me!
My turn!
Because of the Special Effect of Youi from before...
I can't draw a card this turn!
You have a greater chance of winning a war if you have higher numbers.
Such advice can be found in countless numbers of strategical books.
For example, it was said back in Ancient China that, "You can't do harm to a battalion."
Or as they said in France, "Victory lies in keeping a battalion"
These proverbs are spoken even today.
But on the other hand,
A militarist of Prussia once said...
"The quantity of troops is just one of the factors in winning."
And there are many other incidents in history that teaches us the same thing.
You're annoying! Be quiet already!
If I attack with Retrained Elf Swordsman,
and he uses his Deck Master Ability again...
The Elf Swordsman will instead directly attack me!
But it will reduce the number of Monsters he has on the field to use for his Deck Master Ability by doing so.
Even if the attack of the Elf Swordsman doesn't
make him use his Deck Master Ability,
I can still get rid of his sacrificial Monsters.
It's a risk I'm willing to take to get an advantage!
Retrained Elf Swordsman, attack Ipiria!
At this moment, I activate my Deck Master Ability!
So he did it?
I sacrifice Ipiria and Youi!
And launch the Reflector Hole!!
Which makes the attack of the opponent invalid
and in return steals the Attack Points from the opponent's Life Points!
He's coming...!
Damaged twice now, eh?
So, how's it feel? Painful, isn't it?
If you are attacked one more time,
the mental shock will render your body unable to move,
and even if your Life doesn't hit zero,
you could lose your actual life in this world first.
But there shouldn't be any Monsters left for him to sacrifice...!
Why?!
His Tribute Monsters should have disappeared!
By sacrificing Ruklamba,
you can Special Summon two Monsters with a total combined Attack Power of 2000 points.
However, the Attack Power of the Monsters you place on the field
must not total higher than 2000.
So he was able to Summon them with Ruklamba's Ability?!
Yes. So I Summoned another Ruklamba and Wall of Illusion.
Wall of Illusion...
If I remember that wall's Effect,
It can make the Monster attacking it
go back to hand of the player.
When you beat them down,
a new enemy will always take its place!
No matter how many times you attack him, he always counters.
What a lowly strategy.
It's a Duel befitting of a man who has taken on the form of a monster.
A Wall Monster that forces your Monsters back to your hand...
And Ruklamba, whom when damaged, Special Summons more allies...
And adding in the Deck Master Ability,
he holds the Effect to make the player damage himself!
The moment I attack him with Chimera,
my Life Points will fall to zero!
And what's more... What's with the damage being done to my body?
This Duel is too dangerous!
If we don't save the others as soon as possible,
they may be in grave danger!
What's wrong with you?
Is this the first time you feel like you'll lose?
But you don't need to feel ashamed.
A general of Prussia once said...
"A true master of failure will feel his pending fate to lose long before it happens."
Are you going to surrender?
But your body is mine the moment you do.
Well, you were destined to lose when you chose Kuriboh as your Deck Master.
You at least look somewhat threatening when you're angry.
I won't let you insult Kuriboh!
Turn end!
It's my turn, then
Man, I can't put it in words!
Do you have any idea how long I've been waiting for this?!
My attack will cause you so much mental damage, you won't be able to take it! You'll fall into despair!
And I'll finally get a body at long last!
I haven't given up yet!
"Preview"
As Yugi is pushed into a corner by the Deepsea Warrior,
I am caught by Cyclops
And in extreme danger.
Is it possible that they want to eat me?
Isn't this all just Virtual Reality?
I have to hurry and escape!
Yugi is working hard, too!
I won't lose either!
So Yugi, don't you dare lose to him!
Next time!
"Counterattacking Rainbow Arch"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise