Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Iron Knight Gearfried"
That is...
The perfectly Evolved form of...
Great Moth!
Now we're getting serious here, Jounouchi!
Great Moth, attack Wyvern Warrior.
Moth's Perfect Storm!!
Oi, is there a Monster with enough Attack to beat that thing?
That's a good question, Mr. Obvious!
M-Mr. Obvious?!
Yes, in all of Duel Monsters,
only two cards are stronger
than Perfectly Ultimate Great Moth.
Just the Gate Guardian and the Ultimate Dragon!
Moreover, Jounouchi,
I highly doubt a commoner like you has rare cards like that.
It really is useless.
There's no way he can defeat the Great Moth.
It's no use believing in yourself.
It's alright.
My brother won't give up that easily.
That's strange!
If you don't understand something, don't do it from the start!
Studying... Working out...
Those not smart or strong enough have no reason to try from the start.
There's no point in worthless guys trying their best.
That's why you won't leave the hospital, right?
If I stay in the hospital, my Mom and Dad and everyone else are really nice to me.
And it's fine if I don't go to school...
Duel Monsters isn't all about fighting with stronger cards.
I'm counting on you, my deck!
All right! Now this match is back in my control!
All that's left is to rely on the Goddess of Luck!
I cover one card,
and turn all the monsters to Attack Mode.
What? Attack Mode?
Doing that, if the Great Moth attacks again...
Jounouchi's life...!
That bastard... Does he really want to lose?
Jounouchi... Do you have some sort of plan?
It's my turn.
Just as a precaution...
I'll cover one card.
Come on, Haga!
You want to lose that badly?
In that case...! Leghul, attack Jounouchi!
No, he's not my target!
I have to endure it.
Jounouchi!
Now that we've come this far, Paracide is no longer of any use.
This is the end, Jounouchi! Disappear!
Perfectly Evolved Great Moth, attack Paracide!
I was waiting for this!
This decides the match, Haga!
Magic Card, Devil Dice!
This decreases your Monster's Attack Points
by whatever I roll on the dice!
It's only two!
But now...
The Attack points of your
Great Moth will reduce by half.
I knew your planning something...
But you can't beat the Great Moth with a card like that.
You're too naive, Haga.
I open one more set card.
Magic Card! Angel Dice!
This Magic Card increases my Monster's Attack Points by whatever I roll on the dice!
Paracide's Attack is 500!
If I win at least a four, I win!
What did you say?
Let me show you.
My gambler's soul!
Great!
Paracide's Attack points
increase to 2000.
C-Can't be...!
-Alright!
-That Great Moth is defeated!
My word!
It's... amazing.
Big bro defeated Great Moth!
Even though his card was that weak!
This is the end of my round.
How dare you, how dare you,
how dare you...?!
How dare you do that to my Great Moth?!
Jounouchi!
I'll never forgive you no matter how much you beg me!
What you talkin' about?!
Your trump card was just wiped out!
Don't get so confident...
I'll now show you the hidden terror of my Super Insect Deck.
Hidden terror?
A card more amazing than the Great Moth.
It's my turn.
I Summon Insect Soldiers of the Sky...
and this Magic Card as well!
"Splinting Insecticide"
This Magic Card can destroy any Insect card on the field.
But Jounouchi...
I won't be destroying your Monsters...
On the contrary...
That is...!
If that card is buried in the Graveyard,
He can Special Summon a Monster!
What? Is it the...
Exactly. I'll be destroying this guy!
And I'll then Summon
the ruler of Insect cards from my hand.
Insect Queen!!
I can't believe I had to play this card against the likes of you...
Time for you to appear, my queen!
Insect Queen?
But she has less Attack Points than Great Moth...
Is that so? The queen of bugs may not have a lot of Attack, but she has quite the Special Ability!
Jounouchi! The bugs on your field will help me a lot!
What?
Because of the Monsters you foolishly let get turned into Insects by Paracide,
my Queen will power up!
What?
No way!
I see.
That's why Haga turned one
of the monsters into an insect.
Insect Queen is the real reason.
Is that also the reason he stopped
summoning any monsters after he lost the Great Moth?
He just defeated Great Moth,
now he's got a better Monster!
It really is hopeless.
You can't touch those with strong cards.
You can try your hardest with weak cards and nothing will change.
No, things do change.
My eyes will be able to see again soon.
All thanks to my brother.
I didn't believe in myself before,
so I refused to take the operation.
But my brother encouraged me.
The operation was successful.
At the moment I take
off my bandage,
The only thing I want to see is the image of my brother Dueling.
My big brother fighting his hardest!
So I trust myself.
If I cheer for him,
I think my feelings will reach my brother.
What if the result is still the same?
It doesn't matter,
because he has done his best.
Prepare yourself, Jounouchi!\M I sacrifice Leghul!
I-It ate it...!
Attack, my Queen!
Queen's Hell Breath!!
Little-Winguard is beaten.
Also, every time my Queen defeats a Monster,
she lays an egg on the field.
It won't be long before her little babies cover the entire field!
Shit...
So she has the ability to Summon more Insect Monsters to the field...?
If this keeps up, more Insect Monsters will hatch on the field.
But, as long as that barrier card is in play, I can't attack!
Even if I Summon a new Monster,
it will just become an Insect and increase Insect Queen's Attack Power!
What should I do?
My turn!
I set one card on the field!
Turn end!
Oh no! Jounouchi!
You forgot to change your Monster Cards to Defense Mode!
It's too late.
You have already declared "turn end".
Your Monsters are all in Attack Mode!
This is bad! If Jounouchi gets attacked,
his Life will reach 0!
It's my turn.
I Summon Cockroach Knight!
When this Monster is sent to the Graveyard,
it is sent to the top of my deck.
This way my Queen can sacrifice is endlessly!
Let's go, my Queen!
Attack Panther Warrior!
Buzz off, Jounouchi!
You fell for it, Haga.
What?
What did you think this set card was?
C-Could it be a Trap?!
For that reason, you purposely forgot to switch your Monsters to Defense Mode?!
That's right! I'll pay you back for the last move you pulled!
Trap activate! Magical Arm Shield!
The Magic Arm grabbed Insect Soldiers of the Sky!
It redirects Insect Queen's attack to the Insect Soldiers of the Sky.
Insect Soldiers of the Sky is beaten!
I can't believe it.
This guy escaped another pinch!
You can do this, big brother!
Good job...
He's changed things somehow.
The problem is... how will he defeat that queen Monster?
I did manage to get ahead...
...but I still can't Summon any Monsters or even attack...!
Shit! I'm still in a bad place!
Jounouchi, how about you quit while you're ahead?
I've researched that your entire deck consists of Warrior-type cards.
Regardless of which one you choose, Paracide will infect every one of them!
Damn, I can't do anything this turn...!
Turn all the monsters
to defense mode.
Turn over!
Looks like you are defenseless.
I'll slowly take you apart.
My turn! I Summon Cockroach Knight!
Attack, my queen!
Queen's Hell Breath!!
Panther Warrior is gone!
I turned all my
monsters to defense mode,
but Haga didn't attack the Paracide Card!
Is he trying to deter all my monsters
and turn them into insects again?
I can't use Magic Arm Shield again.
If I am attacked again,
My life points will be zero.
My future...
Is this hideous monster really going to shatter it?
You can do it, Jounouchi!
You can't give up!
But...!
I can't do a single thing...!
Jounouchi!
It's not like you to just give up like this!
Weren't you going to become a True Duelist and battle Yugi again?!
True Duelist...!
Jounouchi-kun.
I'll take care of this card until then.
That's right!
I made a promise with Red-Eyes and Yugi!
That the moment I become a True Duelist...
When that time comes, I'll fight you once more.
Don't give up! You can do it, bro!
You have to believe in yourself, right?!
Kenta-kun...
If this guy wins,
I might feel like doing something myself!
Let's cheer him on!
Sis!
-Go for it, big brother!
You can do it, Jounouchi!
Don't you lose to that little punk!
Jounouchi!
I won't give up!
I'll definitely continue onward!
Draw!
This card....
It looks like the Goddess of Luck has smiled on me after all...
Useless, useless!
Paracide will infect any Monster you play.
I play a reverse card!
I Summon Gearfried!
Fool!
A Warrior-Type Monster like that will only end up as food to the Paracide!
Go, Paracide!
What?! Paracide isn't working?!
Gearfried is made of iron and steel!
Looks like you were unaware that parasites can't feed off of metal!
Made of steel and iron?!
Good job, Jounouchi!
The animal-like Paracide is in unable to attack itself to artificial objects.
And it's also an Equipment Card and they don't work on him!
I get it! Now since he's not an Insect,
he can get through the barrier!
Haga! Your queen has one fatal weakness!
I'll prove it to you right now!
What?!
Go, Gearfried! Attack the Insect Queen's egg!
Iron Slash!!
Shit! You were aiming for her eggs?!
Yes!!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi realized the Insect Combo's greatest weakness!
That is Insect Queen's very own ability.
Insect Queen absorbs others to increase her own Attack Strength,
and then lays an egg as a result of defeating her enemy.
But those eggs are wide open.
If I take out a 100 Attack egg,
your Life will greatly fall.
That's why you tried to block my Monsters
with that barrier by turning them into Insects.
But Jounouchi, when I attack you next turn,
you're finished!
You pay a high price when you hurt my queen's offspring!
I'll now hit you with the strongest attack of my Super Insect Deck, Queen's Impact!
My turn!
I Summon Soldier Ant!
Also, the Magic Card Ant Reproduction!
This is...
This Magic Card turns my Soldier Ant into an army of ten for one turn.
Do you know that this means, Jounouchi?!
Insect Queen will absorb them all, powering up... Then she'll attack...
That's right, so my Queen
will have 4300 Attack points!
This is bad! If he defeats Gearfried,
Jounouchi will lose!
Take this, Jounouchi!
Insect Queen's attack!
Queen's Impact!!
Don't lose, big brother!
Big brother...
Haga, this match is over already.
What?!
With your defeat, that is.
Trap Card, activate! Graverobber!
Graverobber, you said?!
Yup. And the card I'm taking from your Graveyard is...
Ya see, I really can't stand bugs!
All right! Insect Queen is done for!
M-My QUEEN~!!
My turn!
Gearfried, attack his Monster Egg!
He made it!
Jounouchi wins!
Good job!
I'll take your Puzzle Cards and
your Rare Card as the rules say.
N-No way...!
Oh and by the way...
Here's a line you once said yourself.
You're... too weak.
Amazing! He's amazing, your big brother!
He never gave up once and defeated such a strong opponent!
Yeah...!
Big sis!
I'm gonna go to school!
I'm gonna try believing in myself again!
I wanna be just like your bro!
I won't give in so easily!
Kenta-kun!
In exchange...
When your big bro comes here, sis,
you gotta introduce me to him!
I'd like him to be my big brother, too!
Sure, I promise! I'll be sure to introduce you!
Yes! You better keep your promise, okay?!
Of course!
Awesome! I can't believe this guy beat Insector Haga!
And it says he's a nobody!
What the hell is with that?!
I see, it's Jounouchi-kun.
You did it.
It won't be long before I can return this card to you.
I won't lose either!
Now that I think about it, Malik mentioned something about a "Silent Puppet"...
I wonder where he is...?
That pantomime just moved...!
Being controlled by Malik, the pantomime heads off to confront Yugi!
Malik did say to be careful of the Silent Doll...!
Is this what he was talking about?
So that means this is the Rare Hunter holding the second God Card, Osiris the Heaven Dragon?!
Next time!
"Malik's Opening Move: The God Combo"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...