Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
We came to America in order to visit Pegasus, but the one waiting for us...
...was Mai Kujaku!
Even more, she claimed to have defeated Pegasus.
And she wants my soul and Yugi's?!
Just what is wrong, Mai?!
This is... The Barrier of Orichalcos?
Stop, I don't want to fight with you like this!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Mai is Falling Into the Darkness"
Dammit...!
Is Mai serious?!
Impossible, because the one who loses...
...will have their soul taken away.
Please stop it, Mai-san!
Why must the two of you fight in order to keep your souls?!
Other Me!
Stop the two of them!
Yes, if I can destroy that barrier..
Give it a rest, Yugi!
It'll be the same no matter how many times you try.
The power of the Millennium items aren't capable of destroying the boundary.
All of you can only watch the battle from there.
Damn it...
Don't be anxious, Nameless Pharaoh.
When this Duel is over, I'll be your opponent.
It will never be your turn, Rafael!
I'll defeat Yugi, too!
Don't you interfere.
Mai!
Mai-san?
Don't decide things on your own, Mai Kujaku.
Have you forgotten Lord Dartz's orders?
Isn't this fine, Rafael?
Let her do what she wants.
Our King won't complain if we can get their souls, right?
Varon!
What kind of Duel will Mai give us?
Let's observe, shall we?
It's not like we can't jump in if things get sticky later on.
Now, what are you waiting for, Jounouchi?
It's your turn.
Didn't I say that I will not accept this kind of Duel?
Running away?
You're showing your back when victory hasn't been decided yet?!
And you still call yourself a Duelist?!
Like I've said, this is no ordinary Duel!
Either you or me, one of our souls will be taken away if we lose!
So what if that's the case!?
Mai-san!
Dueling is always a serious matter!
It's about putting yourself on the line.
I have been fighting like that all this time...
This isn't just a game!
For you to turn tail and escape, won't that make me look like an idiot?!
You have to do this, no matter what?
Mai?
How many times do I need to repeat myself?!
Jounouchi... You..
Please stop!
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Wyvern Warrior in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
Shit, how should I proceed with this Duel?
It's my turn, draw!
Looks like you are still hesitating...
You won't be able to beat me thinking like that!
I Summon Harpy Lady in Attack Mode!
Because of the effects of The Barrier of Orichalcos, her Attack Power increases by 500 points!
Harpy Lady, attack Wyvern Warrior!
Next, my other Harpy Lady will Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!
I can't watch anymore!
How can I watch a Duel with them putting their lives on the line?!
Why is Mai-san initiating such a Duel?
Did she really become one of Doma's allies?
I don't know...
What could have happened to her after parting ways with us when Battle City ended?
Yugi!
I won't lose to you
the next time we meet!
Right!
But Mai is really serious.
She seriously want to defeat Jounouchi-kun.
How could that be...
Jounouchi-kun!
In addition, apart from the fact that Mai is our opponent,
this situation is clearly bad for Jounouchi-kun, too.
Because of the effect of The Barrier of Orichalcos,
Mai's Monsters will have 500 more Attack Points once they are Summoned.
The Monocle of Timaeus...
With this card's power... maybe I can...
That is The Monocle of Timaeus...
But no matter what powers the card possesses...
This Duel can't be intervened!
Have you woken up yet?
If you really want to defeat me, you'll have to give it your all!
Next, I set one card reverse card! Turn end!
Mai...
It was burning a little while back, huh...?
It's really dangerous to start a fire at a gasoline stand...!
What are you doing?!
Please drive more safely!
I have a bad feeling about this!
I'm gonna speed up, so sit tight!
I knew it. It's no good, Big Brother.
I can't get into contact with Industrial Illusions HQ.
As expected.
Brother?
For that guy called Amelda to be able to pose as Pegasus and lure me out...
We can assume Industrial Illusions HQ has already fallen into enemy hands.
If so, isn't it very dangerous to go straight to Industrial Illusions HQ?
This type of danger does not scare me.
Besides...
I'll bet on this card to turn the tables!
Go! The Fang of Critias!
What did you say?! That card is...!
Due to its Special Ability,
I can Summon a Fusion Monster merged with a Trap Card!
A card that has no identity...
So why do I know of this card's Effect?
It's true that I don't take occult-based theories very well,
There can be no doubt that in reality, this card's strength is real.
If that's the case, I am fine with it...
Big Brother?
Let's speed up, Mokuba.
Before the enemy tries to escape, we must grab hold of their tails.
What really happened to Mai?
This isn't the same Mai standing in front of me who was aiming to be a True Duelist!
Something...! There has to be a reason behind this...!
Those bastards...
Was Mai deceived by them?
Yeah, that must be it!
She would never do something like this on her own!
It's your turn, so hurry up.
What should I do to turn Mai back to normal?
It's my turn! Draw!
Yes, with this card...
I Summon Rocket Warrior in Defense Mode!
Next, I set one card in reverse.
Turn over!
Whats with you, Jounouchi? Playing all defensively?
Mai, defeat him in one shot!
Shut your trap, Varon!
This is my Duel!
Whooo~! How cruel~!
Wait for me, Mai.
I'll definitely save you.
As long as I've got a chance to bring her to her senses...
It's my turn, draw!
Come on, my Harpies!
Go tear the enemy into pieces with your claws!
Harpy Lady, attack!
Next, my other Harpy Lady will Direct Attack Jounouchi!
This is bad!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Reverse card open! Scapegoat!
Right, while I block the attack, I can...
You're too naive, Jounouchi!
Reverse card, open! Nightmare Tri-Mirror!
W-Wha...?
Nightmare Tri-Mirror?
This card is activated only when your opponent Special Summons one or more Monsters.
It can create as many "Copy Tokens" of the selected Monster as the number of Monsters that was Special Summoned.
Wha...?!
That means...
There are four Scapegoat Sheep Tokens!
This means that there will be four Copy Tokens of Mai's Harpy Lady created!
That's playing dirty!
Summoning so many Monsters like that!
Due to the effect of The Barrier of Orichalcos,
Mai can Summon up to ten Monsters on the field.
Damnit!
How could that happen?!
Copy Tokens cannot attack when it's their turn.
But as long as you can't defeat them,
you can't defeat me!
Lastly, I set one card in reverse!
Turn end!
So, Jounouchi... How are you going to overcome this trial?
You won't just do nothing and lose this, will you?
Mai!
Show me the strength you fought with in Battle City!
What should we do?
Jounouchi is completely overwhelmed!
The other me...
Nightmare Tri-Mirror is a card we've never seen before, right?
Yeah...
It's probably a special card that can only be used when the Barrier of Orichalcos is in play.
If that's so, that card too...
Jounouchi-kun will have more obstacles come his way...
It's my turn! Draw!
Yes, with this card...!
I Summon Jet-Black Panther Warrior in Attack Mode!
I'll wake you up right now, Mai!
I sacrifice Scapegoat in order to let Panther Warrior attack!
Reverse card, open!
Harpy Lady Pharaoh Formation!
This Trap Card can be activated only when there are two or more Harpy Ladies on the field!
The wings of fire will negate the opponent's attack!
Panther Warrior's attack is stopped!
How can that be!?
A perfect battle tactic centered around the Harpy Lady!
Mai's deck is much stronger than it was in Battle City!
Shit...!
With this kind of attack, I can't get her to wake up?
What should I do to bring Mai back?
Wake me up?
I'm wide awake!
Those guys haven't deceived me, nor are they controlling me in any way!
With my own will, I've chosen to fight with you!
What did you say?!
That can't be true!
You wouldn't understand...
You, who only knows how to move forward...
Go, Tri-Horned Dragon! Attack Harpy Lady!
Reverse card, open! Silver Screen Mirror Wall!
It will halve the Attack Points of the opponent's attacking Monster!
Damnit!
If so, reverse card, open!
Quickplay Magic, Charge!
This way, the Attack Points of Tri-Horned Dragon becomes 2125!
It'll be my victory!
Reverse card, open! Angel's Hand Mirror!
No way!
This card can switch the opponent's Magic Card effects to another Monster!
I'll switch it to Harpy Lady!
Go, Harpy Lady!
I've lost...!
And so...! The winner is Contestant Mai Kujaku!
After Battle City, with hopes of becoming more on par with you guys...
I entered numerous Duel Tournaments worldwide and won all the way...
But winning wasn't enough to calm my heart.
Rather...
It was such a waste. You were so close to winning.
Nah, that was to be expected of someone who was among the Best Eight from Battle City!
That's true... If she's already that strong...
I wonder how much stronger the champion, Yugi Mutou is!
And to be in the Best Four even without a God Card...
Katsuya Jounouchi is superb too!
I hope I can Duel with them one day!
That is still too far off for us!
That's true!
Indeed!
Woman!
Those who lose a Dark Game, their souls will be eaten alive by the darkness!
Slowly! Oh, so slowly!!
No...
No!!
Let me out, please let me out!
Save me!
NO!!
Save me, save me! Jounouchi!
Yes, what was dominating my heart, was the terror of failure.
And also, the desire to win.
Go, Harpy Lady!
Direct Attack the player!!
No...
My Dueling should be more...
Even though you've won, you sure are looking unhappy.
Who are you?
Duel with me.
Are you scared?
Who would be?!
Then, it's decided!
I win.
You're afraid of losing, aren't you?
Stop it...!
Save me...!
Nooo!
Save me, save me! Jounouchi!
I don't wanna lose...!
Save me, Jounouchi!
He won't come and save you!
Understand that.
As long as you're weak and always depending on others, you'll never win.
But, I know that you're a really strong woman.
Isn't that so?
I don't wanna lose...!
I don't want lose to anyone!
Then, come to us.
We'll give you what you really want.
The things you guys obtained in Battle City...!
I want that too!
The power to never lose as a Duelist!
I never knew that...
You were in that much pain...?
Did they corner you that much, Mai?
I want to catch up to you guys!
I want to beat you all, no matter what!
This is the only way!
I activate the Magic Card, Harpy Lady Phoenix Formation!
I can destroy as many Monsters my opponent has as per the number of Harpy Ladies I control using this card!
What?!
There are six Harpy Ladies on the field!
That means she has more Monsters on the field than Jounouchi...
Jounouchi-kun...!
Then, the sum of the Attack Points of the destroyed Monsters
Will be deducted from the opponent's Life Points!
Go, Harpy Lady!
Use your wings to destroy all the Monsters!
Scapegoat has zero Attack Points, so you're safe, Jounouchi.
I end my turn.
This is getting really bad!
4000 Life versus 200!
Also, Mai has six Monsters on her field, while Jounouchi has no Wall Monsters at all!
If it continues, in the next turn, Jounouchi will...
Can't we do something, Yugi?
Mai has gotten much stronger since Battle City.
And she's betting her all as a Duelist in this battle.
That determination already surpasses Jounouchi-kun's.
No way, that's so wrong!
The two of them are friends!
You have to hang on, Jounouchi-kun!
And you have to carve out your own path!
That's it, huh?
I seem to have expected too much.
Had been wondering what he's like, since Mai's always mentioning him.
But his soul will still be the sacrifice for our God.
Mai...
Am I unable to save you?
Is there nothing I can do for you?
No matter what you think, you're still our comrade.
If this goes on, there's no way I can win anyway.
If I can save you in exchange for my life.. that's fine.
Stop that, Jounouchi-kun!
That's the only thing you must not do!
That's something that a Duelist betting his everything must never do!
Yugi...
You won't save your opponent by giving up on yourself!
No...
The thing that you're thinking of doing will only tarnish the Duelist's soul!
Thanks for that, Yugi.
For stopping me.
The thing I have to do now...
To really save Mai, what I can do is...
My turn! Draw!
Mai, let me accept your feelings with this card!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Mai-san screams like she's going mad.
I had no idea that she was in so much pain.
That's because nobody had noticed that.
Even so...
It's strange to battle with Jounouchi in a Duel that has their souls at stake!
Jounouchi, are you really going to Duel with Mai-san seriously?
Hey Yugi, isn't there any way we can save the both of them in this Duel?
Next time, "Revive! The Third Dragon"
Duel standby!