Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In order to get back my lost memories, we traveled to the land of Egypt.
There, the Door of Memories was opened.
Behind it lies the Egyptian world three thousand years ago.
Am I really the Pharaoh?
And the priests who look a lot like Kaiba and Ishizu...
Here, Bakura and I will start the Ultimate Dark Game!
"Enter the Thief King, Bakura!"
Move aside!
Stop right now!
Where do you think you are?!
Shut up!
If you value your lives, make way!
W-Wait!
What's wrong, Mahado?
My Millennium Ring has detected a great Power of Darkness!
What?!
Who goes there?!
So this is the throne room?
Bakura!
We finally meet, Yugi...
Or should I say, Pharaoh!
Okay! Let's get the game started!
Lowly thief...!
As long as we are here, you will not lay even one finger upon the Pharaoh!
You guys wanna fight against me first?
Fine with me... Looks like all the Millennium Items are here as well.
The Millennium Items...?
In that case... I'll just take all of your Millennium Items as well!
The Soul Labyrinth inside the Millennium Puzzle...
The Door of Truth that connects to my other self's memories lies inside!
However, if those who do not wield Millennium Items enter that labyrinth in his heart...
They cannot return unless they find the True Door.
In spite of that, do you still wish to go?
It doesn't matter... Let's go, Yugi!
Let's search for that True Door!
All of you can't go.
I will go alone.
Yugi!
I can't put your lives in anymore danger!
Besides, we may not even find the other me or that door!
What are you saying, Yugi!
We're all friends!
That's right!
While we're wasting time, the other Yugi may..!
We've made up our minds!
Guys...
If so, everyone, please hold hands and concentrate.
Other Me... We're going to save you, no matter what it takes!
Yugi...
Millennium Ankh, use your power
to guide us into the labyrinth dwelling within the Millennium Puzzle!
You really think you guys're strong enough to stop me?!
Listen up, lowly thief.
These seven Millennium Items have maintained order in this world.
The only people qualified
to hold these items...
...are us priests, who have trained our souls and the Divine Pharaoh who rules this land!
If a person like you, with a heart of evil, were to touch a Millennium Item,
your very soul would burn away.
The Gods themselves would punish you with death!
Saying it like that only makes me even more excited...
Now I want them even more!
Then we will use our powers and make you suffer the death penalty!
Don't be so hasty!
Killing the lot of you hardly harbors any benefits for me at all!
Just give me your Millennium Items obediently and be my followers!
What?!
Naturally, I'm not just spouting bullshit.
You can take these in exchange.
These are...!
Don't tell me..!
Whoa there! It's a bit early to be surprised!
I've got more gifts coming your way!
What is that?
That is...
...Akhenamkhanen's coffin!
Vile creature...!
How dare you touch the previous Pharaoh's body in such a manner!
The previous Pharaoh...?
Don't tell me...
Is that... my... father?
Curse you!
You will not be forgiven, wretched scum!
The Sealing Tablet!!
What're you about to do with that thing?
Petty thief, your boasting shall come to an end right there!
Wait! Be careful, Shada.
Kalim...!
Look at how the
Millennium Scales are tilting!
It can't weigh that man's evil!
The darkness in his heart is unmeasurable...
There is terrifying evil residing in his soul!
Millennium Ankh! Lead me into this sinner's soul!
The Ka inside him..!
What's wrong, Shada?
The Ka inside him is way too big!
The Sealing Stone is too small for it!
That can't be!
Don't panic! His Ka is about to appear!
What is this Ka?!
I don't believe it! How can such a demon dwell within a mere thief's soul?!
What's the matter, you scum?!
Has my Diabound given you a good scare?
Hmph. Don't underestimate the power of the Millennium Items, thief.
Using the power of the Millennium Rod...
...I cast you into the Holy Stone!
Watch carefully, the power of the Millennium Rod!
Divine Priest...
Did you really think I'd become a "good person"...
...after sealing the embrasure within me?
What?!
The Sealing Tablet...
Yugi...
Yugi!
Hey, wake up, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Hey! Get up, Honda, Anzu!
This place is...
It's my other self's Soul Labyrinth.
This place?
That's right...
We have entered the room of the Pharaoh's soul by the power of the Millennium Ankh.
Shadi...
Then the True Door is somewhere in here?!
Okay, let's start searching!
Search the hell outta this place!
Yes!
Wait for us, Other Me!
We'll find the True Door and follow you to the world of memories!
At all costs.
What did you say?!
Yugi went to Egypt?
Yes, and apart from Yugi Mutou...
Katsuya Jounouchi, Hiroto Honda and Anzu Masaki have gone as well.
Yugi is in Egypt...
I'll give this to you to make up for it!
This is your invitation to the Ultimate Dark Game we will be competing in.
But aren't you at least a bit interested in the connection between you and Blue-Eyes?
What nonsense.
Your sealing stones are useless against my Diabound!
Vile cur! We will let you witness the true powers of us six High Priests!
-Yes!
Why are there Duel Disks in this age?!
"Duel Disks"?
There are seven "Shrine of Wedju" sanctuaries surrounding the palace.
Being able to summon the servant Ka in those tablets...
...is the true display of our country's alchemical skills!
The DiaDhanks!
DiaDhanks?!
They pulled out something interesting.
Seto, the enemy is strong... if we don't join forces-
No! I alone will be enough to resolve this petty matter!
Seto!
I summon the Ka lying asleep in my Shrine of Wedju!
Come to our side and become our strength!
T-This has to be..!
Galestgoras, I summon thee!
What I'm seeing now is exactly like a Duel Monsters Duel!
Go, Galestgoras!
Rip Diabound to shreds!
Did Duelists already exist back in this age?!
What I'm seeing now is exactly like a Duel Monsters Duel!
Go, Galestgoras!
Snap him in two!
Falcos!!
What?! Falcos?!
Take this!
M-My Lord!
Unthinkable...! He actually had another Ka?!
That was summoned from the Shrine of Wedju...
How is he able to summon separate Ka?!
Aren't you guys forgetting something important?
It was lying there in
Akhenamkhanen's tomb...
I have it with me.
This thing!
That is the DiaDhank belonging to King Akhenamkhanen!
That's right.
There were many of them in Akhenamkhanen's tomb...
The stone slabs lining the shrine!
You lowlife!
Is that something you've summoned from King Akhenamkhanen's tomb?!
Unforgivable!
You are tainting the holiness of the Pharaoh!
Cut the bullshit!
"Holy Pharaoh", my foot!
Akhenamkhanen...!
He's the last person I'd call that!
Didn't he create the Millennium Items you're all wearing to gain evil power!?
My father was the one who created the Millennium Items?!
You're wrong!
The great King Akhenamkhanen put an end to wars between countries,
and brought peace to this land!
And he wished for a millennium of peace for this war-torn country!
That is why he left these Millennium Items behind!
That's right!
King Akhenamkhanen wanted to
stamp out all evil...
To purge all sinners of their wrong-doings!
He left us these seven holy items imbued with the power of justice and righteousness!
Peace and justice...?
Don't make me laugh!
It's true that the holders of the Millennium Items gain great powers.
But those items also respond to the darkness in the holders' heart...
...and drags them into
the World of Darkness!
Quite the problem-makers they can be!
You may not know about this...
But if you place the seven Millennium Items on the stone tablet in the village of Kul Elna...
One can gain the powers
of the underworld!
That's absurd!
The village of Kul Elna, you say..?
Why does this person
know of that village?
E-Everyone who knows about that village should be dead!
If any of you doesn't believe what I say, go and try it yourself.
If you do, the Pharaoh will be nothing...
...because you'll truly
gain the powers of a god!
What do you mean?
Silence your tongue of this nonsense!
Everyone, do not listen to his words!
They are all lies!
Insulting the Millennium Items is no different than insulting us directly!
That is unforgivable!
Fine with me.
Since you want to die so badly, I'll crush you all to pieces!
Come forth, Minotaur!
Bastet!
Spiria!
Zelua!
Gadius!
Magus of Illusion!
Summon!!
Akhenamkhanen!!
Forgive me!!
That was nothing but a piss-level Ka, anyway...!
But my Diabound is worlds apart from it!
Diabound!!
Spiral Wave!!
What power!
Do not drop your guard, everyone!
Then leave this to me!
Don't, Mahado! Your Ka is not powerful enough!
But-!
I'll summon forth a new servant,
the Centaur!
Come forth, Centaur!
Kalim!
By the sacred powers
of the Millennium Scales,
I will combine both Minotaur and Centaur into a new Ka!
Ka Fusion!!
What?! Fusion?!
Appear, Minocentaur!
Minocentaur, attack Diabound!
You're annoying me!!
You couldn't even touch me!
Are you so sure of that?
What?
Mahado, now!
My servant, Magus of Illusion.
Activate your Special Power!
Binding Illusion!!
Now you can't escape.
You're too naive.
You think too little of Diabound.
Diabound!
Spiral Wave!!
What a thing to happen!
Just him alone, and our priests are..!
Your level just wasn't enough to defeat me!
What insolence!
Bakura!
Is this the Ultimate Dark Game you were talking about?!
Shut up!
Let's bring this to "game over" already!
I'll meet you and your priests in the afterlife, Your Highness!
Spiral Wave!!
Spiria!!
Isis!
You..!
That's why I said that before!
In the end, this was all
your level was worth!
Bakura!
Move your dirty foot this instant!
Pharaoh!
Pharaoh, it's too dangerous!
Please step back!
Bakura, how is this the Ultimate Dark Game?
Such senseless murder, plunder and destruction can hardly be called that!
What you've done
just makes me want to barf!
Oh? Well, excuse me.
Even if you don't remember him, this must be quite the emotional reunion for you.
Here ya go!
I'll give him back!
Oh, King Akhenamkhanen! To think you'd return to the palace in such a manner!
Please believe me, Pharaoh!
I served King Akhenamkhanen for many years and so I swear upon my words!
Your father spent his life fighting to keep peace in this country!
He was an honorable king!
My Pharaoh!
My... father...?
Justice is in the name of the Gods...
That voice just now...!
Yugi, to be honest with you, I myself have no idea
what the rules of this
Ultimate Dark Game are.
However, there's one thing I know for sure.
That is, that the seven Millennium Items are already in your hands.
So I have to snatch them away.
That alone is my requirement to win this!
Let's put an end to this right now, Yugi!
It won't be that easy for you!
Bark all you like!
Spiral Wave!!
Bakura, you've forgotten one very important thing.
My strongest servants!
About the Three Illusionary Beasts!
The Three Illusionary Beasts?
Don't tell me... The legendary Three Illusionary Beasts?
The three Gods that are sealed in the tablets within the Pharaoh's shrine?!
But their real names are unknown.
It's been said that only the chosen Pharaoh would know their names.
But... Can this be...?
That this new Pharaoh can control them?
Now, I'll Summon them in the name of God!
My strongest servant, the Three Illusionary Gods!
The first one's name is...
Justice is in the name of the Gods...
I believe your words, Father.
Summon Obelisk!
Obelisk?!
Bow before the Gods, Bakura!
God Hand Crusher!!
Dream on!!
Diabound's Special Ability!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
What?!
Blue-Eyes is weeping...?
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
In the other Yugi's world of lost memories...
There, the Ultimate Dark Game between him and the dark personality of Bakura-kun has begun.
Even though we are now inside the Millennium Puzzle...
...and we made it into the labyrinth...
We have no idea how to find the correct door of truth that leads to the other Yugi.
Please, Yugi!
Please guide us there!
Next time!
"Mahado's Resolve"
Please look forward to it!