A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Saint Fire Giga!!
Yugi... there's something you've lost sight of.
What?!
It's something you can see, but can't see!
Yugi, I wonder if you can find the answer to that.
"The Legendary Strongest Soldier: Chaos Soldier Descends"
As long as she has the Shadow of Temptation in play, I can't use my Monsters in Defense...!
Even if I successfully launch a powerful attack, Silver Screened Mirror Wall will halve their Attack Power...!
What should I do?!
Wonderful!
Her Harpie Deck holds no weakness.
On top of that, Yugi boy's heart is wavering.
I can see the color of defeat edging into him...
Yugi, what's going on with you?
Mai-san's gotten much stronger than when she fought Jounouchi and me...!
Is this Mai's full potential...?
Was it just luck that I beat her before...?
No, Jounouchi.
It wasn't luck that allowed you to beat me.
Back then, I was playing as hard as I could.
Truthfully, when I lost to you, I was completely devastated.
Denying reality, I closed my eyes from the truth.
But even though I closed my eyes, I couldn't get your voice out of my mind.
Right...
"Something you can see... but can't see..."
And only when I confronted my real self did I understand the meaning of those words.
Your real self...?
Jounouchi, do you know why you got so far in this tournament?
That's obvious!
It's because of the friends I've made!
There's no way such a bad player like me would've gotten this far without them!
Right. Jounouchi, you've acknowledged your own weakness.
And you try and become stronger to overcome that weakness.
That's a Duelist's courage!
That's what I learned from Jounouchi.
From me...?
Yugi, a Duelist's courage isn't tested when they win!
It's when they lose!
And a strong heart is born only when you're prepared to lose.
Yugi, do you have that courage in you?
The preparation to lose...?
That's right! Back then...!
When Kaiba put his life on the line...
I became afraid of losing...
I was so afraid of losing and scarring my pride.
But the one who didn't fear losing the Duel, unlike me...
The one suffering most from our loss to Kaiba...
Is the other me...
That's right... I wasn't aware of that.
No... I just wouldn't open my eyes to the truth.
The strength of the other me made up for my weakness.
And that...
Is what can be seen, but not seen!
Mai!
I'm proud I got to fight you.
And this is where the real fight starts!
You're far too late...
Even you can't get out of this situation.
My turn.
I am... no longer... afraid of defeat!
Brain Control!
Brain Control?!
Right. It allows me to control an enemy Monster for one turn.
I'll target Harpie's Pet Dragon with this card!
Too bad.
The Pet Dragon is Harpie's servant...
It won't attack the Harpie, even if it's brain-washed!
I realize that.
But I'm not going to attack the Harpie.
I set one card on the field.
Also...
Catapult Turtle!
I place Harpie's Pet Dragon on the catapult in Attack Mode!
Once in Attack Mode, the Mirror Wall automatically appears.
Harpie's Pet Dragon is prepared for launch!
Dammit...!
Catapult Turtle has the ability to destroy walls and fortresses...!
Here goes!
-Alright!
-Great job!
Silver Screened Mirror Wall just...
Not just the Mirror Wall.
The Monster used as a sacrifice for Catapult Turtle was your Monster.
Therefor, you lose half of the destroyed Monster's Attack Points, 1150, from your Life.
Alright!!
Yugi just completely turned the tables!
Something in Yugi boy's mind has begun to change...
Just what has happened?
Thanks to Mai...
...and the other me, I've realized it.
Once a Duelist prepares for his loss, true power can be grasped!
My turn!
The only Monster Yugi has is Catapult Turtle...
If I dispose of Catapult Turtle with Harpie's attack,
Yugi's Life Points will drop to 0.
Then I'll win.
But...
That Set Card Yugi played bothers me...
I don't have any more cards that can destroy his Traps...
So what do I do?
Do I attack or hold back?
Come on and attack me, Mai.
I...
...won't attack...
I still have the advantage, even if I don't make a move this turn.
Instead...
I'll play this card, making my Harpies even stronger!
Kaleidoscope - Magnificent Replication!
The Harpie Ladies!
What'dya think, Yugi?
I end my turn there.
But next turn, you'll experience the harem from hell!
It's my turn, then.
It's a real shame, Mai.
What are you trying to say?
Had you attacked last turn, I'd have lost.
What'd you just say!?
My Set Card... was the Monster Recovery card.
A hand-refreshing card!
You missed your chance to win, Mai.
Well done.
But next turn, I'll finish you off for good!
With the Harpie Ladies' Triangle Attack, that is!
Because of Shadow of Temptation, the Monster I play will immediately be forced into Attack Mode.
Right now, nothing in my hand will help with that.
In that case...
I activate the Monster Recovery's magic this turn!
I return my Monster Cards and my hand to the deck,
shuffle,
and draw five new cards!
Even in these five cards, I don't have a card that can beat the Harpie Ladies...
The Harpie Ladies' Attack Power is 2700.
Drawing out a Monster with enough Attack Power to take them down
is a bit unrealistic, don't you think?
Plus, thanks to the Shadow of Temptation, your Defense has been sealed.
It's the end of the line, Yugi!
Yugi, what's wrong with you?!
You're not the type of man who'd give up like this!
Yugi, keep trying!
There's got to be some way to beat Mai!
But seriously, Mai's pheromone cards won't go down that easily.
Who the hell cares about pheromones?!
Yugi! Don't you let these sluts mess with you!
Wait... The Harpie's Shadow of Temptation...
That's it! I still have a chance!
This card in Defense Position!
It's futile!
No matter what Monster that is, it'll be switched into offensive position!
Wh-What in the-
Impossible!
Just as I thought.
I'll show you the card I played.
Shadow of Temptation is very effective against men.
But it won't work on a woman!
To think you could come up with that...
My turn is over!
Thank goodness.
I was really nervous.
But even if he got through this turn,
his trouble is far from over with.
It's only a matter of time before the Holy Elf is wiped out.
My, aren't you a tenacious man!
But you're done for.
My turn!
I use the Resurrection of the Dead card to bring a Monster back to life!
Resurrection of the Dead...!
That's...!
Harpie's Pet Dragon has come back!
He gains an additional 300 Attack Points for every Harpie Lady on the field!
What?!
He's got 2900 Attack Points!
And now for this turn's attack...
Harpie Ladies!
Triangle Ecstasy Spark!!
Yugi!
Holy Elf has been incinerated!
Now it's your turn, Yugi.
But before the atrocious power of my Monsters' attacks...
...you have no hope of prevailing.
I beat you, Yugi!
The card sleeping at the top of the deck...
Everything lies on this one draw!
Every single one of our fates!
My other self...
Please lend me your strength!
Give me the power to believe in this card!
No matter what you pull, all that awaits you is failure.
Sealing Swords of Light!?
He actually drew the Sealing Swords of Light...!
Even in this situation!?
Nice!
Now Mai's been sealed for three turn!
Yugi's still got a chance to win!
You really are a stubborn man!
Very well.
If you're going to show me the embers of your Duelist's Fire,
I'll wait it out for three more turns.
Mai!
No matter what happens, my flame of battle never extinguishes!
Harpie's Pet Dragon gets stronger for each Harpie Lady that appears on the board.
If I can't beat him, I have no hope of victory.
Then I have only one goal!
I'll let the legendary strongest warrior descend within these next three turns!
Now, Yugi! You have no Monsters on the field!
I know.
I'll call this card out.
Turn over!
Wh-What the hell is with that wimpy Monster?
It actually got aroused by my sweet Harpie's pheromones,
and it's trying to attack her straight on!
Are you making fun of me, Yugi?!
I'm serious, Mai.
He was chosen out of the many cards I could have drawn.
He's a piece to the puzzle of victory!
I can't even comprehend why you'd keep a card like that in your deck!
I can't attack while the Sealing Swords of Light is in activation!
I'll draw a card and end my turn.
Yugi, just two turns left!
I can't call forth the legendary strongest warrior with just the cards in my hand.
I need the key card...!
My turn!
No good! This isn't the card!
I have no idea what you're planning,
but I do know one thing.
The Goddess of Victory hasn't smiled on you today!
Then how about this card?
Resurrection of the Dead!
I use this card to revive Dark Knight Gaia!
Dark Knight Gaia?
Well, he's a step above that little Kuriboh, but...
He's still no match for my Harpie's Pet Dragon's Attack Power.
Turn over!
My turn!
This is isn't it, either!
Yugi...
It's alright, Anzu.
Believe in him. Yugi still doesn't have the look of defeat!
I see.
So you plan to call forth the legendary strongest warrior?
But I am afraid that is impossible to do without that card.
Yugi boy, will you be able to draw that card?
In just one turn?
My turn!
I did it!
I drew another of my lovely Harpies!
If I play this card next turn...
I'll have four Harpies on the field!
And then Harpie's Pet Dragon's Attack Power will rise to 3200!
The effects of the Sealing Swords of Light disappear next turn.
I'll show you a perfect victory!
Turn over!
Looks like you couldn't gain anything in these three turns.
This card is the door to fate!
Am I still frightened?
I...
Guys!
That's right...
I have no reason to be afraid of losing.
Everyone will stand by my side, no matter what.
Will this card lead to a dead end?
Or will it be the light at the end of the tunnel?
Let's find out!
My word...!
Yugi boy... What a marvelous man you are!
Mai...
I've gathered... all the pieces to my victory!
The Magic Card, Chaos Ritual!
Chaos Ritual!?
I now sacrifice my two Monsters, whose total Levels equal 8 to activate the Chaos Ritual!
One soul shall merge with light!
The other soul shall merge with the darkness!
Between light and darkness, the gateway to chaos is opened!
What!?
The Chaos Soldier descends!
It's the legendary strongest warrior...?
Chaos Soldier attacks!
Chaos Blade!!
I've beaten Harpie's Pet Dragon!
My... Harpie's Pet Dragon has...
A-Amazing...
So that's Yugi's trump card?
The strongest warrior?
What attack strength...!
The match has come to an end.
The girl's mind...
I can clearly see the flame of battle extinguishing.
I just needed one more turn...
If Chaos Soldier didn't appear...
f I could have just played this card...!
I wouldn't have lost.
I no longer have a card in my deck that can beat the Chaos Soldier.
That's the... "Surrender Card"...!
Mai...
Eh, what?
What happened?
"Surrender Card"...
When one places their hand on the deck, it's a sign of forfeit.
Mai-san...
I don't want to see my Harpies killed off next turn.
I lose, Yugi.
Mai.
Thank you.
Yugi...
Thanks to you, I found what I lost sight of during this Duel.
What I can see, yet can't see.
There's no such thing as an invincible Duelist.
Everyone has some kind of weakness in their heart.
But, despite knowing that, everyone tries to cover up their weakness.
Yes. What you can see, yet can't see.
Everyone knows it, yet they put up a bold front.
Yugi, there are two ways of losing.
A loss where everything ends...
And a loss bringing you closer to victory.
I will make myself stronger because of this loss!
And I'll grab my dream in the end!
"Preview"
It's the second match of the tournament finals!
It's finally time for Jounouchi to shine!
But his opponent is the American Champion, Bandit Keith!
God!
No matter what it takes, you better win this!
Eh!?
You lost your entry card!?
What the heck are you doing?! Gosh!
Next time! "Brutal: The Heavy Metal Deck"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship