Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"To the Final Battlefield!
Dartz VS Yugi and Kaiba"
What's...?
Get out of here!
This building is about to collapse...!
Say what?!
The elevator!
We're screwed! There's nowhere left to run!
Seto-sama~!!
Isono!!
Guys! Get moving!
Are you alright, Rafael?
Sorry...
Yugi!
-Yugi!
Director! It's far too dangerous to stay here!
Yugi!!
Rafael!!
Take this!
Now go, Yugi! Change your destiny with your own hands!
Rafael!
Director!!
Quickly, Director!
Rafael!
Forget about me!
Rafael!!
Come on, Yugi!
Jump, Yugi!
Rafael...
So that's what Paradias really looks like...
Does that mean we were tricked by some sort of magic spell or something...?
Not just us...
This entire city...
No, everyone in the entire world.
Rafael...
Kaiba.
Here...
And that is...?
Rafael gave it to me.
This is...!
A map!
That's where Dartz is...
Isono!
Sir!
Take us here!
Who're they?!
The Navy!
Are they working with Dartz?!
Are they asking us to follow them?
I wonder where they're taking us...
What the heck's that?!
Locusts?
A whole swarm?
That's dangerous!
L-Look ahead!
Back! Back up!
R-Right...
Not good! They've got us surrounded!
Becky!
Okay! Come at me if you're gonna!
What?
Are you people soldiers of Doma?
Mr. Kaiba, we have been keeping a close eye on Doma's movements.
And all of your people's actions as well.
What's that supposed to mean?
We are fully aware that Doma has been manipulating the world on a massive scale.
However, Doma's influence has gone as far as to even medium federal taxes. They are beyond our call of duty.
We haven't the authority to launch an attack against Doma.
So Doma really does have control over the major powers and their politics.
It's shameful to say this, but the fate of the world rests with your group.
Hmph! I never asked about your tax situation nor did I request for your authority from the start.
At the very least, we can take you there halfway.
And we'll refuel your helicopter.
We cannot proceed any further than this.
But please keep this in mind.
There are a great number among us who pray for your success.
Hmph... I appreciate that.
My son is a huge fan of Duel Monsters!
Please protect the future of our children!
Isono, start up the helicopter!
His map said it was around here somewhere.
It's out of the question, Director!!
We can't get any closer than this!!
Are the tornadoes inviting us?
Brother!
That's it!
Dartz is inside there...
Go on!
Sir!
This is Doma's stronghold!
Let's go, Yugi.
Yeah.
What is this oppressing aura?
Yeah... I can feel it too.
Yugi...
Guys, stay right by our sides!
Yugi!
There!
Jounouchi!
Mai!
Those must be the taken souls...!
Partner!
Partner!!
I have waited for your arrival...
Nameless Pharaoh.
Seto.
Dartz!
Welcome to my temple.
If I am to gather souls harnessing strength on par with that of your own...
...the birth of my God shall be indubitable.
The "birth" you speak of is nothing but a massive headache!
I feel it...
O Sovereign Souls.
I shall prepare a special place for the both of you.
Cut the bullshit! We already took down the "Three Musketeers" you sent after us!
Dartz! You're the only one left!
I wonder...
What do you mean by that?
You have certainly taken down my Musketeers...
However, their souls were already planned offerings from the very start.
That's just... too cruel!
But that alone will not suffice.
I am in need of your souls as well in order to complete the resurrection of my God.
Dartz! Stop this pointless battle!
And return the souls you took away!
The only way that will come to pass is if you are to defeat me.
What did you say?!
Bear witness!
Nameless Pharaoh!
Seto!
This must be the source behind that oppressing aura.
H-Hey! Look at that!
There's this many people trapped here...?
And they're not just people from our present time...!
Correct.
This place is filled with souls collected over 10,000 years.
I myself am nothing more than a relic of this history.
Dartz...
Yugi, nothing you say will get through to this guy.
Just as Duels were originally...
...this shall be a battle ritual where we
place our very souls at the stake.
We are to follow the way things were meant to be.
In that case, I'll be your opponent!
No, Kaiba! I can't stand here and let you take him on by yourself!
Then as settlement...
...I shall take both your souls at once!
Pharaoh! Seto!
Let's do this, Kaiba!
I don't need you to tell me!
Duel!!
Varon...
Mai...
And me as well...
We still have something we must do!
Yugi...
Brother...
My turn! Draw!
I play a Ritual Magic from my hand!
Descent of White Dragon activates!
And from my hand...
I sacrifice Blood Vorse!
Come forth! Knight of White Dragon!
And I activate his Special Ability!
By sacrificing Knight of White Dragon...
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
I'm unable to attack within the first turn of a match.
So I'll end my turn with this.
Here goes, Dartz!
My turn!
I activate the Chaos Ritual from my hand!
I offer up Magnet Valkyrian as the sacrifice!
I invoke upon the legendary warrior, Chaos Soldier!
And after setting up a reverse face-down card, I end my turn!
They're awesome! Both my brother and Yugi!
They Summoned their Ace Monsters in just one turn!
Very perceptive.
You both seem to have grasped the depth of who it is you are fighting against.
My turn.
O great card born from the bowels of darkness...
Bestow upon them your almighty power!
It's here...!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...!
Wh-What the...?
His fighting spirit's no joke...!
I'm an outsider and I can feel it clear as day!
Yugi...
He's...!
I knew it...! He's no ordinary man!
Arise...
Orichalcos Gigas!
Don't let your guard down, Kaiba!
This Monster has an incredibly strong power!
Humph! If he didn't play a Monster of at least this level, things wouldn't be interesting in the slightest!
I shall then deplete my Life...
...and Special Summon Orichalcos Kyutora!
This will finish off my turn.
My turn!
Dartz, if you are truly the one
composing Doma's actions,
this Duel's victory should also be within your grasp.
Yet, you've only managed to Summon a couple of weak Monsters on your field...
...and victory has already fallen into my hands.
I haven't the slightest idea as to what kind of Duelist you are!
But you've forgotten one very important factor...
For you are now...
...taking on the strongest
Duelists in existence as your enemies!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
I fuse the three Blue-Eyes from my hand and on the field!
Come forth!
My ultimate servant!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!!
The Blue-Eyes Ultimate!
Yugi... If you're the True Duelist you say you are,
you should be able to call forth
our new servant to kill him off!
Kaiba, I'll take it from here!
My turn!
This draw, Dartz, will shatter all of your ambitions in a single blow!
Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Fusion!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!
Chaos Soldier!
The ultimate Fusion Summon!!
Come forth!
Master of Dragon Knight!!
Amazing! It's got 5000 Attack Points!
My big brother and Yugi make the strongest tag pair in the world!
Trap Card, open!
Meteor Rain!
When we attack holding stronger Attack than your Defense,
you receive the difference as direct damage!
It's got 3500 more Attack Points than the Defense Power of Dartz's Monster!
And that'll bring his Life right down to zero!
This one attack alone will put an end to everything!
Go!
Master of Dragon Knight!!
Take this, Dartz!!
Galaxy Crusher!!
Nameless Pharaoh. Seto.
You are unable to defeat me!
What in the...?!
Big Brother?!
Yugi!
Space...?
Dartz!
What's with this bogus illusion?!
Do not lose your cool.
Your attack just now simply triggered the power of Orichalcos.
Within even a very fragment of the Orichalcos lies with it memories that far exceed that of human society.
This is dubbed the "World of Memories" that lies dormant within the Orichalcos.
Memories of the Orichalcos?
Long before this age...
...everything in this world was born from darkness.
All of us... Even the very planet we live on.
And this world is once again headed back to the darkness... taking with it its own demise.
The citizens of this planet caused this and will now pay a very high price because of it.
That is the absolute way of this world.
As a result, it will take with it everything.
Just as human beings and their hearts...
...the threads of time shall embellish in the very darkness itself.
Are you saying darkness of the heart is the way of life?!
Our planet is beautiful...
Perhaps it is nothing short of a miracle that the universe could produce such an existence.
Are you guys unable to hear it?
The cries of this planet?
The planet's... cries...?
That's...!
It is the metropolis I once governed.
As well as it is the city I destroyed with my very own hands!
Atlantis!
What did you say?!
Atlantis was... such a beautiful city...
However, that same path soon carved way for its destruction.
Yugi and Kaiba-kun have formed the ultimate tag team!
And they managed to take down Dartz in one shot using the ultimate Monster, Master of Dragon Knight!
Or so we thought!
All three of them disappeared in a huge flash of light!
Yugi and Kaiba-kun witness the memory of Atlantis's destruction within the light!
And that hit didn't work?!
Then how will they win this Duel?!
Next time!
"The Tragedy of Atlantis"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other