Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In exchange for a return flight, we joined the KC Grand Prix Duel Tournament.
Though I dislike being used by Kaiba as a publicity tool,
It's not so bad to simply enjoy the Duels.
This time, my opponent is this dislikable bastard that carries flowers, Sieg Lloyd.
That arrogant attitude of his... I'll settle this Duel once and for all!
"The Goddesses of Monster Extermination"
I invoke a Magic Card!
Walkuren Ritt!
This card allows me to Special Summon all the Valkyries I have in my hand.
Descend! Warrior-Maidens!
He Summoned four Monsters at once!
It is too late for regrets now.
Watch carefully!
I activate the Special Effect of Valkyrie Zwei.
When this Monster is Summoned, one of the opponent's Monsters will be destroyed.
Then, the Special Effect of Valkyrie Erste is also activated.
By removing one Monster from the game...
By that, I was referring to the fallen Psycho Shocker.
For the turn, she will take on the same Attack Power as the Monster removed.
What?!
You do not have the time to mourn over the death of your Monster.
Valkyrie Erste, attack the opposing player directly.
Look out, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Next, the other three Valkyries will Direct Attack simultaneously!
-Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Did I not say that you are not fit to be my opponent?
I hate to rain on your parade, but I haven't kicked the bucket yet here!
Jounouchi-kun!
Unmöglich! He should not have any Life remaining...!
When you launched the first attack, I went and activated this card.
The Magic Card, Hyper Fresh!
When I don't have any Monsters on the field,
and when the total Attack Power of the opponent's Monsters
exceed my Life Points, it can be activated!
It will double my Life Points!
Whac'cha think?
I'm pretty damn tough, ain't I?
Your resistance is futile.
I set a reverse card and end this turn.
The Valkyries that were Special Summoned due to Ride of The Valkyries...
...are returned to the deck at the end of the turn.
Take a short rest, my Valkyries.
You're still acting cool?
You have no Wall Monsters on the field.
I'll finish you off in my next turn!
Cut off any data inflow.
Protocol shutdown.
Clear memory.
Access standby.
Download complete.
I won't let you have your way!
It's back to normal.
Good, it's my turn!
It stopped!
The system is back to normal!
Seems like it got repaired.
Huh? It stopped...
It's finally peaceful.
This is indeed weird... I'll go to where my brother is!
It's perfectly reasonable for Kaiba to solve such a small issue.
But can he find me?
To be able to infiltrate
Kaiba Corporation's main computer's
superb intelligence and technology...
This bothers me.
Isono, conduct a thorough investigation on Sieg Lloyd's background.
Especially if he is related in any way to the German's Schroeder family.
Did you say the Schroeder family...?
In the past, Gozaburo organized an event
to build strong relationships with European businessmen...
And there was a boy I met at one of those boring parties.
If it really is that man, he'd be capable of doing such a thing.
Okay! Do it now, Jounouchi!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Swordsman of Landstar in Attack Position.
Go on, Swordsman of Landstar! Direct Attack!
Then I shall activate this Trap Card.
Fricka's Mediation.
By removing Wotan's Judgment in my Cemetery from the game,
this card will nullify the opponent's attack during this turn.
I will not allow you to touch me any further.
I set a reverse card and end my turn.
It is my turn.
Even the Goddess of Fate loves me.
Huh?
I activate a Magic Card from my hand known as Nibelung's Treasure.
The card's effect allows me to take the Nibelung's Ring card from my deck
and I place it on the field, equipping it to my opponent's Monster.
And I can draw five cards.
What's up with this ring?!
Then I activate a Magic Card from my hand.
The three goddesses that control destiny...
Weaving threads of destiny that bind the past, present and future...
Descend, the three sisters of Noran!
Continuous Magic!
Goddess Urd's Verdict.
Goddess Verdandi's Guidance.
Goddess Skuld's Oracle.
Three goddesses?!
The one who controls the future, Goddess Skuld, please tell me my future!
Her effect is that during every turn,
I can look at the top three cards in my opponent's deck and change their order.
You can do what?
What would he achieve by looking at his opponent's deck?
Oh, then I shall change the order of these cards.
Place the second card on the top.
What is he trying to do?
Next, the one who controls the present, Goddess Verdandi.
Her effect allows me to
guess the card type of the top card of the opponent's deck once per turn.
If I guess correctly, the card must be set on your field.
What?
The top card in your deck is a Monster Card!
Well... You saw it, so of course you know...!
The Monster will then have to be Summoned in Reverse Defense Position.
Fine...!
And the one who controls the past, Urd, will show me the ignorant one.
Her effect is that at each turn,
I can guess the opponent's reverse card.
If I'm correct, the card will be removed from the game.
What?!
No way!
It's obvious he'll guess it right!
Is that even legal?!
That reverse card is...
...Panther Warrior!
Start your journey toward Valhalla!
My Panther Warrior...
First Psycho Shocker, now even Panther Warrior...!
They're all strong Monsters!
This is bad.
I will complete my turn.
What is wrong?
Perhaps you have come to know your own ignorance before these Goddesses?
Damn it, using all these boring tactics...
My turn, draw!
At this moment, the effects of Nibelung's Ring is activated.
What?
The Monster equipped with this card will not be under the player's control.
But during the Draw Phase, the player can draw two cards.
Then isn't this to my benefit?
What are you thinking of?!
Do you really think so?
This is no time to feel confused!
Draw!
You have now been cursed by the Gods!
There will be no escape for you!
What?!
The effects of Nibelung's Ring...
If there are any Monster Cards in the cards you've just drawn, you must discard one away.
Say wha?!
Goddess Skuld has already seen the future.
One of the cards is a Monster Card, Knight of Black Dragons.
Na, discard that into the Cemetery.
If this goes on, Jounouchi-kun wouldn't be able to use any Monster Cards.
This guy's combo of the three goddesses removes cards from the opponent's deck...
And makes them unrevivable.
Then Nibelung's Ring sends Monsters into the Graveyard.
This is a "Card Extermination" Deck.
Even if I draw Monster Cards, they'll be removed before they reach my hand.
To top it off, he's seen my hand.
Unless I draw a card that he doesn't know, I'll surely lose.
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card!
Continuous Magic, Dangerous Machine Type-6.
Its slots will turn during the Standby Phase.
Special effects will be activated depending on the number that appears.
I have very good luck!
Isn't it said that, "Luck is also a strength?"
That's only something you'd say.
So you are claiming that good luck will be enough to defeat me?
I, someone who is loved by the Goddesses of Fate?
We'll know that in the next turn! Turn end.
It is my turn. I draw.
I activate the effects of the Three Sister Goddesses.
Make the second card the first.
The top card is a Monster Card, Goblin Attack Force.
The Monsters are...
Jounouchi-kun...
I'll set one reverse card face-down and end this turn.
My turn. Draw!
There's a Monster Card, right?
Well then, discard that away.
But now, the effects of the Continuous Magic, Dangerous Machine Type-6, is activated!
Sweet!
Three allows me to draw another card!
And the card I've just drawn is also a Monster Card.
I Summon Single-Strike Samurai in Attack Position!
It's useless no matter what you do.
At this moment, I activate a Permanent Trap Card, Loge's Flame.
What?
As long as this card is on the field, Monsters with 2000 or less Attack Points cannot attack.
But I'll also open my reverse card!
Angel Dice!
The Attack Power of Monsters with Attack Points of 500 or less...
...will get multiplied by the number that appears on the die.
Let's see which one us has the strongest luck!
He'll win if he gets a five or six.
Please...
My god!
It seems like the Goddess of Fate loves me and me alone.
How can this be?! I had no chance to fight back...
Yahoo! Look, Darling! I won!
Dammit!
I even lost in luck...
At least this Trap Card is a card he didn't see.
I set one reverse card and end my turn.
It is my turn. I draw.
I activate the Goddess Combo.
Put the second card on top.
Another Monster's soul is now headed for Valhalla.
I also activate a Magic Card, Swan Maiden.
This card allows me to Special Summon one Valkyrie onto the field.
Valkyrie Erste, on the attack!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
You are finished this time.
I won't let you have your way!
Activate the Trap, One Silver Dollar Coin!
This card can negate attack damage directed at Monsters with 1000 or less Attack Points!
How's that? I won't get defeated so easily!
Dreams are only short-lived.
Oh well.
I set one card face-down, and end my turn.
My turn, draw!
I knew it. One of them is a Monster Card.
But I can activate the effects of Dangerous Machine Type-6!
Landed another three!
I draw one card!
Good! I haven't run out of luck just yet!
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card, Roll of Fate!
I can draw the same number of cards as the number rolled on the die.
And discard an equal number of cards into the Graveyard.
Sweet! It's a six!
This is it!
Magic Card, Hurricane!
All Magic and Trap Cards on the field are returned to their owner's hands!
My Trap activates.
Apple of Enlightenment!
What?
All Traps should have been returned to your hand!
Apple of Enlightenment is a card that is activated when it is removed from the field.
Because of its effect, I can draw one card from my deck.
And the Special Effect of Loge's Flame is also activated when it is removed from the field.
Become one with the fire!
Valkyrie Brunnhilde!
Valkyrie Brunnhilde is a Warrior Type.
She gains 300 Attack Points for every Dragon-Type Monster on the field.
Oh no you don't!
I sacrifice Swordsman of Landstar to Summon Maximum Six in Attack Mode!
When this card is successfully Tribute Summoned, I get to roll a die!
He gains Attack Points equal to the result of the die roll x 200!
Because I got a six, its Attack Power is increased by 1200 points!
Next, from my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Star Blaster.
I can roll this die once by sacrificing one Monster.
I can then increase the level of the selected Monster by the die result.
Single-Strike Samurai's level is two, and the die result is five.
Meaning I get to call a Level Seven Monster!
Come out, Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Awesome move, Jounouchi!
What a great die-rolling attack!
Maximum Six, attack Brunnhilde!
What?! Why wasn't she destroyed?!
Because of Brunnhilde's Special Effect.
When she takes on an attack from a Monster,
her Defense Power will drop by 1000 points to prevent destruction.
Red-Eyes!
I reset the Dangerous Machine Type-6 from my hand!
Then, I set one reverse card face-down and end my turn.
So what now?! Looks like your good luck is about to burn out!
Looking good, Jounouchi!
You did it!
Yes!
Up until now, there has not been a single person who could make me play seriously.
I will no longer hold back.
My turn! I draw!
I activate the Equipment Magic, Enchanted Sword Nothung!
I equip it to Brunnhilde to increase her Attack Strength by 400 points!
Nothung is no ordinary sword.
This is a sword holding polymerization compatibilities.
What?!
Recht.
It will destroy all Dragon-Type Monsters on my opponent's side of the field...
...and exclude them from this game!
Red-Eyes!
I then activate a Magic Card known as Rainbow Bridge Bifrost!
For each of the opponent's Monsters that have been sent out of the game,
it adds 500 Attack Points to a Valkyrie!
I get it!
He has been removing Jounouchi's Monsters out of play
...to increase his Valkyrie's Attack Points with this strategy.
I won't let you do that!
Reverse card, open!
Compensation Mediation!
So you still plan to rebel against fate?
Shut up!
I can place this card together with two of your cards and shuffle them.
Then I will pick one them.
If I pick this card, the battle will come to an end!
I won't lose to you at such a critical moment!
Vorher, take your pick.
This will be a bet on your destiny.
Jounouchi-kun...
The card I pick is...
That one!
Your fate is sealed.
Go, Brunnhilde! Together with the souls of the warriors!
No way!
Jounouchi-kun... lost.
I believe I already told you earlier... that the Goddesses of Fate favors me.
The winner is Sieg Lloyd!
We now have our finalists for the Best Four!
That darn Jounouchi was so close, too.
Jounouchi-kun...
Hey, you! How could you guess wrong in the final moment?!
That isn't like you at all, Jounouchi-kun.
Maybe you didn't win because you're not Dueling with your life on the line?
I see, like how you get a sudden burst of energy during a fire?
Damn it, guys! Enough is enough!
Can't you comfort me at least a little?!
Stop laughing! Why are you running away?
You really were close, Jounouchi-kun... it was a great Duel.
Yes. That man will be a tough opponent to deal with.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Jounouchi lost.
Does it just mean that his luck doesn't favor him at critical moments?
Hey, don't sulk forever. Let's go cheer for Rebecca!
Let's see Rebecca off to the Semi-Finals!
Eh? Yugi's grandpa went missing?!
He should have difficulty moving since he sprained his waist.
Where can he be?
Next time!
"Rebecca VS Leon
Genius Girl VS Genius Boy"
Duel standby!