The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
No matter what card you use, it's all futile before my Insect Army!
Go, Basic Insect with Laser Cannon...
Attack!
Haga! You said "attack" just now, did you not?
What?
It will activate this Trap Card
when my opponent says 'attack'.
Holy Barrier – Mirror Force!
Retreat!
My Insect Army...!
Alright, Yugi!
Yugi!
Let me say this clearly, Haga...
...you are too weak!
The Ultimate Force:
Great Moth"
Awesome!
What now, bug asshole?!
You're not going to beat Yugi!
Go Yugi, beat him!
I wonder.
Yugi-chan has only taken a slight lead in this match.
Duel Monsters is the type of game where you don't know what will happen in one turn.
It's too early to get excited.
This woman's so arrogant!
She even said Yugi-chan, didn't she?!
What the hell?
Yugi has the higher lead!
But, Insector Haga is Japan's Regional Champion.
This match just started.
I agree with Mai-chan on that lead thing, Anzu.
I was thinking that as well.
Whose side are you guys on?!
To put it simply, Yugi will win.
So, he can't let his guard down.
I think so too.
I will Duel against this woman sooner or later!
Yugi, show me if your strength is fake or not.
Yugi, you'll regret making me get serious!
Put your complaints in all of your cards. I'll wipe the floor with them!
It doesn't matter! I have the perfect Insect Card waiting anyway.
Once I use it, it'll be my win.
Yugi, your life as a Duelist will be over soon!
This card doesn't stand a chance against Yugi's Set Card!
Attack the card, Yugi.
I'm not going to fall for that.
I know he has a set Trap Card waiting...
So I'll set this secret card face-down on the field.
Once I declare an attack, all of my Monsters will be destroyed.
Including the two Monsters in Defense Position and Black Magician.
Then, my Life Points will decrease.
To stop that risk, I need to use this card to stop his Trap Card.
Then I'll use this card!
The Monster Recovery card!
All of my Monsters on the field return to my Deck!
Return to your cards, Monsters!
He saw through it?
I return all cards on the field and in my hand to the Deck,
shuffle...
then add 5 new cards to my hand.
Now I'll use the Monster with the lowest Attack Power.
Attack!
Now, your Trap Card disappears.
And now my turn's over.
That went exactly as I planned!
What?
Let me show the card I played!
Larvae Moth.
Both it's Attack Power and Defense Power are very low.
Haga, is this a Combo?
And this is my trump card!
Cocoon of Evolution!
What?
Fuse together with Larvae Moth!
What's that?
The Moth's wrapped inside the cocoon.
Insector Haga is finally showing us his true power.
For five turns, Larvae Moth will be evolving...
...and become the Perfectly Ultimate Great Moth, the Ultimate Form!
And then Great Moth will be unbeatable!
Perfectly Ultimate Great Moth, the Ultimate Form?
His Defense Points go up due to the Forest Field Source!
No Monster can penetrate through its current defenses!
The current Attack Points of your card can't even scratch it!
Yugi, just 5 turns! In 5 turns my Perfectly Ultimate Great Moth will beat you!
Dammit, after it's fully evolved, I will have no way of winning.
I have to kill the cocoon.
Dark Knight Gaia!
Attack the cocoon!
Spiral Shaver!!
Gaia's attack was reflected!
Useless! Useless! Useless!
No use... I don't have enough Attack Power against the Field Power Source.
If I keep going on, my Life Points will drop to zero.
- Yugi!
- Why is that cocoon overcoming you?!
What's so funny?
You guys don't know anything.
Yugi-chan is dealing with a tough opponent.
You called him "Yugi-chan" again!
Hey, what do you mean?
It's so sad that nobody's ever successfully defeated the "Insect Combo".
What did you say?
Do you mean that, Yugi will lose?
What're you going to do? Yugi...
Give it up, none of your cards can scratch it!
Even if I use a combo...
...none of my cards are able to defeat the cocoon's Defense Points.
What can I do?
Until the Monster inside the cocoon is fully evolved into its Ultimate Form...
...I can't play any other cards.
So, I'll play my turns quietly, while inside,
the Monster continues to evolve.
I'll use this card to defend for now.
You're hiding like a coward again.
Don't you wanna fight with me?
This isn't good.
It's gonna evolve again before I can do anything.
Only two turns left until the end of the evolution of Great Moth.
I win this Duel.
Yugi, you can't lose!
I won't let you lose here.
What should I do?
I don't wanna see your losing-face!
Yugi! Get fired up!
Get fired up!
Fired up? That's it!
As a Duelist, when a game starts,
you can only believe in yourself.
It's useless being supported by someone.
No, it does work! Because our hearts reach Yugi!
And Yugi will definitely win.
You people are way too innocent.
Alright.
Yugi!
See?! Our friendship won't lose to your womanly pheromones!
Did he find a way to win?
Alright, Here I go!
Curse of Dragon!
Combo Attack!
Go!
Hell Flame!!
I thought I told you that was useless?!
Damage of that level won't even scratch my cocoon!
What's so funny?
Who said I was trying to attack the cocoon?
Look again, I was attacking the forest!
Impossible! the Forest Field is burning up!
Then the cocoon loses it's power from the Forest Field.
Its Defense is decreased dramatically.
Dark Knight Gaia!
Spiral Shaver!!
Destroy the Cocoon of Evolution!
Alright!
Kill that Cocoon of Evolution!
What's that sound?
It can't be...!
The Monster inside the cocoon...
Just like the rumors stated...
It's here!
This is my Great Moth's fourth stage of evolution!
So this is the Great Moth...
Even though it didn't reach it's Ultimate Form, this is still enough to beat you!
Yugi!
This is my first time seeing
Insector Haga's true trump card.
The Great Moth...!
Now with that, Haga has the game's advantage.
Yugi's been pushed into a corner...
Though I did stop it from evolving to its Ultimate Form...
Now then...
What happened to that confidence you had a moment ago, Yugi?!
Are you speechless in front of my Great Moth?
I was just imagining it falling before me.
I'm trying to think of a way to beat that over-sized bug.
If you think you can, go on and try!
Let's go!
Battle!
My turn! Great Moth, rise!
Haga, I thought you would attack in the sky!
All of Yugi's Monsters on the field right now...
...except Curse of Dragon...
cannot attack Great Moth from the air!
Also, their Attack Power isn't enough to beat the Great Moth.
Next turn, I need to destroy Dragon Knight Gaia first!
This is bad!
Gaia is my key to attack!
I will lose once he's killed!
Just give it up, Yugi!
Your Gaia is a little shrimp in front of my Great Moth's massive form!
Then I'll bet on this card!
No matter what card it is, it's useless!
Moth Hurricane!!
Ruiz just...!
At last! The huge wings spun a strong gust of wind...
...which will destroy all of the Monsters on the ground!
Dark Knight Gaia is beaten!
You sure about that?
Haga, you don't seem to realize this card's effect.
What?
That is..!
Dragon Knight Gaia!
The Fusion Card fuses these two monsters together.
Gaia and Curse of Dragon fused together!?
Now fused, they've become more powerful!
Their Attack Power is now the same as your Great Moth.
Now we can anticipate a battle in the air!
It's Attack Power increased, you say?!
I wonder about that!
What?
The Dragon Knight's body...!
Why's this happening?
That's it!
It's poisonous particles!
You finally found this out?
That's right, Great Moth's "Moth Hurricane"!
When it used it to blow away the Monsters on the ground,
It spread the poisonous particles to all its enemy Monsters!
If you don't hurry up,
the Dragon Knight's Attack Power will just keep decreasing!
This is bad...
If his Attack Points continue to drop...
and he is attacked by the Great Moth, my Life Points will drop to 0!
So, I have to use this card!
The Magical Mist card, "Makiu"!
What?
It's being drenched in mist...!
That right, the Makiu card  envelopes the enemy's Monsters in a magical mist!
I see...! So you plan to wash the poisonous particles off...!
So the Dragon Knight's Attack Power won't drop anymore.
Yugi, if this is the best you can do, I have no need to worry!
Right now, Great Moth has more than enough Attack Points to wipe out Dragon Knight Gaia!
Go, With the Great Moth's ultimate attack!
Moth Burning Death Tornado!!
Dragon Knight Gaia is beaten!
I'm looking forward to you losing all of your Life Points!
Yugi!
Yugi, don't give up, you'll find a way.
We know who the winner of this game is now.
That's not true! Yugi will win!
I haven't lost hope!
It's no use. What can he do now to turn the tables?
Friendship has no effect on the outcome of a Duel.
What the...
What the hell do you think you know about our friendship with Yugi?!
Say something, Jounouchi!
Yugi... Yugi will be fine.
The key to winning this...
There must be one!
There is!
But someone like me who only came in Eight Place in the District Finals wouldn't know!
Jounouchi~!
Yugi-chan had no hope going up against the Regional Champion of Japan.
He shouldn't feel bad losing this Duel, since his opponent was too strong.
No, Mai-chan.
Ma-Mai-chan?
Your prediction turned out to be wrong.
Look at Yugi!
He's laughing!
Yugi is...laughing...!
Why?
What are you laughing for?
What's so funny?!
Haga, if you're a Duelist...
...when do you feel the need to laugh?
The Duel is running smoothly...
...and I believe that victory is mine.
It would be the only moment that I feel right.
Right?
What are you saying?!
Haga, you fell into my trap.
Dragon Knight Gaia was merely the bait!
The Dragon Knight was the bait?!
My turn!
I'll use this card to attack the Great Moth!
Demon Summon!
Impossible!
What's this? So it's just a bluff...!
The Attack Power of the Demon Summon
is not any better than my Great Moth.
Once Yugi's Life Points reach 0 after this next attack...
...I will be the winner!
Now it looks like you're just committing suicide with that card!
Haga, don't you understand what's going on?
Why did I use the Makiu card?
S-
Shit!
The Makiu card made the Great Moth soaked!
Now you get it?
That's right, The Makiu card set the stage for Demon's most suitable attack!
Therefore, the Great Moth's Defense drops due to the Makiu card!
And the Demon's Attack Points go up!
Go, Demon!
Demon Lightning!!
The Great Moth is beaten!
My... my Great Moth...!
Awesome!
He did it! Yugi won!
Is that... how Yugi beat the Kaiba in his Duel...?
This isn't possible~!
I can't believe the Regional Champion of Japan was the first to lose in this tournament.
It's the rules!
I will take your two Star Chips!
Now-
Now get the hell off this island!
You insect-bastard!
I will look after this glove for you.
Retire!
Now I have 3 Star Chips.
I need 7 more to get into Pegasus' Castle.
Wait for me, Pegasus!
Jounouchi, who's in this tournament for the
money to help heal his sister's eyes...
...His first opponent is Mai Kujaku.
She has the ability to guess her own cards.
With Mai Kujaku's "Aroma Tactics" and her Harpie Lady Combo Attack...
Jounouchi is pushed into a corner!
Don't give up!
The key to winning is...
"Something you can see, but cannot see".
Next Time - The Beautiful Harpie Lady
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship