Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
The Memory has been
sealed away somehow!
Even the God Cards
have been stolen!
And... a new enemy has
appeared before us.
The Musketeers of Doma!
Using a Power of Darkness
different from the Millennium Items,
these people calling themselves
"musketeers" challenge me to a Duel.
"Orichalcos"...
Is that power strong enough
to control Obelisk?!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Barrier of Orichalcos"
A barrier that imprisons even the gods?
Even be thou hast Magnet Valkyrian,
ye shall be unable
to beat a God Card!
Dark Obelisk, attack!
Be gone! Magnet Valkyrian!
God Hand Crusher!!
Yugi!
Isn't there a way
to beat the powered-up Obelisk?!
Now your key card is gone.
I'll end my turn.
Is this guy bent on using a God Card,
knowing full well the risks entailed?
Even if we have the power
of the Barrier of Orichalcos,
it's impossible to completely
control the gods, huh?
Perhaps he isn't cut out
to be a musketeer.
He's the best opponent to test the Nameless Pharaoh's power.
I have nothing to fight against
a god with what I have now...!
My turn!
I'll activate a Magic Card!
Angel's Charity!
With the effect of this card,
I can draw three more cards
and discard two cards
to the Graveyard!
And the next...
I'll Summon a Monster in Defense Mode.
Then, set one card.
My turn is complete.
It's my turn!
I set one card on the field.
Dark Obelisk, attack!
God Hand Crusher!!
Shit!
Yugi just lost another Monster...!
It shall happen very soon...
It shall happen very soon, Sir Yugi!
Thou shalt his soul
be offered up to our god!
Offered?
Indeed.
The soul of the loser shall be offered up to God as a sacrifice!
Says he, this world shall be guided down the path of destruction!
Be it food to a new, pure world!
What is that guy saying?
I know we've heard something like that before...
The omen has begun~
Soon this world's gonna be destroyed~
Don't tell me! Did you do anything
to Haga and Ryuzaki?!
Exactly that!
You guys!
So you were up there?!
Wait right there!
Are you okay, Jounouchi?!
Honda! You tryin' to kill me?!
Their souls are
in our hands at the moment.
They are the offerings
for the Ancient God's revival.
Haga... Ryuzaki...
You sealed their souls in cards...?
Do they hold the same
Power of Darkness Pegasus had?
I thought I was gonna die...
Go on. Be it thine turn, Sir Yugi.
If thy does not
play a Monster Card this turn.
thine soul shall
forever perish from this world!
My turn!
Before you worry about my end...
...you'd better worry about yourself.
What did you just say?
I activate the Magic Card,
Resurrection of the Dead!
The Monster I'll revive is...
Magnet Valkyrian!
It's hopeless, hopeless!
Magnet Valkyrian does not hold enough
Attack Power to defeat Dark Obelisk!
It's true that Dark Obelisk
has absolute power.
But if you hold a strength
that surpasses that power...
Power superior to Dark Obelisk?
Right.
The united power of courage!
I'll show you right now!
I deactivate the combination
of Magnet Valkyrian!
Next I activate
a Magic Card from my hand!
Brave Attack!
Go!
Magnet Warriors!
I can't believe it!
What an utterly foolish move.
Art thou maniacle?
Let's find out, shall we?
Look carefully at Dark Obelisk's body!
Madness!
The Magnet Warriors' Attack Points
should be inferior to Dark Obelisk's!
I activated Brave Attack, which throws aside all fear and doubt,
combining the strength of my Monsters...
...in order to fight against
the opposing Monster.
What?
So...
Alpha's Attack Power is 1400.
And Beta has 1700 Attack Points.
Obelisk has 3100 points of damage!
And Dark Obelisk's Attack Power is 4500.
When it takes, lastly, Magnet Warrior Gamma's
1500 Attack Points,
what do you think will happen?
Go, Magnet Warrior Gamma!
Yeah!
Awesome!
He defeated Dark Obelisk!
What a guy.
As expected of him.
I think he's learned
how to defeat the God Cards.
That's for sure.
It's my turn!
True it be that Obelisk has disappeared.
However, the Barrier of Orichalcos's power
has only just shown itself!
Magic Card!
Treasure From Heaven!
Now both sides
have six cards in their hand.
Their Life Points are equal.
But every Monster he plays
instantly gets powered up!
And it's not like
Yugi's disadvantage has changed...
How lucky.
When this guy is added to my hand
by way other than a regular draw,
at the moment I get the card
I can Summon the Monster to the field.
What can you do with a weakling like that?
I'll Summon Warrior Dai Grepher.
Reverse card, open!
Reviving Coffin of Black Magic!
When the opponent Summons a Monster, this card is able to revive a Magician-Type Monster in the Graveyard
after sacrificing Monsters
from both sides.
And the one I'm going to bring back...
...is the Black Magician!
When you used Angel's Charity
you put Black Magician
in the Graveyard?!
Alright.
Now you have no Monsters.
On my next turn, I'll give you a fatal blow
with my Black Magician!
I'll set a card and end my turn.
Alright!
Now I'm sure Yugi will win!
My turn!
Go!
Black Magician!
Direct Attack him!
Quickplay Magic, Shield Wall!
What?!
You think too little.
Shield Wall is able to Summon four
1000 Defense Point Wall Monsters.
Thee attack won't even touch me!
Sir Yugi...
The real power of the Orichalcos Barrier
has just been used!
Magic card, Bronze Knights, activate!
This card Summons Bronze Knight Tokens
for each card I discard from my hand!
Impossible.
There are six Monsters!
H-H-Hey! Hold on a second!
That's impossible!
In Duel Monsters, you can only
Summon up to five at a time!
It's possible!
Within The Barrier of Orichalcos, that is!
This barrier extends the Monster Spaces
into your Magic and Trap Zones!
So...
That means he can Summon
up to ten Monsters on the field?!
Right.
And if the fore-running Monsters
are not destroyed,
you can't attack the Monsters
in the back!
What?
Use the power of Orichalcos
and power up!
My Bronze Knights!!
Six Monsters...!
Against this many enemies, even with
the Black Magician on my side, it's too much...
Plus, even if I were to use all my Attack Position Monsters to attack him at once,
he would still be guarded by the back line of Defense Monsters...!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...
This card has abilities
like none I've ever seen...!
Seems like this'll be a tough fight.
I set two cards face-down!
I'll then Summon Queen's Knight
in Defense Position!
My turn is over!
It's my turn.
Trap Card, activate!
What?!
Dust Tornado!
This card is able to destroy one of
the opponent's Magic or Trap Cards!
I destroy the Orichalcos Barrier!
Yeah!
If you can just get rid of that barrier...!
What?!
The Seal didn't disappear!
Futile effort.
The Barrier of Orichalcos is protected by
the great Power of the Orichalcos.
You won't be able to destroy it like that.
What a pity.
I'll use the Magic Card, The Warrior Returning Alive.
I'll return Dai Grepher from
the Graveyard to my hand.
Then, Summon it to the field.
Absorb the power of the Orichalcos!
Dai Grepher!!
I'll activate the Continuous Magic,
The Allied Forces!
This card is able to enhance the Attack Power
of every Warrior
by 200 points for every Warrior
and Spellcaster face-up on the field!
There are four Warriors on the field.
Thus, my Monsters
will gain 800 points!
Be gone! Black Magician!
Dai Grepher, attack!
My attack isn't over!
Now your other Monster
will be killed as well!
Sacrifice Escape!
What?
Quickplay Magic, Magical Academy!
Black Magician Girl!
After the player
discards 2 cards from their hand,
this card will Summon a Monster of your choice,
while adding two levels and
500 Attack Points to that Monster.
To think you'd offer your Monsters
to add Attack Points to another...!
And depending on the number
of Black Magicians resting in the Graveyard,
she can gain 300 Attack Points!
It's my turn!
He has seven Monsters
on his side of the field...
There's no other way
to overturn the situation...
...than to draw that card.
If I don't draw it...
But I believe in my deck!
Draw!
YES!
Magic Card!
Diffusion Wave-Motion, activate!!
What?!
He drew Diffusion Wave-Motion
in such timing?
Go, Black Magician Girl!!
Black Burning Burst!!
By paying 1000 of my Life Points,
Diffusion Wave-Motion allows me to
attack every Monster on the field!
Impossible!
Yugi!
What a close call.
Master... Ra...fa...el!
Th-The God Card...!!
Gurimo...
If he had just one more turn,
Gurimo would have won.
It's not that interesting any more...
Okay, let's retreat.
Wait!
Give the God cards back to me!
You have to defeat
all three of us first.
Someday I'll come back
to claim your soul.
Ah yes, I'll leave these weaklings to you.
This is...
Until we meet again.
Nameless Pharaoh.
Hey! Wait a sec!
You wanna run away, cowards?!
Come down and fight us!
No rush, Katsuya Jounouchi.
We'll fight you guys soon enough.
My name is Varon.
Remember it.
Wait! Stop right there!
Damn.
Is he dead?
No...
But his soul is gone.
This is...
His soul is sealed in the Barrier's card.
Huh?
Yugi.
Look at this.
So beautiful.
This feeling resembles that of the Power of Darkness and the Millennium Items.
What are you doing all of a sudden?!
Yeah! I'm gettin' the creeps here!
That's our line.
How can you run away
after seeing us?
Let them go.
Jounouchi-kun, Honda-kun.
I wanna ask you
what happened.
I don't remember a word of what
you're talkin' about here!
For real!
Are ye Sir Dinosaur Ryuzaki and Sir Insector Haga?
W-What the hell...?
Do ya want somethin' wit' us?
Words are pointless!
DUEL!
So we fought 'im after he
challenged us to a Duel,
and got our butts handed to us!
Ow!
We had a tough fight.
But he used a wicked card,
some kinda barrier.
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Yeah, that!
What?
You one a' them?
How's that possible?!
Yugi got your souls back
from him!
Eh?
That aside,
what did you mean when you mentioned the omens of the end of the world?
Did we say that?
I don't remember at all.
I see.
Let's not talk about this.
Hey, Yugi-kun, you have the
God cards, don't you?
Won't you let me see them?
Oh yeah, yeah!
About that...
They stole them...
Say what?!
Are you serious?!
Y-Yeah...
We're gonna take em back from
those jerks no matter what!
If you remember anything,
be sure to let us know.
We're counting on you guys!
We'll be sure to!
Yeah right.
We gotta be the ones to find em first!
-And get the God cards!
Speaking of which...
Have you guys heard the recent reports
on TV or in papers...
"The children's character is gone, like a body without a soul".
Yeah.
But this seems to be happening
all over the world.
Perhaps there are people
killing the Duelists around the world?
Duelists that steal people's souls...?
Hi, darling!
I wanted to see you, darling!
Wh-Who are you?!
Come on, darling!
Did you forget about
our sweet promise?
Eh?
Wait! A sweet promise?!
Come on~!
This is the card I got
from my darling! It's me!
Card?
This card...
Rebeca, take this.
The Bonds of Friendship?
I hope you'll accept it.
Yugi!
You're...!
Rebeca!?
Hi!
Huh? You got a
whole different look now.
What happened to
that bear, "Teddy-chan"?
Hmph! I outgrew stuff like that!
Because I have a real boyfriend now~!
And just who is your boyfriend?
Americans sure are growing fast, Honda.
That's not the problem.
You came to Japan
just to meet Yugi?
Yup!
It's actually my grandfather
who wants to talk to him!
Professor Hopkins does?
Professor Hopkins!
Yugi-kun!
I have something important to tell you.
Yugi-kun...
No... Nameless Pharaoh.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
"Preview"
Rebeca's abrupt visit to see Yugi...
Come on!
She called Yugi "darling".
That's really surprising!
And Professor Hopkins
is waiting for Yugi at the Museum.
along with the truth of the incident.
And the ruins under the ocean...
What is the connection?
And it's related somehow to the other
Yugi and his lost memories?!
Ah! I'm totally confused!
Next time!
"The Nameless Dragon, Timaeus"
Duel standby!