Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
After losing the fight with Rafael, Yugi's soul has been taken from the other Yugi.
I don't know exactly how you feel, but now's not the time to be feeling sorry for yourself!
Let's go find the secrets of Doma and get back our lost souls!
But Haga and Ryuzaki going missing like that's bothering me...
You don't think...
...they joined forces with Doma?
"The Runaway Train Duel"
Well then, we're off now.
Take care of Professor Hopkins and Rebecca.
Right! Just leave it to me!
As soon as the professor recovers, we'll catch up to you.
We're really counting on you.
We can't do a thing without the professor, you know.
I'm going too!
I have to save Darling!
Calm down, Rebecca.
Come on...!
Knock it off!
Yugi-kun is the one suffering the most here.
You're an idiot, Grandpa!
Yugi...
Time to go!
See ya!
Be careful!
Of course.
Yugi...
Hey Yugi, take a look!
Isn't it beautiful?!
I wonder what we'll see in Florida!
Ahhh~! I should've brought a swimsuit with me!
Oh, are you hungry?!
Why don't we go find the dining cart?!
Yugi...
Cheer up already, Yugi!
I know you're feeling down,
but you can't just keep feeling sorry for yourself!
We'll all think of a way to get the other Yugi back!
Okay?
I'm sorry...
Yugi...
There's no use talking to him right now, Anzu.
The only one on his mind right now is usual Yugi, you know.
Just let him be.
I, the great Katsuya Jounouchi,
will save the other Yugi no matter what it takes!
Jounouchi...!
Back then, I couldn't stop myself from being consumed by the darkness...
And I lost myself...
It's about time we settled this, Rafael.
I use Black Magician Girl as a sacrifice!
Eat this!
And as a result...
Don't stare at me...!
Don't stare at me with those eyes!
O Nameless Pharaoh!
Bear the wrath of these Monsters!
Guardian Eatos attacks!!
Gospel of Truth!!
Partner!
I lost something I cherished more than my own life...
Damn it!!
I'm sorry...
Partner...
Yugi hasn't come back yet.
Speaking of which, isn't this a bit strange?
Huh?
Haven't you noticed?
Yugi was the only one who got up and left this entire time...
Just when did everyone in the entire train disappear without a trace?
There's no one up here either!
What about the next train?
There's no one here!
Yugi!
Something's up with this train!
Everyone just disappeared without a trace when we weren't looking.
We haven't even reached the first stop.
There's no way something like this could happen!
Could it be their doing?
Wait up, Yugi!
Yugi!
Anzu!
Honda!
Jounouchi!
Shit!
Yugi!
Let's try and contact another train!
Right!
Shit!
What's going on here?
So this really was Doma's doing!
Yugi...
Anzu...
Who's there?!
Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
What the hell?
It was you?
Don't go scaring us like that!
Jounouchi... I got some business to take care a' with ya...
Business with me?
I came ta' take away that soul a' yours!
Is anyone there?!
Please stop the train right away!
Mr. Driver!
Someone please stop the train!
Is there no driver on this train at all?!
Yugi...
I'm going to check the roof.
Be careful!
You're...!
Insector Haga!
Haga?!
What's he doing here of all places?!
Yugi, Duel with me!
What did you just say?!
Haga, you aren't telling me...!
Let me warn you in advance. I'm no longer the same as I was before.
He's one of Doma's now!
Ryuzaki, are you tryin' to tell me...?!
Why?!
Why did you join up with Doma?!
Of course, it's to beat you, Yugi!
Haga...!
Let's have a match, Yugi!
Just hold on!
Anzu!
It's too dangerous up here!
Haga, do you even know what you're doing?!
I won't let you guys have a Duel like that!
Anzu!
Oh my, she's scary~!
A girl like you is much cuter when she keeps her mouth shut!
What's that mean!?
It's too bad, but you aren't the one I'm after.
It's you, Nameless Pharaoh!
What!?
I heard.
That you have two personalities.
You wanna know?!
Where the other Yugi is!
You know?!
Tell me!
If you wanna know so badly,
you're gonna have to Duel me.
I'll tell you if you can beat me.
Haga!
You bastard...!
Now let's fight, Yugi!
Ready?
Let's fight!
Jounouchi!
So you guys are the one who screwed with the train, huh?
What the hell are you trying to pull here!?
What happened to Yugi and Anzu?!
Yugi?
Yugi's bein' taken care a' by that Haga freak.
What?
That Haga "freak" joined Doma?
Shit!
So it's not just Ryuzaki, but even Haga?
Jounouchi, I got a huge score to settle with ya.
It's time we finished this once and for all!
Don't freaking kid around with me!
Do you two have any clue what joining up with Doma even means?!
They're trying to destroy the world, you know!
Stuff it!
That ain't got a thing to do with me!
I'm cool long as I beat ya!
Now get in position!
You givin' me no choice here?
Let's forget this idiot and go find Yugi and Anzu!
Right!
You ain't gettin' away!
I'm serious here!
My turn!
Draw!
Let's get this party started!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...!
Quit it, Ryuzaki!
If you use that thing, the loser'll get his soul taken!
I activate The Barrier of Orichalcos.
Stop!!
Honda!
Power's...
Power's surgin' through me!
Ryuzaki! You dumbass!
You serious?
This Ryuzaki ass is really able to use that thing!
Now no one's able to get out of that barrier until a winner is decided!
And the loser...
Ya lil' bastard...
I told ya I was serious.
This bastard...
YOU STUPID ASS!
Don't, Yugi!
Stand back, Anzu!
Yugi!
But the way you are now,
you shouldn't be Dueling against anyone...!
I'm gonna go now!
Draw!
I think I'll start things off by playing this card!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...!
Why don'tcha tell me, Yugi?
What's it feel like to play this card?
Does it feel good to have your body and soul completely consumed by the darkness of your heart?
Just jokin' with ya!
Don't give me such a scary look, Yugi!
I'll find out this very moment when I play it myself!
Stop it!
Don't you know what will happen to you if you play that card?!
I'm using it because I know!
Anzu!
Yugi...!
So this...
...is the power of Orichalcos!
So it has begun?
Yes.
Though it's true we don't know how those two will fair,
it'll be good if they can win the Duels and make the Pharaoh's soul ours.
And if they are to lose, we get their souls instead.
Just you wait, Partner!
I'll save you no matter what it takes!
Come forth, Pheromone Wasp!
And because of Orichalcos Barrier's effect,
Pheromone Wasp's Attack goes up by 500 points.
I also set two reverse cards.
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Here I go, Haga!
Haga has two reverse cards on the field...
Don't be reckless, Yugi!
Retrained Elf Swordsman, attack Pheromone Wasp!
I won't let that happen!
Reverse Card open!
I activate the Trap Card Mimesis!
Mimesis...!
Right.
When an Insect-Type Monster on the field is attacked,
I can replace it with any other Level Four Monster from my hand!
By Mimesis's effect,
I return Pheromone Wasp to my hand,
and Special Summon Parasite Caterpillar!
What?!
It switched with Parasite Caterpillar!?
You fell for it, Yugi!
Parasite Caterpillar, I mean!
Infect the opposing Monster!
This allots for a great, great amount of torment!
Jounouchi, now your life's on the line!
If you're a Duelist, fight me head on!
Ryuzaki...
I get it.
I won't say anything else!
I'll take this Duel!
Jounouchi!
In exchange, I'll be coming at you full force!
Got it?!
Damn right ya are!
You'd be a retard ta' be holdin' back!
This...
Isn't a Duel to beat Ryuzaki.
It's a Duel to save Ryuzaki!
Here I go!
I Special Summon Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus!
What?!
Special Summoned?!
Yup!
Ya see, this guy's a Monster that gets treated as a Special Summon when ya Summon 'im.
So I Special Summon another Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus!
Another Special Summon?!
Jounouchi!
And once more!
I Summon Chitoptera!
What!?
He Summoned three Monsters in just one turn!
Also, their Attack goes up 500 points cuz a the Orichalcos Seal's effect!
To have a Monster with a Special Effect that lets you Summon three from your hand...
You're one freakin' lucky bastard!
Dumbass!
Ain't you the one that's always dependin' on luck in your Duels?!
Gah! What was that?!
Hmm, good point.
Honda, you ass!
Whose side are you on?!
Mah bad, dude!
Not yet!
I'll place one final reverse card,
and end my turn.
My turn!
Draw!
He Summoned three Monsters with 1900 Attack Points right off the bat...?
Shit...!
I Summon Jet Black Soldier - Panther Warrior!
He can't attack unless I sacrifice a Monster first,
but his Attack Points far exceed theirs.
Even if I can't attack, he's in the same boat.
Scapegoat?
All right!
I'll also play a Set Card!
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
I'll Summon this guy again.
Pheromone Wasp!
I just have one on my field, Retrained Elf Swordsman.
But because he was poisoned by Poison Caterpillar, he can neither attack nor defend against the enemy.
Take this!
Direct Attack!
Yugi!
When Pheromone Wasp successfully directly attacks the enemy,
at the end of the Battle Phase,
I can Special Summon a Level Four or lower Insect-Type Monster from my Deck!
Due to Pheromone Wasp's Special Effect,
I Special Summon Leghul!
And furthermore, the Continuous Magic Card, Insecticide Barrier!
Activate!
Once I activate this, all Insect-Type Monsters are unable to attack!
But Yugi doesn't have any Insect-Type Monsters on the field...
Any Monster you hold that is infected...
...will evolve into its true form, Poison Butterfly, on the third turn of its being infected!
What?!
And at the end of each of your turns,
you lose 500 of your Life Points!
But Poison Butterfly has 2700 Attack Points!
If you were to attack me with that,
I wouldn't stand a chance!
You could almost say I'm giving you a hand!
Turn end!
Insector Haga...
There's no doubt he's much stronger than before...
So this is the power of the Orichalcos...?
But...
Wait for me, Partner!
I'm going to save you no matter what!
My turn!
Draw!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Atop the runaway train, Yugi faces off against Insector Haga.
And back where we left them, Jounouchi is challenged to a Duel by Dinosaur Ryuzaki.
With help from Doma, both of their decks have been powered up.
They push Yugi and Jounouchi into a corner!
Yugi's in no state to be Dueling intelligently right now!
Calm down, Yugi!
Don't let Haga confuse you!
Next time!
"Powered Up Decks!
Haga and Ryuzaki"
Duel standby!