With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Here I go, Yugi!
It's time to determine the strongest!
DUEL!!
Trap Card, activate!
Magic Lamp!
What?!
The lamp deflects your attack
at your own Monster!
Kaiba! To trap me...
Yugi, the real trap I've set for you
is just beginning..!
The heart of the world's strongest Monster
has already begun to beat in my hand...
That's right...
I'm going to fuse 3 Blue-Eyes!
"The Strongest! The Magnificent!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon"
What's going on?
Yugi-kun fell into Kaiba-kun's trap!
He's pretty good!
The match just started!
Do your best, other Yugi!
It's still the first half. They're
just testing each other to start.
The real fight starts now.
Kaiba! It's time we settled our scores!
I will defeat you!
I already have one Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
When I get three, my victory is set.
My plan is to fuse 3 Blue-Eyes.
Strong! Invincible! Ultimate!
Yugi, when you add this formula
there's only one answer...
And that is your loss!
Here I come! It's my turn!
I got my trump card, Undo Magic!
I'll play this card with La Jinn.
And I play La Jinn the Genie
of the Lamp once again!
I destroy one Magic Card on
your side of the board!
What?!
A good card was stricken.
Sealing Swords of Light stops all monsters
from attacking for 3 full turns.
This card is hard to beat.
My turn!
Can Yugi-kun defeat that combo with
La Jinn and Magic Lamp?
It's alright! There's got to be a way!
Good. I drew the Magic Box card.
The combo that will destroy La Jinn and Magic Lamp is finished!
Here I go!
Now! Come on and attack La Jinn!
Even though you'll just fall into my trap!
I'll break the La Jinn and
Magic Lamp combo, Kaiba!
Magic Card, The Eye Of Truth!
The Eye Of Truth...?
This Magic Card lets me see
all the cards in your hand.
That's...!
Kaiba has a Blue-Eyes in his hand...!
Dammit.
That Kaiba bastard!
I knew he had a Blue-Eyes up his sleeves!
There's still 2 left in his deck...
3 Blue-Eyes...?
I didn't realize his deck was that powerful...!
No! He can beat it!
He's beaten them before!
Why...?
Why isn't Kaiba attacking
with his Blue-Eyes...?
Cursed Yugi...!
Exposing my cards is the
ultimate humiliation...!
My plan is to fuse 3 Blue-Eyes...
In order to do so, the condition
is that I have the Fusion card.
I'll surely fuse all 3 Blue-Eyes White Dragons.
I'll return the humiliation you handed to me!
That's it...!
If I were Kaiba, I'd try to fuse
the 3 Blue-Eyes.
There's no doubt.
His plan is to fuse all 3 Blue-Eyes.
But right now, I don't even have a card
strong enough to beat one Blue-Eyes...!
First I have to break Kaiba's combo!
Magic Box!
What!?
Magic Box destroys one magic combo
made by the opponent.
In the other box, Magic Lamp
is sacrificed!
M-my Magic Lamp...!
Now come out, Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
La Jinn is beaten!
Bastard....!
Kaiba!
I won't let you fuse 3 Blue-Eyes!
I'll take your Life Points to 0
before that happens!
That's the Yugi I know!
You know me well.
But don't underestimate me, Yugi!
My formula for victory is more
perfect than you realize!
Your total loss is close at hand...
But before that, I'll show you
something exciting...
Here I come!
My turn!
I'll show you the most terrifying combo
that exists on this planet.
This is the ultimate murder combo!
Saggi the Dark Clown in Defense Mode.
And I set another card in the Sub Stage!
Turn over.
Saggi's Defense is 1500...
Black Magician can easily beat it.
But...
I can't help but feel something's wrong...
Yugi...
You have no choice but
to attack Saggi.
No, until he attacks, I'll keep
playing Saggi until he's forced to.
You are caught in a trap of Hell!
My turn!
Good card.
Dark Knight Gaia...
Gaia beat Saggi in our last fight!
Okay! I change my Main Monster!
Dark Knight Gaia to battle!
Attack Saggi!
Spiral Shaver!!
Saggi the Dark Clown is beaten!
You fell for it!
What?
Dark Knight Gaia!
Not just Gaia!
Black Magician too...?
What is this...?
This card did it!
Deck Destruction Virus of Death!
That is...?
I infected Saggi the Dark Clown
with the Death Virus.
The second your monster attacked Saggi
it was infected by the virus!
Deck Destruction Virus of Death will spread
to every card in your deck!
Not good!
The Virus card's effect...
destroys all monsters with 1500
Attack Points or greater!
I just destroyed your whole deck!
Shit...!
With that worthless deck you've got left,
all you can do is wait quietly for defeat!
Yugi, this time I'll teach you what a
Duel of terror is all about.
That damn bastard Kaiba!
Using such a ridiculous card...!
What's Yugi going to do?
Yugi-kun can only use low-Attack monsters
and Magic cards.
But that Kaiba has 3 Blue-Eyes in his hands!
Yugi...
That sucks for you...
The runner of Kaiba Corporation's not too bad.
With all his strong monsters gone,
Yugi's like a chicken with no wings.
Now, let's see what he'll do next.
My turn.
But we both have no monsters in play.
Draw a card and set them on your disk.
Well, my monsters will slaughter
yours in a second.
The card I drew is...
Demon's Summon.
Its Attack Points exceed 1500.
Even if I play it, it'll just vanish.
What's wrong, Yugi?
Before you play your next card,
I'll pass and wait patiently.
All I can do now is play Silver Fang in Defense.
All you have left is junk designed to lose!
The second Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
Yugi, keep running and playing your
weakling monsters.
In the end, I'll collect the Fusion Card
and the third Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
And Ill fuse the 3 Blue-Eyes
into the ultimate monster!
Until that time, I have to save the
Blue-Eyes cards in the Sub Card Stage.
Minotaur in Attack Mode!
Cut off Silver Fang's head!
Axe Crusher!!
Silver Fang is beaten.
Shit! Can't he do anything?!
The other Yugi has won every time up until now.
He won't lose!
I still have much stronger monsters in reserve!
But even if I stick with Minotaur...
the strongest monster you have
is no match against him!
Now Yugi! It's your turn!
It's no use...
Forget Blue-Eyes...
I don't even have a card
that can beat Minotaur!
Now, go ahead and play your card.
Oh well, it'll just be another measly
Defense monster won't it?
Anyway, all I can do is draw a card...
I won't give up until my Life Points reach 0!
The Griffor card!
Alright! I use this card!
Griffor!
Griffor?
Another weak monster in Defense Mode?
My Minotaur will crush it in an instant!
My Griffor is not in Defense Mode, Kaiba!
What?!
Horn of the Unicorn!
I combo attack with this card!
Griffor Arrow!!
Minotaur is beaten!
Good going! Scared now, Kaiba?!
Yugi!
It's Yugi-kun's turn to show his ability!
We're counting on you, Yugi!
Thanks for killing off that weak Minotaur.
You've now left yourself wide open
for the rest of this turn.
My turn!
Now I have 3 Blue-Eyes White Dragons.
First, I play this Magic Card from my hand!
Holy Elf's Blessing!
Holy Elf's Blessing's effect
increases my Life by 300 points!
Did Kaiba lure me into attacking Minotaur
because he knew he had Holy Elf's Blessing?
It was to get my monster into Attack Mode...!
This turn, I'll play one of the Blue-Eyes.
To fuse all 3 will take another turn.
You'll be at my mercy soon, Yugi!
Come forth, Blue-Eyes!
Here I come, Yugi!
Prepare yourself!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
The trash monster's been killed.
Your Life will vanish soon enough.
Now, it's your turn!
Giant Soldier of Stone in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
It's my turn!
Yugi.... since the first match we had, I've tasted a hunger for victory that was never satisfied...
Now I can finally satisfy this hunger!
This pain....
I'LL LET YOU FEEL IT!!
BLUE-EYES ULTIMATE DRAGON!
Th-This is...
the fusion of 3 Blue-Eyes?
How's that?!
Look, Yugi...!
This is the strongest killing machine!
The ultimate form of monster!
Fusion of 3 Blue-Eyes?!
4500 Attack Points?!
That guy...!
Kaiba-kun's real plan was to
create this Ultimate Dragon?
This match's over.
No miracle will save him.
Goddess of Victory!
Save Yugi!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon...
What can I do against an enemy
with 4500 Attack Points...?
And my Life Points are almost gone...
I have no cards that can fight
against the Ultimate Dragon...!
Yugi, are you ready?
It's now your turn to carry the
cross of defeat like I did!
And you'll crawl on the ground in shame!
Here I come! Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon, attack!
Ultimate Burst!!
My victory is set.
If this continues, I'll lose!
Now Yugi! It's your turn!
If you don't want to surrender, draw a card!
Yugi!
Yugi-kun!
Yugi, don't give up!
Our goal is to get into Pegasus' castle!
It's right in front of us!
If you give up now, we'll never walk through those doors!
Grandpa...!
I...
I will not give up!
That's right. Come at me until the very end!
Yugi! I want to crush you
at your maximum strength!
Anyway, if I can't survive
the next turn, I lose!
This turn determines the match!
Yugi!
Yugi-kun...
YUGI!!
It's useless! No matter what card
you draw, it's hopeless!
I bet my life...
ON THIS CARD!
"Preview"
Yugi is able to come back
after being in a desperate pinch.
Yes! You can get rid
of Kaiba-kun's Ultimate Dragon!
What are you doing, Kaiba-kun?!
It's dangerous to walk backwards
like that!
When your Life Points hit 0,
you'll walk off the ledge?!
NO WAY!
Next episode: "Kuriboh Multiplies!
The Astonishing Conclusion"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship