Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Even with Obelisk's greatest Ability,
Soul Energy Max, I couldn't defeat Ra.
However, I still have the servants who fought hard for me in the Battle City tournament!
I'll borrow all of their power,
as I activate the Magic Card, Ragnarok!
Malik, I shall use this to destroy you and Ra fused as a Monster!
"The End of Battle City!"
It's him...!
Rishid...!
So you were still alive, Rishid?
You're pretty damn tough...
Though, even if you've shown your ass after all this time,
I won't be switching
personalities anytime soon!
Ri...shid...!
Are you alright, Rishid?
You can't even walk straight.
Don't overdo it!
Hey...!
Please let him go.
Because this is Rishid's only wish...
What a vile carving!
But it no longer holds any meaning!
My dominant self's psyche is like that
of a candle flame in the wind!
He doesn't even have the strength
to speak, let alone to live!
Lord Malik...
The cruel fate of the Tomb Guardians
is what brought this tragedy upon us.
Resentment towards the Ishtar clan...
Anger and hatred lying dormant
within you is what created the
evil heart that stands before us.
SHUT UP ALREADY!
Malik, you bastard!
Stop it...!
SHUT UP!
Rishid!
Lord Malik...
You are about to throw yourself
into the darkness of despair!
Shut your mouth!!
Rishid!
I'm... alright....
However, even if your path leads into
darkness, you must continue living!
That is not just
the fate of a Tomb Guardian!
It is the fate of every human being!
The fate... of every human being...
I TOLD YOU
TO SHUT THE HELL UP-
Look, other me!
He's acting strange!
Malik!
Lord Malik...
It is not through death
that people go into the light...
There is light only in life!
WHY?!
You shouldn't have this much
strength left in you...!
Yugi! Attack me!
Malik!
Silence...! Get lost, you leech...!
I've committed
an unforgivable crime...
A crime so bad, a Tomb Guardian like
myself cannot be forgiven for it...
It was my hatred for the Pharaoh
that led to the Ishtar tragedy...!
And created my other self...
I thought I told
you to be silent...!
That's right, it's because of my dark heart
that this evil monster was created!
Lord Malik...
Despite all that, do you think someone
like myself can head towards the light?
SHUT UP! SHUT UP!!
Is there some way I can put an end to
this never ending sorrow and hatred?
Yugi, I'll find out
in your next attack!
SILENCE!!
Hurry and attack me!
Other me, Malik's serious!
He's betting everything
on this one attack!
Yeah.
I can feel his strong spirit.
I understand.
I'll believe in your strength,
your one point of life!
Here I come, Malik!
I activate my reverse Magic,
Ragnarok! Final Destiny of the Gods!
Ragnarok is a Magic Card that can only be
activated when both Black Magician and
Black Magician Girl are on the field.
Its effect allows me to remove from play
every Monster in my deck,
my hand, and my Graveyard.
In exchange, it destroys every
Monster of the opponent!
S-Stop.... it....!
Even if the target is a god!
Osiris is...!
Obelisk is here too!
Every one of Yugi-kun's
Monsters are appearing...!
Amazing...!
Stop it!
Stay back!!
Let me go!
LET ME GO!
Black Burning Magic!!
Amazing...
He defeated Ra!
Did Yugi win?
No!
Malik still has 1 remaining Life Point.
The other me believed that Malik
had the strength to live
on one Life Point...
Please, be alive.
Malik...
Lord Malik...
Malik!
Malik's expression changed...
Is his dark personality gone?
Lord Malik, you had the strength to live
within your heart this entire time...
And that strength has overcome
your evil heart and your evil half.
Yugi... I still have
1 Life Point remaining...
This Duel is not over yet!
Other me!
Look at that!
What the hell?!
Malik and his dominant personality
switched places! Now he's the sacrifice!
This can't be!
There's no way my half-dead
dominant half had enough
will power to overtake me
and take over the body!
Stop joking!
I've become a sacrifice
because of just one point?!
Hey! Dominant Half!
I've always thought of us
as friends sharing the same body!
We're the same!
There's still a chance we can
win this Duel, even with one Life Point...
Kill Yugi!
It was because of him
that you suffered the terrible
fate of the Tomb Guardians!
Get revenge for
you and your ancestors!
You are the dark side I created,
spawned by my suffering as a
result of that very same fate!
You can no longer
control my subconscious!
What....?!
I will destroy you
with my own hands!
Madness...!
Is he planning to give up his body
in order to destroy me...?!
Malik...
I won't die.
The crimes I committed
will never be cleared.
But I will live, bearing my guilt like
these carvings on my back.
And I'd like to chase
the light of hope once again amidst
the darkness of my destiny.
Lord Malik...
Yugi...
No, soul of the Pharaoh!
Thank you for
saving me in this Duel.
Y-You wouldn't...!
Don't!
The terrible fate of the Ishtar
clan lasting 3,000 years...
The tragedy caused by me
shutting myself in darkness.
I must put an end to it myself.
All with these hands!
That will at least be some atonement
for the sin I've committed.
S-stop it...!
This will be the first step...
...into the light!
He surrendered!
He conceded defeat...
His Life Points automatically
dropped to 0!
Sur..... rend..... dered....?!
IMPOSSIBLE...!
Be gone!
My dark self!
I've lost everything, Pharaoh!
Other me!
Partner!
Malik... Our future was not lost...
Thank you, Pharaoh.
Lord Malik...
Malik, you were victorious in
the Duel against your heart.
Mmm.
The Battle City Finals are over!
The winner is Yugi Mutou!
ALRIGHT!
You did it, Yugi!
YUGI!
Alright, good job!
You did it!
Yugi!
Dammit, you're amazing!
You did it, Yugi!
To all my cards
who lent me strength...
And... my friends!
Thank you!
Malik...
Big sister... I...
For thousands of years,
our family has suffered a cruel fate
as we lived in the darkness.
But it was your destiny to end it.
Foolishly pursuing revenge only
leads to further tragedy!
Perhaps we, the Ishtars,
were assigned the duty
of guarding
the Pharaoh's memories...
...so our Pharaoh could
teach us that message.
Sister, do you think our family
can escape the chains of darkness and live?
Yes.
The three of us, after all, are not just
of the same tribe, but family.
As long as we hold this bond...
we can endure any obstacle
we may face!
Sister!
Yugi!
At this very moment,
by winning Battle City, you have just
earned the title of Duel King!
As the host of this tournament,
I applaud your achievement!
Kaiba...
If I hadn't taken the card you gave me,
I wouldn't have been able to win.
It's the rules!
As the winner, Yugi,
you get to take Malik's Ante Card!
Malik.
It is time to fulfill your
final duty as a Tomb Guardian.
Right!
Yugi.
The dark spells placed
on your friends who lost to me
in the Dark Games have been lifted.
They'll regain consciousness soon.
Really?!
We did it!
So Mai...
And me too!
Yugi, here's the God Card!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
The Great War God Obelisk...
Finally, the three God Cards
are in my hands.
Those three cards hold the secret
of the other me's memory...
What could it be...?
And...
The key to the Pharaoh's memories,
which the Tomb Guardian clan
has protected for centuries...
It lies right here!
How awful that
must have been...!
That's horrible...!
This cruel scar...
Is this how the Tomb Guardians
guarded my memory for
so many generations...?!
These hieroglyphs contain a prophecized
message passed down from the first Tomb
Guardian who served under the Royal Family.
"In the future, one will come
who will wield the power of the
three gods depicted on the stone slab."
"This will be proof that the
Pharaoh's soul has been reincarnated."
Yugi, since you now hold the three God Cards, it is proof that you are the Pharaoh.
And thus, you deserve to know the
truth of your long-lost memories.
Yugi...
Can you read this stuff?
Yeah...
The words of this ancient language
hold no meaning to me...
But it's like the three God Cards
are sending a vision through me...!
This is...!
That slate!
Is my memory truly sealed
within that slate?
Now my mission has been fulfilled.
And finally...
Please take my Millennium Rod,
one of the Millennium Items my tribe
risked their lives to protect.
And the Millennium Ring as well.
Have you finished
soaking in all the glory?
The Battle City Tournament
has now officially ended!
Yugi, I will lend you my pride and
the title of Duel King for the time being!
Mmm-hmm.
The final location of
the Battle City Finals, the Duel Tower,
has now outlived its usefulness.
Therefore, in exactly one hour
from now, this structure will explode!
WH-WHAT!?
What are you thinking, Kaiba!?
Every one of you will be
evacuated aboard the Battle Ship and
escorted off of Alcatraz Island!
Eh?
But isn't the engine
in the Battle Ship damaged?
Don't worry about that!
Repairs finished a while ago!
Right, Isono?
Y-Yes...
That's all.
Oi! We can't just stand here!
Kaiba, you bastard!
There's a limit to being a sore loser!
Seriously! What's Kaiba-kun thinking?!
Preparations are all okay, big brother.
Are you all right with this, Mokuba?
Yeah! I'll always be by your side!
Inputting password code.
Inputting... complete...
Big brother, let's go.
Yeah...
Goodbye, ghost of Gozaburo!
1... 2... and 3!
Self-Detonation procedure launched.
One hour remaining until explosion.
Everyone, please hurry! Get aboard!
Mai!
Are you awake?!
Big brother...!
Shizuka, how's Mai?
About that...
What did you say?
You're kidding...!
Mai, how could something
this stupid happen?!
Stop joking with me!
Mai...!
Mai! Why?!
Don't die...! Don't die, MAI!
DON'T DIE!! MAI!!
M-Mai?
Jounouchi, were you crying?!
I'm so happy!
I can't believe you were that worried about me!
Y-you bitch!
You were fooling me?!
See, Shizuka-chan,
it went just as I said!
He's so simple-minded, after all!
Shizuka!
I'm really sorry, big brother!
Gosh, we were so worried about!
You scared me~
Yugi!
You won! Congratulations!
Yeah.
So that leaves Bakura, right?
Where did he go?
Bakura?
Ah, you guys! Thank goodness
I finally found you all!
That's our line!
Where the hell were you up 'till now?
I don't really know.
When I woke up, I was lying in bed.
And what did ya know, I was starving!
You...
What did you say?! Seto-sama and
Mokuba-sama aren't back yet?!
Where could they have gone?
We're running out of time!
What's up with Kaiba?
They aren't on the Battle Ship.
What'd you say?
What the hell is Kaiba doing?!
Don't tell me he's going to
kill himself because he can't
accept his loss to Yugi-kun...!
No way!
There's no way that's true!
If it's the same guy we're talking about,
don't you think he escaped already?
B-But, what if you're wrong...?!
Yeah, we can't just leave them here.
Can't be helped... let's go look for them.
Yup.
Yeah.
Then you guys prepare for our escape.
Seriously, that guy
causes a lot of problems.
There's no helping it...
Start the engine!
Roger!
Compressor running!
Voltage is good! Fuel is good!
Starting contact!
Wha...? What's happening?!
The engine... stopped...!
What!?
I thought you said it was fixed!
No way!
What's going to happen to us?
45 minutes remaining until explosion.
After setting up the explosion for the island, Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun just vanished.
Can it be those two plan to sink with the island and bury themselves at sea?
And to top it off, the Battle Ship's engine stopped working again, so we have no way off!
We have to hurry and find those two, since there's no time left 'till the explosion!
Kaiba-kun, Mokuba-kun! Where in the world are you?!
Next time!
"Alcatraz Burns"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other