The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Insector Combo
Yugi, we’re finally here.
That's the Duelist Kingdom.
Oi, Anzu, what if they discover we have no Star Chips?
We stand out, don't we?
It’s alright, they won’t check again.
But they'll suspect you if you look uptight.
Oi!
You should relax a bit more.
Thank you!
I thought my heart was gonna stop.
Geez, you were frightened like a little kid.
Alright!
At least we all got here safe-
Sorry, Jounouchi-kun. It's my fault.
It'll be over for sure if I do this!
What!?
The treasured cards my grandpa gave me!
Damn!
Don't worry about it, Yugi.
But I can't forgive...
The bastard who tossed your treasured cards away, Yugi.
Haga-kun, I will never forgive you.
All Duelists...
...gather around the castle gates.
That’s Pegasus’ castle.
Alright! Let’s go.
What’s wrong, Anzu?
Was that Bakura-kun just now?
Bakura-kun?
Again?
"Again"?
Huh? He's gone? I guess I was just imagining it.
Let's go.
Oi, look! Those are some amazing members...!
That's Japan's Champ, Insector Haga, and Number Two, Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
And there’s Ryota Kajiki, who came in third place!
If Kaiba were here, there's no doubt he'd be the winner.
Right, but the person who beat him, that Yugi guy, must be here.
He must be very good to have beaten Kaiba.
I wonder who that guy is.
Everyone, the host, Pegasus-sama, will now explain the Dueling rules of this tournament.
Pegasus is finally here.
You are unable to escape me.
I'll see you again at the Kingdom.
If you want back your most valuable treasure.
Grandpa!
Pegasus...! With that Dark Power of his, he took my Grandpa's soul.
You’re here, Yugi boy.
Welcome! Welcome to the Duelist Kingdom!
Now allow me to explain the rules to you.
Please use your Duel Monsters cards freely during this tournament.
You will hold 2000 Life Points.
Players are strictly forbidden from attacking the opponent directly.
Please use the strongest Card Deck you've brought with you while Dueling in this competition.
Every Duelist received a Duel Glove in advance...
...and two Star Chips.
On the Glove's ring, there are 10 holes in which you can keep your Star Chips.
Please keep your Star Chips inside them.
Those Star Chips are proof of your status as a Duelist.
Every Duelist will bet on these Star Chips while Dueling.
I see, so the loser of the Duel must give his Star Chips to the winner.
Duelists with no Star Chips will be disqualified.
Me and Jounouchi-kun each only have 1 Star Chip.
This whole island is a battlefield for Dueling.
The ones to survive this Battle Royal and obtain 10 Star Chips
will be permitted to pass through this door.
You just have a 48 hour time limit to Duel, and you start in one hour.
When this time ends, anyone with less than 10 Star Chips loses.
Then, these people who lost will have to leave the island.
Now then, my cherished Duelists, I wish you all the best of luck!
I have to enter the castle no matter what!
Yugi boy, in order to fight me...
...you have to first fight others on the island.
Wait for me, Grandpa!
I will defeat Pegasus’ Dark Power.
Sorry, Yugi.
You lost your important Star Chip because of me...
It’s okay. Jounouchi-kun, the reason I gave it to you is because I know you'll definitely win.
Yugi...
Jounouchi, work hard for your little sister.
We’ll be rooting for you the whole time.
Guys...
Yugi...
We have to win the first Duel no matter what it takes.
Duel...
...start!
What are you planning to do, Yugi?
I’ve made up my mind.
I’ll fight against Haga-kun first.
That’s what I'm talkin' about!
Yugi!
Haga-kun!
That's low, Haga! Are you running away?!
Yugi!
Wait! Haga-kun!
We can't catch him like this!
This is disgusting! Where’s he running to!?
Who the hell came up with the rule that makes this whole island the battlefield?!
This whole island is a Dueling battlefield.
Something's been bothering me... Why do we need such a large field for a mere card game?
That's it!
Do you know the new rules of the Duels?
So this is what you meant there would be new rules in Duelist Kingdom. I see, Haga-kun!
I see, Haga-kun! So that's what you meant?!
Haga-kun!
Yugi, now I'll challenge you to a Duel and finish things!
I'll never forgive you!
Haga, I praise you for working up the courage to challenge me to a Duel.
If I crush you right from the start, I won't even break a sweat later on!
I was just thinking the same thing!
Duel Standby!!
What’s going on?
This is...
This is the stage of the Kingdom! The Duel Ring!
So this is...
Are these set up all over the island?
Well now, shall we get started?
You only have 1 Star Chip.
If you lose that 1, you'll still be taken out of the tournament.
Then, I’ll bet only 1 Star Chip to even the match.
No, you will bet 2.
What?!
Either me or you will be knocked out!
But, Yugi, what will you use to replace that other Star Chip?
My life as a Duelist.
I’ll bet this Card Deck.
Now that's interesting. Very well.
Had I known this would happen,
I wouldn't have wasted Exodia like that.
Yugi!
Kick that bug bastard's ass!
Oi, guys, a Duel has begun here!
Japan's Regional Champion, Insector Haga, and...
Who's that?
That’s Yugi Mutou, who beat Kaiba.
And I’m his best friend, Katsuya Jounouchi, and...
These guys are our cheerleaders!
Haga and Yugi?! We're seeing an elite Duel right from the start!
Let's go, Yugi!
Duel!
My card is Killer Bee.
Attack Mode!
My card is Mammoth's Graveyard.
The Attack Power is the same for these monsters!
Battle!
Here comes Killer Bee's counter-attack!
Killer Bee beat the Mammoth!
Their Attack Power was the same...
...why was just my Monster destroyed?
Yugi, you don't realize why I led you all the way out to this Duel Ring, do you?
Shall I tell you?
The truth is, Pegasus-san told me the new rules for the Duelist Kingdom tournament.
Take a good look at this Duel Ring's Field.
My area is shown very clearly along the display.
The Field we're battling on right now is 80% Forest,
while only 20% is made of Wasteland!
The Forest Field works best with my Insect Cards.
And because of that, my Insect Cards benefit from the Field Power Source,
and they receive a 30% power-up for both their Attack and Defense Points!
Really?
This ring had a Field Effect right from the start?
Yugi, there's no way you'll win when faced with my Insect Cards!
W-What's so funny, Yugi?
Haga, look at your bug Monster.
What?
My Killer Bee!
Crap!
Yugi's Mammoth's Graveyard is a Dinosaur-type Monster
that only receives a 20% power-up from the Wasteland!
So his Monster also received a power-up from the Field Power?!
Haga, I knew about the new rules from the moment I arrived here!
Too bad for you!
So you realized what the new rules for the Kingdom were...?!
Why did Pegasus make this particular island the Duel location?
I was asking myself that...
...but after I saw this field's display, I knew the answer.
The Monsters benefit from the Field Power Source,
and thus makes your cards even stronger.
Meaning the key is to choose the field that best suits your cards.
Haga, it was you who led me into this forest,
and is how I discovered this. I must thank you.
Just as I expected, Yugi!
You figured things out even this far!
But, aside from the benefits of this forest,
there’s still something you don’t know about the Kingdom's new rules.
Go, Yugi!
Finish off that bastard!
My card is Heracles Beetle.
And thanks to the Forest, its Attack Points increase by 30%!
80% of the field is Forest, the rest is Wasteland.
But I don’t have any cards suitable for this Field.
I have to use this.
My card is Gremlin.
Attack Position.
With the Magic card, Unicorn's Horn,
it's Attack increases by 700 points.
It’s no use, it can't win.
Battle!
Go, Heracles Beetle.
Gremlin's Electric Shock!
The Electric Shock didn't work at all!
What's going on?
Could it be...?
A Monster powered up by the Field Power...
is immune to Magic?!
Exactly!
A Monster powered up with magic is useless against one powered up with the Field Power!
A Monster can only prevail with their natural form!
Heracles Beetle holds 1950 Attack Points.
The natural Attack Points of Gremlin are 1300!
The difference will be reduced from your Life Points!
An Insect Card with that little Attack...
...can become very strong due to the Field Power...!
Isn't there a lot of Insect space?
Yugi, do your best!
Now Yugi, it's your turn.
I don’t have any usable cards to beat Heracles Beetle.
For now I need to place Monsters in Defense Mode...
I can’t believe you keep running away.
I guess victory's as good as mine.
Don’t tell me you beat Kaiba by pure luck?
It’s ready, my sure-kill combo!
The Basic Insect card!
It receives a power up from the Field Power Source!
Then Laser Cannon Armor Level 3!
Then The Weapon-Armor Level 2 boosts its points up even higher!
Thus, the Monster receives a 4-way power up!
This is the strongest Duelist in Japan for you.
This is the all-powerful combo from Insector Haga.
Attack!
So your platoon was Griffor?
You’re too weak to go play against me!
Defense Mode, my cards...
...you have to endure it!
It must be another weak card.
No Monster in existence is strong enough to block my Insect Combo!
But beating a bunch of small fries over and over doesn't sound like fun.
So I'll set this secret card face-down on the field.
Jounouchi, what’s that card?
A Trap Card?
The moment Yugi declares an attack...
A Trap Card will appear that'll wipe Yugi out!
Parasite Worm!
So my attack's been sealed off...!
All I can do is trust in the cards I set.
Did you set a Magic Card to bluff your way out of this most cruel situation?
Behold Yugi, as my Insect Army completely dominates the field!
That’s not enough!
What’s wrong? Why didn’t you attack?
In every turn, the number of Monsters will increase.
No, this is bad, I don’t have any strong enough Monster Cards in my hand...!
The way it's going, his Monsters will keep increasing!
Even if you say that, Yugi's attack's been sealed!
Today is the last day as a Duelist for you.
My Insects will win here and celebrate with a giant parade!
I'm counting on you, my cards.
Black Magician.
This is one of my best cards, even though it can’t attack.
Defense Mode!
No matter what card you use, it's all futile before my Insect Army!
Go, Basic Insect with Laser Cannon...
...kill that card!
Attack!!!
W-What's so funny?
Haga! You said "attack" just now, did you not?
What?!
Have you forgotten the card I set?
Could it be... A Trap Card?
Exactly.
It will activate this Trap Card
when my opponent says 'attack'.
Holy Barrier – Mirror Force!
Retreat!
My Insect Army was...!
Alright, Yugi!
Yugi!
You figured out my strategy?!
I guess you became Japan's Regional Champion by pure luck.
You’re too confident in your strategy.
And you didn’t pay attention to my card.
Let me say this clearly, Haga...
...You are too weak!
He did it!!
This Duel with Haga is easy!
What? We don't know how this match will end?
Ah, Mai Kujaku?
What's with her arrogance?!
There’s a cocoon? And it’s getting hard to fight with Haga's new combo that's never lost!
This cocoon will evolve and hatch, and then Yugi will...
Next time, The Perfectly Ultimate Great Moth.
Duel Standby.
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship