Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"The Black Magician User,
Pandora"
What bullshit are you trying to pull on me?!
That shitty card can't even compare to the rareness of my card!
B-But you agreed to this Ante before we started the duel...
I changed my mind!
The loser has to obey as the winner tells him!
N-No way... come on...
Don't screw with me!
Warning!
Who's this kid?
I'm the Battle City Steering Committee Chairman, Mokuba Kaiba!
It's my job to settle trouble relating to all tournament matters.
Don't screw around with my rules!
Someone who doesn't abide by the rules has no right to call himself a duelist!
What!?
What a poor duelist.
What'd you say!?
Big brother!
S-Seto Kaiba...!
When you insult my little brother...
It's no different than directly insulting Kaiba Corporation.
I assume you're prepared for the consequences.
What'd you mean by that?
A-Amazing...! These are all rare cards!
I'm challenging you to a duel right now!
However, the condition is that you take all the rare cards
you like from this case and rebuild your deck.
You'll regret that...!
Once I claim your rare cards, I'll have the best deck around!
Cards are power! There's a 100% chance of you losing!
Let's go! Duel!
I'll show you God. This is what true power is all about!
God is in my hands.
Two cards left.
When I find the two in this city...
I will own a deck equal to God himself.
Yugi... I'll wait for you on this road of battle!
You found the owner of Obelisk?
Yes. Domino City, North C Block.
The owner of Obelisk is...
Seto Kaiba.
I should have known.
But how did Kaiba get hold of it?
I can imagine... He hosted this tournament because he got his hands on it...
His purpose is to unify the gods.
As I thought, it was you, wasn't it...?
Open the lock.
Malik, my Millennium Tauk warned me you would do this.
For 3,000 years, our tribe has sworn to protect the King's tomb.
Do you intend to defy them by doing this?
Sacrifice myself for what?!
Someone has to break them of this myth!
Once I obtain all three God Cards, I'll gain right to the Pharaoh's title.
And our tribe can be freed from this curse!
That's betraying our tribe!
I cannot let you pass here.
Move and let me pass.
Can you really use your Millennium Rod against me?
If it's for the sake of our future, then I can.
Even if it's you, Dear sister.
Dear sister, it was you who had the last card, wasn't it?
You must have foreseen the future with your Millennium Tauk...
You gave Seto Kaiba the Obelisk card...
Then he held this event.
You knew that, by the god's guidance,
my fate and his would eventually intertwine in Domino City.
But in the end, the final God Card...
Will fall into my hands!
Along with the title of Pharaoh.
Kaiba is still in the North Block.
Shall I assemble a team to attack him?
No, let Kaiba be for the time being.
I finally found Pharaoh after all this time...
Assemble Pandora the Conjurer, for a duel!
Yes sir!
Well then, I'll be leaving.
I'm a bit worried about Yugi and Jounouchi.
Um...
Honda-san...
I have a favor to ask.
Eh?
I was wondering if you could take me to Domino City on the day I get my bandages taken off.
Take you to Domino City?
Yeah. I want to see Big brother dueling with my own two eyes.
Ah, just leave it to me.
Shizuka-chan will have her bandages taken off soon.
Yeah.
You have to try hard for Shizuka-chan, my disciple.
I know that.
We're going to look for Yugi.
Ah, see ya.
Um.
Partner... This card we're holding for him is Jounouchi-kun's courage.
You mean Jounouchi-kun's fighting in order to get his card back.
I'm sure Jounouchi-kun will survive Battle City.
Yeah. When that time comes, I'll surely accept his challenge. The duelist Jounouchi Katsuya!
It doesn't matter which of us wins or loses.
It'll be a good memory for us.
Just like the memories of playing games with Grandpa.
That's right... You don't have any memories from before you met me...
Rare Hunter?!
You're telling me to go there?
Hey, that's Yugi, isn't it?!
Eh? Where?
Yugi!
Where'd you go, Yugi?!
Yugi, answer us!
What did you say?!
Big brother!
Big brother, the portable tracking computer said Mutou Yugi's signal disappeared from the tracking screen!
Yugi disappeared?!
Ghouls?
Mokuba! Try to locate him!
Um!
The Duel Disks should keep a constant signal of every duelist...
If the signal is not being read, Yugi might be inside a building that's blocking the signal...
For example, a basement or something.
My duelist data...!
This is...!
What?!
I've been waiting for you, Yugi.
My master, the great Pandora-sama, will duel you.
Pandora?!
I'll show you there is only one true user of the Magician Spellcaster-type monsters...
Pandora-sama, the Conjurer!
Stop the petty tricks and come on out!
Rare Hunter!
Welcome. I am the second Rare Hunter, Pandora.
Also known as the Conjurer, and user of the Black Magician.
User of the Black Magician?
Yugi, I'm aware you often use the Black Magician to defeat your enemies.
But I am the master of Magicians!
There's no one who can defeat my Black Magician!
We'll see about that.
Duelists choose the cards the trust most
out of a very large amount of cards, this building their deck.
But sometimes the cards choose the duelist.
When the hearts of both the cards and the duelist become one,
the cards' true power can be unleashed!
Rare Hunters don't have the duelists' heart!
Okay!
I'll take you on, Pandora!
My Black Magician will defeat you!
As I expected. You're said to accept any duel. It seems no different with me either.
Now then, this room is a bit crowded.
I've prepared a special duel ring for us... Please.
Duel ring?
It's down here.
The truth is, Malik-sama informed me you would be in this very area.
Malik?!
A Millennium Item wielder, and the leader of Ghouls...
Where is he right now?!
Answer me, Pandora!
Who knows? Where ever could he be?
He's very close.
You might say, he's in here.
Malik has the power to take control of people...
Could it be this Pandora is also...
Now then, please enter.
This will be our duel ring!
Pandora's room!
What do you think of this place?
Cards have often been used here during special occasions.
Besides, this is the perfect stage for the new Black Magician's duel.
The solid vision system can be used here.
But Kaiba Corporation can't locate us here.
Now then, let us get started.
We'll each shuffle our own decks.
The way you cut and shuffle, you'll damage your cards.
I'm used to doing it this way.
I'll cut!
By all means.
There's an old saying among gamblers...
"Trust your friends, but always cut the cards."
"Friends"?
There's no way I'd call you that!
That's a pity.
However, now that we are committed to Dueling,
I'd like to show you something that will prove we are truly blood brothers!
The Nightmare Show will now begin!
What?!
Yes, I am cuffed as well.
Now the both of us can't escape from here.
I will now show you the greatest show in history
as I, "Pandora the Conjurer", escape from the very jaws of death!
What?!
It's a 100-tooth carbide tipped saw you see in magic shows!
Do you understand the rules of this duel yet?
The saws are aligned along a set of numbers.
The Life Points?
The closer they get to 0, the closer the blade gets to us?
That's correct! It's a nightmare game where the loser's body will be sawed apart!
Furthermore, please take a look at your feet!
This contains the final hope of both you and I.
This box...!
Within this box lies the key that will open the shackles at our feet.
It can only be opened when the opposite player's Life Points reaches 0!
In other words, only the winner can escape from here alive!
You bastard!
Pandora's Box...
The Greek god Zeus created a box containing all the misfortune in the world.
But the moment a woman sharing the name opened it,
all the evil escaped, bringing about evil, suffering and pain.
However, a tiny bit of hope was left at the bottom of the box.
The very key at the bottom of this box is our last hope!
Is this fun...?
A battle with people's lives on the line...
I'm asking you if you think it's fun!
Yes. Because I will be the winner.
You filthy scum!
Then I'll show you what a true duelist's fight looks like!
Duel!
I go first!
Draw 5 cards from your deck!
Black Magician is already within my hand, as planned.
It was simple to ensure this...
I have a certain technique designed to let me draw the cards I need most.
This allows me to add certain cards to my hand from the start of the match.
This technique goes by the name 'Stripper'.
All I had to do was cut specific cards so they are slightly smaller than the others...
I cut the three Black Magicians in my deck like this... And when you cut the deck, Black Magician will surely be at the top.
Yugi, I'll teach you what it's like facing a card trickster like me.
In this death game!
Here I go! My turn!
I set a card on the field!
Also, Magnet Warrior Alpha in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
My turn!
Legion of Fiend Jester in Defense Mode!
I just need one more monster to Sacrifice Summon, and I can Summon Black Magician to the field!
My turn!
Pandora, I'm going to play a Magic Card this turn.
Magic Card?
And that card is...
Hand Obliteration!
Wh-What!? Hand Obliteration!?
Now both players' hands are destroyed!
That includes you, Pandora!
Destroy our hands...?!
Black Magician...!
Discard it...?!
As I thought, you have Black Magician in your hand already.
Of course I'd not drop my guard around a trickster like you.
Judging by the way you cut and shuffle, you don't seem to cherish your cards at all.
It doesn't surprise me you'd cut them.
C-Could it be you were aware of my trick from the start?!
My turn's not over yet!
Set card open!
Brain Control!
Brain Control!?
He's going to take control of my monster!?
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Alpha and Legion of Fiend Jester!
I Summon Black Magician!
I'll show you the anger of the cards, Pandora!
He was able to Summon his Black Magician before I played mine?!
You were the one who set up such a dangerous game. But I assume you're prepared to suffer because of that, Pandora!
Black Magician! Direct Attack the player!
Black Magic!!
The attack just now cut your Life Points in half.
Now then! Show me how tough you are facing your own rule!
He got the best of me...!
But the real show's just starting!
"Preview"
It's a battle of Black Magician VS Black Magician!
But in order to win, Pandora offers to take the soul of his own monster, and put Yugi in a great pinch!
Yugi believes in his cards until the very end.
If this keeps up...
Please, Black Magician!
Answer Yugi!
Next time: "Soul Black Magic"
Duel standby.
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...