Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
So Yugi, despite me dominating the game in this undeniable situation,
being able to Summon God first...
I suppose I should compliment you, as I expected nothing less.
But now that the effects of Lightforce Sword have disappeared,
my god, Obelisk, will descend!
At long last, your Osiris, and my Obelisk...
...god against god...
The clash of Titans has finally begun!
"Clash! Osiris VS Obelisk"
Behold, Yugi!
The god that lives in my deck!
So it finally showed itself...
The Great War God Obelisk...!
Amazing...!
My brother and Yugi already
Summoned their gods!
So those are
the legendary God Cards...!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon and...
The Great War God Obelisk...!
Those're the most powerful monsters
across all the oceans of the world!
Honda!
We finally got through!
The helicopter's on its way right now!
Thank you, Honda-san!
Jounouchi, just endure
this a little longer!
Hey...! You guys...!
Th-There...!
That's...!
Obelisk and Osiris are
finally about to fight!
Yugi...!
Now then...! Let's see which god wins!
Yugi! My Obelisk will destroy your Osiris!
You only have two hand cards!
Considering Osiris depends
on the player's hand in order
to raise its Attack Power,
Osiris the Heaven Dragon
only has 2000 points!
But I sure hope you haven't forgotten
about Osiris's Special Ability, Kaiba!
The moment you Summoned Obelisk,
that Special Power was activated!
Get ready!
Osiris's Special Ability!
Summon Lighting Shot!!
Osiris's lightning deals
2000 points of damage to any Monster
at the moment of Summoning!
Good...
That strike took Obelisk
down to 2000 Attack Points...
For this turn, both gods
have equal Attack Points...
Attacking now
would only kill ourselves...
Damn you, Yugi...
You were content with
two hand cards knowing Osiris's
Special Ability would kick in...!
But the effects of spells
and Special Powers only last
for one turn on a god...
By next turn, Obelisk's Attack Points
will return to 4000...
Even when I draw a card
next turn, Osiris will only
have 3000 Attack Points...
This match ends next turn!
I set two reverse cards
and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
This moment, Osiris's Attack Power
climbs back up to 3000 points!
But Obelisk's Attack Power
rises back up to 4000!
Don't even think about it, Kaiba!
Magic Card, activate!
Pot of Greed!
The Magic Card Pot of Greed lets me
draw two more cards from my deck.
Osiris's Attack Points
go up even higher!
Now Osiris has 5000 Attack Points.
It's got more Attack Power
than Obelisk now!
Now go, Osiris!
Thunder...
Not smart enough, Yugi!
Magic Card, activate!
Command Silencer!!
Since Osiris can no longer hear your
attack order, the attack is negated!
Command Silencer drowns out
your attack order and forces
your Battle Phase to a close!
And because of Command Silencer's effect,
I draw one card from my deck!
As expected, attacking you
won't be that easy.
If that Trap is Life Shaver...
It's a card that forces the opponent to discard cards equal to the number of turns its stays face-down.
Kaiba will most likely use it next turn!
Once he does, Osiris's
Attack Power will fall to 4000 points.
They'll be the same as Obelisk's.
Then once I use another card from my hand,
causing Osiris' Attack Power to drop
again, it'll be done for in an instant.
But...!
I place two set cards!
With that, I end my turn!
He lowered Osiris's Attack Value just so he could set a couple of reverse cards?
We're going to finish
this match in the next turn, Kaiba!
Which god's gonna win?
My turn!
Let's finish this, Kaiba!
Magic Card! Activate!
Hand Obliteration!
Both players discard their entire hands...
...and draw the same number of cards
from their respective decks!
The hand renewal card...?
But even if he replenishes his hand,
Osiris's Attack will stay the same.
I'll then play a Trap Card!
I activate Fallen Angel's Charity!
Both players return any card discarded
to the Graveyard this turn
by a Magic Effect to their hands.
A Hand Reinforcement Combo?!
I now have six hand cards.
As a result, Osiris's Attack Strength
powers up to 6000 points!
That was admirable, Yugi.
I'd love to compliment you further,
but you aren't the only one who
got further access to their deck
through that Hand Reinforcement Combo
you just pulled off.
That combo brought me
a step closer to my victory!
What?
I activate an Instant Play
Magic Card from my hand!
Compensation of Desire!
This lets me Summon two Monsters
sleeping in my hand!
Come forth!
Sword of Soul!
Blade Knight!
It's futile, Kaiba!
Osiris's Special Ability
will wipe out any weak Monster
you Summon instantaneously!
Go!
Summon Thunder Shot!!
I read right through that move!
Quick Play Magic!
Guard of Cards!
What?!
By discarding a card
from my hand, this card...
negates all damage inflicted
on Monsters to zero!
The Summon Light Shot...!
Yugi, even if your Osiris
has 6000 Attack Points,
it's still nothing when
faced with my Obelisk!
What did you say?
Have you forgotten already?!
Obelisk has a Special Ability as well!
Obelisk's Special Ability is triggered by
tributing two sacrificial Monsters!
The player, along with every Monster
they have on the field,
is dealt 4000 points of damage!
Even if I can't defeat Osiris...
Yugi! You'll receive direct damage
and be eliminated!
Oh no!
It's over!
My brother'll win!
Yugi! Perish by the hands of God!!
God Hand Crusher!!
Yugi! I win!
Perish by the hands of God!!
God Hand Crusher!!
What was that explosion?!
Damn it...! Yugi or Kaiba?!
Which one of them's winning?!
Yugi...!
Yugi...! How...?!
What's the matter, Kaiba?
I'm still alive over here.
In that battle just now, I activated
Kuriboh's Effect from my hand.
Kuriboh, you just saved me!
Curse you, Yugi...! You dodged my attack
using the Effect of some piece of garbage
calling itself a Monster?!
I set two reverse cards!
My turn is over!
Kaiba's hand is at zero now...
If things keep up this way, I should
be able to destroy his Obelisk next turn!
My turn! Draw!
And now Osiris's Attack Points
rise back to 6000!
Osiris!!
Attack Obelisk!!
Big brother!!
The match is over this time for sure!
Now go, Osiris!!
I've been waiting
for you to do that, Yugi!
Trap Card, activate!!
Power Balance!
What?!
Osiris!
What's the meaning of this?!
Power Balance is a Trap Card that can be
activated only when you have
no cards in your hand!
My opponent discards three cards
from their hand,
and I draw the same amount
from my deck!
What did you say?!
That effect has already
been set in motion!
So your Osiris has already had
his Attack Points decreased!
So, Yugi, you have
six cards in your hand.
Throw away three of those cards!
And I pick that same amount
from my deck!
So now your Osiris's Attack Power
goes down by 3000 points!
The tide has shifted
to my favor, Yugi!
Osiris, repay Osiris
for his earlier "kindness"!
Don't get ahead of yourself, Kaiba.
Even if you manage to beat Osiris,
you won't reduce my Life to 0!
I'll activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Necromancy!!
Hey Kaiba, I bet you're eager
to use Obelisk's Special Ability again,
aren't you?
WHAT!?
Necromancy selects four Monsters from my
opponent's Graveyard at random and returns
them to their field in face-up Defense Mode.
Absurd...!
Are you seriously going to just
hand me the sacrifices I need to activate
God Hand Crusher again?!
Naturally, Necromancy has
another special power...
And the condition is that if any Monster
Summoned by Necromancy is destroyed,
all of the opponent's
Monsters' Attack Points...
...go down by 600 points!
Kaiba!! Since you just Summoned Monsters,
Osiris's Special Ability activates!
Summon Lighting Shot!!
They were all destroyed?!
That means all the Monsters
Special Summoned were destroyed!
That means Obelisk's Attack Power
goes down by 2400 points!
You bastard...!
How dare you make fools of my Monsters
just so you can take a nab at God!
Kaiba! I just turned the difference in
Attack Points between Osiris
and Obelisk once again!
Osiris!!
What?! Obelisk's Attack Points...!
You fool!
The moment you stupidly destroyed
one of my Monsters, Sword of Soul,
you triggered its Special Ability that
increases the Attack Power
of a Monster by 1000 points!
And you can't just take back your order
commanding Osiris to attack!
Counter him, Obelisk!!
Be gone!!
Both gods were stopped in their tracks!
Pity for you, Kaiba.
Your Battle Phase just ended!
What?!
Using the Effect of a Monster
I sent to the Graveyard
to increase Obelisk's Attack Power...
Your tactics are formidable...
But even a trick of that caliber
won't work against me!
The moment you activated the Trap Card,
Power Balance, at the start of your turn...
I discarded this -
Super-Electromagnetic Turtle -
from my hand.
When Super-Electromagnetic Turtle
enters the Graveyard,
all Monsters on the field are affected
by an electrical discharge it gives off.
Using that timing, I can force
the turn's battle to a halt!
So you paralyzed both Obelisk and Osiris in order to end the Battle Phase...!
I place one card face-down
and end my turn!
What an intense battle!
If ya let your guard down
for a second, you're done for!
Stay strong!
Stay strong, Yugi!
How exciting...!
This is exciting!
Yugi, every time I
Duel you it feels this way!
Amidst our intense combat,
both my spirit and body are
brought to their full potential!
And I'm able to
surpass my own limits!
Your very existence pumps
my spirit with adrenaline
that far surpasses any other!
My entire body resonates
with enthusiasm!
But there's no need for two rulers!
You and you alone...!
I will defeat you
with my own two hands!
My turn!!
Yugi, your hand has been
reduced to one card!
Thus, Osiris only has
1000 Attack Points!
There isn't a thing left for you to do!
This time, without a doubt
in my mind, I will prove myself!
It's the end of you!!
Go, Obelisk!!
You shall stand
at the top of all the gods!!
This is my final gamble!
Magic Card, activate!
Textbook of Magic!
By discarding all the cards in my hand,
I am able to
draw one card from my deck.
And if it's a Magic Card,
I am allowed to activate it!
I can't believe you would purposely
bring Osiris's Attack Points to 0...
Now go to hell!
Osiris! Yugi!
Everything rides on this final draw...!
Jounouchi-kun...!
I activate a Magic Card!
What!?
Treasure from Heaven!
It's effect lets both players draw until
they hold six cards in their hand!
Madness...! In this hopeless situation
he was able to draw the
ultimate hand replenishing card?!
Osiris's Attack Points increase
once again to 6000!
Not yet!!
Trap Card, activate!
Life Shaver!!
Dammit...! Osiris's Attack Points
decrease by 3000 points!
Oi! What the hell is that light?!
Yugi!
The destructive power caused by the two gods colliding, Osiris and Obelisk,
caused the field to be engulfed by enormous energy
That massive field of energy has completely surrounded Yugi and Kaiba-kun!
And as he watches in astonishment, Malik's Millennium Rod begins to glow and react to the energy!
As time begins to reverse itself, the two see a vision!
Next time!
"Inherit the Fated Duel"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise