Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Rishid... The darkness of death has come for you...
Bakura...?
I brought a friend.
This is your other half.
A piece of Malik!
Die!
Why don't you stick around a while?
I'm going to kill Rishid.
Then it's your turn.
My arm...!
Bastard!
Those who were chosen by the Millennium Items...
...must settle things in a Dark Game.
My pleasure...
"Dark Malik VS Dark Bakura"
Mai...
Mai!
Jounouchi!
I was really worried!
You alright now, Mai?
Jounouchi, you're a much better Duelist than you used to be.
I'm glad I met you.
Goodbye...
Mai!
MAI!!
Shit...
Wait for me, Mai...
Ra has three Special Abilities...
The Hieratic Text is a text written by the gods.
So why am I able to read it?
But for now, I must focus on coming up with a strategy to beat Ra.
A Dark Duel...
A game of death where the loser dies!
Of course, you'll be the one dieing, Bakura.
Say what you want...
...before the darkness fills your mouth.
If I remember correctly,
Bakura fell against Yugi's Osiris.
Then during the third Duel,
when I crushed that woman...
Well, he was lying
in bed during those events.
Therefore, Bakura hasn't even seen the God Card I hold,
nor does he know what the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra can do!
But...
I can see him.
The soul of my dominate half is beside you, telling you all my secrets!
Saw that, eh?
Yes!
Your alter ego is my partner!
That means I know your entire deck!
But it was weak...
When our personalities changed,
I added many new cards of my own.
And in addition,
I know you're a user of the God Cards.
So what?
Even if you know that much,
you've got no way of countering my god!
Enjoy coming up with a useless strategy!
Now let us begin this Duel, Bakura!
Hold on a minute!
Before we start, your other half has something to say!
What?
Are you the evil self that I created?
Correct.
The darkness that
built a nest in your heart...
Anger...
Hatred...
Pain...
And out of that nest hatched me, the embodiment of your darkest desires!
But Rishid sealed you away...
Even sealed away,
I still helped you by taking away the guilt deep within your heart!
A "thank you" would be nice, you know!
I learned some new information I found to be very interesting through the power of the Millennium Rod.
I learned everything through the girl I brainwashed, Anzu.
My sister told me
the truth of the Ishtars.
Let's start with your bloodbath,
my dear father.
Stop it...!
The truth being that is was you who killed my father!
Hey, hey! You and I
are two minds in one body!
Don't act like you aren't responsible, just because I had the upper hand!
You're just as guilty!
It's true that the idea came from my own heart.
Father... What have I done...?
I feel so bad for you.
Five years ago,
at that very same moment...
You're...!
The one who caused this destiny was the soul of the great Pharaoh.
The Pharaoh will revive soon.
Go search for the Pharaoh, Malik!
The man who appeared
before me that day...
Somehow I thought he was the resurrection of the Pharaoh's soul and that he killed my father.
But that wasn't the case!
So what are you trying to say, my precious dominant half?
Both you and I are both guilty for my father's death, and we will be destroyed together!
Keh! How amusing!
Do your worst!
That turban-wearing man Malik just spoke of...
It had to have been Shadi...
But five years ago he was already...
Let's go, Bakura!
I'll support you with a strategy!
Shut up!
Don't order me around!
All you have to do is come through on our agreement!
I know that.
If you beat him, I'll give you the Millennium Rod.
That's not all. I want you to tell me the secret of the carvings on your back.
I thought putting all seven Millennium Items in the stone slate
would give me the Power of Darkness.
But that's not the case.
Unless I decode the hieroglyphs carved on your back,
the door can't be opened.
Don't think that I don't know.
All right... I promise to tell you!
And one more thing!
As long as you win, you don't care if your body is burned to ashes, right?
I don't care!
I'm glad to hear that!
Now I can kill him without worrying!
Done with your little discussion?
No matter what you two talked about,
you're wasting your time.
Guys like you... I kill instantly!
Start the Dark Duel!
In this Dark Duel, the loser's body and soul will be consumed!
It's the ultimate death game!
Body and soul consumed?
You'll get it soon enough...
DUEL!!
Here goes! I draw a card first!
I'll set a powerful trap in the first round!
I know all about your Occult Deck.
Here I go! I'll set a reverse card!
Then I Summon
Goblin Zombie in Attack Mode!
Turn end!!
My turn! Draw!
I set a reverse card!
I Summon Drillago!
Attack the enemy Monster!
Trap Card, Fearful Earthbound, activate!
Trap!?
Take a look at your feet.
What in the...?
I used a Monster with low Attack Points as a decoy
to activate the trap card,
Fearful Earthbound!
Fearful Earthbound...
Every time the enemy player
attacks one of your Monsters, they'll take 500 points of damage.
I can't stop
my Monster from attacking!
Go ahead and beat
my weakling Monster...
The more Monsters you send to the Graveyard, the stronger my Occult Deck gets!
Only then does its true power shine!
At this moment, the Effect of my Permanent Trap Card is activated!
Earthbound! Chew the player up!!
Sorry to spoil your plans!
Magic Card, activate! Remove Trap!
Thanks to Remove Trap's Effect,
Earthbound is negated!
So you had an anti-trap card...
So, Bakura... Now it's your turn to take a look at yourself.
What?!
What the hell?
Looks like it was you that was bitten!
Just what the hell is going on here?!
This is a Dark Duel
between you and me!
What?
You lost Life Points because of my attack just now.
In this Dark Game,
whenever you lose points...
The darkness eats
the player's body away!
The darkness...?!
So hidden in that darkness is a beast that devours souls...!
Now I see.
This game is going to be rather fun!
And when you lose all your Life Points, you will be eaten by the void, both body and soul!
This is my Death Game!!
Interesting!
So when your Life hits zero, you become a part of the darkness, eh?
Who will annihilate who?
Let's do this, Bakura!
This is...?
This is inside of my heart.
What's going on? I have a bad feeling...
Something's wrong in the Other Me's Soul Room.
It's been a long time since I walked into my other self's room.
Nothing's changed.
It's still a vastly complicated maze.
What's wrong, Partner?
Other me!
Did you sleepwalk into my room?
You scared me!
Sorry about that!
So, what's up?
I felt something strange
from your room.
Yeah, I've been feeling it too.
Before I came here, I didn't understand what it was.
Now I think I've got something.
Huh?
You don't have memories.
So this room is like a map of your soul that isn't sure which path to take.
Partner...
But... one day I'll help get your memory back.
I believe this is my task.
Who will be devoured by the darkness first and be destroyed?
How amusing!
Let's do this, Malik!
Draw!
Choose your cards carefully, Bakura...
I already know your Occult Deck inside out.
If he knows my Occult Combo so well,
I can't use the Ouija Board.
Then...
I'll just have to try a new strategy that Malik has has never seen.
Bring it!
But the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra sleeps in my deck...
It will kill you no matter what you do!
Now! What's wrong?!
Relax!
Malik has one Monster on his field...
Suppose he's already got the God Card in his hand...
If he gets three sacrifices on the field, he'll be able to Summon God...
Don't be afraid of God, Bakura!
Shut up!
You better stay quiet!
Just hear me out!
There is a way to make Ra powerless.
What did you say?!
Hey, hey! Are you two having your "strategy planning time" again?
Let me tell you something. It's futile!
Just hurry up!
I see...
So that's your plan?
Rejoice, Malik!
I'll blast your body apart
using your own advice!
I don't care! Do it!
Damn dominate half...
What'd he tell him?
I'll set two reverse cards!
In addition, I Summon one Wall Monster!
Turn end!
Just what is this guy planning?
But no matter what he does,
It's futile before my God Card!
But, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra is not in my hand...
Card draw!
Then I'll make God come to me using this Magic Card!
Magic Card, activate!
Treasure from Heaven!
A hand reinforcement Magic?!
Correct! We both draw from our decks until we hold six cards in our hand!
Judging by the look on your face, you still haven't drawn the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra into your hand.
Then let me give you a hand!
Reverse card, open! Dying Altogether!
What the hell?
Dying Altogether is a Trap Card that forces us to send our entire hand to the Graveyard,
and then lets us draw five more cards in their place.
And the player who activates this Trap
loses 100 Life Points
for every card he discards
which results in only me
losing Life Points.
Why would he go so far just so I can draw the God Card...?
What's the holdup?!
Just hurry up and draw already!
Still nothing...!
What the hell? You still haven't drawn it?!
You suck!
I set a reverse card
and end my turn!
Do you remember when someone came to this room before?
Shadi!
He used the power of the Millennium Key to see if somewhere in this maze
lied the "true room of my soul" and the door that leads to it.
But in the end, he never was able to find that room.
Yeah... The truth is, I don't even know where the door is myself.
Finding that door in a complicated
maze like this is extremely difficult.
And then Shadi appeared again on the Battle Ship.
All the requirements needed to open the door
to the Pharaoh's memories are gathered aboard this Battle Ship.
The door of the Pharaoh's memory...
Maybe it's just somewhere in this maze...
I wonder if it's really your "true room"?
I can't afford to lose these Duels.
Partner, I'll win for sure!
I'll gather all the requirements
And open my door myself!
Right...
I'll fight for you!
Great.
It's my turn! Card draw!
I got it! I've been waiting for this.
I sacrifice Gelnia!
I Summon the
Puppet Master, Controller of the Dead!
And I activate
Puppet Master's Special Ability!
By the player sacrificing 1000 Life Points as a cost,
they can call back three Monsters from the grave.
But the Monsters Special Summoned by Puppet Master can't attack in the same turn!
I know that! Just calm down!
I'm gonna give you a nice little present.
Using this Magic Card, that is.
What?!
Magic Card, Dark Designator, activate!
Dark Designator is a card that lets you declare a Monster Card name,
and if they have it, the opponent adds the card to their hand.
Are you...?!
I am!
I'm taking the Ra card sleeping in your deck and placing it in your hand!
So how about it?
How does it feel to finally get Ra?
So that's what you're up to...?
I finally get it.
The reason you fools went to such lengths to allow me to draw my God Card.
You left a huge hint lying around on your side of the field.
You lowered your Life Points greatly just to play three weakling Monsters.
And you still have that one reverse card on the field...
You plan to steal my Ra, am I right?
A bit too late to notice now.
Reverse card, open! Exchange, activate!
I knew it...
Because of the effect of Exchange,
both players choose one card from the other's hand and exchange it.
Now! Give me your Ra card!
You took a pretty good card there...
Next turn, I'll let you cower before me
as I play the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra you've been so eagerly anticipating.
"Cower before me"?
I'm afraid not, Bakura!
There's no way you could use Ra!
The only one who can call Ra forth is the one who masters it!
Only the person who can read the ancient letters of the Hieratic Text can Summon the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra.
And there you have it.
To put it bluntly, you're no match for me without the aid of another.
What did you say?!
Forget it. I'll pretend I never saw this.
Talk it up while you can!
Because I'm going to win when all is said and done!
Alright then, let's continue the Duel!
Next turn, we'll Summon the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra,
and it'll kill you!
Bakura-kun finally Summons the Ra card he stole.
But thanks to a Trap only Malik's dark side knew about,
all the sacrificed Monster's Attack Points fall to 0!
So Ra's Attack Power is 0?!
Then, Dark Malik steals the Ra card stolen from him once again!
And then uses the
second Special Ability of Ra!
Next time!
"One Turn Kill"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise