Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
After following Bakura to the underground temple in Kul Elna village,
I learned the secrets of how the Millennium Items were created.
Despite the Millennium Items supposedly being created to maintain peace,
they held such a secret...?!
The resurrected Mahado
was then pushed into a corner by Diabound,
now holding the power of dead spirits!
If this continues...
That's...!
Mana!
"Final Moments of the Thief Bakura"
Master!
Mana... To be saved by you...
You've been studying hard while I was gone.
Yes, sir!
Do not give in!
Shada!
Let me handle this place.
Head to the underground shrine where Pharaoh resides!
Thank you.
We leave this to you, Shada!
Come, vile spirits!
Charge!!
YEAH!!
Mana!
Prince!
The weaklings keep
multiplying one by one...!
Let us go, Mana!
Yes, Master!
Take this, Bakura!
- Thousand Magic Blasts!!
No matter how many of you weaklings there are,
you won't be able to break through
the Spirit Shield's Heka
surrounding Diabound!
Diabound...
...split into three!
Having gained the power of the dead spirits,
Diabound has gained yet another ability!
- Thousand Magic Blasts!!
Such a pity!
All of them missed!
Spirit Wave!!
Prince!
Now take the finishing blow!
Magical Hats!!
What...?!
Diabound! Multiple Strike Attack!!
Prince!
Die, Yugi!!
Pharaoh!
Everyone!
- Pharaoh!
Well, well...
What an honor, Great High Priests.
Are you all right?
I am...
Mahado...!
Isis.
So you've come back, I see.
Yes. My body may no longer exist,
but my soul will always protect the Pharaoh!
Well said, Mahado!
That's why you're the greatest magician in our country!
All of you, save the happiness for after we've beaten Bakura!
Isis, the Pharaoh has very little Ba remaining.
I understand.
Holy Elf!!
A White Magician Ka with the power to restore Ba, huh?
Bakura...!
Pharaoh, you must not fight with your body as it is.
Let the High Priests handle this from here.
To think you'd all stomp on in here
practically laying your Millennium Items at my feet...
This must be what they mean when they say, "Like a moth to a flame."
Bakura, we priests will crush your mad ambitions!
Come forth!!
Curse of Dragon!!
Bring it on, you damn priests!
Diabound! Massacre them!
Surround Diabound!
Attack from all directions!
They did it!
This cannot be! He repelled the attacks?!
It's useless!
I hold the absolute advantage within these grounds.
The souls who hate Akhenamkhanen are wandering all around us.
And they ally with me and Diabound!
None of you are capable of breaking through this Spirit Shield!
It has surfaced...!
That abominable memory...
But this is the place where I will make Seto King.
S-Stay away...!
Ghosts of Kul Elna!
Lord Akhenaden!
Lord Akhenaden, are you all right?
I-I am fine.
The Pharaoh and the others have already gone to where Bakura is.
I must also...
What's wrong, Shada?
What's... this power?
Lord Akehnaden, please wait here.
Shada!
Just what lies down here...?
My Millennium Ankh!
This is...!
This is Diabound's stone slab.
Lord Akhenaden!
Is Diabound the one who created that vision of the future?
So long as this grudge remains, Diabound will be immortal!
However, if we simply destroy this stone slab, Diabound will...
Two-Headed Jackal Warrior!
Lord... Akhenaden...
I will not let scum like you change the future awaiting Seto and I!
What do we do, Seto?
If you're not gonna make a move, allow me to have the pleasure!
Go on, Diabound!
Thousand Poison Fangs!!
Now none of you can replenish your Ba!
Are you all right, Isis?
I-I am fine!
While I'm taking the role of killing these guys...
...I can help Yugi and his pals find the Eighth Key at the same time.
You could call it a coincidence...
But I made the right call to leave one of my clones with them.
Bobasa's starving~!
Don't say that!
You'll make me think about it.
As for those things, they're pretty eerie.
They're gradually increasing in number.
They probably figure they can attack us any time
now that my other self has parted from us.
You think the great Jounouchi-sama's afraid of those things?
Just kidding.
What's the matter, Honda?
Nothing...
Yugi, more importantly, isn't there something we need to be doing right now?
Huh? It's rare to see you being so assertive, Honda.
I-I guess...
Honda's right, though.
If we don't keep searching, we can't be of any help to the other Yugi.
I've been thinking about something, you see.
Our job is to search, but don't you think there's something we're overlooking?
- God...
- Overlooking...?
Honda, you're not making any sense!
No, I think Honda-kun may be right!
Why didn't I realize this sooner?!
No, I realized it from the start!
But I didn't think it was all that important!
What're you talking about, Yugi?
Ever since we came to this world...
No, this entire time, there's been one definite thing we don't know!
Something we haven't
known this entire time?
You mean...?
I do!
The other me's name!
Is that really all that important?
Think back...
Why do you think my other self's name was erased from the stone palette?
Because there's a reason why it had to be erased.
That's right.
This world consists of the other me's memories replaying from 3,000 years ago.
Shadi told us...
About the other me's true enemy, Zorc!
If this world is the same as it was 3,000 years ago,
...and the other me is fated to fight against Zorc...
Don't tell me the other Yugi's name...!
I'm positive that is the key to defeating Zorc.
If I had to guess,
if my other self doesn't obtain his lost name before the final showdown with Zorc...
He can't win this game.
Are you serious?
That's quite the problem!
Let's go look for it immediately!
But where is it?
I mean, the other Yugi said no one in this world knows the Pharaoh's name!
Anyway, let's check the city once again.
We might be able to enter the palace after meeting the other me.
The palace?
It may just be there.
Alright!
Since we've decided on it, let's go!
Hey, wait up, Honda!
Wait up! Don't leave Bobasa behind!
Aura Sword!!
Hey there, now! Take it back!
Eat this!
Our Ka won't even scratch Diabound!
Seto! Let us use the power of the Millennium Scales I possess!
Ka Fusion!
Yes!
Let us combine our Ka and fight him with the power of unity!
My Millennium Scales!
Now is the time to unite our Ka!
I summon thee!
Drake Knight - Duos Dragon!!
Fueled by the power of Mahado, Duos Dragon's attacking force is three-fold!
A fusion between weaklings is hardly any threat to Diabound!
Here goes, Bakura!
Dragon Flame!!
Return their attack, Diabound!
Spiral Wave!!
Their attacking force is equal!
Equal?
What a laugh!
If you guys can fuse your Ka together,
I can fuse my attacks!
Triple Magic Blast Thunder Force!!
What... power...!
Demolish the Duos Dragon, Diabound!
Aura Sword!!
Using a sword in place of a shield...
But how long can you do it...?
Kalim, now!
Dragon Flame!!
Impossible! The Spirit Shield's melting?!
Just a little more, Seto!
If we melt the shield,
we can defeat Diabound!
Hmph! Don't be so sure...
I've still got plenty of Ba
and energy to spare!
Kalim!
This can't be...!
He had another Ka...?!
Without the Millennium Scales, your Ka Fusion will lose its power!
Duos Dragon!
Kalim!
I'm all right...!
The Pharaoh...!
I think I'll put this to use right away!
My Millennium Scales! Fuse together Yushuu with Diabound!
Don't think for a second you scum will be able to silence the anger of these spirits!!
The spirits'... anger?
P-Prince...!
Pharaoh!
It appears it's really time
to settle this, Yugi...
I give the spirits the honor of finishing you!
Come... judge me... spirits.
Pharaoh, what are you trying to do?
Shimon, even if my father, Akhenamkhanen, did not know of this...
...the truth remains that many lives were sacrificed to create the Millennium Items.
For the Millennium Items?
If such a thing ever happened to my friends,
there's no doubt I would also harbor such hatred.
Receiving judgment for the curse
I bear as king is a part of my fate that will never fade!
As he so desires it, take the Pharaoh's soul!
Spirits!!
- Pharaoh!
Prince!
See you in Hell, Yugi!
What the...?!
King Akhenamkhanen...!
Akhenamkhanen...
Impossible... What the hell is happening...?
Diabound!
Father...
Akhenamkhanen's soul is leading the wandering spirits
into the Realm of the Dead.
It's the last of my father's grief and sorrow...
Have you fools forgotten the grudge you have against this guy!?
Don't you want to tear him apart?!
Father!
Father...
Now, Mahado!
Now that Diabound has lost his power...!
You bastard...!
I have eagerly awaited this day, Bakura!
Magic Blast!!
Sleep in the darkness
of 1,000 years, Bakura!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
They did it! They finally beat Bakura!
But Akhenaden suddenly appears looking really strange.
Elsewhere, we arrive at the palace to search for the Pharaoh's name.
We were able to enter the palace this time...
But we can't touch anything and we can't read the hieroglyphs...
Where should we even start to look?
What?! Our bodies won't move!
Next time!
"A New Stage"
Please look forward to it!