Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"The Fiery Dance Battle"
I sure wish it'd stop raining.
Hey Jounouchi, what's up with Shizuka-chan's operation?
Right. Thanks to Yugi, I was able to hire the world's most elite doctor to come heal her eyes.
The operation's gonna be soon.
And you'll be there when it happens?
Not sure...
See, thanks to my dad and mom getting divorced, we've lives separate from each other...
What the hell're ya talkin' about?
You gotta go!
We'll go together.
Why the hell're you coming along?
Shizuka-chan looks completely different than you! She's cute!
You gotta introduce us!
You asshole!
So that's what you were after?!
Anzu!
Ah, Yugi.
Anzu...
Uh, umm...
Are you... free this weekend?
Eh? Y-Yeah...
You see, my other self hasn't been himself recently.
He won't talk to me much either.
I just thought... he'd feel better if he saw you, Anzu!
T-The other Yugi...?
Yeah. Well, I gotta help Grandpa out at the store!
Hold on-
Meet at Domino Station Sunday at 10:00 A.M.!
No way... That all happened so suddenly...
What should I wear?
This stands out too much...
What's up? You're suddenly getting nervous...
Because I promised to meet with Anzu today.
A date?
About time you worked up the guts!
Go for it, Partner!
Though it's a date, it's not gonna be with me.
A date... with the other Yugi...?
I was pretty sure the other Yugi was just another personality that came out through the Millennium Puzzle.
What am I getting so nervous for? Gosh!
The rest is up to you, my other self.
H-hey! What's the meaning of this?!
Yo.
We're just sitting here saying nothing... This is so awkward.
Oh, that's right.
Wanna go check this out?
The Ancient Egypt exhibit!
Why do you want to go there?
S-See? This mark...
It's the same as your Millennium Puzzle, isn't it?
Meaning that puzzle may have some connection to Egypt, right?
Did I say something wrong?
No. It's just that he...
...he put these on in front of the mirror this morning.
I didn't realize it was because of this...
He hides his real self in order to fit in.
Yugi's worried about you, you know...
He's got no need to worry about me.
He doesn't even know what is is he wants himself.
Eh?
Just like I am now, he's looking for who he really is.
Who he really is?
Who am I?
Where did I come from?
I don't know how to find this out.
Just like I thought, the Yugi in front of me is an entirely different personality than the usual Yugi.
So he's been living within the Millennium Puzzle...
But that's just fine.
It's fine the way I am now.
I myself don't know exactly who I am...
Everyone's like that.
For example, I told you that I dream of becoming a dancer,
and that I want to head to America after graduating school, right?
Yeah...
Even now, that dream is getting closer and closer to me.
Time's running out, you know?
It's alright.
I know you'll realize your dream, Anzu.
I know myself it won't be an easy dream to obtain.
But if there's even the slightest chance of me realizing it,
I wanna believe in it!
Let's go, Yugi!
Let's go walk the city!
Even you will find out who you are! Come on!
Where are we going, Anzu?
It doesn't really matter where we go.
"Duel Monsters"
I didn't know there was a card shop here...
You didn't know?
It just opened recently.
Oh?
Wanna go inside?
Yeah!
"Duel Monsters Booster Packs"
I can't decide what to buy!
This is the happiest he's been all day...
Oh! This is sweet!
Lightforce Sword, huh?
I got a good card!
Good for you!
My partner's gonna be thrilled!
Let's go there next!
Over there!
You did it!
Hey, what do you wanna play?
Nice! That's the stuff!
Shit!
Johnny!
Wow! He wiped the floor with 'im!
Yeah! That's cuz Step Johnny's the best!
Who's next?!
Who wants to challenge me?!
Dance Battle Game, huh...?
Hey~! Sounds fun!
Oh! Baby!
Wanna battle me?
There's no reason to face him.
I can't run from a challenge to dance!
Not even you can stop me now!
Hey! Anzu!
It'll be fine!
Nice to meet you!
You sure got some guts.
Sweetheart, you're cute!
Don't lose to Johnny!
Well, let's just have fun.
I'm not gonna hold back.
I don't need you to hold back!
Really?
In that case, come hang out with me tonight if I win.
Oh wait...
That's what you were really after, ain't it?
You're pissing me off.
Music! Standby!
GO!
She's amazing!
Yeah! She's matching his steps perfectly!
She's really a good match for Johnny!
That's low, Step Johnny!
Nice one, sweety!
Not bad, Anzu.
A miss?!
Someone as great as me?!
Wow, you serious?!
The chick's freakin' amazing!
Johnny's in trouble!
Oh no...!
She owned Step Johnny!
That was fun!
I can't believe spending 100 yen on a game could renew my dream this much.
Your dream, huh...?
I can maintain that dream even if I don't go after it.
You really think that's a good idea?
I want to know more about myself... Where I came from.
But if I keep things the way they are, I'll always be with him.
He must want it this way, too.
The other Yugi has already discovered his other self...
I wish the other Yugi will always be here, too...
But...
Even if you have two hearts,
you must take control of your own heart.
So be true to yourself and your heart.
Hey!
You're not gettin' away like this.
The game is over!
Well, let's have a Duel this time.
A Duel?
If I lose the Duel, I'll give up.
Or else, you'll be my girlfriend.
Come on now...
I'll play with you.
It's none of your business!
You just wanna show off in front of her, that it?!
How about you leave this to me?
Forget it! She's mine anyway.
But if I win, you'll never show up
in front of Anzu ever again.
That is, if you can beat me and my Street Duel Strategy!
Why do you dance?
Ain't it obvious? To be popular, of course!
And to pick up nice chicks.
She's bet her dreams on dancing!
I will not let you defile Anzu's dream!
Don't say such stupid shit!
You can't be a true dancer.
Here goes!
Duel!!
I'm first.
Sound Maiden, in Attack Position!
Turn over.
My turn.
Good!
I'm gonna use this to defeat you!
Elf's Swordsman!
Battle! Use your "Elf's Slash" move to destroy the Sound Maiden!
Using a sword on woman...
That's too much.
Then it's my turn now!
My cute Water Dancer baby, in Attack Mode!
What the? It's just a Fan Deck?
Fan Deck?
A deck not really used to win.
They are cards that evolve from
the player's own interest.
His cards are all about dancing
If you underestimate them,
you got it coming!
I'll show a Duel I put my entire soul into.
Be sure to watch!
Then show me...
This "soul" you speak of!
I end my turn without doing anything.
Spirits of the Harp in Defense Position!
Then the Magic Card,
Chorus Sanctuary!
This card's Attack effect
of any Monster in Defense Mode by 500 points.
Turn over.
I thought he was hopeless
But I saw his honesty
in the way he plays.
But a Duel is a Duel!
Let's finish this once and for all.
Step Johnny! Your showtime's over!
Curse of Dragon! Attack Position!
Go! Battle!
Hell Flame!!
Oh no! I forgot to use Defense!
How dumb is this guy?
What happened to that "soul" of yours?
It's not over yet!
My stage is only getting started!
Here goes!
Witch of the Black Forest in Defense Position!
What? He's not using a Fan Deck anymore?
I'm gonna use this.
I activate the Magic Card Fusion!
To fuse Witch of the Black Forest with High Priestess!
I Summon the Musician King!
Battle! I attack the Elf Swordsman!
Elf's Swordsman was...!
Musician King puts his whole soul into that guitar!
Looks like I can start looking forward to my night with the babe over there.
I set one card on the field and end my turn.
You can do it, Yugi.
My turn!
I use Curse of Dragon to attack the Musician King!
Got you!
Activate Trap!
What?
Metal Conversion - Magic Reflection Armor!
This card transforms Musician King into Heavy Metal King and powers it up!
He's gonna play a nice tune for ya!
Now you got no Monsters left!
Is he really this strong?
Giant Soldier of Stone in Defense Mode!
Turn over.
You seemed so arrogant, but ain't ya weak?
It's my turn again!
Metal Conversion doesn't just increase his Attack Power!
Go! Heavy Metal King!
Attack and destroy the Giant Soldier of Stone!
The giant solider too...Giant Soldier of Stone as well...!
It adds half the attacked Monster's Attack Points to the equipped Monster's Attack Strength.
I'm well aware of it!
My turn!
I Summon Black Magician in Attack Mode!
Black Magician, attack the Heavy Metal King!
Idiot! Have you forgotten?
I've got Metal Conversion's Effect here!
Black Magician is doomed!
Are you... misinterpreting something?
What?
Metal Conversion's Effect!
''Heavy Metal King'' is defeated!
Why? Why didn't Metal Conversion's Effect activate!?
When the Monster equipped with this card attacks,
half of the opponent's Attack Points
will be added to its own Attack Power.
In other words,
When Heavy Metal King attacks...
Black Magician's Attack Power is halved and added to your Monster.
The Effect doesn't activate when I'm the one attacking,
and so it keeps its original 2500 Attack Points.
You were too careless, Step Johnny.
I don't believe it...
Who are you?! What's your name?!
Yugi...
It's Yugi Mutou!
I've heard that name from somewhere...
The man who beat Pegasus in the Duelist Kingdom?
That Yugi?!
Try and beat me in this game, though I don't plan on losing.
It's your turn.
I quit! I quit!
How can I defeat
the Duelist Kingdom winner?
You always run away.
If you have the time to pick up "chicks",
why not spend more time
on what you do best?! Like dancing!
I should bet everything on my dancing?
You're better at dancing
than you are at Dueling.
What do you know?
I know what I'm good at better than anyone.
Being a pro dancer
is a faraway dream.
Have you been to any auditions?
Yes.
How many?
One.
One?!
You gave up after one try?
You don't know how it feels to be a loser!
I've failed more than a dozen times!
You too?
But I never gave up.
Because running away
does not solve the problem.
Pace yourself and the future will open up to you, right?
I see... you also...
Well...
I'll try again.
Try your best!
I sounded a bit arrogant back there, didn't I?
Nope.
Let's go to the Ancient Egyptian exhibit.
There are clues about my past here.
I must go in here.
But I feel like my heart's resisting me.
Like I'm afraid to learn the truth.
But today...
I made the decision to do this after meeting with you, Anzu.
Yugi.
Who am I? Where am I from?
The answers are here.
Let's go!
Yes! Lift your head up high!
"Preview"
We went to the museum
to find a clue about his lost memory.
We saw a 3000-year-old
stone tablet there.
On it is an image or a Pharaoh
that looks exactly like Yugi!
The other Yugi is sure that
he is the soul of that pharaoh.
What exactly is this "battle to regain my memories" about that's starting up?
Next time! "This Town Becomes Battle City"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...