Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
I'm going to activate this card from my hand!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Darkness Within Yugi -
Timaeus Disappears"
Obtain the power of Orichalcos!
Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Her Attack Power rises by 500 points!
Because her Attack Strength has now changed, the Crystal Seal is destroyed!
Why would Timaeus...?
I got you.
The power of Orichalcos and the power of the Legendary Dragons...
In other terminology, the very powers of light and darkness!
They cannot coexist together.
Now, the source of my uneasiness is gone.
Timaeus...
But I still have the power to Summon up to ten Monsters with increased Attack Power onto the field.
The Barrier of Orichalcos...
Even if this is a trap,
I can only use this power to continue fighting!
I activate a Magic Card known
as Hand Control!
Hand Control is a card that allows one to declare the name of a card in the opponent's hand.
And I can then forcefully activate it.
I know the card you are after is the Necromancy I now hold in my hand.
Use it then, Yugi!
I activate the effect of Necromancy!
Four Monsters in my Graveyard are Summoned back to the field in Defense Position!
Come out!
Big Shield Gardna!
Berfomet!
Illusion Beast Gazelle!
Kuribabylon!
Then I sacrifice Gazelle and Berfomet!
Come forth! Black Magician!
In addition, the Special Effect of Kuribabylon!
Undo the combination, Kuribabylon!
My Monsters, take in the powers of Orichalcos!
Because of the power of Orichalcos,
The ATK of each Kuriboh increases by 500 points too!
And then, I activate the Special Effect of Kuriba!
Show yourself again, Kuribabylon!
The Attack Power of Kuribabylon is decided by the total Attack Points of the Kuribohs used to form it.
Also, Kuribabylon itself can also take in the power of Orichalcos!
So its ATK is now 4500 points!
It's got 4500 Attack Points?
What an amazin' array a' powerful Monsters!
And he Summoned them all in a flash!
Indeed, a card like The Barrier of Orichalcos...
Is really a powerful card!
This is the power of Orichalcos...?
No, this is your power.
Where am I?
No, don't!
Other Me!
Guardian Kay'est is a Monster that cannot be attacked.
If so, Kuribabylon, attack Guardian Grarl!
Guardian Grarl...!
Now that you have a Monster in your Graveyard,
the continuous effect of Purity of the Cemetery is destroyed.
My Black Magician and Black Magician Girl have yet to attack.
Go! Black Magician!
I activate the Quickplay Magic, Divine Protection of the Deceased!
What?
Divine Protection of the Deceased is a card that, when my Monster gets destroyed,
allows me to discard two cards from my hand.
Even if it's the opponent's turn, I can activate this card to negate the Battle Phase.
Yugi!
Yugi...?!
Impossible!
Wh-Why would Yugi have the mark of Orichalcos on his forehead?
You guys came too?
Haga-kun and Ryuzaki-kun?
I was wondering where you two went. You came here?!
Why?! Why does Yugi have the same crest as those people?!
Th-That's obviously because he used that!
Used that?
He used their card?
Hey! Let go of him!
Just like Haga said, 'cause a' Exchange, they swapped their hand cards!
Get... off...! Stop... it...!
How can that be?
Yugi...
Looks like you didn't expect me to be able to use The Barrier of Orichalcos so easily, huh?
You've made a grave miscalculation.
You'll come to regret ever handing me the Orichalcos Barrier card!
As expected of the nameless Pharaoh.
In just one turn,
you've utilized all of the powers of The Barrier of Orichalcos.
My Monsters...
Lend me your powers!
My turn!
Eatos...
Magic Card! Reincarnation of the Dead!
Reincarnation of the Dead allows one Monster in the Graveyard to return to the deck.
I will return Guardian Grarl back to my deck!
You really don't want any Monsters to be sent to the Graveyard, huh?
Next, I set a face-down card on the field.
Up next! A Magic Card!
I activate the Swords of Sealing Light!
Now Yugi can't attack in the next three turns.
His attacks are sealed.
Even so, this Rafael fella's really puttin' up a good fightin' 'gainst Yugi's attacks!
Yugi...
My turn!
I sacrifice Big Shield Gardna!
To Summon Catapult Turtle!
Catapult Turtle's Effect works by sacrificing a Monster on the field.
I can inflict direct damage to your Life Points equivalent to half the sacrificed Monster's Attack Power!
Swords of Sealing Light can't interfere with this!
Permanent Trap Card! Sacrifice Limiter!
What?!
With Sacrifice Limiter in play, each player can only sacrifice one Monster per turn.
In this turn, since you've already sacrificed one Monster to Summon Catapult Turtle,
you are unable to tribute any more Monsters!
I end my turn.
My turn.
Magic Card! Nightmare Binding!
What...?
Nightmare Binding... It deducts 800 points off the ATK of a Monster.
And adds that 800 points to my Life Points.
In addition, the targeted Monster cannot be sacrificed.
Even if I can't use Kuribabylon as a sacrifice,
it doesn't change the fact that I'll win!
My turn!
I'll use Catapult Turtle to launch Black Magician!
Go! Black Magician!
Because Black Magician is now in the Graveyard,
Black Magician Girl's Attack Points will go up!
Why? Yugi...
What's wrong, Rafael?
The outcome is obvious.
In the next turn, with just one more attack, your Life Points will be completely drained!
My turn!
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
It's about time we settle this, Rafael.
I use Black Magician Girl as a sacrifice!
Don't do that, Other Me!
You can't do that!
Have you forgotten the promise you've made with Black Magician Girl?
Eat this!
Magic Card, Shrink!
WHAT!?
He's using that Magic Card to decrease the impact!
What persistence.
But now your Life Points are lower than mine.
The Swords of Sealing Light will expire this turn.
In the next turn, Catapult Turtle will sacrifice itself,
and your Life will become 0.
It'll be my victory.
Amazing!
It's obvious that Yugi-kun's gonna win!
That's Yugi for ya!
Isn't that right, Jounouchi?
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
No...
That person isn't Yugi!
Sacrificing your Monsters one by one for the sake of winning...
A True Duelist wouldn't do that!
The other me...
The darkness inside his heart is becoming stronger...
You want to win.
You want to win, don't you?
No matter who is it, or whatever means it may take...
What a sight, Nameless Pharaoh.
How do you feel about
your impending victory?
You've proven well.
Hmm...?
You've proven that darkness exists in your heart as well.
Nameless Pharaoh.
Your eagerness to win has caused you to fall into this trap.
What are you saying?!
The Barrier of Orichalcos is a card whereby
the stronger the darkness in your heart is, the more power you can get from it.
Haven't you noticed?
Look carefully at what's on your field!
Your persistence to win has turned these lovely Monsters ugly.
You've become a slave for more power!
What have I done to the Monsters...?!
You activated The Barrier of Orichalcos, sealing away the power of Timaeus with your own hands.
The legendary power in the world of Duel Monsters...
But you didn't even know that what I feared was that very power of the Legendary Dragon!
What?!
My turn!
Our fates will depend on what I draw this round!
Eatos...
You're finally in my hand.
Equipment Magic! Sacred Sword of Goddess!
Come forth, Guardian Eatos!
So she's the aura who's been protecting him all this time...!
The Special Effect of Guardian Eatos!
Soul of the Sacred Sword!!
Wh-What's going on?
My body is moving on its own!
Yugi!
The Special Effect of Guardian Eatos...
It removes from play every Monster in the opponent's Graveyard, and she will absorb their combined Attack Points!
What did you say?!
The first!
It shall be Black Magician Girl!
Black Magician Girl...
The second card is Black Magician!
Black Magician...
The third is Big Shield Gardna!
The fourth is Illusion Beast Gazelle!
The fifth one is Berfomet!
Nameless Pharaoh...
Think hard.
What have you done to these Monsters?
The darkness in your heart has sent these Monsters to their deaths!
Don't stare at me...!
Don't stare at me with those eyes!
The darkness in your heart has enabled Eatos to reach her full potential!
Her Attack Power is...!
10000?!
No way!
Yugi!
O Nameless Pharaoh!
Bear the wrath of these Monsters!
Guardian Eatos attacks!!
Gospel of Truth!!
Yugi-kun!
Yugi!
Other Me!!
Nameless Pharaoh...
You've lost the most important thing in this Duel.
You shall now become an offering for the revival of our God!
Farewell, Nameless Pharaoh!
Other Me!
Yes, with this..!
Partner!
I believe in you, Other... Me...
Partner!!
Yugi was...
...defeated...!
This can't...!
Yugi...
Yugi... Yugi!
I'll take this back.
Yugi!
Take him!
Yugi-kun!
Jounouchi!
I'll return in good time to take your soul as well!
Please look forward to that day!
Bastard!! Get back here!
Pull yourself together!
Yugi-kun!
H-Hey!
Yeah, I know!
Yugi-kun...
Get a grip on yourself, Yugi!
Yugi!
You're conscious!
Are you alright?!
Thank goodness, I was so worried about you!
What's wrong, Yugi?
I'm...
...not "alright"...!
What are you talking about?
Aren't you fine?
In my stead, Partner has...
If that's the case...
The one who's soul got sealed was...
I... I...
Partner!
Partner!!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Yugi lost?
No way! You're lying!
The Yugi that always emerges victorious regardless of how tough it may be...
He actually got defeated, I can't believe it!
The other Yugi is suffering from the loss...
But you're the only one who can stop Doma
and get back the soul of our usual Yugi!
Please, stand up again!
Next, "The Torn Soul"
Duel standby!