Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
We finally arrived at the final battlefield.
The temple of Doma.
It's a place that holds trapped souls from over a time span of 10,000 years.
Partner... Jounouchi-kun...
And everyone else!
We will stop Dartz and his desires without fail!
And we will free everyone's souls in the process!
Kaiba... We have to go all out in this Duel!
"The Tragedy of Atlantis"
The Holy Water Metropolis, Atlantis...
Atlantis was a remarkable city.
Long before I ruled over the land as king,
its citizens received their strength from the Earth and from the spirits.
As we began to spontaneously grow, we became a bountiful metropolis seemingly overnight.
And there, without a care in the world...
...nor greed...
...we were at last content.
But then, once...
...a massive, black dragon appeared and swallowed the sun.
...and the Orichalcos was born.
The Orichalcos...?
So something buried deep within the globe led to its advancement...
The Orichalcos gave our planet an enormous treasure...
At least, that is what we thought at first...
That is because all of our energy, necessities and industrial goods...
Everything we used began depending on that miraculous substance.
As I took the throne as king, the civilization of Atlantis entered a period of advancement beyond imagination...
Yet, I did not notice...
Not me...
Nor did my father, Ironheart...
Quietly and slowly... The hearts of my citizens began to become corrupted.
You're related to Ironheart?!
So you're saying this "Orichalcos" began to corrupt the hearts of the citizens?
Yes.
The desire to satisfy oneself comes with it great irony.
Within lies a breeding ground for the darkness of a person's heart to feed.
No different than the people of today's society.
Pollution has spread all over the world.
Distracted by the convenience of modern technology,
people have forgotten the importance of communication between the Earth and the spirits.
Giving up their faith for modern beliefs, the people have begun to lose all emotions.
Humanity knows not the limitations of their cruelty towards nature.
And they are faced with conflict...
...as their peace is suddenly brought to a halt.
Hiyori! What's wrong?!
Come back!
Why...?
Why has this happened?
I realized everything in an instant...!
The Orichalcos was not meant as a miraculous source of technology!
Instead, it cultivates the darkness within the hearts of human beings...
...and after consuming them,
new life is created from within.
The Orichalcos is a cursed substance that was created in order to test this planet and the human beings that inhabit it.
To test human beings?
Human beings shall destroy themselves by the very same darkness that plagues their hearts.
The Orichalcos is but a substance that hastens the process.
Dartz! You must throw away the Orichalcos!
It has changed our civilization...
But that is of no concern!
We must live among the spirits as we did long ago!
We must return to the traditions of the past, Dartz!
It is too late now, Father.
Even if we were to abandon the Orichalcos, those infected would not return to normal.
Dartz...
Father, I have come up with a verdict.
For I have heard the voice of this planet from within the Orichalcos.
What did you just say?!
Why is it that human beings alone are
blessed with that called "wisdom"?
And why is it that very same "wisdom" exceeded itself, resulting in "imagination"?
That is because... the people of this planet require such gifts in order to protect it.
The Earth sent Orichalcos in order to test its inhabitants.
However, the end result of that test was failure.
As such, Earth granted me a mission.
I am to usher in the God of Orichalcos' descent...
...and send these frivolous humans to their demise!
After which, I am to create new human beings from scratch.
A mission of such aptitude.
And I have been handed this power in order to do so.
Father, what is the meaning of this?
In order to ensure the advent of the Orichalcos God, I require an abundance of souls.
Have you gone mad, Dartz...?!
We are to begin a spiritual ceremony crossing the very voids of history!
We aim to call forth the God of Orichalcos within our planet!
If we seek help from the spirits from our previous era,
they are bound to grant us their strength!
This must be the link to the Spirit World!
O Divine Spirits! Please grant us power!
They foolishly pleaded for the Spirits' aid.
They borrowed the power of what you have come to know as "Duel Monsters",
as they defied me and sought my destruction.
That's... the battle at the Stone Wilderness.
Shortly after, my father sealed the door to the Spirit World.
Any of the remaining spirits' souls were locked away in various locations around the world.
Then I waited.
For a long period of 10,000 years.
However, the world began to rot all over again as human beings repeated the same mistakes they did in the past.
So I once again aimed to call forth the God of Orichalcos,
and I decided to destroy the remaining traces of those Duel Monsters vermin!
But you've already been defeated by the attack of our Master of Dragon Knight!
Seto... Nameless Pharaoh...
From this point forward, you shall personally experience my power first-hand.
Yugi!
Brother!
Impossible! Dartz's Life wasn't affected at all!
This is Orichalcos Kyutora's Special Ability...
It holds the power to make all damage done onto me through a Monster's strike in battle zero.
No way...! Even though that was my brother's and Yugi's most powerful attack...
So that means he takes no damage?!
Be reborn!
Orichalcos Gigas!
Be careful, Kaiba! That Monster increases its Attack Power whenever it's destroyed!
Nameless Pharaoh... Seto... It is futile!
Neither of you are capable of defeating me.
It is my turn!
I am unable to draw another card due to the Effect of Orichalcos Gigas.
However, I can activate this card from my hand...
The next form of power born
from the blackest of darkness!
Orichalcos Deuteros!
What... is this...?
The second Barrier of Orichalcos...!
What is...?!
It's the second barrier of the Orichalcos!
The "second" barrier...?
Orichalcos Deuteros...
As per the effects of this boundary,
my Life is replenished by 500 points for every Monster I control on the field during every one of my turns.
I hold two Monsters on my field.
As such, I receive a 1000 point restoration to my Life.
So it's a Life Restoration barrier, huh?
Furthermore, Orichalcos Gigas...
Declare an attack against Master of Dragon Knight!
The heck?
He's gonna use a 1400 Attack Monster to attack the 5000 Attack Master of Dragon Knight?
Go forth, Orichalcos Gigas!
Fight back!
Master of Dragon Knight!
I invoke the Effect of Orichalcos Kyutora!
I receive no damage.
I get it! The bastard purposely attacked with Orichalcos Gigas!
Just so he could raise its Attack Power!
But even if he continues to increase Orichalcos Gigas' Attack Power...
...Master of Dragon Knight's Attack Power is far beyond it.
It looks to me as if he's purposely trying to get us to attack that Monster...
It couldn't...
Does it hold another Ability we're not aware of...?
My turn! Draw!
So long as that thing's here, we can't attack any of his other Monsters...
And even if we defeat that Orichalcos Gigas, it'll only come back with more Attack Points.
I must admit that it's a pretty formidable battle lineup.
But Dartz!
It's impossible for you to beat us in a direct assault!
I set one face-down card!
Then...
...I Summon Blade Knight!
When I have one or fewer cards in my hand,
Blade Knight's Attack Power rises by 400 points!
I'll end my turn like this.
Are you setting something up, Kaiba?
Yugi, you only have one chance.
My turn! Draw!
At this very moment...
...I sacrifice the Monster I have in play in order to activate this Quick-Play Magic!
Energy Reflect!
Yugi, go now! Use Master of Dragon Knight to attack him from over there!
Energy Reflect allows you to Direct Attack the enemy player!
From his blind spot over there, Orichalcos Kyutora can't do anything!
Kaiba...
Here it comes, Dartz!
I attack you with Master of Dragon Knight!
Galaxy Crusher!!
They did it! He's about to receive a 5000 Attack Power Direct Attack!
This'll end it!
What...?!
The second... Barrier of Orichalcos is...!
The second ability of Orichalcos Deuteros...
That is, by sacrificing a Monster on my side of the field...
...any attack will be nullified.
And in addition, the attacking Monster shall be destroyed!
The one attacking...
...is Master of Dragon Knight!
-Yugi!
Big Brother!
Quick-Play Magic! Fusion Cancel!
So you dodged it by a hair...
So we can't even use Direct Attacks with the second barrier in play...?
But we still have some of the mightiest Monsters on the field.
Is that what you believe?
What?
I know all.
People's weaknesses and their despair...
And of course, the both of you are no exception.
Your greatest weaknesses lie within yourselves!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Ritual Magic, Orichalcos Mirror!
I send the Time Eater in my hand as an offering...
...which allows me to Special Summon Mirror Knight Calling from my deck!
Moreover, as a result of Mirror Knight Calling's Effect...
I Special Summon "Mirror Knights" to the field!
He brought four Monsters out at the same time!
And at this moment in time, I hold six Monsters on my field.
As a result of Orichalcos Deuteros' effects, I regain 3000 Life Points!
No way...!
500 Attack Points?
However, that is but the switch for the Barrier of Orichalcos!
I did tell you...
Your greatest weaknesses lie within yourselves!
Don't tell me...!
Correct. The Attack Power of the Mirror Knights is determined by the Monsters they are facing in battle!
Yugi!
But that's weird!
If they have the same Attack Points, then his Monsters should also be...!
Those shields...!
Yes. So long as they hold these shields...
...the Mirror Knights shall not be killed.
And as long as I have the Mirror Knight Calling,
their shields will continue to reform.
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Life-Shaving Card Treasure!
This card's effects allow me to draw five new cards from my deck!
As per its risks, after five turns...
...my entire hand is sent to the Graveyard!
I activate Silent Death from my hand!
I Summon a Monster from my Graveyard in Defense Position!
Resurrect!
Blade Knight!
I then sacrifice Blade Knight!
In order to Summon Kaiser Glider!
And then I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
Kaiser Glider is a card that cannot be destroyed when it battles against a Monster holding the same Attack Power it has.
I suppose you deserve a bit of credit for your quick thinking.
Our Monsters are facing Monsters that automatically have the same Attack Power...
We can't act carelessly around them...
My turn! Draw!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force...
With this...
I set a reverse card!
Then I Summon Big Shield Gardna in Defense Mode and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
As per the effects of Orichalcos Deuteros, my Life will recover by 1000 points!
His Life rose above 10000...
But Dartz... The next time you declare an attack, every single one of your Monsters will be destroyed...!
I use this moment to activate a Trap Card!
If I destroy Mirror Knight Calling, the Immortality Ability of your Mirror Knights will disappear!
Go! Destruction Ring!!
What the hell?!
Wha-?! Partner!!
Jounouchi!
Mai-san and Pegasus too!
If I had activate Mirror Force, Partner and the others would have...
It would appear that you guys have forgotten.
The fact that every soul I have captured is under my control.
The four Mirror Knights Dartz Summoned were really the stolen souls of Yugi and the others!
What a low method to use against us, Dartz!
Now the other Yugi can't attack!
Kaiba-kun ignores the fact and aims to attack anyway, but the Mirror Knights protect one another!
Is there a way to get out of this pinch?!
Next time!
"The Captive Mirror Knights"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other