Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
I lost my partner and...
Due to my anxiety, I fell into Haga's trap.
In an emotional and uncontrollable state...
I defeated Haga.
I knew very well that this wouldn't bring back Partner.
Suddenly, the train that was carrying us derailed...
...and fell into the valley!
"Battle! The Two Yugis"
Hmm?
The Nameless Pharaoh's presence disappeared.
You don't think he's dead...?
No.
Some unidentified power is concealing the Pharaoh's presence from me.
Then let me be your eyes, Lord Dartz.
I will locate the
nameless Pharaoh without fail.
Other Me!
Partner!
I believe in you, Other... Me...
Partner!!
A dream?
I should be...
Anzu...
Anzu!
Where am...?
Are we still alive?
Anzu!
What's this?
Stop it, Sunny!
That's rude to our guests!
You are...?
I'm Kris.
And this is Sunny.
I'm glad that both of you are fine.
It's really a miracle that both of you didn't get a single injury after falling from such a high place, hm?
You're both awake.
Who are you...?
My name is Ironheart.
I am a guardian of this valley.
Here. These are yours, right?
That's a really rare card.
I can't use this card anymore.
Yugi...
Then I'll hold on to it for now.
Speaking of which, where is Haga?
Uh, did you happen to see another person?
A boy wearing glasses with a big head.
I've placed him in a town at the foot of the hill.
He wasn't the same as you two; his body was as cold as a dead person.
It was as though his soul was taken away.
His soul really was taken away.
And I was the one who did it.
The darkness in my heart is what made me.
Long ago, bounded by love and knowledge, humans were as one with the land.
The land was overflowing with tenderness and kindness.
No matter where you looked, no human being was alone.
Times have really changed.
On you, I feel a sense of overwhelming loneliness that you can't get away from.
I lost my irreplaceable partner.
I...
I'm on a journey to find that soul.
What will you do after finding it?
I don't know.
I just want to tell him that I'm sorry.
Then, follow me.
Anzu!
Be careful.
Even wild beasts lose
their footing in this area.
There is a place called the "Stone Wilderness" ahead of us.
Stone Wilderness?
The fragments of human souls usually reside on such things.
Like the flowers or trees that person has touched before, or the land he has walked on before.
The Stone Wilderness...
It's said to be a place where souls still wandering this world gather.
Will my partner's soul be there?
But over at the place, a lot of evil spirits gather too.
Once you step in there, there's no guarantee that you can come out alive.
But even so, you'll still want to go there?
I...
...want to see Partner.
Where did he go?
Is he still alive?
This is Stone Wilderness?
That is...?
That's the center of the Stone Wilderness.
It's a place that reflects what's inside of your heart.
If I go there, I'll see my partner?
Yes.
Yugi!
You can't go!
It's the nest of the dead from here onwards.
If you don't have an iron will, you can't return alive.
Yugi...
That's...
They are vengeful spirits attracted by his presence.
I believe in you...
Partner...
It's appearing.
The thing that is reflected from inside his heart.
Other Me...
Partner!
Yugi!
Why are you here?
I wanted to see you no matter what.
See me? In such an empty shell?
Partner...
I'm at a total loss.
I don't know what is right or wrong anymore.
When you were around, I could sense it.
That gentle and understanding heart.
I'm just a lifeless being now.
I'll just hurt others if I continue fighting.
Just like what he... what Rafael said.
Nameless Pharaoh...
There should be "darkness" that lies dormant within the deepest thresholds of your heart.
Can you dare say that you were a good king?
There's a great "darkness" that is asleep in my heart.
I'm afraid to even get my memories back.
My other self.
Did you come to see me just so you could say those pathetic things?
Partner...
Was your soul brought back to this world just so you could spout depressing words?
Partner...?
I knew this day would come.
I knew the day I'd fight against you would come!
That's now!
Wa-wait!
If you're really corrupted by the darkness in your heart...
Then I'll need to defeat you here!
Your Dueling skills are really much stronger than me.
But I'll defeat you.
And once I do, this will be
our eternal goodbye!
Partner...
Now! On guard!
Nameless Pharaoh!
Duel!!
Yugi...
Nameless Pharaoh.
Eh?
By guidance of the stars, we knew that you two were coming.
We also know how the Nameless Pharaoh is trying to get back his other half.
Who are you two?
We can only count on him to take care of the rest.
Because he is the savior who is chosen by the two worlds.
Yugi is a savior?
But this will have to wait until he defeats the darkness in his heart.
If not, his soul will wander in this place forever.
Here I go!
My turn!
I Summon a Monster in Defense Position!
Now it's your turn, Other Me.
Partner is...
My turn!
I Summon Illusion Beast Gazelle!
I use Gazelle to attack
the Monster in Defense!
The same Monster?
Don't tell me...
My turn.
I Summon another Monster
in Defense Position!
My turn, draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Fusion!
I Special Summon Winged Phantom Beast Chimera!
Then I Summon Magnet Warrior Alpha!
Magnet Sword!!
Chimera, attack!
Chimera Impact Dash!
I think both of us have the same cards in our hands.
If so, he should have had Resurrection of the Dead in his hand during the previous turn as well.
If he used that to revive Gazelle, he could have Summoned Chimera.
A single mistake will determine the outcome of this Duel.
Partner is really too naive.
Due to Critter's Effect, I can add one Monster with an Attack Power of 1500 or less from my deck to my hand.
And I can reshuffle my deck.
Partner...
My turn.
I set one card face-down.
I use the Magic Card, Hand Obliteration!
Partner...!
With this, I'll have different cards in my hand than you!
Stop it, Partner!
It's meaningless for us to fight against each other!
Why would you say that?
But it's true, isn't it?
You're indeed really strong, Other Me.
At first glance, you appear perfect. But I can tell...
Your weakness - the darkness in your heart!
The darkness in my heart?
That's right.
You're actually really proud deep down in your heart...
You maintain your pride...
And when anything happens, you'll just do what you want to do.
But that's not right!
The human heart isn't capable of making decisions based on just one value.
If you're unable to recognize when you harm yourself...
...and if you aren't aware of the darkness in your opponent's heart...
It's impossible for you to understand the pain and sorrow of others.
For Haga-kun and even Mai-san...
No, even the three Musketeers of Doma...
You can't hear the cries of those suffering!
Everyone's... suffering...!
That's right.
But the present you won't be able to save anyone.
You're just afraid of hurting yourself.
A coward like you wouldn't be able to do it!
How could a person like you ever call himself a king?
Don't make me laugh!
Stop!
I don't want to fight with you anymore!
Why would I have such a card in my deck?
Right now, I'm a mirror that reflects the darkness in your heart.
That's why I would have this card in my deck.
This card...
That's...!
The Barrier of...
...Orichalcos!
Yugi has activated The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Grandpa...
Yes.
Let's put an end to this, Nameless Pharaoh!
Partner...
Now, because of Hand Obliteration, you need to discard the cards in your hand and draw again.
I play a Magic Card! Resurrection of the Dead activates!
Revive! Black Magician Girl!
Next, I Summon Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Now, my Monsters!
Stop!
Absorb the powers of the Orichalcos!
Elf Swordsman, attack Magnet Warrior Alpha!
Black Magician Girl, Black Burning!!
Due to the Special Effect of Chimera, I can Summon Berfomet in Defense Position!
Go on, it's your turn.
I...
...Summon Big Shield Gardna in Defense Position!
With these, I should be able to survive Black Magician Girl's attacks.
My turn!
I Summon Queen's Knight in Attack Position!
Next I activate a Magic Card, Spellbook of Black Magic!
The Attack of Black Magician Girl increases by 500 points!
She's got 3000 Attack Points?!
Queen's Knight!
Attack Berfomet!
Next, Black Magician Girl!
Black Burning!!
Elf Swordsman, Direct Attack!
What happened, the other me?
Partner, please stop!
It's not over.
We're just getting started!
Are you serious? Do you really want to defeat me?
My turn!
I set a card face-down.
Then I Summon Giant Soldier of Stone in Defense Mode.
Next I activate the Magic Card, Sealing Swords of Light!
This should spare me from any attacks by Partner in the next three turns.
You can't beat me using petty party tricks!
My turn!
I sacrifice Elf Swordsman!
To Summon Catapult Turtle!
Catapult Turtle?
That right. I believe you're very clear about Catapult Turtle's Special Effects.
You're gonna be dead in this turn, Nameless Pharaoh!
Become a sacrifice, Queen's Knight!
This is...!
I use Black Magician Girl as a sacrifice!
Eat this!
Shoot out Queen's Knight!
Stand up, Nameless Pharaoh!
My next attack will be the end of you!
This is...
That was me back then...
The me that was controlled by the darkness in my heart!
This.. This is the end!
I use Black Magician Girl as a sacrifice!
Stop it, Partner! You can't do this!
Shoot!
Stop!!
Trap Card!
Divine Wind!
Divine Wind is a Trap Card that reflects back double the damage.
Partner!!
Yugi!
Partner!
Hang on!
Other Me...
Partner... You purposely did this for my sake...
My other self...  No matter how much it hurts, please don't waiver.
Believe in the strength of our bond.
You're not fighting alone.
Your friends and the Monsters who believe in you are always by your side.
Partner...
Even if we're separated...
I'm... always... by your side...
PARTNER!!!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
After being guided by Ironheart to the Gate of Mystery,
Yugi managed to overcome his other self in the Stone Wilderness.
After Dueling one another,
the two were able to regain the confidence once lost and reconfirmed their bond with one another.
Yugi's gonna be fine now!
But now something fishy is going on.
Eh? What's that Monster?!
They're the ghosts of Atlantis's soldiers?!
Next time!
"The Orichalcos Soldier"
Duel standby!