Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
I wasted my time winning an obvious victory against the deadbeat.
And my Battle City is over now.
But Yugi, you said, "I won through the power of the card my friend gave me."
In that case, I'll entrust you with the card that stands a chance against Ra!
There's no such thing as miracles!
There's no such thing
as the power of a friend!
Your defeat
will be the proof of that!
So, take this, Yugi!
"Final: Yugi VS Malik"
"Devil's Sanctuary"...?
This card...!
Big brother...
Why'd you give it to Yugi...?
Kaiba...
Devil's Sanctuary...
This card is the only Magic Card that
can overcome Malik's One Turn Kill.
But then again, you don't even
know what the ability Ra has is.
Let's see if you can discover
its secrets and learn how to
use this card effectively.
That's right! This will be a game with
a mere 20% chance of victory!
Yugi! I believe you said something
along the lines of winning with
the power of your friends!
But amidst the heat of battle,
you can rely on no one other
than your own power!
This card is meant to show you that!
What's the big deal?
I can't believe Kaiba-kun
actually gave Yugi a card...
You think he's up to something?
It's really suspicious...
Be careful, Yugi!
It's probably rigged or something!
Of course, it's entirely up to you
whether or not you place
the card in your deck.
Kaiba...
I'll believe in you!
And I'll defeat Malik!
And now we shall commence the
Battle City Tournament Final Match!
Malik Ishtar versus Yugi Mutou!
Duel standby!
Yugi, I don't know what card Kaiba
gave you, but it's useless!
It will be deemed nothing
against the almighty Ra!
Malik, I will defeat the evil soul dwelling
inside of you through this Duel!
That so?
That I'd like to see you try!!
Yugi!
You have to win this!
It's up to you, Yugi!
But you know, it takes three
sacrifices to Summon a god.
Yugi's still at quite a disadvantage!
What do you mean?
Yugi's got two God Cards now.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon and
The Great War God Obelisk.
But Malik's Ra can easily be
Special Summoned using Resurrection
of the Dead whenever he wants.
Magic Card, activate!
Resurrection of the Dead!!
Now behold God!
I Summon The Winged Sun Dragon
of Ra from my Graveyard!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra
- Final Form!
GOD PHOENIX!
Remember my Duel?
He used Ra's Special Ability to kill
every Monster on my field at once.
Plus, they say another hidden ability
we don't even know about lies within Ra!
Jounouchi...
Kaiba said he was able to decipher
all of Ra's abilities.
Could the card he gave Yugi
be a key card needed to beat Ra?
Will the Duelists please cut and
shuffle each other's decks?
Shuffle thoroughly...
And pray Ra sinks to
the bottom of the deck!
Seto...
Ishizu...
I did lend him a hand,
just like you asked me to.
But that was in order to prove that
there is no such thing as miracles!
That stone slab means nothing to me.
It's just a relic.
Civilizations are built from time and
the ashes of countless people...
the millions of forgotten dead.
I have no connection to someone
who lived 3,000 years ago.
No...
They may have been destined for destruction,
but the human spirit is eternal.
Hmph, if Yugi loses,
your brother cannot be saved.
Will you sink into
the depths of despair?
I believe... in Yugi.
And that the power of friends
will defeat a god controlled
by an evil mind.
Miracles don't happen!
A friend's power is powerless!
Yugi, your defeat is about
to be the proof I need!
Here you go...
Now then, I do wonder if Ra sunk
to the bottom of you wished...
Malik, your deck already
knows the answer to that.
It has already shown me your defeat!
Blah, blah, blah!
Blabber on as much as you need to
so you have no regrets when you
slip away from this realm!
Win, Yugi!
Yeah! You don't gotta
be afraid of Ra!
Kick Malik's ass!
I'm counting on you, Yugi!
You gotta save Mai!
The final fight of Battle City...
The fate of the Ishtars...
No, the fate of us all
now lies in your hands, Yugi!
Defeat the evil side of Malik...
And regain the key
to unlock your memories!
And... Please save Malik...
I beg of you!
Begin the Duel!!
I go first!
Here we go!!
Again?!
The darkness is swallowing
the entire field...!
It's... a Dark Game!
Yugi... My battle with you
will be the greatest Dark Game
the world has ever seen...!
Darkness will cover the Earth...
And the gates of Hell will open!
And now, allow me to show
you something nice...
Mai!!
Can you see the woman?
The sacrificial offering to the darkness?
Her life oh so slowly fades away...
Mai!
You could say today
is a festival of darkness!
And shouldn't we pile the
dinner offerings together?
What...?!
I'm sure I already told you!
That I already planned out
how I wanted to kill you in this Duel!
So I'll show you...
The livestock you'll be offering!!
Partner...!
Eh? What...?
My other self!
So you can see him, right...?
The fresh, living sacrifice
I've placed on the table.
Malik! What the hell
are you trying to pull here?!
And my offering will be this guy.
The other Malik!
Victory or defeat...
We walk the razor-thin line
between them...
What are you talking about?
Let's not be hasty!
You'll understand in due time!
Or rather, I'll make you understand...!
It's my turn!
Draw!
I Summon the Swift-Attacking
Bloodsucking Leech!
Attack the player!!
What!?
The Swift-Attacking Bloodsucking Leech
can attack on the turn it's Summoned!
The players feel all attacks
inflicted on their Monsters...
And look...
Partner!
Your sacrifice is devoured
by the darkness based on the amount
of Life Points you lose!
What did you say?
The moment the player's Life hits 0,
and the sacrifice's body is consumed...
The player, too, will be swallowed
by darkness and suffer
the ultimate pain!
Those are the rules
of this Dark Game, Yugi!
You bastard...!
Ahhhh, very nice...
Writhe in pain! Squirm! Shout!
Every time you do, pleasure runs
through my entire body!
If my Life Points reach 0, my partner
will be taken by the darkness...!
And if I defeat Malik, the other
Malik will be the sacrifice!
What do I do...?
Yugi, we were both chosen
by the Millennium Items.
And the rules state the loser is to
perish into the oblivion of death!
It's a fair fight!
I jest~
If I send your vessel to the darkness,
you will disappear along with him.
But even if my sacrifice is consumed by
the darkness, I myself will not vanish.
You have to fight, other me!
If you have to fight this battle
to find what's important to you,
then I'll fight alongside you!
Partner...!
Defeat Malik's evil heart!
Find the light you're searching for!
It was I who was chosen by
the Millennium Items!
In order to give you strength!
Yes... Thank you, Partner.
You're right.
There's something that
lies beyond this battle!
I will believe!
I will defeat this evil being!
Malik...
Partner...
Along with Mai and Bakura!
I will rescue everyone who's
fallen to these Dark Games!
I'll find a way to do it
during this battle!
I'll save you,
no matter what it takes...!
The both of you!!
Damn it! What kind of
Dark Game has started here?!
Yugi... I don't want you
to hurt yourself with these
dangerous games anymore!
Please don't lose!
My turn's not over yet.
The Swift-Attacking Bloodsucking Leech
has another Special Ability...
By throwing a card out of my hand,
I can switch it to Defense Mode
before the turn ends.
Another Special Ability beyond
the power of Swift Attack?!
Let's see...
Which card should I discard...?
Think I'll pick this...
Can you not sense the terror of
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra
having entered my Graveyard?
The moment I draw that card...
will be the moment of your deadly defeat!
What did he just
place in the Graveyard...?!
Could it be...?!
I place the Bloodsucking Leech
in Defense Position.
Then I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
Damn that Malik.
What a deadly strategy.
If the card he sent to the Graveyard
using the Bloodsucking Leech
was in fact the Ra card...
...then all he needs is
Resurrection of the Dead to activate the
One Turn Kill deadly instant-strike combo.
My turn! Draw!
I'll Summon this Monster!
Queen's Knight!
King, Queen, Jack.
One of the three swordsman possessing
the maximum Speed Summon
ability for calling God.
But you're too late!
Far too late!
Attack the Bloodsucking Leech!
Queen's Saber Crush!!
The Bloodsucking Leech was
my Defense Monster!
My Life is unaffected!
Too bad for you!
I set two reverse cards.
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
Was it really Ra that he
sent to the Graveyard?
If so, and he draws
Resurrection of the Dead...!
I drew a nice card...
But before I play this...
I'm going to Summon another Monster...
I Summon Juragedo!
Juragedo!!
Obliterate the Queen's Knight!!
Queen's Knight's been beheaded!!
Partner!!
I'm still fine!
I set two reverse cards
and end my turn!
It's my turn! Draw!
Trap Card, activate!
Left Arm Offering!!
What?!
That's right. At the cost of placing
my entire hand in the Graveyard,
this card allows me to choose
one Magic Card from my deck
and add it to my hand.
And the card I choose is...
Resurrection of the Dead!
Reverse card, open!
Exchange!
It's the card that allows the players
to exchange a card in their
hands with one another.
Now choose!
I'm choosing your
Resurrection of the Dead!
Hell yeah!
That's our Yugi!
Well, Malik... You lost
Resurrection of the Dead so easily...
I hope you enjoy this to the fullest.
Because with this reverse card...
I activate Resurrection of the Dead!
I Special Summon Queen's Knight!
And then I Summon King's Knight!
When the King and the Queen
are on the field, I can Special Summon
this guy as well.
Jack's Knight!
The King...
The Queen!
And Jack!
The "Three Musketeers of Face Cards"
have been Summoned!
So you managed to make clever use
of my Resurrection of the Dead.
All I need to do now is draw
the God Card, and I'll have beaten Malik!
Yes! Now Yugi's ready to Summon one of his gods!
Now Malik doesn't have his trump card,
the Resurrection of the Dead,
he needs to Summon his god!
But Malik still has some
reverse cards on the field...
He can't let his guard down yet.
Malik only has the
Fusion Cancel card in his hand.
Now's my chance to attack!
And yet...
He doesn't look worried in the least!
I know you don't have
the God Card in your hand.
What's the matter with you?!
Don't be scared now, Yugi!
Go ahead and attack me!
The moment you attack,
you'll fall prey to God!
His face-downs...!
They must hide a terrible trap!
Turn end!
So your fear
saved you for one more turn!
What's Yugi thinking up there?
If he had attacked, he'd probably have been
able to deal Malik some serious damage.
I know the feeling!
Yugi's Dueling instincts
probably told him not to.
What do you mean?
It may look like
Yugi has the upper hand,
but it feels like
Malik's hiding something!
My turn. Draw.
I set a reverse card!
Yugi, I know you don't have
God in your hand right now.
It's pathetic watching you
wait for a God Card on every
Draw Phase of your turn.
And if the God Card
you draw just happens to be
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
with the little amount of cards
you have in your hand,
its Attack Power will be weak!
So allow me to give you a little gift...
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Treasure From Heaven!!
What!?
Now both players are to draw from
their decks until they hold six cards!
He purposely gave me
six cards in my hand...?
Now! You've been given an opportunity
to replenish your hand!
You better not miss God again!
You're going to regret this, Malik.
Well, then? Did you manage
to draw your God Card?
I place Juragedo into
Defense Position and end my turn.
The Battle City rules state that a player
is only allowed to keep one
Resurrection of the Dead per deck.
But if you have that horrible card...!
My turn! Draw!
Now I have seven cards in my hand!
If I Summon Osiris,
it will have 6000 Attack Points!
Will he do it...?
Noble Faces, become my sacrifices!
I Summon... Osiris the Heaven Dragon!!
So you've shown yourself, Osiris?!
There it is!!
It's Yugi's God Card,
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
It even has 6000 Attack Points! Wow!
I don't care what he's planning!
It's hopeless for Malik now!
Yugi...
Here I go!
Attack him, Osiris!
Thunder Force!!
The time is right!
The time for Ra's power, that is!!
Reverse Magic, activate!
Revival of the Dark!!
What!?
Hey brother, what's that thing?
Revival of the Dark.
It's a card that activates when
your enemy's Monster attacks,
and lets you use a Magic Card from
your opponent's Graveyard.
So that means Malik...!
He can activate
Resurrection of the Dead!
Yugi, I'll be activating
Resurrection of the Dead
from the Graveyard!
O great Ra whom sleeps in the Earth!
Be reborn in the form
of a mighty phoenix!!
Now, my Ra!
Rise from the Earth
and dance over the Heavens!!
Become one with
the flames of the underworld and
bear the name of phoenix!!
Osiris' Thunder Force was
absorbed by the God Phoenix!
On the turn God rises,
he possesses the ability of immortality!
No attack will work against him!!
The God Phoenix...!
The same thing he beat me with!
Yugi!! I'll burn you to cinders in
the holy fire along with Osiris!!
Thanks to Resurrection of the Dead, Malik was able to bring The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra onto the field.
Yugi's Osiris' attacks won't work against Ra,
and it's going to be destroyed by God Phoenix's Special Ability!
And Malik managed to Summon Ra again on his following turn!
Yugi! Isn't there something you can do?
He set the card he drew on the field without looking at it!
Next time!
"Devil's Sanctuary Activates!"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other