Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Varon, even though you were the enemy...
...you were also one of the best Duelists I've ever encountered.
We really fought with all our might in our Duel.
Mai, even if it's you, I won't allow anyone to belittle him!
Come on over here, Mai.
We won't be able to understand each other if we don't battle one-on-one.
I won't try to escape anymore.
This time, I'll put in all my best and battle with you.
"Bitter Victory"
Jounouchi! Where are you?!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Damn it! That barrier did appear somewhere around here!
He must be nearby!
Let's not give up and continue searching for him!
Yes.
Trash.
Trying to win just by numbers alone?
Come out, Blue-Eyes!
Get rid of all this trash!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Where are they coming out from?
They keep appearing, Big Brother!
No matter how many there may be, trash will always be trash.
They're hardly a match against me.
Go, Blue-Eyes!
Brother!!
Mokuba!
You filthy scum!
Go forth, Critias!
Mokuba.
Big Brother!
These weak small fries keep coming one by one!
Blue-Eyes! Critias!
Eliminate them all!
My turn, draw.
I Summon Swordsman of Landstar in Defense Position.
And I set two reverse cards...
...two face-down...
And I end my turn.
My vision is getting worse.
The damage I took earlier was no joke.
But... it's too early!
You were talking so big and mighty before...
But aren't you about to collapse, Jounouchi?
Well...
This time, yeah.
You're always like that.
Even when you're facing formidable opponents...
No matter how hopeless the situation may appear to be...
...you'll never give up.
Aren't you afraid of losing?!
That's true.
Let me ask you, then.
What does winning mean to you?
Is winning just about defeating your opponents during a Duel?
W-Well...
I remembered you mentioned about how you can't trust others...
That you only trust yourself.
But after fighting side by side at Duelist Kingdom..
Haven't we all found something more important than winning?
But...
Why have you gone back to fighting on your own?
I...
I've always been alone...
Always!
You're wrong! You're our friend!
Even now!
It's too late! I can only keep fighting now!
Mai!
That's enough of this pointless conversation!
I only want to defeat you!
That's all.
Mai...
No, I believe in the Mai back then.
I will accept your feelings!
Come on, Mai!
My turn!
Draw!!
I use Harpy Lady to attack Swordsman of Landstar!
This is it!
Reverse card open!
Double Magical Arm Bind!
By sacrificing two Monsters on my field, this Trap Card...
...can take control of two Monsters on the opponent's field.
But I still have Harpies on my field!
Go and attack, you two!
Hold it! I still have another one!
Reverse card open!
Vow of Tribe!
When this card is activated...
...if both players have the same number of Monsters on their fields, none of us can battle!
This means that in this turn...
Because two Harpy Ladies are on my side of the field... you can't attack!
The battle ends!
You're good.
I wanted to slowly grow up through the course of Dueling...
And that's how I came to be where I am now.
That spirit is Jounouchi's strong point.
No matter what kind of mess he may be in...
How hopeless the whole situation may be...
He'll never give up.
I don't have that in me...
I finally understand...
Why you're so bent on pursuing Jounouchi...
He holds something we don't.
You know what it is, right?
To face one another in a Duel...
...with a genuine straight-forward passion.
I don't... have that?
Is it true?
No, when I defeat you...
...you will see the true strength I have!
A strength that nobody else has!
Turn end!
Mai.. I feel it...
Your soul as a Duelist has nothing to do with Doma.
You just simply want to continue Dueling until your soul is content.
If that's the case...
As a Duelist... I will Duel with you till the end!
My turn!
Draw!
I sacrifice the two Harpy Ladies I got from you and my Swordsman of Landstar...
Sacrificing three Monsters?!
Come out, Gilford the Lightning!
Because three Monsters were sacrificed when Gilford the Lightning was Summoned...
He will destroy all the Monsters on the opponent's field!
And then I'll use Gilford the Lightning to Direct Attack the opponent!
Stand up, Mai!
Our Duel is not over!
You've definitely become stronger, Jounouchi.
But I'm the one who will win!
I end my turn.
Then here I come!
My turn, draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand.
Treasure from Heaven!
We both can draw until we have six cards in our hands!
You better draw too, Jounouchi.
Did you get that card?
Who knows...
Even though I didn't get Hermos, I did get a pretty good card.
Even if Jounouchi got the Hermos card, I'll defeat him before he gets to use it!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Revive, Harpy Lady!
Then, another Magic Card.
I activate Kaleidoscope - Magnificent Replication!
This card allows me to Special Summon Harpy Lady Replicas!
She Summoned three Harpy Ladies in just one turn.
That card must be...!
Yes.
Here it comes, Jounouchi!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Phoenix Formation!
Phoenix Formation allows me to destroy the same number of Monsters my opponent controls as the number of Harpy Ladies I have,
and also inflict damage equal to the total Attack Power of the destroyed Monsters to the opponent's Life Points!
Go, my Harpy Ladies!
I got hit...
How's that? My Harpy Combo is flawless.
A-As I expected, Mai.
You took my Life Points down this much in a single turn.
You still have the energy to talk?
You're tough.
It'll be a waste if our Duel ends just like that.
You're a True Duelist that I recognize.
Nothing's more enjoyable than Dueling you with my all.
My turn's over!
My turn.
Damn... Just a bit more..!
Just a little longer!
For Mai's sake!
Draw!
Hermos...
Please give me the last burst of power!
I activate the Magic Card, Warrior's Return!
Due to the effect, a Warrior-Type Monster gets revived from the Graveyard into my hand.
I Summon Blue Flame Swordsman in Attack Position!
Next from my hand, I activate a Ritual Magic Card.
Descent of Dark Dragon!
Ritual Magic?!
By sacrificing Iron Knight Gearfried from my hand...
I Summon Knight of Dark Dragons!
Next I activate its Special Ability...
By sacrificing Knight of Dark Dragons...
I can Special Summon Red-Eyes Black Dragon from my deck or from my hand!
Appear, Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
But... You can't attack on the same turn when a Monster is Specially Summoned!
I know that.
That's why I'll activate this card from my hand!
Claw of Hermos!
By fusing Hermos with Red-Eyes...
I equip Red-Eyes Black Dragon Sword on Blue Flame Swordsman!
Its Attack goes up by 1000 points!
Go, Blue Flame Swordsman!
Attack Harpy Lady!
I set two reverse cards and end my turn.
Not yet... it's not over..
Just a little more...
My turn, draw!
No matter how strong the Equipment Card may be...
...it will be nothing once I destroy it!
What?!
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card!
Harpy's Feather Duster!
With its decreased Attack Points, I can now defeat Blue Flame Swordsman with ease...
And I can even attack Jounouchi directly.
But...
Now that it's boiled down to this.. I want to defeat you with all my might!
Magic Card! Magic Reproduction!
With this card, in exchange for discarding two Magic Cards from my hand...
I can return a Magic Card from the Graveyard back into my hand.
The card that you want to get back into your hand...
...is Phoenix Formation.
You're right.
I'm going to use all my power to defeat you.
Harpy Lady Phoenix Formation!
It will inflict damage equal to the total Attack of the destroyed Monsters to the your Life Points.
What?! Zero Attack Power?!
That's because I've activated the Special Ability of Blue Flame Swordsman.
Blue Flame Swordsman can transfer its Attack Power to another Monster.
So you've transferred its Attack Power to my Harpy?!
Yes, I've transferred it all.
Now Blue Flame Swordsman has zero Attack Points.
Which also means that I took zero damage.
In addition, when Blue Flame Swordsman is destroyed...
Flame Swordsman will be Specially Summoned onto the field.
To avoid taking any damage in this turn, you've transferred your Attack Power to the enemy's Monster?
What are you thinking?!
You want to say that I'm stupid right?
I think the same way too.
But this is all that I can do right now.
I want to make you remember...
Using this Duel, I'll make you remember what is important.
You should be relying on your own strength to Duel.
And not depending on Doma for power!
I know that you're a really gentle person.
Come to think of it...
I haven't returned it back to you yet.
It's useless to try to sway my determination by saying all that!
That's not it!
You need to take the first step, Mai!
If not, you'll continue living in pain!
Mai...
I...
I can't go back.
This is my only choice.
Turn end!
My turn. Draw.
I set one reverse card...
Turn end...
My turn! Draw!
I use Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage to attack Flame Swordsman!
This is the end, Jounouchi!
Reverse card, open.
Devil Dice!
Harpy Lady's Attack Points are cut in half.
Even so, I'll still win!
You'll lose once I use Harpy to Direct Attack you next!
Harpy! Strike Jounouchi...
Why...?
Why am I hesitating?
It's obvious that I'm going to win...!
You win... Mai...
Jounouchi!
During your battle with Varon, you were already...
I'm sorry...
I won't be able to see your face anymore...
You Dueled with me when you were already in such a bad state...
I'm sorry...
I couldn't do anything for you in the end...
But I'm glad that your soul isn't going to be taken away...
Jounouchi!
The Duel... was fun.
NO!
Is it here?
The winner is Mai Kujaku.
But...
Yugi...?
Timaeus...
Critias is... crying.
Jounouchi!
No... No! Jounouchi!
I knew it all along!
I knew that winning wouldn't change a thing!
I knew it from the start.
That even if you win...
I'm so stupid.
What can I gain by sacrificing you?
Dartz...!
I'll end it all with you...!
Please wait, Jounouchi... Varon...
I will get your souls back!
You...!
This can't be!
How can this be!
Jounouchi-kun!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
It can't be true that Jounouchi lost!
But that guy Varon's soul was also taken away...
This means that Mai-san was the one that took away Jounouchi's soul.
I can't believe this!
With a sorrowful heart, Yugi enters Paradias alone.
And what he sees...
...is Mai-san with her soul taken!
Who could have done that!?
Next time!
"The Duel of Destiny! Yugi vs. Rafael"
Duel standby!