Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Trying to weaken my big brother by spouting ancient things from the past to try and win won't work!
My bond with my big brother is way stronger than Noah or the Big Five realize!
Just look! Big brother won!
Once he gets serious, the Big Five don't stand a chance!
"The Mystery Deepens: Noah's True Colors"
Mokuba, you don't hate Seto...?
Even though he betrayed you?
I trust in my big brother!
No matter how I might feel at the time, it still doesn't matter!
Wealth, talent and power...
There aren't many born with the same fortune I hold.
There isn't a thing I lack.
There's not a single person I envy.
That's why I thought I could obtain everything Seto has.
But Mokuba... Just what is it about your brother?
You sacrifice yourself
so easily for Seto...
The one thing Seto has that I don't...
I see now... Mokuba is the one thing I don't have!
If that's the case,
I'll just steal him!
Because he's the one
Seto treasures the most!
You really are a good brother,
you know that?
But are you positive your beloved big brother is just as devoted to you?
I'm curious as to what your big brother is thinking right now...
My big brother's always by my side!
And I believe in him!
Do you now...?
But does Seto really feel that way?
Brother!
You came for me, big brother!
I'm growing tired
of you holding me back.
Huh...? What are you saying, big brother?
All you do is get in my way.
You'd be better off if you go on your own and grow up!
Big brother?!
BIG BROTHER!!
It can't be... Big brother...
Seto sure is a cruel guy.
If he really cared about you in the least, he wouldn't say such things.
I, on the other hand, would always treasure you.
Let me protect you.
Noah...
You're a good boy, Mokuba.
From now on, I will be your big brother.
Noah... is big brother...
Big brother...
Big brother!
Mokuba?!
So you're "inviting" me, are you...?
The road...!
Seto, I've just made the treasure you cherish most mine.
Wait, Noah!
Don't you touch Mokuba!
Wait, Kaiba-kun! We're coming to-
This has nothing to do with you guys!
What'd you say?!
This is a problem between us brothers!
We don't need your help!
Dumbass!
I'm never gonna worry about your ass again, ya hear!
Yugi, you've got no reason to worry about that jerk!
Yeah! Just forget about him!
Let's look for a method to get ourselves out of here!
We gotta get my
body back before we do that!
Yeah! I feel terrible for Honda-san the way he is now!
Right, right!
Ahh, you're so kind, Shizuka-chan~!
You're way nicer than that Otogi jerk!
Shizuka-chan~!!
Don't get so close to Shizuka-chan the way you are now!
We can't just desert him!
You guys wait here!
Hey! Yugi!
Me too!
Anzu!
Damn, those guys are too much!
Big brother, shouldn't we stick together?
Hmph, just let em be!
There'll just be more guys "getting in his way" if we go.
Exactly!
Besides, it's their fault we got trapped here in the first place.
But still...
I'm going too!
Shizuka!
Damn it all!
Every single one of these guys...!
Let's go, Otogi!
W-Wait up!
Yugi! Anzu!!
How long do you
plan to screw with me?!
Big brother!
Huh? Mokuba!
Mokuba!
You bastard!
Which way did Kaiba-kun go?!
This way!
Anzu, how'd you know?!
It's woman's intuition!
Woman's intuition!
Woman's intuition?!
Hold on, Anzu!
That light...!
Told you! I was right!
Let's check it out!
Where are...?
I feels... like they don't want us to enter.
Yugi, do you hear that?
Huh?
What is that?
You're right. It's someone's voice.
I know! It's a baby crying!
Let's go inside!
Yeah.
I'm growing tired of waiting.
Are they dead or something?
I wouldn't want those guys killing them off before I do.
Because I'm the one who's going to send them to hell!
Please don't steal away my fun.
This fog's really pouring in.
Keep your guard up.
It feels like something bad's about to happen.
Yeah.
I wonder if Yugi-san and Anzu-san are alright...?
Noah... You little...!
Mokuba!
Noah, you may be interested in the person I used to be, but I'm a completely different person now.
And if you think taking Mokuba hostage will let you surpass me,
you're completely mistaken!
You're wrong there!
It was one of your former subordinates that kidnapped him.
It was I who saved Mokuba from his clutches.
I expect a thanks and not more of your complaining.
Mokuba, we're going.
What's wrong, Mokuba?
Come along.
I won't!
I'm staying with Big Brother Noah!
I've stayed alongside Big Brother Noah my whole life!
Mokuba...
Noah, what the hell did you do to Mokuba?!
Hypnosis? What pleasure do you get out of screwing with my little brother?!
Hypnosis?
You can't take someone's heart with such pathetic techniques.
Mokuba has simply realized what you've done to him.
What exactly did I do to Mokuba...?
We heard everything Daimon said.
We know you betrayed Mokuba.
You used him. Now Mokuba shudders every time he hears your name.
He's wrong! Are you really going to believe Daimon?!
So you're saying he made it all up?
Mokuba, listen to what I'm saying!
Are you really going to
believe these people?!
The poor thing. You're scaring Mokuba.
Come this way.
So you're controlling Mokuba's heart?!
Do you want to beat me this badly, Noah?!
You think it's so I can beat you?
I realize the circumstances at the time.
But you still had no right pushing things as far as you did.
What?!
It's obvious I no longer need to fight you in order to beat you.
Seto, that's because I'm already greater than you.
You're greater than me?
Anzu!
Find anything?
Nope...
Anzu, over here!
It's a rattle, isn't it?
But where is the baby?
Do you think... we've traveled back in time to when Kaiba-kun was a baby?
That would be strange, wouldn't it?
Kaiba-kun was adopted by the Kaiba's when he was 10.
Oh yeah...
What's the matter, Yugi?
This is...!
What?
What the hell is all of this?
That way. Looks like there's something quite valuable beyond those doors.
Error! Error!
Lock! Lock!
Refuse to access!
Are you in there?!
YUGI!?
What's up with him?
Honda, if you don't keep quiet I'm gonna dissect you!
God, are you throwing a hissyfit so you can seduce Shizuka-chan again?
A-A Monster!
You're the monster!
What'd ya say?!
Come on, there's something in the sea!
Saying stuff like that... won't get you back into Shizuka-chan's breasts, you idiot!
Wh-What the?
What the hell, you jerks?!
You're all a bunch of losers, so what are you showing yourselves for?!
We're here to pick you up, of course.
We already had our matches with you!
Yes. We lost our Duels to you.
However...
Big brother!
Don't worry. No matter how many times we Duel these idiots, it'll end the same.
Who wants to face me this time?!
Or do you wanna fight me all at once?!
We no longer have any intentions of playing these petty games.
What?!
This time we'll be taking you all by force!
L-Like hell you will!
GO!
Weaklings!
Hurry up, Jounouchi-kun!
Shit, what the hell is with this thing?
Big brother!
Work... Work...!
Work, you stupid piece of junk!
It worked!
Are you saying I am inferior to you?!
What do you mean?!
I still haven't told you the truth about me yet, have I?
Truth?
You and Gozaburo...?
Yugi!
Kaiba-kun!
Look at this, Kaiba-kun!
This is...
An old photograph of Gozaburo?!
And Noah's beside him!
Who is this?
He's quite intelligent.
This kid I picked up from an orphanage also looks just like you.
Of course, he's no match for you.
Get along with him. It's not as fun all by yourself around here.
Seto will be your lifelong rival, intended to further motivate you in your studies.
Noah, I want to see you surpass this boy in everything you do.
Once you prove this to me, you will have proved yourself qualified to be the heir to Kaiba Corporation.
I understand.
It's a simple task...
...Dad.
Eh?!
"Dad"?!
What does he mean?!
The renowned Gozaburo Kaiba only had one true son. And that is me, Noah Kaiba.
In order to prove myself worthy of my father's company,
he picked me up a rival.
You were meant to inspire me, Seto.
That's the only reason you were taken from the orphanage.
From the start, you were nothing more than the horse I needed to ride all the way to the top.
But a mere horse like you got closer to my father.
Then you went
and stole Kaiba Corporation.
You scum...!
Get it now? You were nothing more than a tool I intended to use to prove my intelligence.
And I am meant to run Kaiba Corporation!
Impossible! There's no way that's true!
Even if what you said was true, there's no way you're Gozaburo's son!
What, do you need proof of my birth or something?
Wait up! You foolish children belong to us of the Big Five!
The guys!
Those guys just never learn...
Seto, this conversation of ours will have to wait until later.
Wait, Noah!
Brother!
I'm working on it!
You alright, Otogi?!
Y-Yeah...! I'm fine...!
Shizuka!
Now then, which one of you shall I take?
I shall be taking the young lady's body.
Wait! I'll be taking that little girl!
What?! Didn't you want the other girl?!
Every pretty girl belongs to me!
What?! You think I'll
tolerate such greediness?!
What the hell are you fools doing?!
This is not the time to be fighting amongst ourselves!
We're running out of time!
B-But...
Silence!
Anyone is fine!
Just pick one and let's get moving!
Noah-sama!
You fools! If you won't do as I tell you, I'll gladly eliminate you all!
Please wait a moment, Noah-sama!
I do not want your excuses!
Otogi! Are you okay?
That was too close!
Guys!
Thank god! Everyone's safe!
Oh! Yugi!
You're alright, man?!
Shizuka-chan!
Are you alright?!
I am, Anzu-san!
Kaiba-kun!
Why do you think Noah isn't his real son like he said before?
If the virtual projection was taken from the "world of memories",
that hologram would have taken place back before I was adopted by the Kaiba's.
Meaning it occurred six years ago.
In this photograph, Gozaburo is much younger than he is there.
Noah hasn't changed at all!
So what does that mean?
We still don't know what exactly Noah is,
but for now we have to save Mokuba, who is still kidnapped!
Oh yeah, we've gotta get Honda's body back too!
Huh?! Honda's over there!
If I remember right, he was taken over by one of the Big Five!
Eh?! They're all inside of him now?!
In order to save Honda's body, we challenge the Big Five to one final Duel!
Please! Yugi, Jounouchi!
Get Honda's body back!
Next time!
"The Big Five's Counterattack"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise