Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
In the Duel Monsters World,
we got a Legendary Dragon card.
But we still have no clues
about the enemies.
Then, Pegasus gave us
an invitation to America.
When we meet Pegasus,
we might know who the enemy is.
Meanwhile, Kaiba-kun has set out to meet Pegasus as well.
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Nightmare of Toon World"
Look.
We're getting close to
downtown San Fransisco.
I'm so excited!
This is the first time
I've been to America!
Gosh, you aren't here for sightseeing.
You seem a bit distracted, Partner.
Yeah.
I'm worried about Pegasus's expression on the video letter.
He looked like he was
being followed by someone.
I'm certainly concerned about it.
Yeah.
Duelist Kingdom...
I didn't think I'd ever
come here again...
Big brother!
Looking at this place, all that comes to mind is a lot of horrible memories...
Seems like no one's here.
Hmph. It's better if there's
no one to interfere.
Let's go, Mokuba.
Okay.
It's a cable car!
Just like the ones
you see in the movies!
Whoa! I can see the Golden Gate Bridge!
It gives you the feeling you're in America!
Right, Yugi?
What?
What's wrong with you?
Are you thinking about something?
Yeah.
I'm thinking about
what Pegasus wants to tell us.
Monsters appearing
all over the world...
And the God Cards were stolen...
And these guys calling themselves the Musketeers of Doma appeared...
And the crisis between the Duel Monsters World and our world.
Pegasus must know something.
What could it be...?
Calling us out here and not having the courtesy to show yourself?
Talk about rude!
Quit the bullshit and
get out here this instant!
Welcome, Kaiba boy!
Long time no see!
Nice to meet you, Kaiba boy.
And...
Mokuba boy.
So you finally appeared, Pegasus.
I have something
I must confirm with you!
Why?
All the strange events occurring around the world were caused by Industrial Illusions, were they not?
What?
Don't play dumb!
I am talking about the incident with Duel Monsters appearing on their own!
There's no problem with my Kaiba Corporation's Solid Vision System!
So who else could it be other than the creator of Duel Monsters himself?!
It couldn't be anyone but you!
I do wonder about that.
What?!
Kaiba boy...
All responsibility falls on you.
What did you say?
Answer me!
What do you mean by that?!
If you want to know the answer,
defeat me in a Duel.
You bastard!
I remember the Duel I shared with you!
You devoted yourself to saving Mokuba boy's soul that eventful day~
Mokuba boy's soul
has been sealed in this card.
Kaiba boy, if you can defeat me
I will release Mokuba boy's soul from the sealed card.
But you couldn't defeat me then.
And then...
Kaiba boy, I presume you are aware of what it means to lose a game?
The loser loses everything.
What is precious to them...
And even themselves.
You shall suffer the
same fate as Mokuba boy!
Mind Card!!
Shut your mouth!
Why are you so angry, Kaiba boy?
I'm just telling you the truth!
Plotting to throw me off by bringing up past humiliations is nothing but a waste of breath.
Bring it, Pegasus! It's about time we settled the score once and for all!
Fine by me, Kaiba boy.
We shall enjoy the greatest Duel!
Since you have come all this way to Duelist Kingdom,
I have prepared for you
a nostalgic Duel Ring!
I am sure you would
love to have your revenge!
I could care less
what system I Duel with,
but I just can't trust you.
So I'll be using this!
There's no possible way you can beat me in a fight using fair conditions!
That's right!
My brother won't lose
to someone like you!
Sounds fabulous!
We will know very shortly whether those words hold any weight to them or not!
Mokuba, you stay back.
But Brother...
This is Pegasus we're talking about. No one knows what he's up to.
Big brother...
You have no idea of how long I've been dreaming of this day...
He sealed away his mindset as a Duelist before...
But my brother's going to unleash it once again!
Big brother!
Kick Pegasus' ass!
Hey, you fiend! Have you set up another cheap trick to look at my hand again?
No!
Please do not worry!
Defeating you without the aid of my Mind Scan is like taking a walk in the park!
Don't kid yourself now!
I don't know what you're up to, but I'll be the one to win!
Brother...
Duel!!
I take the first move.
Draw.
I Summon a Monster in Defense Mode!
That card...
Then I set a reverse card and...
...complete my turn!
Humph! What a show off.
What?!
Why do you say this?
You played the same opening move you did in our first Duel,
in order to try and
sway my battle strategies?
Oh...! Is that so?
Sorry! I forgot all about it!
I told you before!
I'm an entirelly different person than I was back then!
Your psychological warfare won't work on me any more!
My turn!
I Summon Spear Dragon in Attack Mode!
Attack Toon Alligator!
By the Special Ability of Spear Dragon,
When it attacks a Monster with Defense Points lower than its Attack Points,
the Player will receive the difference as damage to their Life Points.
Also, after it attacks, it switches to Defense Mode!
I set two reverse cards!
Turn end!
Good job, Big brother!
Rare cards~
IT STINKS~!
It hurts~
Who're you?
Where...
...are we?
HELP ME~!!
It's my turn.
Oh! This card should put a little spunk in our funk!
I activate the Magic Card, Toon Table of Contents!
Toon Table of Contents?
I can take a card with "Toon" in its name and add it from my deck to my hand!
What did you say?
Could it be...?!
Yes! That's right!
As expected of Kaiba boy!
You are very clever!
This invincible card's name is...
Toon World!
Kaiba boy...
I'll once again invite you to the world of perfect beings!
I pay 1000 points as a cost,
in order to activate Toon World!
I then Summon Toon Masked Sorcerer!
You can only use Toon Monsters to attack or defend against other Toon Monsters!
That's the Toon World that caused my brother great suffering...
How is he gonna fight?
Attacks from Normal Monsters
can't harm Toon Monsters!
You really think the
same trick will work twice?
Reverse Trap activate!
Clone Token!
Kaiba boy has also
Summoned a Toon Monster?
Attack as you wish!
It'll just destroy both Toon Monsters!
Goddamn!
I hold the data of every Duel I've ever played in the past.
And of course, I have analyzed a new strategy to use against you from that information.
It's perfect!
I end my turn...!
My turn!
I don't intend to fight you
on your own turf!
I sacrifice Toon Masked Sorcerer and Spear Dragon!
What?
What do you think you are doing?!
I Summon Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Brother's Blue-Eyes!
I'll obtain victory alongside my Blue-Eyes!
It's useless!
Even if it's Blue-Eyes attacking, it won't work against a Toon's Effect!
I'm not scared of your Toons!
I thought I told you my Duel strategy is perfect?!
Then I activate a Reverse Trap!
Toon Mask!
This card lets me sacrifice my own Toon Monster,
and Special Summon a Toon Monster exact copy of the opponent's Monster!
What?!
It's name is Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon!
Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon...!
You actually placed this disgusting form in front of me again?!
Oh! What cruel words to utter!
Don't make my repeat myself!
I have a strategy
to deal with your Toons!
Magic Card, activate!
Shrink!
Now the Attack Power of Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon will be slashed by 1500 points!
But my Toons are the ultimate life forms!
Even if you slash their Attack Points with Shrink, it's meaningless!
I'll then activate the Continuous Magic Card from my hand, Card Treasure of Lamentation!
And I use Blue-Eyes White Dragon to attack Toon Dragon!
Wasted effort!
Are you looking to repeat the same stupid mistake you made in the past?!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Have you forgotten already?
Normal attacks
don't work on Toon Monsters!
Hmph! I know that better than anyone!
I'm aiming for something else!
Why?!
The Continuous Magic, Card Treasure of Lamentation!
During your Battle Phase, when one of your Monsters attacks and destroys the opponent's Monster,
I can add one card
from my deck to my hand.
I have a key card in my Deck capable of destroying Toon World...
I'm doing this so I can draw it faster.
It's my turn now!
I'll pay 500 Life as the cost...
So Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon can Direct Attack you, Kaiba boy!
You don't have
any Toons on the field!
You cannot avoid this attack!
Reverse Magic, Attack Nullification!
Oh no!
You can use this card when the opposing Monster attacks,
and then negate that attack and end the Battle Phase!
It doesn't make a bit of difference whether it's a Toon attacking or not!
Then I'll use a Magic Card...
Toon Rollback, activate now!
I have two chances
in the Battle Phase now!
Impossible!
Monsters can attack only once per turn!
Even if you get a second Battle Phase,
you can't attack me with him again!
That's right!
However...
I am yet to Summon
a Monster on this turn!
What?
So it will be no problem for me to Summon a Monster on this turn! Mondaiarimasen!
Thus, I sacrifice Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon!
I Summon Toon Black Magician Girl!
Direct Attack the player!
Yes, Master!
No way!
I can't believe he lost 2000 Life in just one shot...!
So, what do you think?
My Toons have evolved!
My turn!
Draw!
I use my Blue-Eyes to attack Toon Black Magician Girl!
He can't defeat the Toon by attacking with Blue-Eyes this way.
So why?
NO, NO, NO, NO, NO!
Tada~!
Because of Card Treasure of Lamentation, I draw one card...
Whatever is so funny?!
"Perfect beings"? That's worth a big laugh!
You're going to tarnish your title as the creator of Duel Monsters like that!
Why?!
I can admit as much that Toon Monsters are invincible, but only under the protection of Toon World!
So I just have to destroy Toon World!
Toon World?!
I activate the Magic Card!
A Wingbeat of Giant Dragon!
What?!
This card lets you return a Level 5 or higher Dragon-Type Monster to your hand,
and in exchange destroy every Magic and Trap Card on the field!
So your beloved Toon World will now disappear!
My Toon World has...!
Alright!
There's no card
capable of defeating me!
You're amazing, Big brother!
I'll also Summon God Of Destruction - Vasago
in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
Who are you...?
It's true my Toon destruction
plan was flawless,
but you should have fully understood the situation.
All you're doing is simply imitating his previous style of Dueling.
The Pegasus I know isn't that dumb!
You're not Pegasus!
Who the hell are you?!
Tell me!
I expected no less of Seto Kaiba.
You saw right through my disguise.
You're right.
I'm not Pegasus.
What's going on here?
I am one of the
Musketeers of Doma! Amelda!
Doma? Musketeers?
I won't forgive you!
What are you talking about?!
This is my revenge... Seto Kaiba!
Activate now! Barrier of Orichalcos!
What?
What is this?
What on Earth is this?
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
The ones imprisoned within this barrier
can't escape until someone wins the Duel!
And the one to lose...
His soul will be sealed
within the boundary!
What did you say?!
Seto Kaiba...
By order of the king of Doma, Lord Dartz...
...I shall claim your soul!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
We have come to America in order to meet with Pegasus.
But our ride suddenly comes to a stop.
And the driver takes off somewhere.
Is Industrial Illusions really out here in the middle of nowhere?
Elsewhere, the impostor Pegasus finally reveals his true identity.
This "Amelda" seems to hold a strong grudge against Kaiba-kun...
Did something happen between them in the past?
Next time!
"Wake Up! Critias"
Duel standby!