Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
The driver sure is taking his time...
Yeah, what the heck's he doing?
Guess we should go check on him...
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"An Unexpected Enemy"
What the?
There's no one here.
It feels like no one's used this place for years...
He's not using the toilet either.
What's going on?
Hey, can you hear that?
I hear it!
It's coming our way!
W-Who the hell are you people?!
We don't have any money! So get lost!
Partner!
Other Me!
Switch with me!
What do you want with us?
Are these guys henchmen of Doma?
Damn them...!
Guys! Run towards the car!
Yugi...
We're in serious trouble here...
That's low, you jerks!
What?
Wh-what?
Let's take this chance and get outta here!
O-Okay!
Harpy... Lady?
She's...!
C-Crap...!
Jounouchi, hurry!
Who exactly was that person?
It's Mai. I'm sure of it.
What did you say?
Mai?!
Let's go, Varon!
Mai Kujaku...!
The Musketeers of Doma... Amelda...
He was another victim of Gozaburo...
My little brother was...
...killed by your company!
Big Brother...
What should we do?
Mokuba, you don't have to worry about that.
I took on Gozaburo's sins along with control of Kaiba Corporation.
This is a problem I must solve on my own.
Brother...
They most likely have already gotten to Pegasus.
But what is their purpose?
And this card...
What is this place?
Am I supposed to pull it out?
Why?
I know your name.
Your name is Critias!
When was this card placed in my deck...?
Is this some kind of magic trick...?
Is it a fake?
Or...
Some kind of tremendous power guiding me...?
Is this the new path I'm supposed to follow?
Big Brother.
We have mail from the company.
"Please come back immediately..."
No.
I'm going right to Industrial Illusions from here.
I may find more information about them there.
I don't take orders from anyone...
I'll decide my path myself!
I'll defeat anyone who
dares to stand in my way!
Really!
Why didn't you keep driving straight?!
Thanks to you, our ride is ruined!
Shut up!
Because you were spacing out, we almost got caught in the explosion at the gas station!
What'd you say!?
You sayin' it's my fault?!
Wanna fight, you jerk!?
Stop!
Knock it off, you two!
Now's not the time to be fighting each other.
That's right.
We should be thinking about what to do next.
Anyway, all we can do is go to Industrial Illusions.
That's right. The limousine Pegasus sent for us got taken over by those other guys.
I'm worried about Pegasus.
That's true...
The problem is how we get there from here...
So tight~!
Honda! Your suitcase is in my way!
What're talking about?! Yours is!
But what the hell did you bring in that suitcase?
Some very important stuff!
I'll let you take a small peek.
Look!
What the hell's this?
A cultural characteristic!
I'm gonna teach Americans about Japanese culture!
You twit...
Let me see this crap!
What the hell is this?!
It's my stuffed animal!
I can't sleep without it!
What the flipping hell is this?
Those are American boxers right there!
Give it back, you jerk!
Not a chance!
GIVE IT NOW!
Fighting at a time like this...
Speaking of which...
Hey Jounouchi, was the person who saved us really Mai-san?
I saw her.
She had the Harpy Lady.
There's no doubt. She's Mai!
Since she took out those Doma punks,
that must mean Mai's
fighting against them too.
As long as she's here, I feel relieved.
Indeed.
Yeah! She's so cool, that Mai-san!
Mai...
If that's the case, why didn't she tell us it was her...?
What the hell did we do ta' deserve this?
Shut up for once!
I don't wanna hear your damn complain--
The hell?!
That's dangerous!
My wallet's gone!
What'd ya say?!
S-shit... WAIT!!
WAIT~!!
Aw shit!
Here.
Take it. It's yours, right?
Wow, you surprised me!
I can't believe you two are close friends with Yugi-kun!
I can't believe we'll really meet in America.
What an amazing coincidence!
Close friends?
Huh? You aren't?
No, we're...
No no, YEAH! We're his best friends!
For the time being, let me do all the talking!
Speaking of which...
From what you told me,
it seems Yugi-kun's God Cards were stolen.
Everyone knows Yugi won the God Cards in the Battle City Tournament!
So there's a ton of people after them!
They're the ultimate rare cards, after all!
That's why we, as his closest friends in the world,
came to America to help him get the God Cards back!
We were thinking maybe we'd understand more if we paid Pegasus a little visit at his headquarters.
Okay!
Got it!
I've been troubled because I haven't been able to get a hold of Pegasus.
This is perfect.
Let's go to Industrial Illusions!
Sweet!
Yeah!
Is this Industrial Illusions?
Amazing!
Let's go!
Y-Yeah.
There's no one here.
Is today a holiday or something?
Then why would the doors be left wide open?
It's fishy...
Be careful, Other Me.
I have a bad feeling about this...
Yeah. I know.
I sensed someone with a murderous
intent when I came in here.
No good. The phone lines are dead.
Wh-what the?
Shit! It won't open!
Same here!
No good, it's not opening!
This is...
Mai!
Mai-san!
See?
Just like I said!
Speaking of which, that was a pretty extreme entrance there, Mai!
Mai, did Pegasus call you here too?
But be careful.
Something weird is going on.
Pegasus is no longer here...
Pegasus...
You are...
You are... Mai Kujaku!
Why are... you here?
Pegasus... I'll be taking that soul of yours!
What?!
My turn!
Draw!
The Magic Card, Harpy Lady Phoenix Formation, activates!
This card destroys Monsters on the opponent's side of the field equal to the amount of Harpy Ladies on my field!
N-NOOO~!!
Also, the Attack Power of the destroyed Monster is taken as damage from the opponent's Life Points!
NOOOOOOOOOOOO~!
I've... disposed of Pegasus!
Mai!!
I-It can't be...!
You're lying! There's no way Mai-san would do that!
Mai! What's going on here?!
Simply put, Mai Kujaku said she wanted to take care of you groupies with her own hands.
What!?
Mai!
You were only supposed to go after Pegasus!
Nameless Pharaoh and Jounouchi are our opponents!
I'll be taking these two on!
So you two better keep your hands off them!
Mai!
What are you saying, Mai?!
I had a lot of fun
hanging around you guys.
So much so that I lost track of time.
But...
I guess your friendship was
a little too bright for me.
Do your best.
Right back at you!
Why would you?! What the hell is going on here?!
You have a lot of explaining to do!!
Shit! Are you betraying us!?
There must be a reason!
Otherwise, Mai-san wouldn't do this...
Has Doma blackmailed you or something?
If you guys want to leave this building...
...you'll have to defeat me in a Duel first.
Jounouchi! I'll start with you!
Here I come!
My turn!
Draw!
Jounouchi...
I'm not the Mai Kujaku you once knew.
I have been reborn!
By obtaining new strength! The power of the Orichalcos!
O Magic Card, dyed in the darkest black! Awaken thy soul of darkness!!
Field Magic!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!!
This is...
Stop this, Mai!
I don't want to fight you!
Mai...
The Barrier of Orichalcos...
The only one who can leave that barrier...
...is the winner of the Duel.
Why do Mai-san and Jounouchi have to Duel each other like this?!
This Duel is too much...
Mai, you...
Come out! Harpy Lady!!
Gain the power of Orichalcos!
Inside the boundaries of the Orichalcos, all of my Monsters become Dark Monsters.
And their Attack Powers go up by 500 points!
Stop, Mai!
Turn end...
Now, Jounouchi... it's your turn.
No...
I...
I DON'T WANT TO FIGHT YOU LIKE THIS!!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
I can't believe the one waiting for us at Industrial Illusions was Mai-san!
Then after she captured Pegasus' soul with The Barrier of Orichalcos, she demanded to Duel Jounouchi!
Stop!
It's too strange for you two to fight
under this situation!
What's going on with you, Mai-san?!
Have you really become our enemy?!
Next time: "Mai is Falling Into the Darkness"
Duel Standby!