A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
My turn!
Black Chaos, attack!
Spell of Destruction!
Death Ultima!!
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice was beaten!
YUGI WON!
ALRIGHT!
"The King of Duelists"
Where did Pegasus go?
What is it, Anzu?
He's probably there.
Where is that?
At the top of the tower, Pegasus' secret room.
But my memory's not clear and I thought I was dreaming.
You too?
I couldn't tell if it was real or a dream, so I didn't say anything.
What are you talking about?
Explain it clearly for us!
It was real after all. Let's go!
Oi~ You still haven't told us everything yet!
I've seen many different types of minds using the Millennium Eye...
But for there to be two minds in one body...
Is that the Millennium Puzzle's power?
Cyndia, I'm beginning to think I may have been wrong...
Who is it?!
You're a user of the Power of Darkness.
So the Millennium Eye grants one the power to read people's minds.
But can you read your future?
Just stay put in this room a while and you'll learn everything.
I'll use these cards to help you out.
This card represents your birth and youth.
Happy Lover? You seem to have gone through happy romance.
But this card is upside down.
In other words, you and your lover suffered a tragic end.
Seems like I guessed right.
The next card represents your current self.
Mask of Darkness, eh?
Your current position and actions are to hide your original objectives, like a mask.
In order to cover up the true objectives deep within your heart,
you cooked up quite the lengthy scheme.
-And those true objectives...
-Shut up!
Shut your mouth!
Oi, Oi~! I just drew an unlucky card!
The Angel of Silencing Death, Doma.
It's supposed to be an angel but it brings death.
And once it appears before you, there's no escaping your passage to the underworld!
Is this all the power the Millennium Eye can muster?!
Because of the Duel with Yugi boy, my mind has reached its limit.
Who are you?
I'm collecting the seven Millennium Items.
Did you know?
Once one gathers them all, you are granted a power strong enough to control the world.
Stop... Stop it!!!
NO~!!!
What?
Pegasus!
Croquet-san, what happened?
Master Pegasus was attacked by someone.
Then what about Grandpa, Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun?
No's not the time!
Just who did this to Pegasus...?
Anyway, let's check out his room.
That's right. Maybe we could find some clues in his room.
That lady sure is pretty.
This is a diary... It's Pegasus' diary!
What?
Pegasus' diary?!
It's in English!
Of course! Pegasus is an American!
Can you read it, Anzu?
I can try reading it.
"To the one who defeats me and becomes the new Duelist King."
"Why did I create Duel Monsters?"
"In order to explain this mystery, I must talk about this girl."
Pegasus must have wrote this just in case he lost!
Hey~ Look at this.
It's the same girl as the portrait.
"Cyndia, that was the name of this young girl."
She was my lover and she passed away from this world at the age of seventeen.
It has been 14 years since I first met her.
My father was a wealthy man who managed casinos in Las Vegas.
In the evening, important people assembled for parties.
At that time I met Dad's friend's daughter, Cyndia.
We were attracted to each other.
We have always talked about our dreams.
I dreamed of becoming an artist.
Also to travel to many countries.
We swore the two of us would live together.
Soon after I turned 17, Cyndia died of an illness.
For months I stared at the blank canvas of my heart.
At that time, I had heard about how according to Ancient Egyptian belief, souls lived on after death.
Perhaps I could meet Cyndia if I used the technique handed down in Ancient Egypt...
I visited Egypt with that purpose in mind.
In a certain village in Egypt, I met a young boy.
Thank you.
You, stranger.
Let me give you some advice.
Leave this place at once.
What you are looking for is not here.
You won't heal your grief for your begone beloved in this place.
This is...
You ignored my warning.
What are you doing? Let me go!
I'm the guardian of the Millennium Items.
The only way to leave this sacred place is to be one of those chosen by the Millennium Items as their owner.
I won't tell anyone about this, so please let me go!
From this moment, you will be tested by this Millennium Eye.
Millennium... Eye?
If it recognizes you as its owner,
the Millennium Item will grant you one wish.
Wish?
Right. The doors of the underworld will open, and you will be able to see your lover again.
Cyndia...
But if it doesn't recognize you as its owner, the only thing awaiting you is... death.
Cyndia!
Cyndia...
I wanted to see you, I wanted to see you, Cyndia...
"It might have been lingering affection, but I wanted to meet Cyndia once again."
"At the time, I became aware of Kaiba Corporation's Virtual Simulation System."
"In order to materialize Cyndia's card,
Kaiba Corporation had to be mine, no matter what it took."
Pegasus wanted to meet his dead lover from the bottom of his heart
and was willing to take over Kaiba Corporation for that.
A man's true love?
If we don't care about Bakura and Mokuba, they'll be in danger.
And Kaiba too.
Let's go.
This card?
Yugi, what are you doing? Let's go.
I'm coming now.
This is...
You are...
It can't be. It's this young man who has the Millennium Puzzle?
Is this kid the one who stole Pegasus' Millennium Eye?
I need to confirm this young man's true identity.
What?
I'll use the Millennium Ankh to look at this young man's heart.
What are you doing?
This is...
There are two rooms in this boy's heart.
One has toys laid out all over the floor.
Doesn't look like the criminal who took the Millennium Eye.
There's another room.
I didn't think anyone would come to investigate my room.
If you're brave enough, come in. A game is waiting for you.
I have looked into many humans' rooms in their hearts in the past.
But this kind of serious and cold room is like the Ancient Egyptian grave of a king.
I don't know what kind of powers you have used to come into my room.
State your purpose.
Answering your question is a common courtesy.
Since Egyptian times, for 3000 years,
The royal families have handed down the Dark Millennium Items.
The seven items have the ability to rule the world.
And there are an infinite number of people collecting these items.
I am the guardian of the Millennium Items.
Right now I'm searching for the one who took Pegasus' Millennium Eye.
And you think this criminal is me?
By looking at one's room, I can sense any power within.
I see. In this heart you've found my room.
The truth has been revealed.
But this is a game. A Dark Game.
I shall accept this game.
Game Start.
A Maze. This young man's room is to hide the truth of the heart's maze.
What is it? If you don't take the first step, it is impossible to start.
Among all the doors, only one of them is the real room.
It's a trap.
This door and this door aren't it. It's not the real room.
Just which one is the real door?
This young man's heart, it's determined to not allow others to invade and has gotten me lost.
But I must know.
Yo. You came?
I've come to the real room?
No, this is also a trap.
If I fall into the deep hole of darkness,
I will never be able to leave this young man's shadowy heart.
Hold on.
I didn't think it would be you that saves me.
Other me, this is enough. Release him from the game.
This is...
Counting from now, 3000 years ago in Ancient Egypt,
There were stone tablets sealed under the control of magicians.
The battle for the king's throne begins with this.
Soon after the magicians were destroyed, the stone tablets and their magical powers went into sleep.
Those stone tablets' legends were all recorded in a history book.
After it was around humans, it soon was made into cards,
And it is the starting point of the card game.
These stone tablets are Duel Monsters in its original state?
What the?!
Black Magician!
He wants to protect this room. He wants to kill us.
How's that...
If defeated, we will be unable to leave this room.
This stone tablet is Blue Eyes White Dragon!
If the card completely resembles the monster's power,
Blue Eyes White Dragon wins over Black Magician's power.
If I use Dark Power to make Blue Eyes White Dragon appear and battle...
Stop.
Why do you stop me?
Black Magician is my card.
Black Magician, we aren't here in this room to cause chaos.
Allow us to escape from this room!
Black Magician!
What?
The Kings top magic wielder, Black Magician will listen to this young boy?
Then the other young man's real identity... impossible...
Tell this to the "Other You".
It was my mistake accusing him of being a criminal and stealing the Millennium Eye.
In order to find the criminal, I met something unexpected.
From today, you and the "other you", will unlock the true power hidden in the Millennium Puzzle.
For 3000 years, you've kept this secret sealed away.
That is the fate of the one who solved it.
What do you know about the Millennium Puzzle?
You have to watch out.
Another person looking for the Millennium Puzzle has come close.
A Millennium Item possessor.
Millennium Item possessor?
You mean Bakura-kun? But his Millennium Ring was thrown away.
Wait! I still have a lot of things to ask!
My name is Shadi.
This is the first time I've ever told anyone my name.
Young man, there will be one day when we meet again.
Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun have returned to normal.
And Grandpa is feeling very healthy as well.
Then, let's go back.
Who is this girl?
Eh? The Whole America Dueling Champion?
Return the Blue Eyes?
Are you saying, the card Yugi's Grandpa got from a friend?
But, Kaiba-kun...
What are you going to do, Yugi?
Next Time: The Girl From America
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship