Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Jounouchi!
Yugi-kun!
Why the hell are Yugi and Jounouchi Dueling in the first place?
And what's up with that huge anchor they're attached to?
A "Death Duel".
Death... Duel... as in...?
We've got just under 4 minutes left...!
If things keep up like this, me and Jounouchi-kun are gonna sink into the ocean!
My turn!
Draw!
Death... Meteor...
You drew a nice card, Jounouchi!
Now! Use that card to finish him off!
You still want to Duel, am I right?
"Attack Me!
The Fatal Last Turn"
If you insist on finishing the Duel and killing Yugi,
then use that card to finish him off.
You're running out of time.
This turn will determine the outcome of the Duel.
If you use that card to destroy Yugi,
your life will be saved!
And if you choose otherwise...
...you can both die together!
Shit!
Is there nothing we can do?!
Jounouchi...!
My brother!
Brother! We're almost out of time!
Please!
Someone stop them!
If this keeps up, they're both going to die!
Forget about me!
Just save Yugi and Jounouchi!
But we can't sacrifice the hostage in the process...!
Goddamn Ghouls...!
I've got no choice but to make a gamble...
It's me.
Can you hear me?
Death Meteor has a cost of 500 Life Points,
while giving the opponent 1000 points of damage.
Now!
It's time for you to use this card to finish Yugi off!
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
If you won't toss aside your heart as a Duelist,
and insist on defying me to the bitter end...
then you can have the pleasure of killing your friend in this Duel!
And it'll be branded into your memories forever!
My... memories...?
My... memories as a Duelist...
That's the Duelist Kingdom.
The Harpie Lady Beauty Combo!
Because of this card, they get more charming and stronger...
Alright, let’s go!
Thousand Dragon!
Thousand Nose Breath!!
All right! Here it is! My ultimate card!
Time Magic!!
As promised, give your star chips and Red-Eyes to me!
This is my card!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Also, I play the Fusion Magic Card I had hidden on the board!
Fuse with Demon!
Meteor Flare!!
What happened to the confidence you had before, Jounouchi? Gone already?
Jounouchi... it really suits you to be on your knees.
Like a loser dog unable to stand up after a single loss.
Stand up, Jounouchi!
Save those tears for if you lose the Duel!
Huh? What's this?
This little baby's gonna seriously Duel against me?
Against the great Bandit Keith?!
Eat this!!
Dark Mega Flare!!
The final round will feature Yugi Mutou versus Katsuya Jounouchi.
Bring it to me, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun, the prize money belongs to you.
Eh?
I'd like you to use the prize money for Shizuka-chan's operation.
Thank you!
Please duel with me again.
Alright! Insect Queen's exterminated!
MY QUEEN~!!
That was splendid, Jounouchi.
I lose.
I'll be sure to cherish this card!
I'm countin' on ya!
Next time, I'll be sure to win!
I'll continue to get even stronger!
I want to become someone I can respect... a True Duelist.
No, in this Battle City, I'll become one!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
My... memories...!
Kill him!
Kill him!!
KILL YUGI!!!
Now! Kill your best friend along with your memories, and obtain ultimate victory!!
Now! Kill him! Kill him!!
SHUT UP!!
I DON'T WANNA HAVE THAT IN MY MEMORIES!!
Jounouchi-kun!
Silence!!
All you need to do is keep your mouth shut and do as I tell you!!
So get a move on! Finish Yugi off!
Jounouchi-kun...
You're fighting against Malik's brainwashing, aren't you?
And you're trying to find yourself...
But...
We're almost out of time!
But I won't let you die!
Malik!
I know you're watching this Duel from somewhere around here!
I finally figured out who the loser of this Duel is!
And it's not me, or Jounouchi-kun!
It's...
Malik!
It's you!!
What!?
You can implant your evil thoughts within him using your Millennium Item,
but Jounouchi-kun will never give in to you!
Jounouchi-kun beat you!
There's only a minute left in this Duel.
And in that time, I'll get Jounouchi-kun's heart back!
I will!
Yu... gi...
And when I do, even if the both of us are dragged into the ocean and lose our lives,
The fact that you lost will be branded in your memories forever, Malik!!
You're nothing but a vessel!!
Just what are you trying to pull, Yugi?!
Yugi!
Big brother...!
Jounouchi...
Yugi...
Let's fight, Malik!
Will I get back Jounouchi-kun's heart first?
Or will you take my Life Points to 0?!
We've got no time left!
So try attacking me, Malik!
As you wish...
I'll assassinate you with this Death Meteor, Yugi!
Don't...
Silence!!
I have no further use for you!!
I'll completely take over that body of yours!!
DIE, YUGI!!
DEATH METEOR!!
It's all over!!
Yugi...
DON'T DIE, YUGI!!
Jounouchi-kun!
Wh-What!?
That's impossible!
Jounouchi revived his heart, even though I had complete control over it!?
Yugi!
You got your heart back, didn't you, Jounouchi-kun?!
Reverse Card, open!
Spirit's Mirror!!
A Counter Trap for when the opponent uses a Magic Card!
The Spirit's Mirror allows me to absorb and redirect the attack!
Yugi...
The Effect of Spirit's Mirror places Death Meteor in Yugi's hands...
And now Yugi can redirect the attack at his opponent...
He can attack Jounouchi...
...or attack himself!
There's no time...!
Still not here?!
Why are we fighting?
That's enough, Jounouchi-kun.
Our fight's over.
Over?
I believed...
That we weren't the ones fighting in this Duel.
You were fighting Malik within your heart.
And I was fighting to ensure our friendship stayed in tact.
Even though I had to fight myself!
And we both won!
Yugi!
They're so slow! Still not here?!
What!?
I've only got one chance!
Goddess of Dueling, please let this be a common card!
Forgive me!
You bastard!
I won't let you!
-Anzu!
Guys!
Thank you, Mokuba-kun.
Now we're even.
Let's hurry to Yugi and Jounouchi!
Right!
Unfortunately, I'm too good a drawer...
Brother...
I played Spirit's Mirror so I can buy a little time.
So I could say everything I wanted to say at the end...
"The end"?
Jounouchi-kun...
You taught me I wasn't alone.
And you taught me courage... you're my best friend.
Yugi...
Jounouchi-kun...
I love you!
Yugi!
Spirit!
Aim the Death Meteor attack at me!
Yugi!!
-Yugi!!
Jounouchi-kun...!
The bomb has been activated now...
Only thirty seconds left...
In that time... use that key... and escape...
Hurry...
Before the anchor falls into the ocean...
You idiot!!
I can't leave you behind and run away!!
Thanks for fighting with me... my deck...
I really... thank you...
What can I do...?!
What the hell can I do?!
That's right!
If I remember correctly, Death Meteor has one more Effect...
Death Meteor allows me to force one of the opponent's Monsters to attack...!
Red-Eyes!
Attack me!
Shoot a Black Fire Bullet, and reduce my Life Points to 0!
Thanks, Red-Eyes!
Yugi!
I won't let you die!
I don't have time to grab my own key!
Big brother!
Please make it in time!
Jounouchi!!
Honda!!
No!!
Yugi!! Jounouchi!!
Yugi!
Jounouchi...-kun...
I'm sorry, Yugi...
And thank you...
Yugi!
I've got you! Just hang on!
Where's Jounouchi?!
The key!
Jounouchi didn't grab his key!
Mokuba! Go grab the other key!
I'll go down after him!
Right!
I knew it, the key won't work...
I-I can't breathe...!
Am I... gonna die like this...?
Huh?
Is that Yugi?
He's such an idiot...
So he came back down...?
Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Jounouchi!
Shizuka...!
You...
Everyone brought me all the way out here.
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi!
Guys!
In his haste to remove the Duel Disk, he purposely didn't grab his own key...
His stupidity is something to be admired...
So he's finally reached the level of a deadbeat Duelist...
Yugi...
I...
S-Sorry!
It's fine, Jounouchi-kun.
No it's not...!
What I did to you was...
You protected what's important to us.
That's enough.
No, it's not enough!
It's true I have no memory of when it first started.
I was completely being controlled by that bastard.
But I gradually became aware of what I was doing...
I knew full well what I was doing to you...
And even then...!
I couldn't stop myself...!
Jounouchi-kun...
I can't forgive myself for that.
I'm a failure as a Duelist!
Don't be such a baby!
I didn't know you were a man who would throw away his Duelist's pride so easily!
You fought hard at the Kingdom so your sister could see!
And now you're gonna crawl into a hole because you're ashamed of something you did?!
I don't want Shizuka seeing me like this! I'm a failure of a brother!
I'm already long past gone!!
Stop feeling sorry for yourself, Jounouchi!
Shizuka-chan came all this way to give you courage!
That's right, Shizuka...!
Your eyes...!
You've given me more than enough courage, big brother!
The first thing I saw...
...was you putting your life on the line to save Yugi-san!
Shizuka...
We were separated, but now I'm by your side again.
Because your friends supported me.
At last, I found you big brother.
Yugi.
This belongs to you.
Yugi... thank you...
You saved my life back there...
I almost cast our treasured friendship to sea...
Because I was such a stupid idiot...
Other me... Jounouchi-kun and I won...
I got Jounouchi-kun's heart back from Malik!
Partner...
I learned something from you.
That kindness lies the greatest strength of all...
One day... you will surpass me in every way...
When that time comes...
Let's go, Mokuba.
Kaiba-kun!
Tell the other Yugi this...
That you and your friends have give me "the answer"...
Kaiba-kun...
I'll be waiting for you at the final stage of the Battle City tournament!
The Battle City finals...
The battle for the God Cards is finally starting!
I'll defeat Malik!
"Preview"
After learning Malik failed to kill Yugi, the dark personality of Bakura-kun
sets off to enter the Battle City tournament in order to accomplish his own goals.
Bakura-kun challenges Ghost Kotsuzuka to a Duel, betting for all six of their Puzzle Cards.
Since they both use spooky Occult-themed cards, this Duel's gonna be really scary!
Next time!
"The Ghost Deck VS the Occult Deck"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...