Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
All right!
Yugi won!
He won the Battle City Tournament!
Now that Malik's dark half is gone,
Mai and Bakura have returned to normal!
Yugi's won all the God Cards!
This is incredible news!
And- what?!
The island's gonna explode?!
Kaiba! There's a limit to being
a sore loser, you know!
And just as we were about to escape, the Battle Ship's engine stopped working!
What the hell's gonna happen to us?!
"Alcatraz Burns"
Kaiba!
Seto-sama!!
Mokuba!
Hey, you two! Stop being babies
and get your asses out here!
This is no time for jokes!
If we leave those two on the island,
they're really gonna die, you know!
yeah, my bad, my bad.
But if they can't fix the engine in the
Battle Ship, we're in hot water too!
True. Either way, our best bet
is to find Kaiba and have him
deactivate the time switch.
Anyway, let's keep looking for him!
This island isn't that big.
We're sure to find him.
That's true.
Yugi...
I fought you on this tower and lost.
Kaiba...
Hatred does not lead to true victory!
You had to lose to me...
so you can defeat your own madness!
My friend lent me this card.
I won through
the power of my friends!
The power of friendship, huh...?
Big brother, I put in the password!
No good?!
God dammit!
Battle City was not only
my struggle to become Duel King...
I've also been fighting my grudge
against Gozaburo, deep in my heart...
Was it my hatred that
called him back from the dead?
He's been an obstacle standing
in my way almost my entire life...
Good of you to come, Seto.
I've been waiting to have a nice, long chat with you.
Humph. Don't make me laugh.
Now don't be like that.
We've got plenty of time.
Even if we had a hundred years
to sit and chat, I would only have
one thing to say to you...
Let us return to
the Real World at once!
You know, it's been some time
since we used a game to settle
one of our disputes.
Just like the time I took you
on as my adopted son.
SETO~!!!
Gozaburo!
I will not be swallowed
by the likes of you!!
But in the end, he was nothing
more than a crazy ghost...
And I already beat him until
there was nothing left...
And now, as the new president
of Kaiba Corporation,
I am about to sink all traces
of him into the sea.
But...
Was I able to defeat those feelings
inside of me, holding me back...?
What's wrong?
We have to hurry, big brother!
But what road
should I walk now...?
That day a long time ago...
I told Mokuba my dream...
It's finished, Mokuba!
Our Sand Park is complete!
Wow! That's awesome, big brother!
That's my big brother for you!
This is nothing!
Hmm?
Listen up, Mokuba!
This is your big brother's dream!
I want to build amusement parks
all around the world!
Not parks made out of sand!
Real amusement parks!
An amusement park where kids
who don't have parents...
...like us kids at the orphanage...
can play for free!
You mean we can all play together?
Yeah!
Perhaps, like these ruins on Alcatraz,
my heart was buried in its own ruins...
Big brother, hurry up!
Lying somewhere under this rubble...
...is the road to my dream!
We've only got a time limit
of 13 minutes left!
What?! Just 13 minutes?!
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
You gotta stop the time switch!
The Battle Ship's still not
going anywhere, right?!
Seto-sama and Mokuba-sama are
the only ones who know how
to stop the time switch...
Damn that bastard Kaiba!
You don't think Kaiba-kun
really plans to sink along with this
island into the sea, do you?
There's no way he would.
Other me...
Kaiba is the kind of man who only
looks forward to the future and
never looks back on the past.
I'm certain he has already found
another way to escape this island.
I want to think that, but...
We're running out of time.
Let's return to the Battle Ship.
You're right.
It's possible those two returned
while we were out looking for them.
Or maybe they fixed the engine.
Yeah.
Otogi! Have they fixed the engine yet?!
It's not looking good!
It still isn't fixed!
What'd you say?!
We've only got ten minutes left...
Damn! What the hell are they doing?!
Hold it! Can you fix the engine?!
Shut up!
I'm just gonna pulverize it!
It's the helicopter that came
here to pick up Jounouchi!
It's still here!
Lucky!
We're abandoning this ship!
Let's get a move on!
It's going to explode!
We have no time!
I never thought the
helicopter that came here for you
would come in handy now...
Less than one minute left!
We have no choice...
Bring her up!
30 seconds remain...
Kaiba...
Mokuba-kun...
Ten seconds left!!
Detonate!!
Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun!
The Duel Tower!!
Even the Battle Ship...!
The island... is sinking...!
That's...!
The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
WHAT~!!?
What'cha think?!
Amazing, ain't it?!
W-Well, it is amazing...
I don't believe this...
These guys are genuine idiots...
I-I guess, as long as they're safe...
Hey big brother,
they're riding on a helicopter...
Humph... Looks like they had some
trouble with the Battle Ship.
OI, KAIBA!
H-Hey!
It's your fault we almost went
down with that island!
Then you have the nerve to laugh?!
See, in order to build
Kaiba Lands all over the world,
me and my brother
are goin' to America!
Build... Kaiba Lands around the world?
I'll invite you all
one of these days.
Kaiba...
So, Kaiba... This is your new road...
Yugi... Our battle is not over!
Kaiba...
Let's go, Mokuba!
To America! Depart!!
Kaiba-kun has started
a journey toward his new dream!
Yeah!
And now... the other me's journey to
find his memories has just begun.
All right! Time for us
to return to Domino City!
Kaiba Land all over the world, huh...?
I'm really looking
forward to it, big brother!
I really wish
he could see it, too...
It's all thanks to you...
Malik has been freed from the curse
of his dark half plaguing his heart.
Thank you, Pharaoh.
We three will take a new path...
and rebuild the Ishtar family
in a shining future!
Pharaoh... And "vessel" Yugi.
A day will soon come where
you visit the land of Egypt.
When that day comes, I hope you
will see us again... as friends.
We will!
Egypt...
The place where
the other Yugi must return...
I... get the feeling
there isn't much time left...
And now, we bid every single
one of you farewell.
Goodbye!
See ya, Malik!
Take care!
Now then...
I'm going back to America.
Otogi!
After hearing about Kaiba-kun's plan
to build Kaiba Land around the world,
I decided I can't
waste any more time.
It's time I think of
a new plan for my D.D.M.
Goodbye, Shizuka-chan.
Goodbye.
He slipped her
his cellphone number!
Otogi!!
Damn you!!
See you again!
Do your best!
Everyone's leaving...
Yeah... Everyone's got their own goals.
They've all got
their own paths to follow.
I wonder... what my path...
and goals are.
Don't rush it.
You'll find it eventually.
I'm sure of it.
You're right.
You're right about that, Shizuka-chan!
Honda!!
Well, I suppose it's my turn.
Mai!
You're also leaving, Mai-san?
I've spent a little too much time
roaming around here...
The Battle City Tournament is over.
So there's no reason for me
to stay in this town any more.
Mai-san...
I... Mai-san...
I don't want to see you go...
I'm sure he'll be just fine.
He really is a good man.
He's kind... and courageous...
Even back in Duelist Kingdom, he fought for you as if his very life was at risk.
That's why I'm certain the brother you see will be one who will never betray you.
Mai-san!
Well, I may have over-exaggerated a bit there...
I really thank you very much...
I'm the one
who should be thanking you.
You were by my side the entire time I was
unconscious, weren't you, Shizuka-chan?
Thank you.
Yugi!
I won't lose to you
the next time we meet!
Right!
All right then!
Take care, everyone!
Bye bye!
Mai...
Hey. What the heck are you doing?
Eh?
At least have the decency
to say goodbye properly!
Mai!
Ya see...
What was it...?
I had a lot of fun
hanging around you guys.
So much so that I lost track of time.
But...
I guess your friendship was
a little too bright for me.
Do your best.
Right back at you!
Well, see you around.
Later!
Jounouchi...
You sure have grown.
Into a fine True Duelist.
I wonder if I'm being unfair to him...?
But I can't let things end here!
Every one of us are about
to walk down a new road!
And I'm going to
walk down my road!
Alright, it's finished.
Where you headed
this early in the morning?
Uh, right... Just a walk.
I see.
Just be careful.
Mmm-hmm!
It's a good chance
to pay them back.
You should beat these guys up too.
Stop!
There's no way
I'll do that to my friends!
It'll be over for sure if I do this!
What!?
Damn!
Jounouchi-kun!
Wait for me, Yugi!
I'll find it.
I... I can't leave without the puzzle.
1, 2, 3...pull!
Jounouchi-kun, this is your card.
Yugi...
Right now I can't take Red-Eyes back.
I want to become someone I can respect... a True Duelist.
No, in this Battle City, I'll become one!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
I understand.
We'll fight each other then, Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi-kun...
You taught me I wasn't alone.
And you taught me courage... you're my best friend.
Yugi...
Jounouchi-kun...
I love you!
Stop screwing around...!
If I lose, I'll never see Mai...
...and Yugi...
...EVER AGAIN!!
WHAT!?
Yugi...
I...
Gearfried... The...
I won...
But...!
After that...
What will I have left then...?!
Please...!
Don't die on me...!
I wanted to ask you
what a True Duelist is...
Jounouchi-kun...!
You're early, Jounouchi-kun.
Heh, I was working
on my deck until morning.
Same here.
Let's do this, Yugi!
Our Battle City isn't over yet!
Yeah!
DUEL!!
Now that the Battle City Tournament has ended, everyone has begun walking their own path.
And now that the other Yugi has obtained a clue on how to find his lost memories along with the three God Cards,
a new adventure is
right around the corner.
Saying that, when I think back on everything that happened with Yugi in Domino City,
it feels kind of nostalgic.
So what awaits us... is a farewell?
Or...
Next time!
"A Sign"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other