Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Noah, why have you trapped us inside this Virtual Space?
Why are you so bent on trying to surpass me?
I'm sure the answer lies in whether you are truly Gozaburo's real son or not.
But your claims are nothing but bullshit and mind games.
I'll expose the truth!
And I will save Mokuba!
"The Big Five's Counterattack"
First you lose the Duels... Now you're trying to steal their bodies by force.
You sure are the lowest of men.
Your job has long ended.
Don't ever show your
faces before me again.
Oh! Please wait a moment, Noah-sama!
There aren't even enough bodies for you to obtain?
Outa has one already...!
We just need for more bodies!
Now wait a moment. Noah-sama has made himself perfectly clear.
The truth is that you four lost your Duels, so you don't get a second chance.
What?!
I am the only one who obtained our prized goal!
I won my Duel and obtained it!
As such, this body belongs to me!
"Won my Duel"?
Cut the bullshit.
You lost!
That's right! You lost your Duel!
As such, the prize you obtained belongs in right to every one of us!
What was that?!
But Noah-sama...!
There's no helping it.
I will grant you guys one final chance.
The one you will be facing is our Seto Kaiba's one and only rival, Yugi Mutou.
If you win, the remaining four of you will also be granted a body.
I'm sure there is no problem with that, right?
Yes, we thank you very much, Noah-sama.
We shall not disappoint you this time around, Noah-sama.
This time, for certain!
Seriously, I don't want to see a single one of you any more!
Noah is the true son of the former president of Kaiba Corporation?
Yeah, he said something to that effect.
But why would Noah want Mokuba so badly?
Noah seems to have a serious grudge against Kaiba-kun.
So he kidnapped Mokuba-kun in order to make Kaiba-kun suffer...
Hold it!
What do you want...?
Where are you off to?
If it's to save Mokuba-kun, we're going to!
Humph, I already told you.
Eh?
That this is a problem between us brothers.
It has nothing to do with any of you.
So out of the way!
But it does concern us!
Isn't that right?
We were all dragged into this mess without knowing why.
And besides... Mokuba-kun is our friend as well!
It's only natural to
worry about your friends!
In that case, you should start worrying about him.
Honda!
No! He's not Honda!
My-! My body!
Give it back!
Well we know the one who stole Honda-kun's body was Outa, the former President of Military Affairs of Kaiba Corporation.
I'm not alone!
Is "Honda" the name of the kid this body used to belong to?
Inside this body lies us...
...the Big Five!
The Big Five!
Yugi Mutou, you are to Duel against us, the Big Five!
This time I'll get myself a cute, sexy body all for myself!
That voice is...!
The penguin!
I get it! But if I win, you must return Honda-kun's body!
Very well. It's a deal.
Hang on!
Don't promise that on your own!
And why must I share the body I won with the lot of you?!
Stop complaining.
We'll return it to you once we get bodies of our own!
I would like you all to leave the negotiations to a trained lawyer such as myself.
Okay! Let's Duel, Yugi!
Okay! Whatever you want!
I accept this Duel!
Hold it right there!
You jerks! How is five-on-one fair?!
That's way too much of a handicap!
Count me in, too!
Jounouchi-kun!
I don't know if Honda's body will really return or not...
...but we can't just stand here when it's right in front of us, right?
Yeah. Help me out, Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi, you're that worried about my body...!
You better win, ooh~!
I understand. Very well.
Wait! Won't that put us at risk?!
"Put us at risk"?
Jounouchi will only hold Yugi back.
It's actually in our favor.
He's that type of Duelist.
Completely ignoring the fact that you lost to this very same Jounouchi, mind you.
Anyway, I ask of you all to leave all negotiate matters in this Duel to me.
I have a plan!
I suggest a Tag Duel is the best solution for this situation.
But that would leave the matter of Life Points questionable.
It puts as at an unfair disadvantage.
As such, I propose that you two each hold 4000 Life Points while we hold 8000.
Are you two alright with that?
Just as I expected from the liar lawyer.
No helping it. I get it.
Now choose your deck!
Mai...
Just wait a bit longer, Mai...
Right now we have to get back that idiot Honda's body.
But after we do that, we'll get the hell outta here and settle things with Malik!
Then you'll get back to normal.
My Deck Master will be Black Magician!
I'm using Flame Swordsman!
We will pick a new Deck Master on each one of our turns.
I, Ooshuta, will take the first turn.
You will be facing Deepsea Warrior!
You can do this, Yugi! Jounouchi!
Don't worry! Yugi and Jounouchi will win for sure!
Right! You'll be back in your own body before you know it!
You guys~!
Thanks alot, ooh~!
And you,too, Shizuka-chan!
Do your best, big brother.
Now let's go!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate the Field Magic, Legendary City of Atlantis!
Run, Shizuka-chan!
Damn!
A Field Magic right off the bat?!
And then I Summon The Legendary Fisherman!
That's the Monster Ryouta Kajiki cherished so much!
But hold on... I'm sure that Monster was Level 5...
How come he was able to Summon it right away?
It's the Field Magic's Effect.
Correct. Legendary City of Atlantis is a Field Magic Card holding the effect to downgrade a Monster Level.
As such, a Level 5 Monster automatically becomes a Level 4.
So it can be Summoned
without a sacrifice!
His Deck Master
is also a Water-Attribute.
So he's pretty much guaranteed his own victory, right?
Turn over!
Be careful, Jounouchi-kun.
Don't let him shake us to his will.
I know that, man!
I already made it this far by beating Ryouta Kajiki!
Yugi, I'm taking the next turn!
My turn!
Here goes, Wyvern Warrior!
Summon!
No one can attack in the first turn of a Tag Duel.
Now my turn's over.
Just you wait, Honda...
I'll get your body back no matter what it takes!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Illusionary Beast Gazelle!
Defense Position!
My turn is over!
My turn!
Draw!
Huh?
You've done well, Ooshuta.
But now that The Legendary Fisherman is out, it's my turn.
Hey! Hold on!
I'm still not done here!
Silence your tongue!
Penguin Nightmare's Deck Master Ability raises the Attack Power of all Water-Attribute Monsters!
Let me handle this now.
Draw!
His voice changed!
Does that mean he's traded places?
That is correct.
You will now be facing me, Shuzo Outaki at age 55, along with Penguin Nightmare!
I'll be beating you guys here and getting my hands on a cute girl's body!
Please, Yugi! You have to beat him!
Thanks to the effect of Field Magic, Legendary City of Atlantis,
all Water-Attribute Monsters will have their Attack and Defense Power increased by 200.
But The Legendary Fisherman is currently unaffected by the effects of Magic Cards.
That means his
Attack Power won't change.
Still, I'll be attacking your Gazelle with The Legendary Fisherman!
Since my Deck Master Ability is not a Magic Effect, The Legendary Fisherman's Attack Power increases by 200 points!
Following that, I place Catapult Turtle in Defense Mode!
He was able to Summon another Level 5 Monster without even breaking a sweat!
Turn over!
Dammit.
We're in trouble if we don't get rid of that Legendary City of Atlantis!
Yeah.
The renowned Gozaburo Kaiba only had one true son. And that is me, Noah Kaiba.
So Gozaburo adopted
me as a test for Noah...?
Noah claims that, anyway...
But if that's really true, it's strange that Noah isn't around the same age I am.
But the "Noah" in front of me now is just a little kid.
There's only two
explanation I can think of...
One is that everything he said is nothing but nonsense.
And the other that Noah is already dead and is a ghost who rose from the dead to appose me.
So I'm fighting a ghost...?
Sounds like occult garbage Yugi would come out with.
Worthless.
Shit... If I can't see
your Monster, I can't attack!
My turn! Draw!
Chain-Equipped Boomerang...
Good. With this,
I can slip past his Field Magic
and lower The Legendary Fisherman's Attack Points.
I set one reverse card!
I'm counting on you, Mai!
I then Summon Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage!
And I then switch Wyvern Warrior into Attack Mode!
Turn over!
My turn!
Draw!
I don't have a card in my hand that can destroy their Field Magic.
Jounouchi-kun's set card...
I'll let Jounouchi-kun handle this.
I Summon Holy Elf in Defense Position!
Turn over!
Looks like it's my turn next.
Not yet. My subordinate is still on the field, so your turn will have to wait.
Draw!
I'm the one who'll beat Yugi!
Legendary Fisherman, attack the Holy Elf!
Hold it right there!
Trap Card, activate!
Chain-Equipped Boomerang!
Nice one, Jounouchi-kun!
Too bad!
Thanks to the Chain-Equipped Boomerang, your Legendary Fisherman is forced into Defense Mode!
And one of the Monsters on my field has their Attack Power increased by 500 points!
God! You guys keep on going "Yugi! Yugi!" all the time!
But you're fighting more than just Yugi here!
Heaven's sake!
What are you playing at?!
Pull your act together!
Shut yer traps!
I'm not out of the picture yet!
I set one Monster in reverse!
My turn is over now!
Sweet! Nice one, Jounouchi-kun!
That was great, big brother!
But he's still got that Field Magic on the field, ooh-ah!
We still can't rest at ease, ooh-ah!
By the way, I've been wondering about this for a while now...
"Ooh-ah"... Honda, you're sounding more and more like a monkey every minute!
You alright?
Huh? You serious, ooh~?
I'm in some serious hot water here!
I'll spend the rest of my life as a monkey, ooh!
Come on, Jounouchi! Hurry and get my body back!
Here I go! My turn!
Draw!
Booyah!
Now I can get rid of his Field Magic!
I knew I made the right choice putting Mai's card in my deck!
Magic Card! Harpy's Feather Duster!
Activate!
And now the effects of The Legendary City of Atlantis Field Magic Card are gone!
Go on, Harpy Lady Cyber Bondage!
Attack The Legendary Fisherman!
There's more where that came from!
This time I'll attack with Wyvern Warrior!
Oh snap, Catapult Turtle has 2000 Defense Points.
Even with the power up Wyvern Warrior gets from Chain-Equipped Boomerang, they've still got the same Attack Points.
Alright! In that case, I'll dispose of that face-down card instead!
Wait, Jounouchi-kun!
That's far too dangerous!
It's fine, man!
Just you watch, Yugi!
Nothing's impossible for me!
Wyvern Warrior, beat his face-down Defense Monster to smithereens!
I activate Saint Magician's Reverse Effect!
I am permitted to add one Magic Card from my Graveyard to my hand.
What?
And of course, this is the Magic Card I take back!
Dammit! After all that work, he got The Legendary City of Atlantis back!
You youngin's sure are soft!
Shit! Turn over!
Sorry about that, Yugi...
I got a bit full of myself...
Don't worry about it, Jounouchi-kun.
It's not that big of a deal, really.
My turn!
Draw!
On my next turn, I'll activate the Field Magic, The Legendary City of Atlantis once more...
And using Resurrection of the Dead, I'll bring back The Legendary Fisherman and bring back perfection!
Looks like a bunch of whipper snappers like you two are always one or even two steps behind an intelligent adult such as myself!
I wonder about that.
Sorry, but it looks like I was one step further than that!
Say that again...
I Summon Kuriboh in Defense Position!
And I activate the Magic Card, Hand Obliteration!
Now you must return The Legendary City of Atlantis you worked so hard to get back to the Graveyard once again.
Nice one, Yugi!
You're really something else!
Now we all draw the same number of cards from our decks!
Turn over!
Shit...! My turn!
You've done enough!
Your turn is over now.
I'm up this turn!
They switched again?!
OOOH~! What do ya think my body is, ooh-ah~?!
That aside, the tension here is unbelievable.
You guys didn't notice?
Even after all of this harsh Dueling action,
not a single person lost
any of their Life Points!
But that all ends right here and now.
Now that I, Ouka Chikuzen, along with Judge Man are your opponents,
it is just a matter of time before all of your Life Points drop to zero!
MOKUBA~!!
WHERE ARE YOU?!
ANSWER ME~!!
What will you do?
Will you return to his side?
No... My only brother is Noah-sama...
That's...
Kaiba Land!
The Big Five keep switching back and forth, launching wicked attacks.
But it looks like they're just aiming for Jounouchi now!
Yugi launches a strong Trap in self defense,
but a certain Trap-destroying Monster appears that's similar to Jounouchi's.
But hold on! Yugi seems to have figured out a way around their scheme!
Next time!
"Jounouchi is Targeted: Working Together for a Victory Play"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise