Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Iceberg Duel: Anzu Targeted"
Almost there.
You can do this, Anzu!
How far does this go on for?
Partner... we can't waste anymore time.
Didn't those guys say that they're here to get our bodies?
We have to hurry and find the others.
Their Duels might begin soon.
Let's hurry.
Yeah.
Yugi Mutou...
The man who defeated Seto Kaiba and then went on to beat Pegasus.
It'll be hard on you if you exhaust yourself.
Let me prepare a
special labyrinth for you.
Wh-What's happening?
Noah-sama...
Is this Outaki?
Yes.
Can you assign me the next fight?
Sure... which opponent shall I choose?
No thanks, I've already got my target.
Do what you want then.
I can't take anymore.
Hey Yugi, do you have the Black Magician Girl card?
I heard that it's a pretty rare card.
Yeah, I have it.
See?
That's it?
But why do you wanna see this card?
Oh, I get it.
It's that musical, "The Black Magician Girl and the Sage's Jewel", right?
Yeah... It's a musical I attended in Broadway that I'll never forget.
If I ever get to go abroad to study dance, I'd like to play that role someday.
You're kidding!
Yugi!
Yu... gi...
A penguin?
You're...!
Before...!
What?
You're saying, "follow me"?
You want me to get on this raft?
That hurt.
Hey, where are you taking me?
Wait!
What?
There's so many penguins!
A colony of penguins?
Welcome. Anzu Mazaki, 16 years old.
Who's there?
Show yourself right now!
Relax.
The audition has begun already!
Audition?
You really want to
play a role in it, right?
"The Black Magician Girl and the Sage's Jewel" musical.
Our company, Kaiba Corporation, has sponsored countless musical performances in Broadway.
Choosing you for the lead role would be a breeze.
You want to perform in Broadway?
Sounds good, doesn't it?
It's a musical you've been wanting to take part in, right?
Don't tell me you're...!
Right... I was with Kaiba Corporation.
I used to work as the manager of the personnel department.
I am Shuzo Outaki at age 55.
Let's start the audition process!
What are you getting at?
Anzu Mazaki at age 16.
Because of your father's work, you've been moving around the world since your childhood.
After attending the show, "The Black Magician Girl and the Sage's Jewel", in New York, you were touched.
How do you know this?
Our information network is not to be underestimated!
Good performance in every kind of sport.
But you refused invitations
to multiple clubs,
and secretly took a part-time job in a hamburger shop.
All to save money so you can study dance oversees.
That sure is admirable.
But do you have what it takes to make that dream come true?!
I'll never know unless I try!
I think the result is clear.
Because in the resume, you have clearly stated...
You're also the kind of person that lingers in the same position
and never looks into their self...
...who cares only about their self.
With the exception of a certain foolish young man present among us.
You have no potential!
All that awaits you
is a pathetic future!
Hold on!
Don't go labeling me like that!
Since your birth, you've littered 12 times.
Forgot to turn off the faucet 35 times.
Forgot to turn off the lights 62 times.
Liar!
If all of the people on Earth were to learn this about you, what will happen?
Wasting energy and resources is one of the leading causes of global warming.
And this will make the penguins suffer even more!
The penguins?
Those who can't understand the penguins are sentenced to never accomplish anything!
What're you talking about?
But you can be at ease...
I shall use your body...
...and you shall be reborn!
I'll make you into a High School girl who respects the Earth!
Like hell I'd accept a challenge from a sickening old fart like you!
I won't let you escape!
Anzu Mazaki, age 16...
You failed your interview!
What?
What's going on?
I have chosen the
Frozen Ocean to be our field!
Come on, Anzu Mazaki, age 16!
Pick cards from those in front of you and make your deck.
The only way to escape from here with your body in tact
is to defeat me in a Duel!
You told me to choose them...
But I don't know where to start...
The Sage's Jewel?
That could be of some help...
Anyway, I have to pick cards that look powerful.
Now if you're done, be sure to choose a card to act as your Deck Master.
My Deck Master is this one...
Black Magician Girl!
So there's two young ladies...
My excitement just doubled!
My Deck Master, as you can see, is Penguin Nightmare.
Let's begin the... "Cold Duel on Ice"!
I won't let myself lose to you!
Duel!!
What the heck is this?
Don't touch that!
I can sense there is something bad about that door.
A Monster appeared
in the doorway!
Partner... it seems a new game is going to start for us.
My turn!
Draw!
I drew a good card!
I'll set one reverse card!
And... I'll Summon Ancient Elf!
My turn is over.
Then it's my turn. Draw.
I'll Summon The Giant Red Sea Monster, Caesarion!
Caesarion's Attack Power
just went up!
Right... My Deck Master Ability lets me power up my Water-Attribute Monsters.
So that makes my Monster's Attack Power way stronger than yours!
But... I have Mirror Force on my side!
Alright, hurry up
and attack me already!
I'm in no rush.
Despite the fact that I'm pretty old, there's one thing in my benefit.
You know what it is?
What is it?!
Well you see...
I am an extremely cautious person.
The card at your feet
is very likely to be a Trap.
I can't believe you have the nerve to try and trap an old man!
But your tricks won't work on me at all.
I'll launch another Magic card, Extreme Cold Wave.
The power of this Magic Card makes all set cards invalidated for one turn.
Now there's nothing interfering with my attack on you!
Go, Caesarion!
Ancient Elf!
I forgot to tell you...
In this Duel, a part of the player will be frozen as their Life Points decrease.
Feeling cold? I bet you are!
Before long,
you'll be completely frozen.
''Yu-Gi-Oh Episode 102 Subbed''
Timing for original raw episode corrected by latiasfan2004
It's... it's so cold.
Yugi...
Anzu! Where are you, Anzu?
It's so cold.
Anzu!
Do you think Anzu's started a Duel against someone already?
He's letting us hear that Anzu's in trouble on purpose.
What a wicked thing to do.
We have to hurry and find Anzu!
Don't panic, partner.
Even if you get out of this darkness, you won't be able to do anything.
But Anzu...
Look up above the door...
I see... the star means the level of the Monster.
Correct... Noah set that trap for our next little game.
Now that we know that, it'll be easy to get out of here.
No Level One Monster
can beat this card!
Go, Winged Dragon Guardian of the Fortress!
We did it.
Look, partner.
There is still a door there.
Let's go.
Well, it's your turn.
I know.
My turn... Draw.
I-I'll place a Monster in Defense Position.
Hey now, your hands are shaking.
That's what you get for wearing such shameful clothes!
Th-This turn is over now.
You poor little thing.
Perhaps you'd like my favorite underwear as a present to help you warm up?
My turn.
Now then, whatever shall I do?
This one? No, maybe this one?
You're procrastinating on purpose! That's really cruel!
I'm not really afraid
of a female Spellcaster...
But if Black Magician is Summoned and they both use their power, I'll be in trouble.
I'd better watch out.
Black Magician?!
Huh?
Anzu Mazaki, 16 years old. What's wrong with you?
Nothing at all!
You don't mean to tell me... you didn't even include Black Magician in your deck?!
Hey now, seems I hit bullseye!
So ignorant!
Having Black Magician and Black Magician Girl work together in a pair in your deck
is Duel Monsters common sense!
Black Magician Girl
without Black Magician...
It's just like eating
curry without pickles!
Shut up!
You won't complain when I win!
Too bad you aren't any good.
You don't have a reason to be confident.
You really are just a young ignorant child stuck in the present!
I set two reverse cards.
I'll then end my turn.
This guy set reverse cards to try and persuade me not to attack...
What's that empty brain of yours trying to cook up?
I bet you're scared.
You're an agitating old man!
My turn!
I'll use the Instant Magic, Cyclone!
This card will destroy
one of your set cards!
You sure fell for it!
I've been waiting for this moment!
Trap Card, activate!
Driving Snow!
Driving Snow is a card that is activated when a covered card is destroyed.
Now your set card will be destroyed!
That was close! Too close!
So that was the
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force, eh?
Now the obstacle before
Caesarion is gone.
No, I'm not out of turns yet.
I'll be your hand.
Black Magician Girl...!
I'm gonna play my next card! Offerings to the Dead!
In exchange for skipping my next Draw Phase, I can destroy one of the Monsters on your side of the field!
Also, I'll switch my Defense Position Monster into Attack Position!
Wake up!
The fire magician, Fire Sorcerer!
Please... give us warmth!
Thank you!
Now I'll use
Fire Sorcerer's Special Effect!
I discard two cards from my hand in order to inflict 800 points of damage on my opponent!
HOT, HOT, HOT~!!
My attack is not over yet!
Go, Fire Sorcerer!
Fire Blast!!
Well? It's your turn to be frozen!
Not too shabby there.
However, it takes more than this to make me cold!
I am a penguin, you know.
There is one thing
I'm interested in about you.
Oh, I take that as a compliment.
Why do you insist on disguising yourself as a penguin?!
Oh my, so that's what you were curious about...
The penguins literally saved my life!
A penguin did?
My parents didn't
get along very well.
Since my childhood, they were always quarreling.
Despite me being a child, they could care less when they did it in front of me!
I couldn't find the hope I needed to live in a place like that.
Soon after that,
I met the penguins.
Their parents got
along extremely well.
And they would even
hatch eggs together.
I had to do my
homework everyday.
I just had to watch penguins in the aquarium while doing it.
Penguins were the only support for me at that time.
I dreamed of somehow getting to live with penguins.
Finally I was able to get my dream.
When I worked at Kaiba Corporation,
I worked hard and asked the company to set up a penguin theme park in Kaiba Land.
I believed the penguins' cute looks would be very appealing and touch people's hearts!
But...
Penguins, you say?
If it's about black and white, why not go with a panda?
I refuse your proposal, Outaki.
Instead of making space for your ridiculous games,
why didn't you teach kids true kindness through the penguins?!
You're just teaching
them to hate each other!
I knew a no-talent High School girl like you would never understand me from the very start!
What's more, I can't forgive you for helping Kaiba!
I will steal your body,
return to the Real World
and follow me dream by creating the theme park, Penguin Land!
My turn!!
Come forth, Flying Penguin!
Because of my Deck Master Effect, he gets a power-up!
And I'll use a Magic card to equip him with the Penguin Sword!
Which gives him an
800 point power-up!!
It's got 2200 Attack Points?!
Go!! Crush that nuisance of a being!!
ICE COLD!!
Fire Sorcerer!
Anzu Mazaki, 16 years old...
Your flame of hope
has been put out.
I'll crush your dream and freeze it along with you.
Yugi...
Damn! How long is this maze?
Yugi, save me! Yugi!
That's Anzu's voice again!
We have to hurry and get out of here!
Partner, look over there by your feet!
That's the coin I dropped earlier.
So we're...
...back to where we started?
I can't defend against the attack of the old penguin!
But wait, Black Magician Girl.
If you are defeated again, we'll lose.
So before Yugi gets out of the labyrinth Noah trapped Yugi in,
I have...
I can just bet on this turn!
Come on! A method that'll help me turn this around!
Next time!
"Shine! The Sage's Jewel"
Duel Standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise