Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Haga! Ryuzaki!
Are you guys saying that your despair is caused by Yugi and myself?!
Is it because of those vengeful thoughts,
that you both decided to join forces with Doma and bet your souls?
I'm sorry, but we can't afford to lose to you guys!
Not before we wipe the floor with Doma, anyway!
But I'm worried about Yugi.
He's still in shock from that defeat...
Can he Duel properly?
"Timaeus Can't Be Activated"
It's my turn.
Draw!
Reverse Trap open!
Activate Natural Selection!
What?!
This Trap Card can only be activated during the opponent's turn.
I can create a Monster identical to a chosen Monster on my opponent's field.
The original Monster is then destroyed by this card!
What did you say?!
The Monster I choose is...
Insect Queen!
Now you've done it! How dare you destroy my queen?!
Watch carefully!
I offer this Insect Token as a sacrifice!
And I Summon Soukou Hyakusoku - Armored Centipede!
Take that!
I use Armored Centipede to attack Kuriboh!
Each Insect-Type Monster that Armor Centipede destroys...
...increases its Attack Points by 500!
I end my turn!
The Monster that resulted from Natural Selection...
...is destroyed when the opponent's turn ends.
Now the only thing still on the field is the infected Retrained Elf Swordsman...
Here goes!
Tyrant Dragon, destroy Red-Eyes!
Red-Eyes...!
We ain't done wit' you yet, Red-Eyes!
We ain't ready ta' let ya take a nap yet!
Activate Reverse Trap!
Chain of the Underworld!
What?!
Red-Eyes got brought back?!
Chain of the Underworld is activated when the opponent's Monster is destroyed.
The Attack a' the destroyed Monster goes down 700 points!
And it's returned as a Special Summoned card.
What are you planning to do, Ryuzaki?
Why would you want to Summon back the Monster you defeated?
Don't ya get it, Jounouchi?
Tyrant Dragon is a Monster that can attack twice in the Battle Phase.
But in order to do that, there's gotta be Monsters on the opponent's field.
What did you say?
So you purposely revived Red-Eyes just so that you can send it to the Graveyard again?!
Yup.
Red-Eyes betrayed me.
I won't forgive it so easily!
Now, hurry up an' draw!
Draw?!
When Chain of the Underworld is activated, the opponent gets ta' draw one card.
Draw one quickly.
Ryuzaki, do you want to this badly...?
Is that... supposed to be the punishment you have for Red-Eyes?
Everything is caused by you, Jounouchi! All your fault!
Tyrant Dragon! Destroy Red-Eyes again!
I won't let you get your way!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Blessings of Birth!
You numb?!
Traps ain't workin' 'gainst Tyrant Dragon!
Who says I'm setting that trap for Tyrant Dragon?
When a Monster has been Special Summoned as per a special effect,
this card can end the opponent's turn.
Ryuzaki, your Battle Phase is over!
Wh-What'd ya say....?
Red-Eyes...
I won't let you enter the Graveyard again!
My turn, draw!
It's finally time!
The third turn of Parasite Caterpillar's Effect!
Retrained Elf Swordsman will be destroyed,
and Poison Butterfly will be born!
Jounouchi!
You only got 300 Life Points!
No matter how much ya try, you'll never win!
You can't be sure about that until the Duel is over!
My turn, draw!
Here I go!
I Summon Iron Knight Gearfried!
Next, I activate Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
This allows me to draw another two cards from my deck!
Do you know, Ryuzaki?
Long ago, there was a Sword Master in the Duel Monsters World...
...that was known to be "unbeatable" because he was too strong.
Just one swing from the Sword Master's sword...
...can split the sea, tear the skies, and destroy the land.
It was said that nobody ever returned alive after meeting him.
Because his power was too strong...
...the Sword Master chained himself down and sealed his sword forever.
This seal will now be broken!
I activate the Magic Card, Release Restraint!
Unchain yourself and descend!
Sword Master - Naked Gear Freed!
What the?!
His Attack Power is only 2600!
Fancy creatin' such a scene!
You've drawn The Claw of Hermos, huh?
Yugi.
As long as Poison Butterfly exists on your field...
...you'll suffer 500 points of damage every turn, starting right now!
Wh-What's up?
Don't tell me he has gotten that card?!
Indeed he did... Darn!
To think that he drew that card at such a crucial point!
This is as far as you can go, Haga!
I'll end this Duel!
I activate the Monocle of Timaeus!
I'll fuse him together with Poison Butterfly to form...!
Timaeus!
Why...? Why won't it activate...?!
Hey now, don't go scaring people, Yugi!
Did Timaeus abandon... me?
What is going on?
You actually got abandoned by the card! How pathetic!
If I were you, I wouldn't be able to take it!
It's so embarrassing that I wouldn't even dare call myself a Duelist!
Shut you trap, you idiot!
End...
Turn end...
You said "end"  just now, didn't you?!
Then the Effect of Poison Butterfly will start right away!
Your Life Points will go down by 500!
Yugi has only 700 Life Points now.
If this goes on, the soul of the other Yugi will...
Yugi, you're finished!
My turn, draw!
I set one reverse card and end my turn.
The Claw of Hermos...
I remember that this card can be combined with any Monster...
...becomin' an Equipment Card.
Be prepared, Ryuzaki!
I activate The Claw of Hermos!
Sword Master!
I'm gonna give you an ultimate sword!
I equip the Red-Eyes Black Dragon Sword to Naked Gear Freed!
In this way, the Attack Power of the equipped Monster goes up by 1000 points!
In addition, for every Dragon-Type Monster existing on the field,
its Attack Power goes up by 500 points!
What'd you say?!
My Tyrant Dragon is the only Dragon-Type Monster on the field currently...
So in total, the Attack increases by 1500 points!
Naked Gear Freed now has an Attack Power of 4100 points!
That's impossible!
My Tyrant Dragon's gonna lose!
In addition, when Naked Gear Freed is equipped with an Equipment Card...
It has the Special Ability of destroying a Monster on the opponent's field, which activates now!
So, Tyrant Dragon is destroyed!
No way!
If Tyrant Dragon is gone due to a Special Ability instead of a battle...
Ryuzaki... You did have your soul taken away before, didn't you?
But you went back to normal.
So, there must surely be a way to save you!
Wait, Jounouchi!
That is why...
I need to defeat you in order to save you!
Here goes! Naked Gear Freed's attack!
Direct Attack on Ryuzaki!
Dark Mega Slash!!
Save me...!
I'm sorry, Ryuzaki.
Ryuzaki!
Get a grip, Ryuzaki!
Hey, is his soul really taken away?!
I'll definitely bring Ryuzaki's soul back.
What Doma did was unforgivable!
Playing around with these people's hearts!
Jounouchi...
Pegasus and Yugi as well... I'll bring everyone back to normal!
And Mai, too...
Just you wait, Doma!!
I'll never forgive you guys!!
I'll defeat all of you!!!
My turn, draw!
It's useless.
You're obviously gonna lose.
You're really a king who doesn't know when to give up.
I'll never give up until I save my partner with my own hands!
I Summon Magic Warrior Breaker!
This very moment, I activate a Trap Card!
Insect Swarm!
This card has the effect of reducing the Attack of all Monsters on the field by 100.
In addition, for each Monster a player controls, they receive 100 points damage per Monster.
It's my victory, Yugi!
You only have 500 of your Life Points left.
When this turn ends, Poison Butterfly's Effect will bring you to 0!
And it'll be "the end" for you!
Yugi...
Anzu-chan, you just sit there and watch him get defeated!
Hey, Yugi.
I recall some sort of promise before we began...
Didn't I say that I'd tell you where your partner is if you beat me?
Looks like I won't be able to tell you...
Because you're going to lose.
You scum!
But well, I have a very kind personality...
So I'll do you a favor and tell you.
Because you look so pitiful.
I saw it... Your partner
I saw the card that sealed the soul of the other Yugi...
Where is it?! Tell me!!
Don't get anxious, now! Calm down!
This is that card.
What?!
Hand it over!
What should I do?
Okay. Since I pity you, I'll hand it over.
On second thought, forget it!
How the hell could I?!
We're in the midst of a Duel here!
So let's get on with it!
H-How could you...?!
Haga!!
Kidding~! I was just pulling your leg~!
That was just a normal card.
You're the worst!
It was just a joke, a joke!
Prepare yourself, you stingy bug bastard!!
I activate the Special Ability of Magical Warrior Breaker!
Mana Break!!
The... The Special Ability of Magical Warrior Breaker...?
Y-You can't...!
When one Magic Counter is removed from Magical Warrior Breaker,
It can destroy one Magic or Trap Card on the field.
Destroy Insecticide Barrier, Magical Warrior Breaker!!
This Effect can only be used once with every Magic Counter expended.
Once this Effect is activated, the Magic Counter disappears....
And the Attack Power of Breaker goes down by 300 points.
Now I can attack with the Poison Butterfly you gave me!
NOOOO~!!!
Here goes, insect asshole!!
I use Poison Butterfly to attack Armored Centipede!
It's not over yet!!
I use Magical Warrior Breaker to Direct Attack!
I'm joking.
But now, you have no more Monsters to attack with!
And because of Poison Butterfly's Effect, your Life Points will become zero!
Great!
I win!
Are you mistaken about something?
My Battle Phase is not over!
What are you talking about?!
Haven't all your Monsters finished their attacks?!
I activate a Quick-Play Magic!
Berserker Soul!!
Berserker Soul?
I can activate this when I discard all cards I have on hand!
I can keep drawing cards until I reach a non-Monster Card.
And I have to discard them into the Graveyard.
Then, for each monster card that I've discarded...
A Monster with 1500 or less Attack Power allows me to keep attacking!
A Monster with 1500 or less Attack Points?
At that time...
Once this Effect is activated, the Magic Counter disappears....
And the Attack Power of Breaker goes down by 300 points.
That Yugi...
He planned this far ahead...?
Here I come!
The first card, draw!
I discard the Monster Card, Queen's Knight into the Graveyard!
Magical Warrior Breaker, additional attack!
I draw the second card!
Monster Card!
The third card!
Draw!
Monster Card!
Monster Card!!
Draw!
Monster Card!
Monster Car-
Stop it already, Yugi!!
Let go of me!!
Haga's Life Points dropped to 0 a long time ago!
It's clearly your victory!
Oh well.
After Dueling with the ones chosen by the Legendary Dragons,
their souls have become much more powerful.
You became valuable sacrifices for our God to revive.
Haga, I won!
You promised me! So tell me!!
Where is my Partner?!
Out with it! You promised me!
Where is my Partner? Where is he?!
Answer me!!
That's impossible...
You know that too, Yugi.
Haga's soul has already taken away.
HAGA!!!
That's why Haga made a promise like that... He couldn't have kept it from the start!
Speak!!
Partner...!! WHERE IS HE!!?
Poor Yugi...
Partner...
Yugi...
Yugi!!
Hmm?
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Yugi, who was still trapped by the darkness in his heart, managed to beat Haga.
But the train got derailed and fell into the valley.
We're still alive?
When we regained conscious...
We found that we were saved by an old man who guards the valley and a young girl.
Who are they exactly?
Why do they know about Yugi?
Next, "Battle! The Two Yugis"
Duel standby!