Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Right now, several have gathered to fight for the title of Duel King.
Battle Ship, take off!
The first round of the tournament will now begin!
All participating Duelists and everyone else, please assemble in the central assembly hall!
Let's go, Partner!
Yup!
"The First Sky Duel: Yugi VS Dark Bakura"
The finals are finally here, Yugi.
Yeah.
This time, I'll definitely defeat you.
At that time, let's fight honorably.
Of course!
This looks delicious!
And this one too!
Shizuka, this is delicious!
Dammit, that bastard Malik...
I'll pay you back in our duel...
Remember it!
Sorry!
Ah, Bakura!
Jounouchi-kun, I'm a bit nervous.
Yeah. Oh, by the way, what kind of deck do you use?
Ah! My deck is an Occult Deck.
O-Occult Deck?! Is that like Kotsuzuka's Ghost Deck?
He has a creepy deck like that?
Ah, I dueled Kotsuzuka-kun and won easily.
You won easily against Kotsuzuka?
Yeah.
This Occult Deck that won easily against that Kotsuzuka...
Just what...?
Well then, see you later.
Yeah! If we're matched up, go easy on me!
I don't wanna duel him at all...
What's wrong?
Your face is pale.
Er, no... just a bit nervous...
Are you alright, Big Brother?
Oi, Kaiba. How are we going to determine the final match-ups?
Hmph... Can't you even wait quietly?
What's wrong? Why haven't you begun?
Yeah, well, the eighth duelist has yet to arrive.
Forget it.
Begin.
What the heck is that?
We will now draw lots to determine the first round match-ups!
Draw lots...!
Each and every match-up will be decided in this format, starting with the first match.
The match-ups will be decided using this Ultimate Bingo Machine.
And when the winners of each Duel are determined, the next draw will be held.
In other words, you will not know who your opponent's identity
until mere moments before the match!
A Bingo Machine will decide?
So there's no mistakes.
This Bingo Machine was equipped with each of the numbers we assigned the participants,
And it will randomly choose two of them.
Come in.
Please excuse me.
Number 8, please report to the main assembly hall.
I know the order of the duelists' matches.
Huh?
My battle is the fourth round.
You may not believe me, but I have the power to see the future.
A man wielding an evil mind will duel in the first round.
If all are ready, we shall begin the lottery for the tournament's first match-up.
Ultimate Bingo, start!
The first person in the first match-up is...
Duelist Number 6!
Ryo Bakura!
Huh? Me?
The first one's Bakura!
Hey, are you sure your arm is alright, Bakura-kun?
Your face seems a bit pale...
Are you sure you shouldn't be in bed right now, Bakura?
I really don't wanna fight against you!
Go rest~!
I'm alright!
Even so, I'm just a bit shocked to be chosen first.
Now, the other duelist is...
The Duelist matchup against Ryo Bakura in the first match is...
Duelist Number 3!
Yugi Mutou!
It's been decided! Yugi Mutou VS Ryo Bakura!
Ehh~? With Yugi-kun?!
Oh man~!
Bakura...
Ryo Bakura... I'd like to see how skilled you are as a Duelist...
Thank god it ain't me...
You're out of luck, Bakura!
Having to fight Yugi so suddenly!
It kind of feels like you've got no chance.
Eh~ No way~
Now, is that so?
He's the wielder of a Millennium Item.
And right off the bat, the Millennium Battle starts.
This battle will be his first test...
Yugi, I'm pleased to be able to fight you so soon.
The tournament will be held on a special ring on the Battle Ship!
The Aerial Dueling Ring Platform!
Aerial Duel Arena?
Those participating in the first Duel, please take the central elevator to the arena.
Those wishing to act as spectators, please come along.
Yeah! Let's go!
Of course!
In the case Bakura's heart is being controlled by the evil spirit...
This duel will be a much more dangerous fight.
Now, this is the Aerial Duel Arena.
We're dueling here?
This is the Aerial Duel Arena?
It's freezing~!
We're expected to fight in this freezing wind?
The Battle Ship is now flying at an altitude of 1,000 meters.
The air current will feel like blades cutting into your bodies,
adding even tougher conditions for the Duelists!
This will test each participant's endurance!
This is really exciting!
Yeah! There's a reason this is called the "finals"!
How about you reveal your true identity?
You're not Bakura.
You're the dark personality residing within the Millennium Ring.
I knew it...
The Millennium Ring?!
That idiot! He's wearing that thing again?!
That's impossible!
I definitely threw that ring away...
How could it have returned to Bakura?
Hey, what do you mean?
What's a "Millennium Ring"?
That's right. Namu-kun, you don't know anything about this, do you?
Me either!
Ever since Bakura received the Millennium Item his father bought in Egypt,
he's been controlled by a dark spirit.
That's the Millennium Ring.
Then this "dark spirit" has taken control of Bakura-kun?
I can't believe it.
I couldn't believe it at first either...
I've got a bad feeling about this Duel!
Big Brother!
Let me make one correction.
Right now, Bakura is not being controlled by one mind... but two!
Yugi, I haven't fought you in a Duel since that Dark Game back in the Duel Kingdom.
Taking control of Bakura-kun's body like this, what are you aiming for?
Are you after my Millennium Puzzle?
Who knows?
Yugi, I need you to stay alive until I open the Dark Door...
After all, you possess the Millennium Puzzle...
The Millennium Puzzle is the final piece I require to obtain the Power of Darkness.
I don't need it right now.
Right now, that is...
Yugi, I've entered this tournament for one thing only.
And that is for your God Card!
My God Card?!
Why is he after Osiris...?
You shouldn't even question it!
If you wanted to dominate the gaming world,
it's only natural you'd want to enter the ultimate tournament
and earn the title of "Duel King".
No, that can't be the only reason...
There's got to be more to it.
But what is it he's after?
That face shows he doesn't believe it at all.
Forget it. I'll focus on fulfilling my agreement with him...
I'll trade the Osiris Card for the Millennium Rod.
If worst comes to worst...
I don't mind taking direct control of him and defeating Yugi myself.
Back off!
You shouldn't talk so big, as you just lost to Yugi!
I will defeat Yugi!
Round one of the tournament finals will now begin!
Duel!!
Yugi! Don't lose!
Return Bakura-kun to normal!
Yugi, demolish this weakling with your God Card!
With the Pharaoh up first, the Millennium Battle will now begin.
Now, show me if you've improved your dueling skills or not!
I'll do more than that!
I'll go first!
Draw card!
My turn! This guy in Attack Mode!
Turn over!
He played a 1200 Attack monster in Attack Mode?
Is he trying to lure me?
It doesn't seem to have any special abilities...
Take that card out, Yugi!
It's my turn!
Draw!
I Summon Illusion Beast Gazelle!
Attack Possessed Painting!
Beaten!
I'll also set a reverse card!
Turn over!
My turn! Draw!
Spirit of Traumatic Nightmares in Attack Mode!
I-It appeared...!
Turn over!
Using Attack Mode again?
He doesn't have any set Magic or Trap cards...
He's fighting style seems to have no meaning at all...
My turn! Draw!
I attack with this monster!
Magnet Warrior Gamma!
Magnet Punch!
Pulverize Spirit of Traumatic Nightmares!
Then I'll direct attack the player with Illusion Beast Gazelle!
That monster was nothing!
Is he even serious?
It feels like he doesn't even know the Dueling basics...
Bakura, do you even have a strategy?
My turn! Draw!
Attack Mode!
The Headless Knight!
Now! It's your turn!
Defeat it, Yugi! My monster...!
Again...?
Just what are you plotting?
Even so...
Magnet Warrior Gamma, attack!
The Headless Knight is beaten!
I'll then direct attack!
In just the first three turns...
Bakura lost three monsters without putting up any resistance...
You know, this is kinda creepy...
Is this really his plan?
Or is he really just weak?
Either way, if all goes well next turn, Yugi will win.
Turn over.
Yugi!
You've fallen right into my trap!
What!?
My turn!
Draw card!
Trap? Don't be stupid!
Yugi's got the clear advantage in this duel!
That's true! Yugi has two monsters on the field!
Bakura has no monsters on the field at all!
Is he just bluffing?
Or does he actually have a strategy to turn the tables?
Hidden in my Occult Deck...
...lies one of the most terrifying cards in existence!
But there's a special requirement in order to Special Summon this high-level monster...
Special Summon Monster...?
That's right!
The conditions to Summon this monster are
that I must sacrifice 3 Demon-type monsters from my Graveyard to Summon it.
Now revive, ruler of the world of the dead!
Dark Necrofear!!
I Summon Dark Necrofear!
I let my guard down...
I never thought he's Summon a first-class Monster using a method like that...!
What the hell's that?
Something incredibly creepy just appeared!
But why'd he put his Monsters in Attack Position when he lost almost all his Life...?
If he wanted the Monsters in the Graveyard, wouldn't Defense Mode have been enough?
Don't you get it, deadbeat Duelist?
If his opponent hadn't seen his Monsters in Attack Position,
and had used Defense Position instead, he would have feared it was an Effect Monster and thus not attacked.
Yugi, I'm going to teach you...
The true terror of my Occult Deck.
A monster that requires 3 monsters to be sleeping in the Graveyard to be Summoned...
This thing must have powerful abilities...
Bakura gambled his Life Points away for the sole purpose of Summoning Dark Necrofear.
It's a Monster requiring great risk to Summon it.
It must have a terrifying ability.
Now, what will you do, Yugi?
It's still my turn!
I set 2 reverse cards.
Turn over!
He didn't attack with Dark Necrofear?
Even though he could have defeated any of my monsters on the field...
Is he wary of my reverse card?
Or...
Now, what's wrong, Yugi?
Hurry up and attack me!
My turn! Draw!
I'm unscathed, with 4000 Life Points.
Bakura only has 450 left.
I can finish him with this card!
I sacrifice Gazelle the King of Mythical Beasts!
I Summon Black Magician Girl!
That little magician girl doesn't have enough Attack Points to defeat Dark Necrofear.
We'll see about that!
You thought my reverse card was a Trap!
It isn't a Trap...?!
This card is really Spellbook of Black Magic!
What?!
This card raises Black Magician Girl's Attack Power up by 500 points!
She now has 300 more Attack Points than Dark Necrofear!
Alright, Yugi!
Defeat Bakura's creepy monster!
Let's go, Black Magician Girl!
Attack!
Black Burning!!
Dark Necrofear is killed!
Alright!
O-Oi, he's...
...laughing?
I thank you for defeating Dark Necrofear, Yugi.
Now that Dark Necrofear has been sent to the Graveyard...
I can activate the Field Magic Dark Sanctuary!
Field Magic...?!
I'm scared, Shizuka~!
Big Brother~!
You just triggered the most terrifying switch of my Occult Combo!
What did you say?!
Yugi, I'll let you enjoy Dark Sanctuary to the fullest!
"Preview"
Not good! The Field Magic Hateful Soul of Dark Sanctuary has appeared due to it's Effect,
And Yugi's monsters are being possessed!
If the monster with the Onryou attacks, Yugi's Life Points are cut in half,
And Bakura-kun regains his Life in return!
And finally, Bakura-kun's trump card Ouija Board activates!
Eh? When the letters D, E, A, T, and H are gathered,
It's determined Yugi will lose?! No way!
Next time!
"Ouija Board's Death Call"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise