With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
I’ll turn the tides with this card!
The entire Zombie Army’s attack is zero!
Here I come, you zombie freak!
Ultimate Screw Knuckle!
Jounouchi!
I did it, Yugi!
Hey, we’re leaving!
Bro…
W-What?!
Now they’ll be trapped in that cave for life!
"Tag Duel in the Labyrinth!"
Damn it!
This isn’t moving an inch.
I guess we can only look for another exit.
What? How are we supposed to search for one?
Well…
Bakura-kun?
Pegasus’ castle is most likely this way, everyone.
Why?
Let’s go.
Big Brother…
Don’t worry…
I’m fine…
You always protected me, always.
Whenever you were around, I was always happy.
Always…
Big… Brother…
I want to see you, Big Brother…
Hey Bakura, is it really ok to go this way?
We’ve been walking for awhile.
Plus the pathway’s getting smaller and smaller.
The walls have changed in landscape, too.
They were all disorganized before.
But then they became like this…
Maybe they're man-made...
But this is kinda… like a maze.
Well, which way now?
This way.
The exit’s this way.
Hey, wait a sec!
What’s the matter, Bakura?
Hey, is the exit really this way?
What?
What’s with this room?
We are…
The guardians of the caverns…
The Labyrinth Brothers!
The Labyrinth Brothers?
What the hell?
A comedy duo?
Star Chips!
Are they player killers?
My, oh my. It sure is rare for the rats to wander into our maze.
Ah, but they are far from lost.
Lost ones, can you determine the correct path?
The correct path!
Then…
Duel us for the answer!
Is that a duel ring?
One of those doors is the correct way out.
If you win, we’ll tell you which one.
If you lose or run, you’ll wander the depths of the cave for all eternity.
In other words, we can’t leave if we can’t win, right?
By the way, this will be a two on two match.
Two duelists, please step forward.
Two on two?
A tag match?
Be careful, it could be a trap!
It seems we have no choice but accept the match, Jounouchi-kun!
Yeah!
Just as they want it.
Welcome to out Labyrinth Field!
Eh? Where do you see a labyrinth?
You’ll see soon enough.
Now then, place your star chips!
I’ll bet two!
And I’ll bet on four!
I bet six!
Accepted!
Let’s go, Jounouchi-kun!
If we win this, we’ll both have ten star chips!
And then we can head for Pegasus’ castle!
That won’t be happening. After all, we’re the Labyrinth Player Killers!
They don’t know what they’re getting into.
Good luck, you two!
Hurry up and beat them, so we can get out of here!
Duel Start!
It’s my turn to start off!
I summon this!
Labyrinth Wall!
Labyrinth Wall?
The walls of a maze…
That’s…
What is that?
This…
The Labyrinth Wall can only be summoned on this type of field.*
Welcome to our Labyrinth Field!
Mokuba…
I end my turn here.
Allow me to explain the new rules.
Each player has 2000 Life Points.
However, if any player loses all of their life, then his tag team loses!
Shoot! So if I lose, then Yugi loses too?
You are also permitted to use your teammate's cards on your turn.
Now then, onto the Labyrinth Field rules.
Here, each Duel Monster will move like a chess piece on the board.
When that card is summoned, it can move in accordance to its star level.
The monsters battle when they meet up on the board.
You also win by getting to the end and deciding which one of the doors is the correct exit at the end of the Labyrinth!
Which door you choose is for you to decide.
We’ll say if you picked the correct door.
Hey, hey, hey, that’s dirty!
We’re betting our lives on this here!
Can you at least give us a hint?
Agreed.
Then from here on out…
One of us will be telling the truth…
And one will tell nothing but lies.
Well now,
Yugi-boy…
Must you have such a scary face over this mere turn of events?
From here on out, you’ll have to figure out which one will tell nothing but the truth…
And which one will tell nothing but lies.
Hey,
That wasn’t a lie just now, right?
Not at all. Nothing but the truth.
Now then, my Mei door is the true exit.
No, no, my Kyuu door is the true exit.
Which one is telling the truth?
Wait a sec…
I’ve heard this quiz before.
If I’m right…
A traveler was lost at the crossroads between the village of truth, and the village of lies.
The traveler wanted to ask a villager at the crossroads, but couldn’t tell which village he was from.
The traveler wanted to get the village of truth, and was allowed to ask the man one question.*
What he asked was…
“Take me to your village!”
Because, if he was telling the truth, he would take you to the village of truth.
And if he was lying, he would take you to the village of truth, because it isn’t his village.
Alright then, I have a question for you two.
Accepted.
We will allow one question from each of you.
Ok then.
I’ll have you tell us which one of yours is the real exit.
Which of you is protecting the true exit?
This way, they’ll both point at the true exit.
Alright!
The real exit is the Kyuu exit, Yugi!
Now it’ll be easy to get out of here!*
The Kyuu exit…
Is that the true exit?
What’s the matter, Yugi?
You still suspicious?
If one of them really was on our side, then what you said would be correct.
But,
I don’t think its okay to just believe them so blindly.
What do you mean?
I know the village of truth quiz you’re referring to.
But the differences between that and the situation at hand are lethal for us.
First off, in the original,
There was one person at the crossroads. In our case, there are two.
And we can’t from their words if they’re from either the village of truth, or from the village of lies.
And there’s something else that worries me.
To know that one was lying, they would have to both be from the village of truth.
And there’s also the possibility that they’re both from the village of lies.
If that’s the case, then there’s no way of knowing which way to go!
I-I see…
Let’s continue this game.
Don’t be swindled by their words.
We’ll eventually find out which one is the real door.
Yeah, you’re right!
We can’t figure it out now, no matter how much we think on it!
The duel continues!
At any rate, we have to beat them before we can leave this dungeon.
My turn!
I summon the card Ruiz in attack mode!
We will not attack it.
Continue with your monster’s movement in accordance to its star level.
Okay then. He’s 4 stars.
Luis, move forward 4 spaces!
I’ll show you the horrifying strength of the labyrinth field!
My turn!
I summon Shadow Ghoul!
And then I fuse him to the Labyrinth Wall!
What?
He’s…
Wall Shadow, Labyrinth Wind Cutter!
Luis is defeated!
W-What is that?!
Wall Shadow?
Hey, that’s cheating, dammit!
That’s not legal!
It is very much so.
Our Wall Shadow is the wall itself.
And even more so, there are no spaces on the wall.
Wall Shadow…
It’s now impossible to walk within the walls without the possibility of being destroyed in one fatal slash.
He’s dangerous!
It is a labyrinth, so it’s natural for it to have a guardian.
Yes. It is impossible to leave this labyrinth alive!
Alright, it’s my turn!
I summon Axe Raider in attack mode!
And I set one more card face down.
I can’t attack what I can’t see. Therefore, I won’t move this turn.
This way I'm safe from your wall-jumping freak.
And you can’t attack, right?
That’s right, Jounouchi-kun.
If you don’t get close, the Wall Shadow can’t attack.
See what I’m thinking, Yugi!
I hope Jounouchi doesn’t screw up.
It’s alright. Yugi will follow up if that’s the case.
I hope so.
In tag matches, they usually aim for the weaker prey.
It’s my turn!
First, I set a card face-down.
This is the trap, Land-mine Spider.
The more cards they bring in, the more they will lose to the monster form of Jirai!
I summon Labyrinth Tank, and move him ahead!
Now you stand no chance of leaving this maze.
I end my turn!
My turn!
I summon Elf Swordsman in attack mode!
Move ahead 4 spaces into the Labyrinth!
But the Elf Swordsman doesn’t have the attack points to beat the Wall Shadow.
Then the same thing will…
Fool.
My turn!
Wall Shadow, attack!
Your target is the Elf Swordsman!
What an ignorant fool. Now the Elf Swordsman is dead!
You fell for it.
What?
That’s…
The Chained Equipped Boomerang!
No! The Wall Shadow is trapped!
The card I set before was the Chained Boomerang, intended to power up my monsters, and trap my opponent’s!
I used it on Yugi’s Elf.
Now the Elf Swordsman has 500 more attack onto his original 1400!
Now, bury the Wall Shadow!
Wall Shadow is defeated!
Yes!
A great combination has just been born!
Jounouchi, you really have become strong.
The duel has all but started!
Correct, let the game continue!
We’ll show you that we’re the greatest tag team out there!
Let’s go, Yugi!
We’ll win with our combined strength!
Fantastic!
Simply marvelous!
This is looking to be very interesting indeed.
Excuse me.
It’s about Seto Kaiba.
So he still hasn’t been found, huh?
My deepest apologies.
We’re looking with everything we have, so please just wait a bit longer.
I don’t mind.
Kaiba boy will definitely come out at some point.
I'm certain of it.
Get a hold of yourself!
I can’t lose to something this weak.
It's alright. My brother will definitely come for me.
That’s right.
Give it!
My brother would always come when I really needed him.
I won't lose, big brother.
I will not give they key to anyone.
I will protect Kaiba Corporation!
Mokuba, I’ll be there soon.
"Preview"
Yugi and Jounouchi kill beating all of the Labyrinth monsters.
Amazing!
They're winning play after play!
But it doesn't look like they're gonna win that easily.
Look, the three boxes became one huge monster!
So that’s the ace of the Labyrinth Brothers, The Gate Guardian?
Next time!
The Three Demon God Fusion! The Gate Guardian
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship