Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
While he waits for the Great Wicked God Zorc to revive,
Bakura revealed his plan to separate us!
And Kalim ended up being sacrificed as a result...!
I must not let any more of my companions fall!
I must save Seto from the hands of the High Priest of Darkness!
Then I have to keep Zorc from reviving!
Partner! Please find my name as quickly as you can!
"The White Dragon"
This must be the Pharaoh's tomb...
Honda-kun!
Hey! Hold on, Honda!
What is...?
What is this?
There ain't nothing here!
Is the other Yugi's name really here?
It has to be!
But still...
I found it, Yugi!
Found what?
Where?
Right here.
He's right...
But what the heck's written here?
"O ye who solved the Millennium Puzzle.
Thou must return that which thine has wished upon the Millennium Puzzle.
Only then will the door open."
Honda, how the hell can you read that?
Does that even matter right now?!
Yugi, the Millennium Puzzle is supposed to have the power
to grant one wish the solver asks.
Honda-kun...
What you've just said... Is it the truth?
Yugi, return it at once!
Do you not care about what happens to the other Yugi?
The wish the Millennium Puzzle granted when I solved it...
It's...
Seto! You must accept it!
The Pharaoh's fate is to ours as light is to shadow!
But now that the Power of Darkness has awakened, the world will enter a new age!
Seto, you will become the new king.
And this land will be yours!
This place...
Lord Akhenaden!
Behold, Seto.
Taking the power of that God as your own will be your proof as the Pharaoh!
And your means to do so is on its way!
Kisara!
Seto! Destiny desires for you to rule the throne!
Lord Seto!
Kisara, why are you here?
Your village was destroyed because you saved my life.
It is now my time to save you, Lord Seto!
Kisara...
That man...
So you have come, one who holds the White Dragon.
Seto, your proof as ruler is right before you!
This person's heart is being led by evil intent.
Lord Seto, you must not do what this person wishes of you.
Lord Zorc's revival has begun.
Seto, kill that woman!
Doing so will allow you to extract the God from within her!
Become king along with the White Dragon, my son!
Lord Akhenaden, even if you are my father,
I would never sell my soul to the darkness!
Let's go, Kisara.
Yes.
Seto!! You cannot
escape from our destiny!!
Duos!!
Aura Sword!!
SETO!!
You will not step one foot beyond this point!
Duos!
Open your eyes, my son!
Lord Seto!
So your behavior is because of that woman?
You intend to deceive my son?!
The likes of you will not have Seto!
This is the God-like power!
The White Dragon...
The Blue-Eyes...?
That's...
Are you there, Seto?
Kisara!
Don't do it, Kisara!
You will drain your Ba...!
It matters not.
What?
But you, Lord Seto, I will protect at all costs.
Kisara...
What do you think you are doing, Seto?
Kill that woman and claim the power of the White Dragon!
That power will grant you Lord Zorc's approval as the King of Darkness!
You are mistaken!
Lord Akhenaden, what possible meaning could a world of darkness ruled by Zorc possibly hold?
After meeting Kisara,
I've come to realize how much darkness there is in this world...
And how dry everything is.
And the light that shines through this darkness is love!
Lord Seto!
Damned fool...
You are the only one...
...who can undo our
blood's past humiliations!
Kisara and I are not
tools for your revenge!
The father I am proud of gave his life bravely on the battlefield long ago...
SETO!!
Kisara!
As long as this Ka is sealed, you are no longer needed!
Kisara...!
Kisara!
Kisara!!
Lord Seto...
KISARA!!
I knew that this girl would protect you if I aimed in your direction.
This is the birth of a new king!
Seto, you alone have been chosen to sit at the throne!
Kill the Pharaoh and rule the world with darkness!
That's it.
Come to me, my son!
My father died when I was a child!
Is this your answer...?!
Your blood and flesh are a part of me...!
For my last gift, I give you my soul...!
My son...
I love you from the bottom of my heart!
I call to the blood in your veins!
Flow with my love and boil with my hatred of the Pharaoh!
Join with my soul and become the King of Darkness!
SETO!!
Yugi...?
Seto!
Are you safe?
I've been waiting for you, Pharaoh...
The Almighty Great Wicked God Zorc's resurrection is all but assured.
I will defeat you here and become the new Pharaoh!
What are you saying, Seto?
That woman...!
The Blue-Eyes' stone slab...!
What happened here?
What happened to Akhenaden?!
If you mean me, Pharaoh, I am right here within Seto's soul!
I will defeat you and become the King of Darkness!
I can see it in his eyes...
Seto's not himself...
Could Akhenaden have...?
Now is the time for my wish to be granted!
Destroy the Pharaoh, my son!
Using your power of the White Dragon!
Diaha!!
Stop it, Seto!
You are being controlled!
Behold, Pharaoh! The power of my God shakes even the Heavens!
Come forth, White Dragon!
Is this duel the only way?
Come forth, my servant!
Black Magician!
Be prepared to accept our attack of hatred!
I am going to use all my Heka in this attack!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Magic Blast!!
Pharaoh!!
Mahado...!
Pharaoh...
What a truly pitiful look for a king.
Prepare yourself, son of Akhenamkhanen!
Can you hear me, Seto?
Have you really forgotten the light you held in your heart?
Have you forgotten your duty to protect this country?
Do you wish to continue living as a king trapped within the dungeons of your heart?
Nothing you say will help!
White Dragon! Kill the Pharaoh!
Ki... sa... ra...
White Dragon!
Why?!
Why are you not attacking?!
Blue-Eyes... is disappearing...
What.. is this light?!
What?
This cannot be!
S-SETO!!
Lord Seto.
You must not let your heart be trapped by the darkness.
Kisara...
Yugi.
Kaiba!
You were in this world...?
I saw that deadbeat collapsed in front of the stone slab...
And then that occult speech from Bakura...
And that vision I saw when we were Dueling in the Duel Tower...
If I had to make a theory based on all that occult nonsense...
...then I'd hypothesize that this is the world from 3,000 years you've been preaching about.
But...
This scene now is somewhat different from the vision I saw back then.
This is the world of the Dark Games constructed
based on my memories from 3,000 years ago.
Some of the events may differ from what actually happened in the past.
A Dark Game, you say?
It's up to you whether you want to believe this or not.
But in this world, the revival of Great Wicked God Zorc is coming.
You better escape from this world quick.
Since its you we're talking about, you will surely be able to find some way out of here!
I don't care what your identity in this world is.
I will take orders from no one.
Show me how just powerful this "Wicked God" you're so fearful of is.
Kaiba...
Unbelievable!
Or rather... how useless.
Who would've thought the High Priest of Darkness would lose?
With that, your plan to make Seto your slave has failed.
Don't you get cocky, Yugi.
The sand in the Hourglass of Desperate Isolation is still falling, as you can see.
And with it, the countdown to your death.
You're still the loser in the end.
Great Wicked God Zorc...
When all the sand in the hourglass runs out...
The real horror this world will face will begin...
Nobody has any idea how strong he is...
But if Zorc is really revived, there must surely be some way to defeat him.
And that's...
Looks like you've already noticed... the secret to Zorc's seal.
As long as this is a Dark Game we're playing,
there has to be a way to defeat him.
And there's only one thing that we can't ascertain yet
even though we're so far into the game...
And that's my name!
That's right... I used my name and soul three thousand years ago...
...to seal Zorc behind the door to the Underworld.
That means my name is the key to Zorc's seal.
But unfortunately for you,
it looks like you are nowhere near finding out your own name.
Although...
Perhaps I'll present you with a tiny ray of hope...
Your four little partners are currently present within your tomb.
They are there to find out the Pharaoh's real name.
My partner and the others...?
In this world, only those granted by you are able to enter your tomb.
Why are you telling me this?
Because it hurts the most when your hope suddenly turns to despair!
The moment your partners
learn your name...
My servant will kill them.
Your servant!?
There's someone in their midst...
...whose mind I've corrupted using Parasite Mind.
Yugi, just what did you get after putting the Millennium Puzzle together?
That's...
I want true friends...!
Okay, Yugi, I challenge you!
Yugi, stay back!
Yugi, want to go together?
That's...!
You don't mean, Yugi...?
Us?
Is that so?
You jerk!
Hey!
What the hell's your problem?!
What the hell?!
That's the Room of Truth holding the Pharaoh's name.
I get it!
To "return the wish that was granted"...
If Yugi gets into that room, then since we're standing on this side of the balance...!
Go on, Yugi!
I can't do that!
How... can I possibly do this?
You're right, Yugi.
How could someone as kind as you be capable of sacrificing his friends?
Honda!
Let me help you then.
Yugi!
Come on! Run!
Good!
Yugi, you climb up first.
Okay!
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
1... 2...
We're safe!
Let's go!
Right!
- There it is!
It's the Other Me's...
Real name....
Sweet! Be sure to carefully memorize it!
Oh right, where's Honda?
Yugi, Jounouchi, look here!
Is this some escape passageway?
Honda!
Where'd you run off to?
I thought you guys were dead!
God, what a persistent bunch.
Honda! What the hell happened to you?!
Honda-kun!
You still don't understand?
Bakura!
Bakura-kun!
It's too late to notice now.
I regret to say this...
But even I don't know what's going on in the royal tomb.
But there's no way Yugi's soul, no longer harboring you, can beat my clone.
I can tell exactly what you're thinking.
You're probably thinking of getting the Pharaoh to the royal tomb.
But that's impossible.
Look, it's time for Zorc's revival.
What?!
What the?!
Looks like it's finally starting... Zorc's revival.
Zorc's revival?
That's why I won't let you inform him about his real name.
I will be the only one who knows the Pharaoh's name.
A Duel Disk!
This is the most fitting way to kill you guys!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
I've been suspicious for a while now...
But I didn't expect Honda to be infected with Dark Bakura's parasite.
Dark Bakura shows himself and challenges Yugi to a Duel.
Stop it, Yugi!
This Duel is a Dark Game!
You will lose your life if you lose the game!
But Zorc has revived.
We need the Pharaoh's name in order to defeat Zorc.
Is the only way to beat him for Yugi to win this Duel?
Next time!
"Revival of the Great Wicked God Zorc"
Duel, standby!