Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
My turn.
Field Magic, activate!
Temple of the Royal Family!
Rishid... Seems you've gotten your "Trap Hell" started.
Allow me to show you!
This is the card that shall deliver onto you God's punishment!
Watch!
You have already activated the Trap Card this turn!
What'd you say?!
The Trap Monster Card!
Embodiment of Apophis!
He Summoned three Monsters at once...?
"The Inherited Card:
Psycho Shocker Counterattacks!"
Jounouchi!
A Trap Monster Summon...?
Was that what Malik was aiming for?
Not good!
The Effect of Jounouchi-kun's Monster Box disappears this turn!
If Malik attacks with all three next turn.
all of Jounouchi's Monsters will be destroyed!
No way! Is there anything that can save my brother?!
If Jounouchi can somehow set a counter card before he ends his turn, he may have a chance.
Shit...!
I got ahead of myself
and went on the attack...
... only to fall straight into another one of his traps!
I set a reverse card!
I then switch Wyvern Warrior
to Defense Mode!
Turn over!
Is that meant to help you somehow avoid my attacks?
Yeah! This will do the trick!
My card is Scapegoat.
Even if all three Apophis attack me at the same time,
three of the four will take the hits and I'll make it through this turn!
It's my turn now.
You had best prepare yourself, Jounouchi.
Avatars of Apophis!
Three-way attack!
Jounouchi-kun!
Now! Reverse card, open!
These guys'll block your
Trap Monsters' attacks!
Great!
He can avoid direct damage now!
Too naive!
Counter Trap!!
Magic Jammer, activate!!
What?!
Magic Jammer!
By discarding one card from your hand,
you can negate the activation of your opponent's Magic Card!
It's a legendary rare card!
So then the goats...!
Scapegoat is wiped out!
Dammit...!
Go! Apophis!
Rocket Warrior!
Wyvern!
There's still one target left!
Go! Direct Attack!!
Big brother!
Jounouchi-kun!
So he just barely made it out alive...!
Jounouchi...
With your strategy,
you cannot defeat me.
All of Jounouchi's Monsters are dead...
...and he only has 200 Life Points left.
Rishid...
Even if you do nothing, he will have no choice but to place his hand on his deck
and surrender to you.
It was too easy...
This fool's lower than a lab rat!
He's a lab fly!
It's no use...
I just can't win...
He's way too strong!
Malik's strong even without using dirty tricks!
I have nothing else up my sleeves...!
Jounouchi!
Honda-san, my brother really can't win anymore?
W-Well...
It's very unlikely.
No way...
Mai-san...
Shizuka-chan, I told you this before.
Dueling is a world of cruelty.
Even if it's your sibling fighting, you can't turn your eyes away from this reality.
Mai-san...
But at the very least, he can fight on until the very end.
It's over...
There's... nothing more...
Jounouchi! I have something to tell you before you surrender!
A winning Duelist has to take responsibility!
Responsibility?
Those who lost to you...
Insector Haga, Esper Roba, and Ryota Kajiki...
If it was them fighting here in your place, what do you think they would do?
Those who lost to me...
What would they think if they saw you like this?
Of course, maybe you shouldn't care about those who lost.
But you inherit the loser's dreams along with your win!
This is the fate of someone who wants to win.
It is what makes a real Duelist who they are!
If you don't mind shaming them,
place your hand on the deck!
Mai...
Big brother!
You can do it, big brother!
You've worked so hard!
For yourself and for your friends!
And for me as well!
If I didn't have you by my side...
I would have been to scared to have my surgery!
I wouldn't have been able to take off the bandages either!
If I didn't you you, big brother...!
I would still be wandering in the darkness!
You've continued to fight!
And you gave me the light I needed to live!
Shizuka...
Gave you light...
while you wandered in darkness...?
Back then, I...
You poor thing! If we leave him all alone, this child will surely die!
When I met the Ishtar family,
I was given the light to live.
So Jounouchi gave light to his sister...?
I don't want to see you give up!
Shizuka...
Jounouchi, will you answer one question for me before the end arrives?
What did you seek by fighting in this Battle City tournament?
There's someone I must fight no matter what!
To keep my promise with him!
I've met all kinds of people on my journey to this point...
And I fought them!
That's right...
I followed my path while fighting against them...
That's it! That's my Battle City!
That's enough of an answer!
Now I got something to say to you!
Take back that "before the end" crap!
I haven't lost yet!
Jounouchi-kun!
That's right! If I lose here,
what am I gonna tell the guys I fought who paved the path for me?!
Every single one of them fought me 'till the very end without giving up!
Big brother!
Jounouchi!
Thank you! Mai, Shizuka and Yugi!
My turn!
But there is nothing more you can do.
Is having the courage to accept their loss not also a part of being a Duelist?
Partner!
Mm-hmm!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi!
"What can you see, but can't see?"
Right!
I may have a close to zero hope of winning.
But I can't just give up that easily!
That's not what a real Duelist is, the thing I'm aiming to become!
I'll struggle down the path I've chosen with the deck I built!
Here goes! Let's settle this!
Malik! My fight has just begun!
So you still have the guts to press forward?
I'll set two reverse cards on the field!
And Swordsman of Landstar in Defense Position!
My turn ends now!
Is it a Trap or a Magic?
But there is no way he can stop all three of the Apophis' attacks.
And he only has 200 of his Life remaining...
If my prey so desires it,
I shall destroy you in a flash!
Oh Avatars of Apophis!
Eliminate the enemy!
Jounouchi-kun!
I won't lose!
Magic Card, open!
Foolish Burial!
This card lets you
choose a card from your deck
and place it in the opponent's Graveyard.
I'll also open my other set card!
The Trap Card Graverobber!
You plan on robbing my Temple of the Royal Family?
That's right.
I call the Monster I placed in your Graveyard back to the field with Graverobber!
And the Monster I call back to the field is...
Come out!
Psycho Shocker!!
Impossible! You Summoned a 7-Star Monster in a little-to-no time at all!
That's right!
And due to Psycho Shocker's Special Ability,
all Trap Cards on the field are destroyed!
I recall that you Summoned those Apophis guys with a Trap Card earlier!
Oh no...!
So I'll activate
Psycho Shocker's Special Ability!
Trap Crush!!
Did you see that?
This is a card I won from someone I fought against, containing his very soul!
Good job!
You turned the tables!
Well done, Jounouchi!
Brother!
He finally found a way to counter Malik's Trap Hell!
Now what're ya gonna do?
Your strategy won't work on me anymore!
Psycho Shocker...
So he had that in his deck all along?
This guy's poison for
that Trap Deck of yours!
Alright man!
Go, Jounouchi!
Yes! He turned the situation around!
If I hadn't won this card from Roba,
I would have lost.
I've gotten stronger thanks to the guys I fought who got me this far!
So the near-dead cat got back up?
Struggle more for me, my lab rat!
Let me see the third God Card.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Kung-Foo Fighter Ultimator!
And I switch Swordsman of Landstar into Attack Mode!
Let's go, Psycho Shocker!
Direct Attack the player!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
My attack ain't over yet!
Go! Kung-Foo Fighter Ultimator and Swordsman of Landstar!
He did it! Now Malik's Life Points were greatly reduced!
He just needs one more attack to finish him!
Good job! Keep it up!
Jounouchi!
You're almost there, big brother!
Did you see that?
That's payback for your three attacks from those Apophis freaks earlier!
That was an impressive comeback, Jounouchi...
Despite being almost out of Life Points,
you showed your pride as a Duelist by standing up to me!
Is this guy really the same Malik we've been fighting all this time?
I know you don't mean that!
I won't forget how you brainwashed me and forced me to fight my friend!
Malik! I'm gonna kick your ass no matter what it takes!
My turn is over!
My turn. Draw card.
Rishid, I can't believe you let Jounouchi push you this far...
Don't disappoint me too much.
I need you to win this tournament as my double.
There is no need to worry, Lord Malik.
I have already prepared what I need to dispose of Psycho Shocker in my hand.
Magic Card, activate!
Sealing Swords of Light!
Sealing Swords of Light?
Not good at all!
Now none of Jounouchi's Monsters can move for three turns!
He almost had him beat, too...!
He's using Magic Cards to make up for his Trap Cards' flaws!
No, even if his Monsters can't move for three turns,
as long as he has the Psycho Shocker's abilities,
Malik can't use his Trap Strategy.
Jounouchi-kun should still have the advantage here.
Turn over.
My turn! Draw!
Even if I can't attack, I can still keep Summoning Monsters!
I sacrifice Kung-Foo Fighter Ultimator!
I Summon the Legendary Fisherman!
Defense Position!
Kajiki, I'm using your card!
Lend me your strength!
I switch my other Monsters on the field to Defense Mode!
Turn over!
My turn. Draw!
Th-this card...!
Looks like you finally drew it.
Our "Special Card" that should be placed in the sacred alter!
Why is this in my deck?
Temple of the Royal Family is the card I've used to pose as Malik...
The actual card needed to be placed in that alter should not be in my deck!
I placed that card in your deck just before the Duel began.
So you can play the role of Malik even more realistically...
Lord Malik!
Oi, Malik!
Hurry up and play your damn card!
I-I set a card face-down on the field.
I doubt he'd play a Trap Card with Psycho Shocker's Ability in play...
So that means... it's a Magic Card!
Good! Place that card in the sacred alter!
As long as it is within the sacred alter of Temple of the Royal Family,
it can't be touched by the enemy's attacks or their Magic effects!
But Lord Malik, if the temple should fall...
...if that card should lose, the player will automatically lose!
Fret not, Rishid!
That card is invincible!
Since he drew that card from his deck this turn,
he's been acting strangely.
Just what could it be...?
Other me...
Something really bothers me...
That ark in the temple's alter...
So you noticed it too?
That temple is meant to protect something and keep out intruders!
The ark must hold some kind of secret!
But he hasn't
revealed what that secret is yet.
Be careful, Jounouchi-kun!
Hey! Is your turn over yet or what?!
No, I have not declared its end.
I seal one card away within the ark in the temple!
You sealed a card?
So there really was a secret...!
What card did he just put in there?
It couldn't be...!
Now I end my turn.
Good job.
My turn!
I'll use the Magic Card Resurrection of the Dead this turn!
Revive, Wyvern Warrior!
I'll then sacrifice Wyvern Warrior and Swordsman of Landstar!
Appear! Insect Queen!
Defense Mode!
Haga! This is the card you gave me!
Lend me your strength, guys!
That valuable card sure is wasted on a mere lab rat...
Wonderful!
Among all of Duel Monsters,
those are some of the most valuable cards!
It seems Jounouchi-kun's deck has really powered up from the Battle City tournament.
Now then! The Effects of Sealing Swords of Light disappear on my next turn!
But you don't have a single Monster on the field!
You're history if I attack you with all three of my Monsters at once!
No, you will not be touching me with any of those Monsters.
So long as the card I placed in the ark remains within the Temple of the Royal Family's alter,
it shall not be harmed by the enemy's attacks or magic effects.
What?
And I was simply using the Sealing Swords of Light
as a way to buy time while I prepared for a ritual.
But the time has now come!
The three cards I've gathered on the field
hold the power to Summon the great guardian of the temple, protecting the sacred sealed card!
Guardian of the temple?
Behold!
Magic Card! Cup of Sealed Soul!
Then I open my reverse card!
Seal of Selket!
And the Temple of the Royal Family!
When I gather these three Magic Cards together,
I can Summon the Mystical Beast, who protects the secrets of the alter!
Mystical Beast?
That's right! The guardian of the temple!
The Scorpion God that shall devour your Monsters!
Show your glorious form before us!
I Summon the Mystical Beast, Selket!
What the?! What the hell just came out?!
What the hell?!
Another monster just appeared!
The Mystical Beast Selket exists to guard the sacred card sealed in the ark!
Sacred card?
So then, the card you sealed in that ark...!
Yes! It's the God Card!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
"Preview"
The card he won via the Ante Rule helped Jounouch escape countless pinches,
but what the heck is that grotesque Monster?
After attacking Jounouchi's Monsters,
it ate them from head to toe!
Eh? Selket absorbs the Attack Points of the Monsters it eats,
increasing its Attack Points?!
And the Ra Card is sealed in the ark!
Next time!
Summon the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise