The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Damn Pegasus... He intends to take over the Kaiba Corporation?
Appear! The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
What?
It can't be... that's really my brother's deck!
Actually, Yugi Mutou's duel data is stored inside it.
However, there's a need of a password in order to enter it.
It won't work! Get inside!
Start the battle!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon Strikes Back
I missed?
All right! He did it!
Yugi...
Go, Yugi!
It's my turn. I play this card.
What? It didn't appear?
I still have three silk hats.
If you can defeat the Black Magician,
My Life Points will decrease. However, under one of the silk hats...
I've put a trap card.
What?
Now... it's your turn!
Yugi... what's he planning to do?
His chances are one in three!
All right! The middle one! Attack!
Wrong guess.
Activate Trap Card!
Hexagram Curse!
Blue-Eyes is really almost invincible... but there's a method to reduce his attack.
Now, Go! Black Magician!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon is defeated!
You did it, Yugi!
It can't be...
Black Magician is defeated!
In all my deck there're three Blue-Eyes White Dragons!
It can't be that you've forgotten, can it?
So, is Kaiba really dead?
You are afraid of me. Of my spirit that has revived from the dead!
That's the reason that you made a mistake.
Now, Yugi, it's your turn.
Yugi...that's not the reality! My brother is definitely alive! Definitely!
So?
The security system was frozen.
The central control room's alarm was set off.
The virtual system was unlocked.
From now on, our access mode can be detected.
Ignore it. Keep on going.
Understood.
Successfully entered booth 146!
Yugi Mutou's duel data found!
All right! Image!
That is...
Who's fighting Yugi?
The name displayed is "Seto Kaiba"...
Identity unknown.
They're not only using my deck...
but my name as well for a duel like that?
Damn Pegasus!
What's the situation of the duel?
Presently in the field there's the second Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
The first one was defeated by a combo attack from Black Magician and Magical Silk Hats.
He defeated a Blue-Eyes without using Exodia... Yugi... as expected...
But, now he has no way out.
Yes. He has no cards capable of defeating this second one.
This means it's a desperate situation?
What is your decision?
There's still a way. Now we will decrease the second Blue-Eyes's attack.
He already played it on the field, so we can't do anything to the card.
If we can infect the monster's apparition with a virus, his attack should decrease.
Understood.
Please set the virus level.
Maximum! Start attack!
Understood. Starting virus infection.
There is no card in my hand that can defeat him.
At this rate...
Finally realized?
Hurry up and play a monster for the Blue-Eyes to destroy.
As long as the Seal Defense card is in play,
I can't put monsters in defense mode.
Gremlin in attack mode!
Gremlin has appeared in the field.
If the Blue-Eyes starts the next attack, it will all be over!
Virus infection at 50%. It seems the Blue-Eyes still wasn't affected.
Infection in 70%
Blue-Eyes's attack didn't change.
Hurry up!
Finally it's time to end this!
Yugi!
Damn! Isn't there something that we can do, Jounouchi?
And what do you want me to do?!
Yugi...
Blue-Eyes White Dragon.... attack!
What?
Infection has reached 95%
Blue-Eyes White Dragon's attack is decreasing.
All right! It's started to work. Reduce it! Reduce more!
W-What is that?
What the hell?
Why is the Blue-Eyes...?!
What's going on?
What is that...
Contact the central room.
Seto Kaiba is alive.
Virus infection reached 100%.
Blue-Eyes White Dragon's attack is currently 2300. Continuing to reduce.
All right. Prepare to attack the third one.
Understood.
What happened?
It froze. Attack's reduction stopped. Unknown reason.
What?
Hello Kaiba-kun!
Pegasus!
Quickly!
Blue-Eyes's attack's reduction stopped at 2000.
Pegasus!
The Burst Stream has been fired!
What?
Shoot it Blue Eyes! Burst Stream!!
YUGI!!
Kaiba?
Kaiba...
What?
Impossible...
D-Disappeared...
What in the-?!
Unfrozen. Blue-Eyes White Dragon's destruction confirmed.
It can't be. Hey, can you say how this happened?
I can't. Unknown reason.
Is that what the heart of the cards is...?
Why?
Why?!
Kaiba... is alive... he is....
Shut up!
I am dead!
No! Seto Kaiba is alive!
You did it, brother!
What do you mean?
It's obvious, isn't?
There's no one other than my brother that could destroy the Blue-Eyes like that!
That's my brother's doing! I knew it! My brother is alive!
It's proven that Kaiba is alive...
Now I can concentrate in the duel.
Hey... it's already time for you to reveal your identity!
I won't let you fool me anymore.
Damn! I told you that I'm dead, didn't I?!
This form is more comfortable.
I am "Puppeteer of the Dead", sent by Industrial Illusions.
Now, Yugi. Come on. Let's have some fun playing.
How's that? I knew something was happening!
Disgusting...
Yugi! You don't have to hesitate anymore! Finish off this guy!
This is group A.
So?
Really?
That Blue-Eyes was destroyed?
That's really a mysterious thing.
That's Yugi boy for you!
-Is luck part of his abilities?
-I understand.
Excuse me... Seto Kaiba is really alive.
Kaiba's terminal hacked in our Millennium server.
But in the moment our team invaded, he was nowhere to be found.
No problem. Don't worry about him.
So... the duel's continuity will be fun.
My brother's card can't be used by anyone else. Serves you right!
Damn Yugi!
Somehow he survived the last attack, but Kaiba has one more Blue-Eyes.
Now... You have no monsters in play.
Hurry up and draw!
The remaining Blue-Eyes is still in my deck.
There won't be another miracle.
When I draw the other Blue-Eyes, my victory will be decided.
Grappler in defense mode.
Until the last Blue-Eyes is drawn, he will play monsters in defense mode.
My turn!
As long as Seal Defense is on the field, my monsters will be in attack mode.
If the Blue-Eyes is drawn next, it will be my loss.
I play a face-down card on the field.
And play Elf Swordsman in attack mode!
Grappler is defeated!
You got me in that one.
Next I play Centaur in defense mode and set a card on the field.
Another set.
Is it a magic card or a trap card?
I too play a face-down card.
And Holy Elf in attack mode.
Plus... I do a combo with Writing of Secret Arts,
increasing it's attack and defense by 300 points.
Turn over.
I don't know what that is but it's useless.
Stop these foolish things!
He has three face-down cards and three monsters.
He increased the power of the Holy Elf to attack Centaur.
But if I draw the Blue-Eyes now....
...then his Life Points will reach zero, won't they?
All these face-down cards...
Who's trump will triumph?
The battle will be decided now!
It's all right. Yugi will win!
Yugi! Win this!
Let's go!
I did it!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Yugi!
It's all right! My brother will surely come and do something about this!
Fool!
Do you think that will happen twice?!
Look at the Blue-Eyes!
If Kaiba were to be doing something to this one like the previous one,
it would be just like the other one.
But, the third Blue-Eyes didn't change at all.
Damn!
That means...
That means that Kaiba isn't in any position to help you anymore!
Dammit!
What a good feeling!
Burst Stream of Destruction!
Activate Trap Card!
Holy Barrier Mirror Force!
A trap card?
The Holy Barrier will reflect the Burst Stream!
Just joking.
Magic card Activate! Attack Nullification!
So he was waiting for my trap card?
Useless. useless. I've seen everything beforehand.
Now, what will you do?
Yugi!
It's over?
I still have a trump!
The Resurrection of The Dead card!
Can't be!
It can't be that you plan to revive my Blue-Eyes, can it?
You're wrong!
The card that I will revive is...
Kaiba's card!
I may have thought that got me...
but they have the same power...
This would be impossible.
My Holy Elf has been chanting a magic spell since she appeared on the field.
That spell lets it lend it's Attack Points to another monster in the field.
W-What?!
Blue-Eyes's attack is really nearly invincible!
But that quantity of points, 3000, is not definitive.
It all depends of the battle's situation.
That's what Kaiba taught me!
Wait a minute... That can't happen!
Prepare yourself! This is Kaiba's anger!
Here I go!
Holy Burst Stream!!
You stole Kaiba's deck and soiled his heart.
I will not forgive you!
Mind Crush!!
Pegasus...
Can you hear me?
My voice filled with anger!
You used a fake to soil Seto Kaiba!
I will never forgive you! Be prepared!
I could feel an amazing Power of Darkness, Yugi-boy.
I can't wait to battle with you.
The day that I will destroy you with these hands will come.
Kaiba...
You did it... Yugi!
Man... For a moment, I wondered what would happen.
Huh?
What is it?
Mokuba-kun is not here!
Mokuba!
Burning with revenge after losing to Jounouchi,
Mai Kujaku uses Dinosaur Ryuzaki in order to defeat Jounouchi.
With Yugi's advices again, it will be easy!
Advice is forbidden? That way he can't win!
Where did Honda go to? And even Yugi...
Do something, Jounouchi!
Next, Friendship Power! Barbarian 1 and 2!
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship