Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
You say you're going to "reset the world"?
You're going to set the world back to zero and rebuild it?
Amelda, that's nothing but the howl of a loser dog!
The future is something one creates with his own hands!
A future built by someone else holds no meaning at all!
Now behold the glimmer of one of the Chosen Ones!
No one else is capable of walking the road I've chosen to march down!
"The Stealthy Dartz's Shadow"
Kaiba Corporation has been bought out?!
But it's strange...
I mean, me and my brother own more than half the stocks of Kaiba Corporation.
They shouldn't have been able to without our consent...
There's only one possible way it could have been pulled off...
It must be the workings of a world supremacy.
A world supremacy?
Can Doma really pull something like that off?
I think they've made it obvious that we can't take their strength lightly.
Seto-sama...
Not another word.
I'm no longer the director...
Seto...
Not true, Seto-sama! Until we restore Kaiba Corporation to its original state...
...we will continue to follow you, Seto-sama!
Isono! Fuguta!
I'll remember what you said...
Kaiba, we need to get to Florida Museum as fast as possible.
I'm certain they've already made that their territory as well.
Then we'll lose the only information we've got left on them!
There's still a small possibility left.
Who the hell are you?!
What happened?!
Hurry!
Director! You've got an urgent call!
Director!
We have finished scanning the undersea relics!
The undersea relics?
So that means Kaiba's already reached the museum?
Of course he has!
My brother always plans two, no three steps ahead of the enemy!
Seto-sama!
Kaiba!
But at least we managed to scan images of them...
Data on the relics...!
Let's meet up. Otogi, Rebecca.
Rebecca...
Rebecca, forgive the other Yugi already.
We're all fighting a painful battle here.
And I wish to know the truth.
Of the one you've come to accept.
Grandpa...
Yugi-kun, we won't be able to work with the image data here.
You must send it to a computer that has the equipment neccessary
to process such large images containing such a complex alphabetical system.
Then let's take it to the Kaiba Corporation American Branch.
You serious, Kaiba?!
But hasn't it been taken over by Doma?
The computers at Kaiba Corporation will be the fastest method to process such a large quanity of data.
But...!
No, Kaiba's right.
Yugi...
Industrial Illusions...
They managed to seize Kaiba Corporation as well.
And now all the Duel Monsters in this world are under their control.
We can't afford to waste any time!
Oh? I thought you were moping around after tarnishing the title of Duel King?
Kaiba, I have a long list of promises to defeat Doma I must fulfill.
And no matter what happens, I will bring my partner's soul back!
Hearing those words, I can once again acknolwedge you worthy of holding the title of Duel King you tarnished.
Yugi... Looks like you're back on your feet again.
Professor, let's meet up with each other.
Great! Let's speed it up!
Aurora? Don't tell me what happened before will happen again...
Very shortly, after a long span of 10,000 years has passed,
the moment where our God's power will reach its maximum level shall arrive.
In order to assure God's revival, I must gather bountiful soul offerings.
Lord Dartz...
Amelda...
Be at ease.
Amelda shall also serve as food to our God to ensure the birth of a new future.
In due time, the nameless Pharaoh and his friends shall come here.
Nameless Pharaoh?
This time, I shall personally...
Time shall open up a path.
Scattered across the world...
...lies the fragments of our God!
From your lives, God shall undergo its surpreme transormation!
Cheerio!
Bye!
What's this now?
What's with this spiffy crystal?
Now then... Shall we prepare our "Chosen Duelists" with a warm welcoming?
Hey! Down here!
You two transport these two to the nearest hospital.
-Yes!
Amelda...
Ryuzaki...
Rebecca, professor.
Otogi, thanks for watching over these two.
I took care of things.
Though, a variety of things happened on our end.
A variety?
On our way here, we ran into Mai-san.
And we met this guy named Varon from Doma.
You met Varon?
He said he's going to defeat you for sure.
He's a scary Duelist!
Shit...!
Bring it on whenever you want!
Other Yugi...
I'm just not ready to forgive you yet.
Not until you bring Darling back to me...!
You have my word. I will bring Partner back, by any cost necessary.
Me and Kaiba are headed for Kaiba Corporation.
I'll help you guys! I'll lend my support from the outside!
Humph. I never would have guessed this kid was the U.S. Champion.
Be sure not to get underfoot.
What's that mean?!
Let's go, Yugi.
Brother!
Don't worry, Mokuba.
That's our castle.
Those quacks can't touch me.
Right!
Be careful, Yugi.
Yeah.
All right, Anzu. Come with me to tell the police.
They may be able to help us.
You're right.
Where are you taking us, Kaiba?!
This underground tunnel was designed to act as a shelter for Kaiba Corporation in times of crisis.
We should be able to avoid any detection and enter the control center from here.
Watch me, Doma...
Try all you like, but I won't let scum like you act as they please!
What the?!
There's something up there!
That thing wasn't Solid Vision?!
Kaiba! We have to Summon our Duel Monsters as well!
I knew their Monsters don't operate off of our system ever since I fought Amelda!
But our Monsters...
Just believe, Kaiba.
Duel Monsters really exist.
There's just no scientific evidence to prove that theory.
But if you think about it,
it's not so far fetched.
That's a ridiculous theory, but it's worth testing.
Then let's go, Kaiba!
To the top of the corridor!
Doma?
It's true!
The world-spread issue with Duel Monsters appearing was caused by Doma!
Ya sure you's wasn't dreamin' or somethin'?
Please believe us! They're trying to destroy the world!
That so? These "Doma" people...
They don't happen to wear crests on their foreheads like this...?
You two...
Run, Anzu!
What?!
A Monster?
The thing that attacked Yugi at the Stone Wilderness...!
This way, Anzu!
Go, Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Blood Vorse!!
Now! Let's move!
Impossible! The pass code has been rewritten!
Oh no! There's nowhere left to run!
Looks like you need a hand!
Still think I'll slow you down, President Kaiba?
Rebecca!
Kaiba Corporation's security is nothing to brag about.
We've got no clue what you're doing...
So that's the code, is it...?
President, you should hire me next time.
I'll write you a more complex program.
I'll consider that.
Let's go, Yugi.
But I was only able to disarm the security outside.
The system controlling the corridor has been hacked and I can't access it.
That was enough!
One moment, please.
You have been identified, Master Seto Kaiba.
Switch to voice-only mode!
Discard the previous system.
Transfer to the sub-system.
Affirmative.
Begin analyzing the undersea relics of this ancient civilization!
Grandpa!
"When the Dark Serpent swallows the sun,
10,000 years of time shall come to pass.
In which, mankind will give rise to a new paradise."
When the serpent swallows the sun?
A 10,000-year-old paradise?
The legendary paradise, Atlantis!
What did you say? Absurd...!
This crest is the mark of Paradias!
Paradias?
An enormous conglomerate still existing today that has extorted businesses around the world and bought them out...
...and leading the market towards supremacy.
His strength is said to rival that of all the major world powers and their representing presidents.
He's both a tyrant and a leader!
That person is...
Dartz!!
He's...!
He looks just like that man...
No... This man is him without a doubt!
But that's not possible!
I was shown a memory fragment from over 10,000 years ago!
Yugi! President!
Paradias? Rebecca, where's it located?!
I'm searching the map...
Found it!
So this is where Doma...
What the hell are you doing?!
That's where our troubles originated...!
That's where Mai and Ryuzaki...
Nameless Pharaoh.
Seto Kaiba.
So you have finally located me?
So you're the leader of Doma?
You would be correct.
My name is Dartz.
Not too long from now, Doma shall guide the world onto an ideal path.
And it shall be changed.
Destroying the world is "ideal"?!
You're doing the exact opposite!
There's no justification behind it!
What is your goal?!
Goal?
Nameless Pharaoh, I am simply following the fate I have been handed.
You're trying to destroy the world's future by your own whim!
And you call it fate?!
You two haven't the slightest clue.
Nameless Pharaoh... Seto Kaiba...
Your very existence is what will allow me to guide this future.
Our existence will?
What do you mean by that?!
There is no need for you to know.
As the both of you will soon fall victim to the coming path of destruction as well.
Dartz! Let's settle this here and now!
You will return my partner and all the other souls you've taken!
The Legendary Dragons, eh?
It's been quite some time.
Timeaus, that eye of yours must ache.
An illusion!
You shall not be able to stop the movement of the coming destiny that will change everything.
The both of you can wallow in your own uselessness!
Wait, Dartz!
Dartz!
Get in, Yugi!
Yugi, we're going to jump right down!
What?!
Kaiba!
I won't let anyone have Kaiba Corporation!
What's that?!
Those guys are headed your way.
Take revenge for Amelda, Varon.
Sorry, but I only fight for myself.
Varon!
It's time to face me, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!
Hey!
Where the heck does that idiot think he's going?
The Monsters are coming from that direction!
You go back to the trailer, Anzu!
Honda!
Doma, I'm going to
settle this once and for all!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
This incident with Doma is getting out of hand!
How do we fight against beings that come and go as they please?
And Jounouchi's gone to Doma's base by himself...
And we've got Monsters attacking Yugi over on our side!
But the one waiting for Jounouchi isn't a Monster.
Varon waits to settle things, while Mai-san moves alone!
What's going to happen?!
Next time!
"Clash! Jounouchi VS Varon"
Duel standby!