Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Yugi! Why didn't you attack?!
Even if the Mirror Knights are controlling them, this is all part of Dartz's scheme!
You should understand.
If we lose now, neither their future or the future of the world will hold any meaning!
What?! The third barrier of the Orichalcos?!
You said you're going to activate its true power?!
"The Third Barrier of Orichalcos"
Orichalcos Tritos!
Including this card, the Barrier of Orichalcos has now been fully completed!
The third barrier of the Orichalcos...!
And due to the effects of Orichalcos Deuteros,
I regain some of my Life!
Dartz's Life just went up again...!
Orichalcos Diablos!
Special Ability, activate!
The Special Power of Orichalcos Diablos pressures pressures Defender Monsters into switching into Attack Position.
What?!
Kaiba!
I attack with Orichalcos Diablos!
If he's attacked like this...
My brother's Life will...!
Magic Card activate! Shrink!
Orichalcos Tritos - its power nullifies all Magic and Trap Cards used against me!
Seto, your tricks will no longer work against me.
It increases the Attack Power of all Monsters and increases the player's Life Points...
And it negates both Traps and Magics.
It's truly an impregnable barrier!
This is goodbye, Seto.
Orichalcos Diablos!
Element of Cry!!
Brother!
Trap, activate!
Ambush Shield!
I tribute Big Shield Gardna!
That 2600 points of Defense Power...
...will be added to the Attack Power of Twilight Zone Dragon!
Twilight Zone's Attack Points...!
They're stronger than his Monster's!
Counter him!
Twilight Zone Dragon!
Rainbow Burst!!
I activate Orichalcos Kyutora's Effect!
Even if we raise our Attack Power,
we can't damage him as long as that absorption Monster stays on the field!
Ah, I see.
You actually wasted your own Monster to save Seto.
This must be the "power of bonds" you people talk about.
But as a result of that Trap just now, Nameless Pharaoh...
...you have lost the only Monster you had to act as your protective shield!
I shall allow you to have a special reunion.
My Mirror Knights!
Within the three layers of the Orichalcos Barrier, you will be unable to resist me any longer!
Attack the Nameless Pharaoh!
Partner...!
Yugi!
Squirm, Nameless Pharaoh!
Yugi boy!
Is my voice reaching you?
Pegasus!
It is now time to use the nameless card I entrusted to you!
Nameless card...?!
Hidden within this room is a new card I have created!
The card we got back then...!
That one card holds within it the power needed to break the seal on the Legendary Dragons!
The seal on the Legendary Dragons...?!
Mirror Knight Pegasus!
Yugi!
I'm... fine!
More importantly, the nameless card Pegasus spoke of...
I did add the card among my deck after getting it...
But by breaking the seal on the Legendary Dragons...
What did he mean?!
I will place two cards face-down and put an end to my turn.
Now then, Seto. This will be your final draw!
But just like he said, I've only got 600 Life Points...!
I have to find a way to turn this around on this turn...
...or I'm going to lose for sure!
Am I... going to lose in a dump like this?!
Amelda...
You said that you would be able to save your brother...
Can you really save him? Your little brother?
I can.
Then show me.
Turn end.
Amelda... The future you entrusted me with...
And my own road of glory...
I won't let it all end in a place like this!
Watch my Duel closely and burn it in your heart!
My turn!
Draw!
It's here! It's come!
The one card in my deck that can turn this around!
Come!
Legendary Dragon!
Critias!
Yugi, you've had a set card on the field that you've yet to activate.
If I know you as well as I think, it has to be Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Kaiba.
I'm going to awaken that power!
Critias! Fuse yourself with Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Come forth!
Mirror Force Dragon!
Yugi, as long as those Mirror Knights stay on the field, we can't win!
Kaiba...
If you refuse to sever the ties you have with your friends...
...then I'll sever them for you!
Mirror Force Dragon!
Attack Mirror Knight Pegasus!
Mirror Burst!!
It's no good! Pegasus still has his Mirror Shield!
No! Big Brother specifically chose him because he still has a shield!
He's right!
I activate Mirror Force Dragon's Special Ability!
The energy he shot back...!
It's being absorbed by Mirror Force Dragon!
The Special Ability of Mirror Force Dragon takes all damage sent towards it and redirects it towards every Monster on my opponent's field!
What did you say!?
Then they'll all be...!
You'd really slay your comrades?
This "darkness of the heart" you keep going on and on about...
Me and Mokuba have seen it throughout or entire lives!
Darkness in our hearts that we ignored and ignored some more!
Until our hearts were nearly pitch black!
But we've surpassed it and come this far!
We've carved out the light that exists in our hearts!
As long as we've got that, we're fine!
Kaiba...
If those four are really True Duelists, they should have no regrets disappearing right there!
Reduce them all to nothing!
Mirror Force Dragon!
Genocide Big Bang!!
Partner!! Guys!!
We're okay with this...!
Kaiba boy!
Thanks!
Yugi...
I see now, Seto.
I believe I have underestimated you a little.
But as long as Orichalcos Kyutora is before us to absorb all damage sent my way,
that Special Ability of yours can be tamed.
Guys...
But now he's lost all his Monsters.
Are you sure that is accurate?
My Orichalcos Kyutora...
Reveal onto us your true form!
What is... that thing?!
That's...!
This is the evolved form of Orichalcos Kyutora!
Orichalcos Shunoros!
Orichalcos... Shunoros?
Its Attack Power is determined by the total points of damage absorbed by Orichalcos Kyutora.
That means...
...the Attack Power of Orichalcos Shunoros is...!
20000!?
Impossible!!
No way!
That's not fair, no matter how you slice it!
Why are you all so surprised?
You guys were the ones who created this being!
This is the Monster born from your malice!
And it goes by the name of Orichalcos Shunoros!
From our hatred?
Shunoros' Attack Power will go down each time it battles against a Monster.
I then activate Orichalcos Shunoros' Special Effect!
Arise!
Orichalcos Dexia!
Orichalcos Aristeros!
Orichalcos Dexia...
It cannot be be destroyed so long as Shunoros remains on the field.
Its Attack Power is equal to the Attack or Defense Points of a Monster it battles with plus 300 additional points.
It is the ultimate sword of Shunoros.
Orichalcos Aristeros...
It also cannot be destroyed so long as Shunoros remains on the field.
It will always hold 300 more points than the opponent's Attack Power, so it is capable of withstanding all attacks.
It is the ultimate shield of Shunoros.
Once the two have been activated...
...Shunoros will be untouched by any and all attacks!
Moreover, Shunoros is virtually untouchable.
And unless we can destroy the two in the front, our attacks will never even reach it!
I shall proceed to invoke a Trap I had face-down!
Curse of the Martyrs!
This card launches whenever one of my cards on the field is destroyed.
It seals away the Effects of my enemy's Monsters!
It then forces a Monster of my choice into unavoidable battle!
And the Monster I will select to partake in battle is naturally...
Mirror Force Dragon!
The Special Effect of Mirror Force Dragon will be unable to reach Shunoros.
This time you will truly meet your demise, Seto!
Orichalcos Shunoros will engage in attack!
Photon Ring!!
Kaiba!
Brother!!
Trap...
Acti...vate...!
Hope After Death...
Whenever one of my Monsters is destroyed...
...the Attack Power of that Monster...
...is... added to your Life...
Kaiba!!
Kaiba!
Brother!!
Brother!
Big Brother!!
Kaiba!
Yugi...
Now I've... paid you back.
Step over my corpse... and go forward...
Kaiba!
Seto, become an offering to my God!
Kaiba!!
Ye empty shell of a body holding no soul!
Farewell!
Big Brother!
Kaiba!
Kaiba-kun!
Big Brother...! Open your eyes!
Open your eyes, Brother!!
No matter how loudly you may weep, your voice shall never reach Seto.
For Seto's soul no longer resides in the being lying beside you!
Dammit...! My brother...!
Return my brother's soul right now!!
What the?
Can you hear it?
My God's voice rains over the heavens with joy at having received Seto's soul.
I'm not gonna let you offer my brother's soul to no one!
Anzu!
Mokuba!
Honda-kun!
Guys...
Be at ease.
The souls of those lying there are safe.
But by doing this, you have lost the remaining comrades you had to support you.
Dartz!!
I will give you the final piece of information.
Why is it that I seek to destroy the present world?
The reason behind this, Nameless Pharaoh, lies with you!
What?
Why do you suppose it is you were resurrected after a 3,000-year slumber?
There is reason behind all of it!
Are you saying you know about my lost past?!
This is... a city in Ancient Egypt!
That's... me, 3,000 years ago...!
It is a serious crime to damage this sacred temple!
The rest of you get back.
Justice is in the name of the Gods...
And the name of the God is...
One of the Three Hidden Gods!
Obelisk!!
Take this!
The iron fist of a God!
God Hand Crusher!!
This battle...!
3,000 years ago in Ancient Egypt...
...the seal on "Duel Monsters" was broken.
And those with darkness in their hearts began to gather.
And once again, people began to wallow in the darkness of their hearts...
Jut as what happened to me 10,000 years ago in Atlantis...
I knew I must awaken the Orichalcos God and lay this world to rest.
And that is what led this planet.
This is the vision of Ancient Egypt the Millennium Puzzle showed me before...
However, back then, those with darkness in their hearts went on a rampage.
And thus it was destroyed.
We... destroyed it?
But after 3,000 years of passing, another surprising event occurred.
That day, a powerful soul who controlled the darkness in his heart was reborn!
Your cursed soul in turn attracted others.
My cursed soul?
Why, Nameless Pharaoh?!
Why is it you have come back after all these years?!
I don't...
There is but one answer!
It is because you yourself defy history!
For you are a hateful king who carries with him a vile fate!
What did you say?!
Nameless Pharaoh, your main purpose is to congregate the darkness of the heart!
Right. You yourself are the source! The darkness in the heart!
You are destined to be the end of this 10,000-year span of history after your sacrifice!
With Kaiba-kun down, and Yugi fighting all by himself...
Dartz claims, "You are the cause for this world's destruction."
Faced with unimaginable pressure from his unbeatable strategy,
Yugi is pushed into a desperate corner and begins losing the will to fight on!
Please! We have to save Yugi somehow!
That's it! The nameless card Pegasus gave Yugi!
Maybe with that...!
Next time!
"Revive! The Three Legendary Warriors"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other