Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Diabound was defeated by Mahado.
And Bakura turned into sand.
But time stopped for no reason...
The Millennium Items were taken by Akhenaden
and placed upon the Stone Tablet of the Underworld.
Why? Wasn't it my victory?
When I regained consciousness, a huge table was in front of me.
So this world is itself a Dark R.P.G?
"The High Priest of Darkness"
Seto.
Lord Akhenaden...
What you said earlier...
Was it the truth?
That I am your son?
It is the truth, my son.
Very soon the Great Wicked God Zorc will be revived.
Come join forces with us
to defeat that man.
With that, you will be able to become the Pharaoh!
Lord Akhenaden... is my father?
Come, Seto!
Do not listen to this foolish man who has sold his soul to the Wicked God.
Seto, you are a priest who serves the Gods.
You should fight hand in hand with the Pharaoh to protect this country and the people!
Seto.
Seto...
Listen to the royal blood that is flowing within you...
You must heed to what
this voice is telling you.
You mustn't go against your fate.
This guy is... Bakura?
Why is he here?
Yugi! Deadbeat!
They're unconscious...
What exactly happened here?
This is...!
Seto, don't be misled!
It's our duty to protect this land and our country!
That is why we must defeat Zorc!
How can we allow such evil to destroy our precious motherland?!
Hmph. Precious motherland?
Who has been protecting this land...this country?
You?
No, that's not it...
Then perhaps it is your father?!
What are you trying to say, Akhenaden?!
My useless brother, Akhenamkhanen, was unable to do it!
It was all myself, his younger brother! It was all me!
Dear brother...
No, Pharaoh...
Denied! There has to be another option other than waging war in this country!
But Pharaoh...
That country is eying our country and has started building up their military forces.
If we do not strike them first...
Silence! Say no more, Akhenaden!
I'm sorry, younger brother.
I know very well that you are concerned about me and this country.
But I do not wish to resort to wars to resolve our problems.
Pharaoh...
Hatred breeds new hatred.
Such battles will continue
forever without end.
Please understand, Akhenaden.
But I was right in my views.
Because of that foolish Pharaoh, thousands of soldiers died on the battlefields.
Despite that, he was revered as God.
He was no doubt the Pharaoh and nothing but that.
I made up my mind then.
That if my elder brother is the "light", then I shall become the "shadows".
Even if it means getting staining my hands with blood...
Subsequently, I used the power of the Millennium Items and the country was saved.
No... my brother was saved.
Then why, Sir Akhenaden?!
If you cared for the former king, Akhenamkhanen, so much,
why betray him now?!
Shimon!
Do not use lowly terms like "betray" to describe the relationship I had with my brother!
You only used King Akhenamkhanen.
You are only deceiving yourself... You have darkness within yourself!
What are you talking about, Hasan?!
If you are really the guardian of the former Pharaoh, you should be very well aware!
About the details of the birth of Akhenamkhanen and me!
You should know fully well that we were twins!
Twins?
We were born at the same time...
But the one chosen as the elder brother was Akhenamkhanen.
And that was only because his cries were louder than mine!
You knew that much about it...?
Akhenaden...
Even so, I still served my elder brother with all my might.
I deserted my wife and Seto...
I went so far as to cover my hands in the blood of sin!
My loyalty never wavered!
But Seto...
You came back. You returned to my side.
Seto... Don't you feel that this is the work of fate?
I was brought up by my mother believing that my father died on the battlefields.
I wanted to be a priest, in order to serve the country and the Pharaoh.
It was always you, Lord Akhenaden, who supported me during these times.
In my eyes...
You were like a father to me.
But...!
You took extra care of me because you knew that I was your son!
But so did you reveal that you were my father now...?
Seto.
Think about the White Dragon!
That white dragon now drives your fate!
Seto, you are the chosen one!
The White Dragon...
Does the White Dragon symbolize my fate in becoming the Pharaoh?
White Dragon...?
Blue-Eyes White Dragon?!
What nonsense!
If the Great Wicked God Zorc revives, everything in this world will be destroyed!
What meaning is there in becoming the Pharaoh after that?!
Seto, do not get confused!
Pharaoh!
Lord Akhenaden!
Do you still not understand, Seto?
When the almighty Great Wicked God Zorc revives,
this country will become the World of Darkness.
We will worship the Great Wicked God Zorc as our God and create a new world.
And the Pharaoh who governs this new world is you, Seto!
You must become the King of Darkness!
King of Darkness...?
Come, your destiny is fixed.
Come to me, your father!
...Father...
Seto...
L-Lord Seto...
You mustn't go...
Come on now, Seto.
Seto!
Father...
This is... The White Dragon...
Seto, you are the true king!
Stop messing around!
There's no telling for sure if this land will be shrouded in darkness!
Seto, we must stand united and defeat the Great Wicked God Zorc!
Seto!
- Seto!
Lord Seto!
Seto!
Do not be swayed! Come, Seto!
Akhenaden!
You, who has been taken over by darkness, has no right to talk about the king!
I do not wish to hear that from you!
If so, I shall wait for Lord Zorc's revival...
...and I shall kill the Pharaoh and snuff out all the light!
Let your soul rot, Pharaoh! Join that cursed Akhenamkhanen!
Hasan!
Pharaoh, I will hold him off here.
I will not let you get injured!
Hasan!
Lord Seto...
That's right, run along!
I'll be in a fix if you
don't get to Seto's side.
Now then...
I'm starving...
There's no food left...
This guy was the only one who could move when I stopped time.
Does it mean that this Non Player Character is out of both Yugi's and my control?
Hey Fatty, what is your role in this game?
Stop messing around, you bastard!
What are you doing, Honda?
N-Nothing much...
Why is Bobasa crying?
H-How would I know?!
What's wrong, Bobasa?
I'm starving~!!
I suddenly feel very hungry!
Yeah, I can't move anymore...
I smell food.
Could this be the warehouse?
What?! But this place is all empty!
Bobasa, don't tell me...
You finished everything..?
You jerk! You shoulda left a little for us, at least!
But I am really hungry!
Hey, we shouldn't be wasting time here.
Let's try to find Pharaoh's name quickly!
Even if you say so...
We've looked everywhere but found nothing.
It's probably not in the royal palace, right?
I think the same too.
If it's not here, then it should be somewhere else...
Let's head off then.
You're right...
No use wasting time here.
Bobasa really starving! Can't walk anymore!
We're dealing with it too!
Stand up!
Hey, let's just leave this guy here.
He's of no use anyway!
Well... You're right, but...
C'mon... I feel bad for him...
What can we do since he can't move anymore?
At the very least, we could find some food for Bobasa to eat.
That's right. It's the least we can do.
Hey...
Are you guys serious...?
We have no choice...
What the hell are these guys thinking?
Have they gone mad from their hunger?
Bobasa is hungry!
Just.. a bit more, Bobasa!
Our hands'll just pass right through it.
You're the only one who eat it, anyway.
Bobasa, here!
Grapes!
Everyone!
We're so exhausted...
I'm hungry!
That's why we've found it for you!
Eat up!
Eat it, Bobasa.
Help yourself.
Is it really okay? Is it really?
Argh, just eat it already!
Or I'm gonna eat it.
Look at how satisfied he is.
Seriously.
I'm happy for you, Bobasa.
W-What the?!
Because Bobasa is very full now!
So I'll grant you guys a wish!
Come on everyone, get on my back.
What is going on?
Leave it to Bobasa!
Everyone, let's do as Bobasa says!
Yugi...
Will it be okay?
All of you want to know
Pharaoh's name right?
Bobasa, do you know Pharaoh's name?
I don't.
What? You don't know?
I may not know his name, but I know where his name is.
I don't get you at all!
This guy must be a crucial part of the game's scenario.
He's an important "switch" for the whereabouts of the Eighth Key.
If not for Yugi and the rest, I would have missed this "switch".
The "Bo" in Bobasa
is the "Bo" "Bobbing Glutton"~
The "Ba" in Bobasa is
the "Ba" in "Dinner Bash"~
The "Bo" in Bobasa
is the "Bo" "Bobbing Glutton"~
Bobasa seems so happy.
The "Ba" in Bobasa is
the "Ba" in "Dinner Bash"~
Enough with the "Bo"...
But what about the "Sa" in his name?
Over there!
Can that be...
The Valley of the Kings!
The Valley of the Kings is where all the Pharaoh's tombs are, right?
I see.
I've heard that the Pharaoh's tomb is built even before he is born.
A place as holy as a Pharaoh's tomb...
My other self's name must be here. Nobody erased it!
I've finally reached
where the Eighth Key is!
Many thanks, Bobasa!
Bobasa should thank you all instead.
All of you have been so nice to me...
I can be so full because all of you let me have the bunch of grapes.
For some reason, I suddenly feel full too.
Me too.
Strange... Me too.
So the reason we've
been feeling so hungry...
Is it because of you?
Don't worry, I'm not hungry anymore.
But...
..But?
The "Bo" in Bobasa
is the "Bo" "Bobbing Glutton"~
The "Ba" in Bobasa is
the "Ba" in "Dinner Bash"~
The "Sa" in Bobasa is...
He's singing again.
"Sayonara"~
Bobasa!
This can't be!
Bobasa?
Bobasa!
- Bobasa!
Now it makes sense...
What's wrong?
Your partners are quite efficient.
They're quite close to finding your name.
My partner...!
Why do you know about that?!
Masters should have no way of knowing what the None Player Characters are doing!
I do wonder...
Well, let's countdown to my... No...
to Great Wicked God Zorc's revival!
The climax is approaching!
But if the main cast
doesn't make a move...
...this will become boring.
Hasan!
Your pawn is quite a tough nut to crack.
I won't let you run around
doing as you please!
Let me add some twists to the game.
If our lead actor isn't here to witness the revival of the Great Wicked God Zorc...
...it would be too much of a waste.
Lead actor?
You used it once before yourself!
What you'd call "Transferring Ba"!
You got it from your partner before.
Pull yourself together, Other Me!
We're here with you!
That's right...
I still have power remaining...
Power within my irreplaceable friends!
Then I shall use that on my pawn as well.
Your pawn?
That's right. I've invited someone interesting.
I'll bring him into this world and use some of his Ba.
Time for your debut, President!
You can't mean that Kaiba's...!
What... is this light?
What?!
What is this place?
I'm gonna borrow your soul, Kaiba.
Just a little, though.
Seto!
I will still choose to stand by the Pharaoh.
I'm back, my dear Pharaoh.
A pawn will always remain a pawn.
These guys aren't enough for a finale.
Without me around, this game cannot come to an end.
Bakura...!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Bobasa disappeared after bringing us to where the Pharaoh's name is...
Thank you, Bobasa!
We will surely find how the Pharaoh's real name!
But isn't this the tomb where Yugi's Grandfather found the Millennium Puzzle long ago?
Meanwhile, the revived Bakura separated the Pharaoh from rest...
In order to prevent them from helping the Pharaoh when Zorc is revived.
Next time!
"Countdown to the Revival of the Great Wicked God"
Please look forward to it!