"Legendary Fisherman"
Jounouchi! Right now Kajiki-kun has no Monsters on the field!
It's your chance!
I know that!
But...
The Field is Sea...
Because he played that card, I can't attack!
Draw card!
Now what'll ya do, Jounouchi?
Ya have the courage to tread upon this sea?
Here I go! My turn!
Baby Dragon in Attack Mode!
I see.
So you're gonna use this against me?
No, that's wrong, Kajiki.
I'll also use the Fusion card!
Now he levels up to Wyvern Riding the Dragon!
So you did this in order to increase his Attack?
According the the Battle City rules, Fusion Monsters can't attack in the turn they are Summoned!
Turn over!
Then it's my turn!
Draw card!
I Summon a Monster!
Out on the field!
You played a Monster Card?
Turn's over!
That Kajiki...
He's completely hidden in the sea.
Yeah...
Which card did he play?
Defense? Attack?
I can't tell at all...
But...
Now what's wrong, Jounouchi?
Come at this sea!
Indeed I don't know what card you've played,
but there's no doubt the Monster you played is a Water-type Monster!
What?
Go, Wyvern Riding the Dragon!
Because his Water-type Monster is hidden in the sea, you can fly over it and Direct Attack him!
Glide Sword!!
Alright! Now your Sea Field is no match!
The sea...!
You did it, dad!
Dad!
That...!
Don't you dare underestimate the sea!
My turn!
I set a card and end!
Another card?
But Kajiki, we're about to finish this fight.
My turn!
I set 1 card!
Wyvern Riding Dragon!
Go forth!
If this direct attack is a hit...
Jounouchi wins!
Go!
Direct Attack!
Reduce Kajiki's Life to 0!
I won't let ya so easily!
Permanent Trap activate!
Tornado Wall!
What?
As long as the Sea Field is in play along with Tornado Wall,
the player can't be direct attacked!
Wait... in order to play that, the field is completely sucked dry...
But I can't see any Monsters on the field.
Strange...
Didn't Kajiki Summon a Monster?
It's not strange, Jounouchi.
You can't see my Monsters.
Turn over!
It's my turn!
I sacrifice my Monster on the field.
To Summon a new Monster!
Sacrifice, he said?
Did he really Summon a Monster after all?
Here I go, Jounouchi!
Where's it gonna attack from?
Go, Sea Stealth II!
The Legendary Fisherman!
Quick-Play Magic, Energy Drain!
This will drain the opponent's Attack Points to 0!
It's useless!
Impossible!
Wyvern Riding the Dragon was...!
Why?!
As long as I have the Sea Field,
the Legendary Fisherman can't be attacked or affected by anything!
Wh-What did you say?!
The Legendary Fisherman is a Monster of the sea itself!
You can't possibly defeat it!
My turn!
Card draw!
I place a Monster in Defense Mode face-down!
Turn over!
My turn.
I Summon a Monster.
Attack!
Where's it gonna come from?
Little-Winguard was...!
Jounouchi, you'll never know where I'm gonna attack from!
Fear is the sea's biggest threat!
This is Sea Stealth II!
Behold!
What is this Monster?
It's almost as if it was really human...
Jounouchi, that card is alive.
That card is a clone of my father.
There's no way someone like you could beat it!
A clone of your father?
That's right.
I received that card from my father who disappeared at sea 3 years ago.
It's my one hope!
Dad...!
Dad?
Dad!
DAD!!
In the end, my father's body was never found.
My father was presumed dead.
One day, I decided I would build a graveyard facing the sea and stare out at it every day.
If my father really disappeared at sea,
it was the perfect area for his grave.
But it wasn't really my father's grave.
In fact, it was the opposite.
I built the grave in hopes my father would return to me someday.
Yeah, I believed that.
RYOUTA!
It's insane!
I got a letter from your father!
W-What did you say?!
The handwriting was certainly from my father.
"Ryouta, this is a man's card."
You can win with it!
My father is...!
MY FATHER IS ALIVE!
I thought it at the time, but...
My father had given this card to a friend of his to give to me in case of his disappearance, before he went out to sea.
So that's a gift from your father?
Even if he really is dead, this card showed me a miracle!
My father's soul is within this card!
I believe this!
So don't think you'll be defeating this card!
Kajiki...
Now, it's your turn, Jounouchi!
Draw card.
Shit... I feel it...
I feel it!
The Fisherman's presence...
Is there a way for me to beat him?
I set 1 set card!
And a Monster in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
You think you're runnin' away, Jounouchi?
But ya got nowhere to run.
This isn't the full extent of the sea's fear!
My turn!
Fortress Whale's Oath!
I sacrifice Monsters equaling 7 Stars!
Come forth, terror of the sea!
Fortress Whale!
What the?!
Jounouchi! You're now finished!
I quit, I quit!
What's wrong?
There's no way I'd lose to you,
but our goals are one and the same.
Am I right?
A well thought out decision.
The best way to defeat Yugi is to take out his friends first.
That's why I've been waiting for a good chance.
Of course, I have been as well.
With this Millennium Rod's power.
But their bond with him is strong.
It won't be easy to pit them against one another.
They aren't as convenient as my host, Bakura.
Host?
That's interesting.
This guy...
I can use him.
I Summon Fortress Whale!
And of course, the Sea Field powers him up!
How do I beat something like this?!
Jounouchi, I'll make you fully aware of the sea's terror!
The Legendary Fisherman, attack!
Now your Wall Monster has disappeared!
Prepare yourself, Jounouchi!
Not good!
Attack!
Whale Bombard
Oh no!
Jounouchi!
That whale monster just determined the match!
That young Duelist's gonna lose!
Jounouchi!
You can't lose!
Aren't you gonna win this Duel and fight Yugi once more?!
I know!
But as long as the Fisherman's here, my Monsters will be wiped out one by one...!
He'll just use that Trap at the right timing...!
If things keep up like this, on Kajiki-kun's next turn, Jounouchi will lose.
All he needs is a way to find the location of the Fisherman.
But where'd he go?
What's wrong?
I'm sure I saw two shadows in the pool just now...
Now, what's wrong, Jounouchi?
It's your turn.
In the sky is Fortress Whale.
And in the sea the Fisherman!
Is this as far as I go?
Was that real water that splashed me just now?
I thought that was part of the Sea Fie-
I found the location of the Fisherman!
My turn!
I have 2 Magic Cards in my hand.
And a Monster and a Trap.
And 1 set card on the field.
Now I have to take a chance,
and fight on ahead, eh?
Right?!
I set 2 Set Cards on the field!
And I Summon Panther Warrior!
Attack Mode!
Panther Warrior is a Monster that needs a sacrifice in order to attack!
He can't do a thing!
Turn over!
Then it's my last turn!
Let's finish this!
I may lose if I make a mistake.
Fortress Whale, attack!
Whale Bombard
Over there!
Trap Card open!
Magic Arm Shield!
I found you, The Legendary Fisherman!
Your hiding over there!
You placed your Sea Field in this special pool,
and were able to hide your Monster within it!
He read through my Sea Stealth strategy?!
The Fortress Whale's attack will be changed!
Instead of Panther Warrior, The Legendary Fisherman will be attacked instead!
Fisherman...!
I've lost...
I lose this Duel.
W-What are you saying?
To me... if the Fisherman disappears, the match is over.
Don't screw around!
You still have Fortress Whale!
You have Life Points, and the advantage is yours!
No, I have to fight alongside my father, that card.
But that card is now gone.
Kajiki...!
That's why... this Duel is over!
Kajiki.
That's not true.
Are you saying that The Legendary Fisherman is all you have left of your father?!
If he saw you right now, your father would be laughing!
What did you say?!
We Duelists fight for the faith we hold inside our hearts.
The opponent you're always fighting is your heart!
Your heart?!
That's right!
Didn't your father gave you that Fisherman for that purpose?!
And right now, all you're doing is trying to find your father in the card, and not becoming independent!
Dad!
Ryouta, surpass me.
Let's go, Jounouchi!
Fortress Whale, attack!
Whale Bombard
Trap Card activate!
Chain-Equipped Boomerang!
Kunai with Chain
Fly, Panther Warrior!
Due to Chain-Equipped Boomerang's Effect, Panther Warrior's Attack Points go up!
But even with the power boost, Fortress Whale is still stronger!
This is the end, Jounouchi!
No, Here I go, Kajiki!
Panther Warrior, counterattack Fortress Whale!
What?!
What a shame it is, Jounouchi.
Panther Warrior still holds more Attack Points than Fortress Whale.
Now Panther Warrior is finished!
Indeed, Fortress Whale is 50 points stronger than Panther Warrior currently.
But I still have a Reverse Card on the field!
Set Card?
Here I go, Kajiki!
This is my trump card!
Lightning Sword!
Lightning Blade
Its Attack goes up by 800 points!
Fortress Whale is fried to a crisp!
Alright!
Good job!
How's that, Kajiki?
Jounouchi, my turn hasn't come to an end yet!
I play the Magic Card Revival of the Dead!
Return of the Doomed
I revive a Monster this turn!
So... that means...
Then... he'll revive Fortress Whale!
So it's useless, eh?
My turn!
Draw!
Hurricane...!
This card returns all Magic and Traps to our hands...
It can destroy Kajiki's Sea Field!
But if its Fortress Whale hidden under the sea, Panther Warrior can't match it!
What's wrong?! Now hurry and come!
After all that boasting you did before, show me how you fight!
I can't afford to lose here!
I have my sea to fight against!
I can't give up until the very end!
Magic Card activate!
Hurricane!
What?!
After all, I can't let this card stay in the Graveyard.
Don't just stare! Now come and get me, Jounouchi!
I Summon Scapegoat!
I sacrifice 1!
Panther Warrior, attack!
That was splendid, Jounouchi.
I lose.
Kajiki...
Now then...
It's the rules.
Idiot!
There's no way I can take that card!
I really want you to take the card.
If I hold this card, I'll continue to depend on it.
If I give it to you, I'll be able to grow independent.
Kajiki...
I'll be sure to cherish this card!
I'm countin' on ya!
Next time, I'll be sure to win!
I'll continue to get even stronger!
Understood.
I've successfully located your friends' location.
Sorry, Kaiba.
Don't misunderstand me.
I have no interest in that nobody.
I just want to hurry and get your God Card.
Kaiba.
Let me say one thing.
Right now, Jounouchi-kun is a very talented Duelist.
I won't allow you to insult him!
I promised that I would fight with Jounouchi-kun in Battle City.
As a Duelist.
A true match!
Just follow me.
In order to save your friends.
Preview
Ah! Bakura-kun!
What's with that terrible wound?!
Namu-kun, who saved Bakura-kun, asks Jounouchi for advice on Dueling.
But the Ghouls appear and capture us!
Holding us hostage, the Rare Hunters Mask of Light and Darkness corner Yugi and Kaiba-kun into a Duel.
A life-and-death Duel atop the skyscraper begins!
Next
Time
Spell of the Mask
The Skyscraper Duel
Next time!
Spell of the Mask
The Skyscraper Duel
Duel standby!