Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Rafael... As I thought, you were wrong.
You shouldn't have used The Barrier of Orichalcos.
You turned your precious Monster into an evil form...
Was sending her to the Graveyard also a part of Dartz's so-called "destiny"?
In that case, I will change destiny.
I will smash the darkness of your heart with this card!
"Destroy the Darkness of the Heart!"
Yugi...
Yugi.
Where am I...?
A cemetery!
It's true that I activated a Magic Card called Underworld - Heaven Circle that lets us Summon Monsters from the Graveyard.
But this is a real graveyard...
Rafael!
That boy is....
Wait, Rafael!
Rafael...
These tombstones belong to my family.
What?
Dartz!
This is... that day...
Don't tell me... This is your memory?
Regardless of how far you may run, it shall remain the same.
Rafael, no matter how far you may run, you shall always arrive here once again.
Do you understand the reason why that is true?
It is because you are afraid to admit the reality of their deaths.
In that shipwreck incident, you were the only one to survive.
Big Brod'er!
Help me, Big Brother!
Sonia!
Julien!
Big Brod'er!!
Sonia!! Julien!!
"Because I am alive, my family must also be alive."
That is what you are thinking. Isn't that right?
But you are the only one destiny has chosen!
Your family is dead.
Those who are unable to accept reality will never be able to understand the answers of their destiny.
If you accept your fate, you will begin to see those answers unfold in due time.
Come along. It is now time for you to clarify it with your own hands.
That your family is sleeping within this cemetery!
If you wish to leave this place, you must confirm it with your very own hands!
This isn't right...
That's not possible! Rafael's family was supposed to have gone missing...!
Rafael, everything begins from here on out.
Your destiny.
Activate it! Your fate!
Leave yourself for the darkness of your heart,
then absorb and surpass it, Rafael.
The answer of your destiny lies just beyond that.
Deathscythe!
This is the Monster the darkness in your heart created.
Yes, my destiny was decided that day.
Assimilating myself to the darkness of my heart and then giving myself to it is what saved me.
"Saved you"?!
Then why don't you want to send your Monsters to the Graveyard that much?!
If you gave yourself to your destiny, then that should be indifferent to you!
Nameless Pharaoh, what exactly do know of me?
I do know! You don't want to put your Monsters through the same pain your family suffered!
That's why you fear the Graveyard so much!
That's the real you!
I...
I have succumbed to the darkness in my heart long ago!
I cannot return after all this time!
We can finally see them again...
Yugi!
Underworld - Heaven Circle removes every Monster Card in our decks from the game.
And each player can Summon from the Graveyard one Monster every turn without Summoning Conditions.
When activated, All Monsters on the field are destroyed.
My Black Magician Girl was destroyed.
So why is Deathscythe the only one left...?!
By sacrificing one card from my hand, Deathscythe is revived.
But the one who decides that is not me.
What do you mean?
Deathscythe is revived by its own will!
What?
Even I can no longer remove Deathscythe.
What did you say?
A Monster that can't be destroyed...?
As long as Deathscythe is on the field, the player cannot Summon a new Monster.
So you're saying that it's not possible to bring your Monsters back from the Cemetery?!
That's why I told you before that I can no longer return!
My destiny now lies with Deathscythe!
Then I will leave myself to this destiny.
Deathscythe... This is the darkness of your heart?
If I don't defeat this thing, Rafael... You'll...
Due to the effects of Underworld - Heaven Circle, I Special Summon Black Magician from the Graveyard in Attack Position!
He's revived the dead?
Yugi still has a chance if he can Summon Monsters from the Graveyard.
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
My turn! I draw!
Because of Underworld - Heaven Circle's effects, I Special Summon Jack's Knight in Attack Position!
You can even Summon Monsters from the Graveyard during your opponent's turn?
Nameless Pharaoh!! Engrave the darkness of my heart into your soul!
Deathscythe attacks your Black Magician!
Forbidden Requiem!!
Reverse card, open! Gravity Release!
This card changes the Battle Position of all the Monsters on the field.
Sweet! If all the Monsters on his field are in Defense Mode, there ain't gonna be a battle at all!
Don't be so sure of that.
What?!
Reverse card, open! Death End of Hunting Soul!
I change the Battle Position of one of my Monsters on the field.
And destroy all the Defense Monsters on my opponent's side of the field!
No way!
Yugi!
H-He killed his two Monsters with almost no effort...!
My turn!
Draw!
Due to the effects of Underworld - Heaven Circle, I Special Summon Black Magician Girl from the Graveyard!
And then I activate Altar of Resurrection from my hand!
I remove two cards from the top of my deck.
And I return one card from the Graveyard into my hand.
And the card I choose will be the Eye of Timaeus!
I combine Timaeus with Black Magician Girl!
Show yourself, Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
It's Special Effect holds the power to destroy one of the opponent's Monsters in exchange for a card in your hand.
Still, that won't work against Deathscythe!
I'll move on to attack Deathscythe with Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Black Dragon Burst!!
Did it work?
You cannot defeat Deathscythe!
But why, Yugi?
Even though you know attacking Deathscythe is pointless...!
I place a card face-down, ending my turn.
If you're set on stupid things like trying to change the heart of your opponent,
you'll wind up losing!
My turn! Draw!
I launch the effects of Underworld - Heaven Circle!
So I'll Special Summon Queen's Knight from my Cemetery into Attack Mode!
I'm going to discard the card I draw in this turn...
...and activate Sealing Sword of the Orichalcos!
This will rid Timaeus of its Special Effect.
Deathscythe!
Attack Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Forbidden Requiem!!
-Yugi!
This finishes it!
What?!
I activated Reduction Barrier.
This card makes it so the battle damage a player receives is only 1/10.
He saved himself...!
But now he's only got 10 Life Points...
Yugi...
This won't end yet, Rafael!
I won't ever give up until my Life Points hit zero!
Can you not see it, Nameless Pharaoh?!
The game has already been settled.
Like I thought, destiny has been determined!
That destiny...
Along with the darkness in your heart...
I'm going to destroy it when I kill that monster over there!
My turn! Draw!
Due to the effects of Underworld - Heaven Circle, I Special Summon Big Shield Gardna from the Graveyard in Defense Position!
I then activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
I draw two cards from my deck!
So I finally got you...?
I'll activate the Magic Card called Spider Web from my hand!
It allows me to add one card sent to the opponent's Cemetery in the previous turn into my hand!
What are you playing at?
The card you sent to your Cemetery one turn ago was Resurrection of the Dead.
If you're not able to light it, then I'll do it for you!
The light of your heart!
That Monster!
Do... Don't tell me...
I revive Guardian Eatos from the Cemetery!
Eatos...!
Yugi revived Eatos...!
Yugi...
And from my hand...
Jounouchi-kun, lend me your strength...
I activate The Claw of Hermos!
Jounouchi, Yugi's... using your... your Hermos!
Hermos will fuse with Queen's Knight!
I equip the Equipment Magic, Saint Bow of Goddess - Artemis, to Eatos!
Her Attack Power goes up by 2500 points!
Deathscythe loses 500 Attack Points because Eatos is no longer in the Graveyard!
Their Attack Points are equal!
Are you planning to have them kill each other?
Even if you do, Deathscythe won't die!
Destiny will not change!!
Think back, Rafael.
Your Monsters and the bonds you shared with your family!
Those bonds hold the power to change destiny!
Isn't this Guardian Eatos?!
Julien and me worked really hard to find this!
Sonia!
Congrats!
Eatos, attack Deathscythe!
Forbidden Song!!
I activate the effect of Saint Bow Goddess - Artemis!
In battle, when the opponent's Monster activated a Special Effect,
I can ignore the battle damage and continue attacking!
WHAT?!
I see! If the opponent's hand reaches zero, Deathscythe won't revive!
EATOS!!
I figured as much. Eatos was the one you called at the very end.
You weren't able to truly become one with the darkness in your heart.
In reality, you were just lonely from the fact that your family went missing.
In order to escape from the solitude, you began to rely on Dartz and his made up "destiny".
The darkness of your heart was an illusion you created.
Your fate hasn't been decided for you.
You're supposed to open it yourself.
But The Barrier of Orichalcos takes the soul of the loser without prejudice.
That, at least, is one fact you cannot deny.
Rafael!
My turn! Draw!
Because of Underworld - Heaven Circle, I Special Summon Guardian Grarl from my Cemetery.
Monsters from your Graveyard...
Then I activate Soul Charge from my hand!
It allows me to Special Summon the Monsters from my Cemetery.
So the guy's still after Yugi?!
No, the Monsters revived by Soul Charge can't attack this turn.
So then... What's Rafael trying to do?
Now there is no longer any Monsters in the Cemetery...
Now I'm at ease.
Rafael... You...
By the effect of Soul Charge, I take 500 points of damage to my Life for each Monster.
Rafael!
Eatos...!
Eatos! All of you!
I caught you!
I caught ya, bro!
Big Brother!
Big Brod'er!
Rafael!
The barrier disappeared!
What does that mean?
Did you pull it off, Yugi?
But why? Why wasn't my soul taken?
The Barrier of Orichalcos is the manifestation of the darkness in its user's heart.
The darkness in my heart?
And that's why... I should be...
The darkness of your heart is gone.
The darkness in my heart... disappeared?
What the hell?!
What's...?!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Rafael's barrier disappeared?
So The Barrier of Orichalcos is really the darkness of its user's heart, huh?
The location where Dartz hides was given to us by Rafael,
so we head to the temple of Doma after the destruction of Paradias.
Then suddenly a swarm of unidentified soldiers surround the helicopter we're riding.
Are they goons as well?
Is this also Doma's doing?!
Next time!
"To the Final Battlefield!
Dartz VS Yugi and Kaiba"
Duel standby!