Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Silent Swordsman LV. 5!
Attack Obelisk the Great War God!
You're naive, Partner!
Trap Card, activate!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
What a pity, Partner!
You couldn't see through my set card.
No, I did see through your set card!
My God Defeating Combo was completed the moment you activated Mirror Force!
This moment, all three gods will vanish before me!
"Strong Heart, Kind Heart"
What?!
Impossible!
He said his "God Defeating Combo" is completed?!
The gods' Attack Power did drop, but...
Yugi doesn't have any Monsters on the field!
Partner!
Here I go, Other Me!
I activate a Quick-Play Magic, Magnet Reverse, from my hand!
I can select one Rock or Machine-Type Monster
sent to the Graveyard during this turn
and Special Summon it in Face-Up Defense Mode!
Magnet Valkyrian returns!
This Special Summon triggers Osiris' Special Ability!
Summon Lightning Shot activates!
But because of the effect of the Trap on my field, Magnet Force,
Summoning Lightning Shot strikes your Monsters!
Obelisk was...!
I then activate Magnet Valkyrian's Special Effect!
It splits into the Magnet Warriors!
It split into three!
Because he Summoned new Monsters,
Osiris' Thunder Summon Shot will be forced to activate!
And because of the effect of Magnet Force,
they will be repelled to your Monsters!
Amazing...!
He defeated all three of the gods?!
I don't believe it!
Yugi conquered the Three Illusionary Beasts?!
He beat them in an instant!
He really did create a miracle!
Amazing! Simply amazing!
You pulled it off, Yugi!
That's my grandson up there!
Other Me, I came to know after fighting alongside you all this time.
The greatest weakness of those who hold great power.
And that is their very same power.
He defeated the gods with the power of the gods themselves...
Other Me, you were right.
I was searching for it deep within my heart when you were using the gods.
I spent a lot of time thinking it over.
A way to defeat the gods.
It's only natural, Partner.
It's natural instinct to search for the openings of those standing before you.
That alone is proof you are a True Duelist.
But the same applies to me as well.
I still haven't shown you all my strength!
Yeah!
Other Me, I'll fight you with all I've got!
Right! Let's do it, Partner!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Fusion
Magic Card from my hand!
I sacrifice both Gazelle the King of Mythical Beasts and Berfomet from my hand!
In order to Summon Winged Phantom Beast Chimera!
Incredible!
His gods were beaten, but he's still got a very powerful Monster!
Go, Chimera!
Attack Magnet Warrior Alpha!
Impact Dash!!
That will finish my turn!
H-He's strong!
To think that even after Yugi beat his gods,
Atem's advantage hasn't changed a bit!
No, you're wrong.
Brother?
Life Points are one thing...
But Yugi pulled off a combo that was capable of toppling the Three Illusionary Beasts.
He's forced the flow of this battle towards him.
Yugi, I now believe it!
What you said before!
Kaiba-kun!
EH!!?
Is Kaiba the Bastard really rooting for Yugi?!
My turn! Draw!
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Beta and Gamma!
To Summon Buster Blader!
Come out, Buster Blader!
Yugi-kun's not budging an inch!
In just one turn, he also Summoned a powerful Monster!
Man is this incredible...
It's like it made no difference whether the gods showed up or not!
Those two are...
Here I come, Other Me!
Buster Blader, attack!
Destructive Sword!!
Slice Chimera in half!
Pretty good there, Partner...!
But now that Chimera has been destroyed,
Chimera's Special Ability activates!
I can choose to Special Summon either Berfomet
or Gazelle sleeping in the Graveyard...
I Special Summon Berfomet!
Come back to me, Berfomet!
As expected!
Atem-kun didn't lose his Monsters!
But now that the gods are gone,
Atem shouldn't have too many other Monsters in his deck
with Attack Power higher than Buster Blader.
So you mean... Yugi really does have the upper hand?
My turn is now over!
Partner... You called out quite the powerful Monster there.
But...
My turn!
Draw!
I sacrifice Berfomet!
Come forth, Gilfer Demon!
And then I place a card face-down on the field, finishing up my turn.
Gilfer Demon?!
Its Attack Power isn't higher than Buster Blader's...
...but the thing has the ability to lower the opponent's Monster's Attack Power
by 500 points after it's destroyed.
It's obvious that's what my other self is aiming for here.
But that still gives me a chance to attack right now!
I can't afford to step down!
My turn! Draw!
I set a card on my field!
And then I use Buster Blader to attack Gilfer Demon!
Go!
Buster Blader!
Destructive Sword!!
But Gilfer Demon's Special Effect will activate this very moment!
By sending this card to the Graveyard...
...it becomes an Equipment Card,
and the equipped Monster has its Attack Power decreased by 500 points!
Turn end.
My turn! Draw!
I place a card face-down,
and I activate a Magic Card from my hand known as Awakening From Beyond Death!
In exchange for letting my opponent draw two cards,
I can add one Monster Card from my Graveyard into my hand.
Now, Partner.
Draw two cards.
And I'll add one Monster Card from my Graveyard into my hand!
That card...
The gods aside, it could be any of the Monsters he's discarded up until now.
In terms of Normal Summoning, The Tricky would have the highest Attack Power...
But Tricky is a Five Star Monster.
You have to discard a card from your hand in order to activate its Special Ability.
But currently, Other Me only has one card in his hand.
If he doesn't have the cards to meet that cost,
it shouldn't be possible for the Other Me to call back
a Monster with Attack Points higher than Buster Blader's.
Partner, I can see right through your calculations!
Still...
My Dueling is still one step ahead of yours!
This is the Monster I've chosen to bring back!
Show yourself, Gale Dark Knight Gaia!
What?! Gaia?!
Whenever Gale Dark Knight Gaia is the only card left in my hand,
I can Summon it without sacrifice!
I don't believe it!
When did you place Gaia in your Graveyard?!
Before...
There was only one possible chance I could place Gaia in the Graveyard.
I take the lead!
Draw!
I discard one card from my hand...
Back then!
That's the only possible time you could have placed Gaia in the Graveyard!
So the card then was Gale Dark Knight Gaia!
That's correct, Partner.
This situation was entirely within my initial predictions.
This situation, from the very start?!
Yes.
As the Pharaoh, I am holding extremely powerful cards.
The three Gods.
It's very true that they give me an unquestionable advantage.
But if by some chance, they were to be defeated...
Partner, you defeating the gods in our match was also within my prediction!
He predicted from the very beginning that Yugi would defeat the gods?!
Power before a True Duelist is nothing more than an illusion.
The real battle started the moment the Gods disappeared.
The mental strain inflicted by limitations...
Having the courage to place faith in your cards as you create miraculous draws!
Pushed to your limits and far beyond!
Here goes, Partner!
Gale Dark Knight Gaia!
Attack Buster Blader!
Yugi!
But as you are now,
you have the power to see right through the Pharaoh.
The only one who can put the Pharaoh to eternal rest
and return him to his friends from 3,000 years ago...
...is you.
Spiral Shaver!!
Yugi!
Yugi-kun!
I activate the Trap Card, Soul Rope!
When one of your Monsters is destroyed and sent to the Graveyard,
I can pay 1000 Life Points
and Special Summon one Level Four Monster from my deck!
I Special Summon Witch of the Black Forest from my deck into Defense Mode!
I now end my turn!
Atem-kun got himself the upper hand again!
If he's hit by those 2300 Attack Points, he's in for some pain!
Yeah...
I guess Atem-kun really has seen through him.
No, not yet.
Why did Yugi pay 1000 of his Life to place a Monster on his field?
I see!
For a sacrifice!
That's right!
Yugi hasn't given up yet!
Yugi!
My turn!
Draw!
I sacrifice Witch of the Black Forest!
Come, Demon's Summon!
And by using Witch of the Black Forest's Effect,
I can add a Monster with 1500 Defense Points or less
in this case Marshmallon, from my deck into my hand.
The Demon's Summon?
Dark Knight Gaia and Demon's Summon...
They're both Monsters that have supported Yugi all this time.
Yeah...
They're Monsters that've helped both Yugis in a pinch.
I can't believe they're about to fight against each other now...
This match between these two may be the most painful... for their Monsters.
Here goes, Other Me!
Demon's Summon attacks!
Demon Lightning!!
Blow up Dark Knight Gaia!
Turn over!
I expected no less, Partner.
You pulled out a card and turned the situation around in an instant.
I have never before felt such fear in a Duel up until now.
And it's coming from you, who used to always watch from behind my back.
From you, who's always been there to support me.
You are now trying to exterminate me!
Here, before my eyes...
We will overcome this trial and we will both grow as a result!
The greatest rival of my entire life!
Yugi Mutou!
There's only one way for you to win.
You just have to believe in yourself and believe in your deck!
My turn!
If you created a miracle, I will also call forth a miracle!
I'll Summon Big Shield Gardna!
Draw!
I Summon Big Shield Gardna in Defense Mode!
What's going on?
Atem just said the Monster's name before drawing it!
Almost like he knew what the card he drew was.
No, it's not that he knew what the card he was going to draw was.
The Pharaoh drew the card he visualized in his mind.
The card he visualized...?
How can he even do that?
Your deck's order is set when you place it!
No, to me, drawing is the act of guiding your own destiny.
But the Pharaoh just now guided the course of his destiny with his own will.
He's... guiding his destiny with his own will...?
Atem and Yugi...
Does that mean their Duel far transcends our very existence?
My turn's done.
My turn!
I activate Pot of Greed!
I draw two new cards from my deck!
Then I Special Summon Watapon!
I'll then sacrifice Watapon!
To Summon Curse of Dragon!
Yugi-kun Summoned another High-Level Monster!
Go, Demon's Summon!
Demon's Lightning!!
Why's he targeting Big Shield Gardna when its Defense Power is higher?!
No, it's fine!
When this Monster takes an attack, it switches into Attack Mode.
But he's only got 100 Attack Points.
Curse of Dragon attacks Big Shield Gardna!
Dragon Flame!!
My turn is over!
Now Atem-kun and Yugi-kun have about the same Life Points!
And Yugi-kun has two High-Level Monsters on his field!
It's starting to look like Yugi's win!
What's wrong, Anzu?
I can't... watch this anymore.
I'm sure Atem really doesn't want to return...!
He must still want to stay with us!
So why, then?!
Anzu, these two aren't fighting for personal reasons anymore.
The Duelist's souls have been absorbed into their decks.
The souls of the Duelists?
Those two have fought against many Duelists to get to this point.
Me and Kaiba...
Malik...
Bakura...
Mai...
Haga...
Kajiki...
Pegasus...
And many more.
The souls of many Duelists they've competed with have been carved within those decks.
That's why they have to fight hard enough for those Duelists as well.
Jounouchi...
I'm positive those two aren't even thinking about him returning to the Afterlife right now.
None of us can stop this Duel now.
They're simply hoisting the souls of those other Duelists and fighting with all they've got.
No matter what destiny awaits them afterwards.
It's painful, but there's nothing we can do.
Isn't friendship all about watching during times of hardship?
Yeah...
I feel it... I can feel it!
The pulse of the soul
sleeping within my deck.
I've kept you waiting, Mahado!
Here goes, Partner!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand, Curtain of Black Magic!
This card allows me to cut my Life Points in half
in order to Special Summon Black Magician from my deck!
Black Magician!
The trump card the other Yugi has complete faith in.
He used this timing to call it out?!
I then activate the Magic Card on my field, Book of Secret Arts!
It increases Black Magician's Attack and Defense Power by 300 points!
Go, Black Magician!
Attack Demon's Summon!
Black Magic!!
Mahado...
My Pharaoh... I have transcended 3,000 years of time...
...so that I may once
again serve your soul!
What's wrong with you, Sister?
Uh, no... Nothing is wrong...
Black Magician...
What is this nostalgic feeling that has enveloped me...?
So you really showed up, Black Magician!
Partner, my final trump card,
and my mightiest servant,
the Black Magician!
If you don't defeat this Black Magician...
...there will be no victory for you!
Me...? Defeat the Black Magician?!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
After what seemed like an eternity, their Duel is about to come to its end.
And when it does, the other Yugi...
Hey, do you remember?
About the Circle of Friendship we drew using a magic marker.
No matter how far we may be separated, we're always connected by this circle!
No matter how far we're separated...
Next time!
"The Story That Concludes in the Light"
Within the Duels...