Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
I may not know your reasons,
but I do know one thing!
You aren't the guy who did that before!
You aren't Malik!
What utter bullshit!
This Millennium Rod is proof that I am Malik!
Finish him off, Mystical Beast Selket!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Sorry, Yugi...
This is as far as I go!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Big brother!
Jounouchi!
Wait, Rishid!
Don't attack him!!
Why, Lord Malik?!
Kill Jounouchi...
by the hands of the God Card!!
"Ra's Anger!
Stand Up, Jounouchi"
Rishid...
If you are a true member of the clan of the Tomb Guardians,
your strong heart will allow you to control the copy Cod Card.
But I...
If you can control the copy God Card...
my late father will
accept you as his true son.
You will no longer be
treated as a mere servant
You shall be treated
as a true heir to the clan!
All I wish is to undergo the ritual and be called your son!
Nonsense!!
You're just a servant!!
If you ever talk of
my family's secrets again,
I'll cut off your miserable tongue!
Out of my sight!!
Then you will be
an heir to the family, Rishid!
Why isn't he attacking?
This turn, I shall prove that I am a wielder of the God Cards.
God Card, you said?
Is it possible... he's gonna Summon the card in that arc?!
Right now, the God Card is resting in the Holy Ark.
I must sacrifice Mystical Beast Selket and half of my Life Points to open the lid.
But the moment I do, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra will be Summoned to the field.
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
I give up Mystical Beast Selket along with my own life!
O soul of the god
that sleeps in the ark!
Rise and show us your sacred form!
WINGED SUN DRAGON OF RA!
I-It's...!
What the?
Come forth!
God of all Gods!!
So this is...
The third god!
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
Ordinarily, it takes three sacrifices to Summon a god.
Ra's Attack and Defense Points are determined by the total Attack and Defense Points of the three sacrificial Monsters.
But Selket had absorbed Psycho Shocker, Insect Queen and The Legendary Fisherman, totaling in three Monsters.
Therefore, my servant, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra, has Attack Points totaling those three Monsters' Attack Power.
It has 5825 points!
Jounouchi...
You only have 200 Life Points remaining.
When the god attacks this turn,
your loss is guaranteed!
Yugi...
There's nothing Jounouchi-kun can do before Ra...
So this is the end?
Rishid! You've done well controlling the counterfeit God Card!
This proves that you have the same blood as an Ishtar!
When they see Ra before them,
no one will doubt that you are a user of the gods!
No one will doubt that you are Malik!
Prepare yourself, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi...!
Big brother!
Jounouchi...
Your job is finished.
This will be a loss befitting a mere lab rat.
Rishid!
God's power is yours!
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Attack him!!
Don't do it!
Don't do it, Rishid...!
If you attack with that card...!
What the hell is this aura...?
I feel it...
Anger...
It's getting stronger by the second...!
Impossible...!
The true god from within my deck...
...is emitting an aura of anger?!
What's wrong?
Why isn't God attacking?!
It's... acting a little strange.
Look at that, Yugi!
Ra's form...!
That's...!
What the?
That's not what Ra
is supposed to look like!
This is God's wrath for using a copy card!
What the heck?
What's going on here?!
That's it...
God's wrath is striking down the players of the game!
Jounouchi-kun!
Big brother, look out!
Rishid...
Has fate not accepted me as your real son?
Are you saying that I do not have the right to command you?
The Millennium Rod...!
So this man really isn't the real Malik!
Rishid!
Malik...
Rishid~!!
My lord...
RISHID!!
Hey!
Hang in there!
Jounouchi-kun!
Run, big brother!
My brother!
Jounouchi! You alright?!
Step back!
This Duel is not over!
You dumbass!
They're both out cold!
Both Duelists have Life Points left.
Both Duelists must abide by the rules, regardless of the situation!
Otherwise they will both be disqualified!
Now ain't the time for this!
They were both hit by lightning!!
Cut it out!
The Duel Disk's "Realism System" is not set at at a fatal level.
The two of them most likely suffered mental damage due to the flashing images earlier.
Then how the heck do we know who won the Duel?!
Then I shall simply call this a draw and disqualify them both!
Wait!
Both of them have 200 Life Points.
We will wait for five minutes.
Whoever shows the greater will to continue the Duel within the next five minutes shall be deemed the winner!
What?!
Big brother!
Jounouchi-kun!
You better stand up!
Jounouchi!!
Please get up, Jounouchi!
Lord... Malik...
Malik's other personality...!
Stand strong, Jounouchi!
Wake up, brother!
Stand, Jounouchi!
If you don't get your ass up, you're gonna regret it later!
Just three minutes remain!
In the case that neither player stands up,
both of them will be kicked out of the tournament!
Lord... Malik...
Malik...! His other personality is awakening!
Help me! Help me, Rishid!
Rishid, help me!!
Rishid!
RISHID!!
On the day of that ritual,
another personality was born within Malik.
Someone who wishes for everything to be destroyed...
A being who controls the darkness,
born straight out of pure suffering!
Please tell me, Rishid...
Who do I hate for this?!
Rishid...
Your face...
I cannot share the pain that you are suffering from, Lord Malik.
Rishid...
Then at the very least...
I shall swear allegiance to your family with this scar.
That day, Malik's heart was swallowed by darkness.
And Rishid has stayed by his side since he was little, keeping Malik at bay.
However... if Rishid falls...!
Rishid...
you mustn't...
If you awaken that personality...
What?!
Eh? No way!
Jounouchi!
I... cannot... afford to fall here...!
So this match has been determined?
And the winner is...
Lord... Ma...li...
You can still make it, Jounouchi-kun!
Stand up, big brother!
-Jounouchi!
Come on, Jounouchi!
How long do you plan on napping?
Huh? What time is it, you guys?
That's what we should be asking, you damn lazy ass!
Class ended hours ago!
Jounouchi-kun, hurry and get ready!
Huh?
If you don't hurry, you'll miss the City Duel Monsters Tournament!
You've been saying all day that you're gonna be the town's "number one"!
Oh yeah, that's right!
I gotta go prepare my deck!
Gosh, what the heck are you doing?!
We've gotta hurry and pick up Jounouchi-kun's cards.
And if you waste your time here, your chances of winning will fall to zero!
Shut it!
You deadbeat Duelist.
Bastard!
I swear to beat him with my own hands!
Who cares about Kaiba right now!
Right! You have to focus on preparing your deck!
That's right.
I wrote down the cards I wanted in my deck.
Huh? Mai and Shizuka!
Why are you guys here?
Well, I guess we're here to see you participate in your first tournament.
This is your first chance to shine, big brother.
We gotta cheer you on!
You guys...
Oi, Jounouchi...
Hmm?
Come her a sec.
Who's this guy?
"Jou Hatashi"
It's one of those trouble-making seniors.
Last time one of em bothered me, I kicked his butt.
Now he wants revenge on me.
When?
It's today.
Behind the gym.
But you...!
I'm not gonna go.
I don't give a crap about that nonsense anymore.
I don't wanna worry those who care about me anymore.
That's what I decided.
Jounouchi...
It's done!
We finished your deck, Jounouchi-kun!
Okay! Sorry about that, guys!
Here!
Thank you!
Alright!
This is gonna win me that tournament!
Let's get going.
Right!
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
No.. well...
How do I put it...?
My body feels really tired...
I can't stand up.
Could it be you're chickening out already?
Goodness gracious...
You're really a handful!
Don't say that...
Can someone give me a han-
Thanks, you guys!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
You stood up, big brother!
Guys...
Huh?
Is this the City Tournament?
City Tournament...?
Why the heck are you spacing out?!
I...
Why's he on the ground?
Oh yeah!
Now I remember!
When he Summoned Ra...
Me and him... were both attacked...
This Duel's winner is Katsuya Jounouchi!
Me?
I won?
Jounouchi-kun!
You did it, big brother!
Alright!
You did it, Jounouchi!
I can't believe Jounouchi won...
What is this,
a Duel based on sheer endurance?
But why didn't his Ra materialize?
And why were both players attacked?
As if a raging storm stirred the Heavens...
Is it possible that card...
A fake!
Snap out of it! Hey!
Jounouchi...
I am... proud...
...to have fought... against you...
Yeah!
Me too!
You were a really good Duelist!
But you aren't Malik, right?
Then who are you?! Answer me!
Do not worry about me... Please...!
Stop Lord Malik's...
-Malik?!
That's the thing he had before!
That's the real Millennium Rod!
So he's the real Malik!
That's right...
I am the very Malik you've been fighting this whole time.
Malik...
So he's the one who controls Ra?
So that means that Namu...!
Yugi, that was merely an alias to get closer to you guys.
So that bastard was...!
He controlled Jounouchi-kun...!
I guess you could call it...
sacrificing your friends for a better cause?
Lord Malik...
A cause that stretches back 3,000 years ago...
Yugi, in order to destroy you,
I will do whatever is necessary!
You bastard...!
Please...!
Stop him...!
That man's... other...!
"Other"?
If I fall...
That... thing sleeping will gain the power to...
...awaken... once... agai...
Hang in there!
I finally broke free...
I no longer need a shadow...
When he is around... I am hidden...
Hidden?
Compared to me, the other Malik is a child.
That is why he can never finish a Duel properly...
He's afraid of the darkness...
But...
I love the darkness.
Another Malik?
Don't tell me...!
Malik has another personality?!
Well... to me, every single one of you are merely shadows...
And that man in particular...
...was one of the more convenient ones that disappeared on me.
Malik...! You bastard...!
In the Duel just now...
...that man proved something for me.
As I expected, the only ones capable of controlling the God Cards...
...are only those connected to the Millennium Items.
Isn't that right, Kaiba...?
Rubbish...
I have no interest
in your occult nonsense.
But the God Card Obelisk obeys me as my loyal servant.
So you say, Kaiba...
But perhaps your memories also stretch back 3,000 years...
Kaiba's...?
Could it be...?
Could that figure on the mural be...?
Forget it...
We will find the answer soon enough...
So he has finally awoken...
Malik's dark side...
No one can change the course of their destiny...
We are headed to a future of despair...
The last flickering light has been lost...
Yugi...
The real Millennium Battle
has finally begun...
We are headed for the true darkness...
And none of us can turn back...
"Preview"
So Namu-kun was Malik!
That's terrible! He tricked us!
And that very same Malik was chosen along with Mai-san for the third match of the tournament!
Go for it, Mai-san!
We'll be cheering you on until the end of the game!
"I don't need you to cheer for me"?!
"I can fight on my own"?!
What's wrong with you, Mai-san?!
Next time!
"Mai VS Malik:
the Dark Duel"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise