Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Kaiba vs the Eighth Duelist"
Mai...
Mai-san...
I won't forgive that Malik.
It's about time for the fourth battle.
Jounouchi-kun...
Big brother, you need to watch the next Duel for the sake of your next battle.
Leave Mai-san to me.
Shizuka...
When I was having the eye surgery,
your encouragement made
me feel very strong.
Now, Mai-san is battling by herself.
Perhaps I won't be able to do anything,
But I want to be by her side, at least.
You...
So, I will watch over Mai-san.
What you have to do now is
go back to the heart of the duel.
Even if it's just one step, you're moving forward, aren't you?
Mai-san would certainly say that too.
Thanks to Mai-san, Honda-san and Otogi-san,
and every one of you who has given me courage,
I could take off the bandages of my eyes.
I know nothing about Dueling,
but I can at least do my best to help out my friends, right?
Shizuka-chan...
Shizuka, take care of Mai.
Yes.
The Ra card Malik owns...
What kind of secrets lie in its text?
Big brother...
Mokuba, do you understand it?
I'm sorry, big brother.  Although I'm using the computer network of Kaiba Corporation,
it's taking a while to analyze the data.
I'm accessing the host computer of Industrial Illusions.
Is that so?  When you've analyzed it, contact me.
Yeah.
We will now hold the fourth Duel of the tournament!
Kaiba...
Yugi, watch me!
This will be a battle for the God Cards
and the title of 'Duel King'!
In order to settle the score with you,
I will win this battle!
That bastard Kaiba...
He's just as arrogant as always.
It feels more like he's
just trying to show off.
Let me see the skills of a prodigy.
This unknown Duelist who hasn't shown themselves yet...
Who cares?! I'll crush any foe who stands before me!
So he finally shows himself...?
Fourth match! Seto Kaiba VS...
His opponent is...!
You're late!  You've got some nerve, making me wait!
Or if you don't want to be here, it's fine for you to surrender now.
That person is...
You're...
Contestant Number 8, your name please!
My name is Ishizu. Ishizu Ishtar!
My sister!
Don't show your face!
Yugi, isn't that person the one we met at the Egyptian exhibit?
Ah.
And you are...?
I am Ishizu Ishtar.
My family has kept watch over the king's memories for over 3,000 years.
Why are you...?
I am guided here by my own fate.
Explain it in a way I can understand.
Can it be that you have been chosen too?
That person is my younger little brother...
No...
He is now being controlled by another personality.
He is only a sorrowful vessel.
In order to save my younger brother, Malik, I will win this Duel.
Didn't that scumbag Malik say his last name was Ishtar too?
So they're siblings...
They sure give off a similar feeling...
Malik, I swear I will save you!
Dear sister!
Stay out of this, weakling!
Seto, this Millennium Tauk
has the power to see into the future.
You will lose your battle with me.
You cannot escape that fate.
The future, right?
More of that Occult rubbish again?
I've grown tired of your ridiculous jokes!
Who was it that gave the God Card, the Obelisk at the museum...
and asked for my help in destroying the Ghouls?
And this tournament was held for that sole purpose.
What'd he say?!
So Kaiba and this woman secretly planned this tournament?!
Now you say you will defeat me?
You are quite bold...
You've made a much better impression than our first meeting.
The commander of the Ghouls, thieves who raid Duelists all over the world in secrecy,
is my younger brother, Malik.
What?!
But he's not the Malik over there.
My dear sister,
is it time to disclose this secret?
As the leader of the Ghouls,
it's natural to not forgive him
for the crime of stealing Rare Cards.
But compared with this, there's a more terrifying threat
in Malik now.
I see. That's why you spoke to me and
asked me to hold this tournament as bait for the Ghouls.
I have to keep winning
and die with the one dominating Malik.
Now I know what drives your resolve,
but something still bothers me.
You use me for your goals and then claim you're going to beat me!
I don't know what his relationship with you is like,
but I will crush you for sure!
You're saying
you can see the future...
I'm sorry, Ishizu...
But your superstitious Occult paraphernalia won't work on me!
I'll use my cards
to decide my future!
And I'll use the power of the Obelisk you handed me to do so!
But what if that very same Obelisk instead leads you to a path of destruction...?
Declare the start of the Duel, Isono!
Yes!
Let the Duel begin!!
Let's go!
Seto, I can see everything in your future.
My turn!
You're summoning
Blood Vorse in Attack Mode.
I Summon Blood Vorse in Attack Mode!
Furthermore, you will set one reverse card.
Then I'll set a reverse card!
Turn end!
Everything is the same as my vision.
It's my turn, right?
If she really has the power to see into the future,
does that mean Kaiba-kun can't win?
I wanna see him get his butt kicked,
but then my plan to wipe the floor with Kaiba myself would be ruined...
Man, I don't know what to pick...
This is tough...
It's really not that tough.
Don't worry.
Kaiba won't lose so easily.
You think so too?
Against Jounouchi, that is.
Kaiba, the power of the Millennium Tauk ...
The power of the Millennium Items aren't a joke.
Be careful.
It's just what I thought.
It's easier to get information from Industrial Illusion's data banks.
Keldo in Defense Mode.
What?
she didn't look at the card she drew.
Has Ishizu really seen everything that will happen in this match?
So you mean that she already knows what
card she will draw?
It's a trick.
Mai did the same thing before.
It's not the same as the Aroma Tactics trick Mai was using.
The wind is too strong up here, so the fragrance would just blow away.
This woman's abilities are far from a trick.
You will find out soon enough.
And now I activate a Magic Card...
Fellow Traveler of the Grave!
Fellow Traveler of the Grave?
An annoying card that exposes both of our hands...
She'll make my discard my best cards!
Such a humiliating card...!
Please discard Kaiser Glider and Fusion.
That woman knew the cards in my hand without seeing them.
Can it be some kind of trick that lets her see my hand?
Let me see your cards!
Discard Resurrection of the Dead and Revival Magic from your hand.
I understand.
Turn end.
How scary. Is my dear elder sister using that strategy?
Even the surfaced Malik couldn't beat that deck!
Only I can defeat that tactic.
Malik...
No...! The evil being that lies within my brother's heart...
I will win this Duel and
bury you in the
darkness with my own hands.
Your precious little brother has been sealed deep within my heart...
Sister!!
It's my turn.
Blood Vorse, attack!
Keldo is eliminated!
How's that?
Is this what you saw in your future?
Malik, please wait for me.
Before you look into the future, you should look at the enemy right in front of you, Ishizu.
It appears that you still don't understand.
I've seen everything concerning this battle.
What cards you will play...
And how you will lose.
I know it all.
It's you who doesn't understand.
Did you think using a faint would
work with me?
In my next turn, I will use this magic card Shrink
and lower the Attack Power of Blood Vorse by half as an offering.
Then I'll invoke my face-down card, the Virus Card.
It will destroy your deck.
Ishizu's power is certainly eerie.
But Kaiba has Obelisk.
Can she beat him?
But if Ishizu-san's
power is the real deal,
it doesn't matter how
good Kaiba-kun's deck is.
We will see the answer soon.
Furthermore, I will set a reverse card on the field.  My turn is over.
It's my turn, right?
Come, attack me.
At the moment your Monster attacks,
I can activate the
Shrink and Virus cards.
I summon Mudora!
Before the power of the Millennium Tauk,
even the best Duelists fall.
All has been decided.
You'll lose your
Life Points along with Obelisk.
This is your inescapable fate.
Seto, please forgive me.
Ordinarily, the power to predict the future should never be used in a Duel.
But if I can save Malik's life,
I will offer my life to the gods
as punishment for my sins!
In addition, on this turn I equip Mudora with the Equipment Card, Sword of Dogra!
Mudora's Attack Power
goes up by 500 points.
Attack Blood Vorse!
You fell for it...!
Reverse card, open!
Fall into the trap of Hell!
He shrunk his own Monster
and then infected it with the virus!
Now that this Dark Attribute Monster has less than 1000 Attack Points, he becomes the carrier of the virus!
All the Monsters on your field and in your deck are destroyed!
There it is! Kaiba's Deck Destruction Combo!
He just killed every powerful Monster in Ishizu's deck with that attack!
Did you predict this
strategy as well, Ishizu...?
Now put all of your Monsters with 1500 Attack or higher into the Graveyard!
Very well.
Now, the Virus Combo has left only weak Monsters in Ishizu's deck.
But my Virus Combo isn't over yet.
I will invoke this now.
Sealing Swords of Light!!
So you plan to strengthen your hand
and use this to escape demise during the next three turns?
I'm not planning to escape.
The Sealing Swords of Light shall act as a countdown to your defeat!
What?
During these three turns, you will draw the card
that will decide your defeat.
Save the sleep-talking gibberish for when you're actually asleep.
You've already got one foot in the grave!
You're the one whose lost their best cards, their main battle force!
You can just wait out these three turns and pray that you draw better cards.
I will set one card on the field.
My turn is over.
Magic Removal Virus Cannon...
I'll wipe out every Magic Card in your deck on my next round!
Ishizu, I will pluck every feather from your wings,
and bring you back to the ground!
Seto Kaiba... You've played right into my elder sister's hands.
Now it's simply a question of when she will play that card...
I'm coming. My turn!
Draw!
Moreover, I put one card in reverse. Turn end.
It's my turn, isn't it?
Turn end.
What's wrong? Didn't you draw a Monster?
Don't you see the future
of my failure?
It seems very different.
you'll draw the card which
guides you to destruction
in just two turns.
I'm not the one
who's putting on a show here!
Listen up!
the card I'll draw next...
And every card I'll draw after that...
Are nothing short of the road you're walking on that will lead to your loss!
Kaiba's always saying the same crap,
but don't you think
he's being a bit impractical?
Well if someone told you they could see your future,
how could you not get frustrated?
My turn, draw!
Turn end.
Nice one, big brother!
You've backed her into a corner!
The Sealing Swords of Light are useless in front of my brother!
Turn end.
There's just one more turn.
So Ishizu, this is the supposed "countdown to my loss"?
It's hard to believe that you played the Sealing Swords of Light,
yet couldn't manage to get a single card out on the field.
How about struggling a bit more for me?
But no matter what you draw, all that awaits you is a pit of despair!
My turn! Draw!
Turn end.
It's my turn.
Bomb Held By A Tribute...
Turn end.
And wen this turn ends...
The countdown to your loss has been completed.
And even though you gave yourself three more turns to live,
and you couldn't even play a mere Wall Monster...
How can you even say that?
The effects of the Swords of Sealing Light have vanished!
Are you ready for this?!
I can feel it...
God's pulse being
emitted from my deck!
Are you aware of the existence of three legendary rare cards Pegasus hid away?
They are the three Illusionary Beasts.
The Giant War God Obelisk!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
It is said the one to acquire these three rare cards...
Will reign over the world of Duels...
and be given the highest ranking Duelist's title...
the title of "King of Kings".
I would like you to help us get the two remaining God Cards back from the Ghoul Rare Card Hunters that stole them.
This card.
This is...
The Giant War God Obelisk...!
In order to take back the two cards that were stolen,
I am entrusting you with this.
Looks like handing me Obelisk...
...was a huge miscalculated
miss on your part!
I feel it...!
Draw!
God is in my hand!
Obelisk...
Death Gremlin! Direct Attack the player!
The future is infinite!
The past is merely a string of footsteps!
The stuff that happened long before my time in the past has nothing to do with me!
Ishizu, the same goes for the fact that you gave me a God Card!
But God's hand will
not bring you a path of victory...!
Listen carefully, Ishizu!
I won't be controlled by the future!
The road I walk myself...
That is what determines my future!
"Preview"
Because of Kaiba-kun's Virus Combo affecting Ishizu's cards
They've all been destroyed!
What's going on with
her unusual calmness?
What's that Trap Card?
Their decks and
the cards in the gave
have been exchanged!
Kaiba uses his six cards
Kaiba-kun Tries hard to call Obelisk.
Will the future be
what Ishizu predicted?
Next time!
"One Attack Changes the Future"
Duel, Standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise