Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Summon the Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Here I go!
This is my Battle Phase!
Rocket Warrior!
Transform into your Invincible Mode!
Attack the Red-Eyes!!
I-It hurts...!
Wh-What the hell is this pain?!
Jounouchi-kun...
I want you... to keep my Millennium Puzzle.
In my place...
"The Countdown to Despair"
We've got about 20 minutes left in this Duel before the time limit's up...
If neither of us wins by then... we'll both get pulled into the ocean...
But I won't give up 'till the very end...
There's not much time... but if I can get back Jounouchi-kun's heart...
There has to be a way out...
Red-Eyes...
If you have any strength left...
Fight with me 'till the end!
Jounouchi!
Take off the cursed Millennium Item!
Smash that Millennium Puzzle, along with the Pharaoh's soul!
Vessel Yugi actually came and handed us his Millennium Puzzle!
That proves he's given up!
I won...!
Me?
That's right!
It's our victory!
I really wanted to inflict more pain and suffering on the Millennium Puzzle
and that hateful Pharaoh, but...
But forget it.
If he won't come out, we'll just break him!
Jounouchi-kun...
That's it!
And in order to ensure the Puzzle is never solved again,
throw the pieces into the ocean!
Later!
So you're saying this is your treasure?
It's a good chance to pay them back.
You should beat these guys up too.
Stop!
There's no way I'll do that to my friends!
SHIT!
Why?!
Why are you disobeying me?!
I'm... a Duelist...
Jounouchi-kun...?
I could care less about some "revenge for what happened 3,000 years ago" crap...
Right now, I'm gonna settle this in a Duel!
Jounouchi...!
You bastard!
Yugi!
It's your turn!
Jounouchi-kun...
Malik's brainwashing is gradually wearing off.
We've got about 14 minutes left now...
I'll fight as a Duelist.
Jounouchi-kun, until I get your heart back...
I'll continue on to the end!
My turn!
Since the Effect of your Rocket Warrior is gone, Red-Eyes' Attack Power increases by 500!
Card draw!
Jounouchi-kun has Rocket Warrior on his field, holding 1500 Attack Points...
And it'll transform into its Invincible Mode on his turn.
The Magnet Warrior holds 1700 Attack Points.
If I attack it now, I can beat the Rocket Warrior!
But that alone won't be enough to get Jounouchi-kun's heart back.
There's only one card that can get his heart back!
Only Red-Eyes can!
I set two reverse cards!
Then I Summon Magnet Warrior Beta in Attack Position!
Turn over!
My turn!
He just made a huge mistake!
He left that dying Red-Eyes in Attack Mode!
We're going to finish Yugi off this turn!
Draw!
If you attack his Red-Eyes with the Panther Warrior,
you'll win!
I'll... win?
Yes indeed.
You will beat Yugi.
Beat... Yugi?
Not good!
Malik's control over him seems to be getting stronger again!
Kill him!
Kill him!!
I Summon Panther Warrior!
Also, Rocket Warrior changes into it's Invincible Mode!
That dying Red-Eyes has only a mere 900 Attack Power.
On the other hand, the Panther Warrior holds 2000 Attack Points.
And the difference... is 1100.
Vessel Yugi has but 1000 Life Points remaining.
This attack will kill him!
Jounouchi!
Attack the Red-Eyes with your Panther Warrior!
Attack!
Rocket Warrior!
What!?
I attack Magnet Warrior Beta with the Rocket Warrior!
He's attacking the Magnet Warrior with Rocket Warrior?!
Jounouchi!
Why didn't you attack Red-Eyes with the Panther Warrior!?
Trap Card, activate!
Magic Arm Shield!
This card grabs onto the Invincible Rocket Warrior!
Attack Panther Warrior!
And because of the Permanent Magic Attrition,
Panther Warrior receives damage equal to half
of the Rocket Warrior's 1500 total Attack Points!
And because of Rocket Warrior's Effect,
its Attack Power drops by 500 for the duration of this turn!
Jounouchi-kun...
I'll fight..
...until I recover your true heart!
I get it now.
Jounouchi, it seems you have no plans on obeying what I tell you to do...
Then let me tell you this instead...
I hate those who don't do what I command of them more than anyone else.
After Vessel Yugi sinks into the ocean, Jounouchi...
I'm destroying you along with the Millennium Puzzle!
There's no doubt Jounouchi's already headed to the location of the tournament finals.
Assuming he wasn't already captured by these Ghoul guys.
Big brother...!
You idiot!
Don't say those things in front of Shizuka-chan!
We've got no proof that he's been caught yet!
R-Right...
A-Anyway, let's head to the location of the finals.
But we have no clue where that is.
We've got no choice but to look for someone who's already collected six Puzzle Cards.
Found one!
Hey! I've got a quick question for you!
My turn.
Now that Rocket Warrior's Effect has disappeared,
Panther Warrior's Attack Power goes back up by 500 points.
Card draw!
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Beta!
I Summon the Archfiend of Gilfer Demon!
Attack the Rocket Warrior!
Gilfer Flame!!
Rocket Warrior explodes!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Not yet, Yugi!
You can't reduce my Life to 0 with such a weak attack!
Just like I thought, the Gilfer Demon's attacks aren't enough to bring your heart back...?
Only the Red-Eyes can shake Jounouchi-kun's soul...
But it's so injured it can't even stand up...
What should I do?
What can I do?!
What?!
You still only got one?!
God... What the hell have you been doing all this time?
Hey, how about you?
No, we still haven't-
...found a Duelist who knows...
Hey...
Jounouchi...
You better not have been caught by the Ghouls...
Crap! They found us!
Run!
Hold on a second!
What? We'll be caught!
Otogi! Take Shizuka-chan and run!
B-But what about you?
I've still got business with them!
Honda-san!
Just run away already!
Got you!
Okay, this way, Shizuka-chan!
Don't let em escape!
Hold it!
You aren't takin' a single step past me.
Hey! That's dangerous, you two!
W-We're so sorry!
We're being chased by some weird guys!
How...?
How can I get Jounouchi-kun's heart back?
Where's Jounouchi?!
You know, right?!
Tell me!
D-Domino Pier...
Domino Pier, you said?
Honda! I'm here to pick you up!
Mai!
Shizuka-chan! Otogi!
She said she's friends with you and the others.
They told me everything.
So these Ghoul guys are after you?
You know about the Ghouls?
I heard countless stories relating to them.
They're all over the newspaper.
There's some pretty sick rumors going around about them.
So, about Jounouchi-
See!
I know the location of the finals!
No, he's not there.
Jounouchi's at Domino Pier.
Domino Pier?
Yeah! I heard it from one of the Ghouls!
So we have to hurry there!
Okay!
Hang on tightly!
It's my turn!
Demon Dice?
There isn't much time left...
If I simply have Jounouchi do nothing this turn,
they'll both be headed to the netherworld.
This should be amusing.
In just about eight minutes...
...my clan's 3,000 year grudge shall come to an end.
You can share the "bond of friendship" with one another for all eternity!
Enough...
You no longer need to plan a strategy or think for that matter...
You no longer need to fight.
All you need to do is wait patiently until time runs out...
Jounouchi-kun...
Do you remember what happened back in the Kingdom?
Back then, you fought really hard for your sister, Shizuka-chan...
Fought as a Duelist.
And you won the prize!
Shi...zu...ka...
Hang in there!!
Shizuka!!
And... then you promised me in Battle City...
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
I place two reverse cards on the field.
And then...!
Panther Warrior goes into Attack Mode, and my turn ends!
Just as I expected, you ignored my orders and continued Dueling, Jounouchi!
But there's no way my brainwashing wore off...
He's...
He's fighting purely by instinct?!
My turn!
That's right, Jounouchi-kun!
We have no choice but to fight.
Fighting's the only way to get your heart back.
I have to believe that!
If I don't hurry, we're gonna run out of time!
Card draw!
Bring it on, Yugi!
I set one reverse card face-down!
And I'll attack Panther Warrior with the Gilfer Demon!
You fell for it, Yugi!
I left my 500 Attack Power Panther Warrior in Attack Mode to lure you into attacking!
I know that!
Gilfer Flame!!
Magic Card, open!
Consider this payback!
Angel Dice!
Demon Dice!
It's a Double Reverse Combo!
Angel Dice strengthens the Panther Warrior's Attack Power multiplied by the number rolled!
And Demon Dice weakens the Archfiend!
Your Monster is as good as eliminated!
I won't let you!
What?!
Reverse Card! Magic Removal, activate!
This card negates the Angel Dice!
Now the Panther Warrior's Attack Power won't increase...!
In that case, I just have to hope Demon Dice reduces the enemy's Attack Power enough.
A two?!
Shit! It didn't work?!
Yes! We're finally here!
Jounouchi's somewhere around here, right?
Big brother...!
It's alright.
Your brother's a really good man!
You better watch him real close at the finals!
Right!
Huh?!
Over there!
What the hell is that?!
Now the gap between our Life Points is gone...
If I can somehow get both mine and Jounouchi-kun's Life Points
down to 0 at the same time...
Maybe that's the way for both of us to escape...
Yugi's only got 700 Life Points left...
But there's almost no time before the countdown to their deaths starts...
Jounouchi!
Yugi-kun!
Shizuka-chan!
Anzu?
What's going on here?!
Stay back, Honda!
Why, Mokuba?!
Look...
Shit! What the hell is that?!
They've taken Anzu hostage.
What for?!
So we don't interrupt Yugi and Jounouchi's Duel!
Why the hell are Yugi and Jounouchi Dueling in the first place?
And what's up with that huge anchor they're attached to?
A "Death Duel".
Death... Duel... as in...?
Yugi's been fighting with his life on the line to get Jounouchi's heart back from the Ghouls!
What'd you say?!
Jounouchi-kun's...?!
Jounouchi...
Big brother...!
Don't!
Shizuka-chan can't see Jounouchi like this!
Don't do it, Shizuka-chan!
Don't take off your bandages!
She can't see Jounouchi the way he is now!
Seeing her cherished big brother acting the way Jounouchi is now...
It'd be way too much for her to take!
Big brother...
It'll be alright...
Have faith in your big brother.
We've got just under 4 minutes left...!
If things keep up like this, me and Jounouchi-kun are gonna sink into the ocean!
My turn!
Draw!
Death... Meteor...
You drew a nice card, Jounouchi!
Now! Use that card to finish him off!
You still want to Duel, am I right?
"Preview"
Seeing Jounouchi no longer obeying Malik's orders,
Yugi begins to call out to the true enemy, Malik.
Meanwhile, a frustrated Malik completely takes over Jounouchi's body to finish him off.
Jounouchi, who finally got his heart back, is faces Yugi as they're put into a desperate situation.
But Yugi wants to save Jounouchi's life...!
Next time!
"Attack Me! The Fatal Last Turn"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...