The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Bakura-kun?
T-That's...
This is a Dark Game!
What complete fools you are.
With this the Millennium Puzzle is mine.
What?
If it's a Dark Game.... I'll be your opponent!
Trap of the Metamorph Plot! Flame Swordsman in Danger
Bakura...
You are a duelist of the Dark Games, aren't you?
Bakura? I'm not Bakura.
What is your objective?
Yugi... you should know this.
Whoever gets all the Millennium Items will have everything he wants from this world.
If you win, I'll bring back everyone's soul.
But if I win, I'll take your Millennium Puzzle.
Try it!
Duel!
My card is Commander in defense mode!
Honda-kun?
W-What's this?
Where am I?
Yugi?
Everyone's souls were...
transferred to the card they like the most?
It's too late to realize that now... And now, it's my turn.
My card is...
White Thief!
Attack!
What?
What is that?
Honda-kun!
In this duel, the soul card that loses, just like the other cards, goes to the graveyard.
What?
Soon, the God of Death will get to the graveyard.
When Commander is taken by the God of Death, Honda's body will die.
Honda-kun will...
Honda-kun!
What is this place?
"Hiroto Honda"
What is this?
You finally got it. But the Dark Game can't be stopped!
Now it's your turn! What will you do, Yugi?
Honda-kun...
I will surely save you from the graveyard.
I can't play everyone's soul card carelessly.
But... to defeat the White Thief now...
...there's no other card than Jounouchi-kun's Flame Swordsman.
Next is this card!
Flame Swordsman!
What?
Jounouchi-kun!
You are... Yugi?
What's going on?
Be calm and listen.
Your soul is now sealed inside the card of the Flame Swordsman.
What?
If we can't win the duel, you can't come back.
And if you're defeated in battle, you will go to the graveyard, like Honda-kun.
Graveyard?
But, to stop this dangerous duel, and to get everyone back safely...
Your power is necessary!
All right. Leave it to me! Don't worry!
Jounouchi-kun...
This is just a dream, isn't?
Let's get this over with! So, who's the enemy?
Ba-Bakura?
Bakura's the enemy? I don't get this dream one damn bit...
That's not Bakura-kun. He is using Bakura-kun's body...
A Dark Duelist!
I don't get it at all... but let's do it!
All right! I did it, Yugi!
Now, it's your turn!
I'll use this!
What is that card?
That doesn't matter, the enemy is weak!
Wait, Jounouchi-kun!
Let's go!
I did it!
Understand?
Metamorph Pot!
Eh? Did I do something bad?
When Metamorph Pot appears, our entire hand must go to the graveyard.
In this moment, it's a good thing that I have no cards with the guys' souls, but...
S-Sorry!
Black Magician!
Black Magician is the card that has Yugi's soul!
It's my turn!
And also...
My turn is over.
Another set one? To have the card with Yugi's soul in my hand would be dangerous.
And also a Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead, to revive Honda-kun!
Jounouchi! Yugi!
You too? What is happening here?
Seems we were transformed into Monster Cards from Duel Monsters.
Though, I really don't understand it at all...
But... Yugi... Aren't you up there?
That's...
Yugi...
Now's not the time to keep secrets. We have to fight with everyone!
That Yugi is the spirit of a "Yugi" that sleeps within the Millennium Puzzle.
It's the other me.
Sorry... for not telling you about this until now.
It was not my intention to hide this from everyone, but...
Don't worry... Yugi is Yugi! And we are friends, aren't we?
Yeah!
Guys...
By the way... where's Anzu?
She must still be in the deck.
Let's get this over with before Anzu shows up!
That's right.
All right! Let's hurry and end this!
Wait a moment! This turn is mine!
Black Magic!
Metamorph Pot!
We have to discard our hands again, right?
S-Sorry...
It was the same card as the previous one!
This is Anzu's soul card.
Did you draw a good card?
You're allowed up to 3 of the same card in a deck.
There's still one Metamorph Pot...
My turn.
I set a card.
Metamorph Pot?!
And also...
I activate Just Desserts!
What?
For each monster you have in the field,
it inflicts 500 damage points directly to your Life Points.
Are you alright, Yugi?
Yeah... but one more attack, and I lose!
If this keeps up, I'll lose, and everyone's lives will...
If he uses another Metamorph Pot...
Keeping Anzu's soul card in my hand is dangerous.
Guys!
T-This is bad!
B-Be quiet!
Why is everyone cosplaying?
Me too?!
Hey. Shh! Don't speak too loud! That weird Bakura will notice you!
What do you mean?
Now we are in the Duel Monsters world.
And now Bakura-kun is being controlled by a Duelist of the Dark Games.
Yugi...
There's two Yugis?
That's the other me.
I really don't get it, but to put it simple, there's a cool Yugi and a normal Yugi here.
It's not like that!
My bad!
All right! I'll show you that I can be cool too!
Hey! Yugi!
I'll defeat the hidden enemy!
Battle!
Wait, Yugi!
Black Magic!!
He did it!
Yugi! That's amazing!
Yugi!
What happened, Yugi?
My body... is paralyzed!
Hold on!
Yugi...
If the monster that attacks the Electrical Lizard isn't an electric type,
it doesn't attack in the next turn.
My turn is over.
Trying to hide is useless.... that's Anzu, isn't it?
I'll tell you that...
This is Flesh-Eating Insect!
Yugi... what's that card...?
When that card is activated, one monster on the field is destroyed!
One of us will, then...
I don't want to go back to that graveyard!
But, if it's so powerful, we just have to defeat it in the next turn!
We can't.
When the card's attacked, it activates!
Really?
Yugi! There isn't a way to prevent it from activating?
If we use the Trap Card... Hunting Horn of Death...
What? So that's a trap card?
But, to activate it, it requires a sacrifice.
We can't do such a thing!
All right! I'll go!
Don't, Honda!
But, if the Flesh-Eating Insect is activated, who knows which of us it will destroy?
What the hell are you...?
You just came back from the graveyard.
Now it's my turn to go!
- Jounouchi-kun!
- Jounouchi!
Prepare yourself!
Other Yugi! This is your chance! Use me!
Please! I don't want my friends to be sacrificed!
I activate the trap card Hunting Horn of Death!
I sacrifice one monster on the field to activate it...
Your monster's effect is negated and it is destroyed!
- Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Now I leave the rest up to you... Yugi!
Damn...
Why did you do this?
Don't worry, you will all go to the same place.
Now... it's my turn.
Where am I?
That's...
Jounouchi...
For us...
Like I'll just die?!
Jounouchi...
Anzu's body is...
When Saint Magician is activated...
I can recover one magic card from my graveyard and add it to my hand.
Magic card!
Resurrection of the Dead!
- Jounouchi!
- Jounouchi-kun!
Guys...
None of them being in the graveyard is weird...
The friendship between the four of us will create a miracle... definitely!
Friendship, huh?
Don't make me laugh...
I'll teach you that this bond between you will not last long.
And also this...
That's Bakura-kun's favorite card!
Change of Heart!
That's right!
I'll use this card's power on Black Magician Yugi...
You will obey me as if you were mine!
What did you just say?
You will fight your friends!
Just how low will this guy fall?!
Say what you want! With this, your friendship ends!
You'll all die in despair!
Yugi!
Bakura-kun?
Bakura-kun's soul was also sealed inside a card?
Yugi-kun... now... attack me now!
What?
Now...Hurry up and attack me to defeat the Duelist of Darkness!
But... if I do that... Your soul will...
I don't care! That's better than having an evil being controlling my heart!
Now...
Bastard!
That's impossible!
It's my turn! Black Magician Yugi, attack the High Priest!
Understood!
Black Magic!!
Damn! Just a little more and I...
Are you alright, Bakura-kun?
Thanks.
This Millennium Ring is...
My father is an archaeologist that travels around the world, but...
When he went to Egypt, he found and bought the Millennium Ring and a card.
The person who sold the Ring and the card to my father said he was from the Dark World.
What a long dream I had...
That's right. A terrifying Dark Bakura was in mine.
- What?
- Don't scare us...
By the way.... there were two Yugis... that was really a dream?
That voice is...
Let's take a look!
Running to see what happened, we find Mai Kujaku-san who lost all her Star chips!
In order to retrieve her star chips, Yugi duels with the Dark Player Killer!
You want him to bet his life?
Stop, Yugi! How will you fight if you can't see what is hiding in the darkness?
Next time: A Duel of Darkness! The Castle that Disappears Into the Darkness
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship