The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Sea God Leviathan
I can’t believe how well I played.
Jounouchi is still smiling.
He should be very happy.
He beat Mai Kujaku in his first Duel.
Even I find it hard to believe.
Jounouchi-kun, if you continue like this, you may win the next Duel too.
I’m getting kinda hungry.
Anyone got any food?
Nope.
But... why didn’t anyone prepare food for this tournament?
Right, that is a problem.
The game will last for two days.
We’ll eventually need food and something to drink.
Shouldn’t the organizer of this event...
...provide it for us?
They aren't very organized!
Oh yeah! I brought something with me.
Tada!
Survival Book.
What?
If there’s an emergency...
...we can follow the steps in here for looking for editable plants, and mushrooms.
Idiot! That’s too risky to eat!
I smell something good.
That way.
Let’s go guys!!
Food!
He can smell it?
He beat Mai Kujaku with his sense of smell.
His nose must be very sensitive.
We found food!
Really?
That's lucky...
Stop! Those are someone else’s!
It must be a blessing of food from God!
He has no self-control.
No, I think Jounouchi may be right this time.
Hey, don't eat by yourself!
It does smell nice.
Let's eat!
Ya freeloading bastards!
Who dares to touch my fi...
What was that?
Let me try again...
I knew we’d get caught.
Damn ya freeloaders!
Ya can’t just eat my fish without permission!
We didn’t even eat it yet...
Don’t pretend you didn't!
Give the fish back to me then.
Star Chips?
Are you the 3rd place runner-up of the National Championship...
...Ryota Kajiki-kun?
Yeah, that's right.
That's a lie!
You’re just homeless...
Who are you calling homeless?
I'm Ryota Kajiki.
And I'm a great Sea Duelist!
What's so funny?
Octopus.
Dam
mit!!
Octopus!!
-I was gonna eat it!!
You guys sure seem to be Duelists.
Nice to meet you.
I’m Yugi Mutou.
So you're the Yugi Mutou who slaughtered Kaiba in that Duel so easily?
I’ve heard you’re really good.
It’s an honor to have ya in this tournament.
N... not really...
Ok, ok.
Sorry for my rudeness.
Since Yugi is friends with you all...
...I will forgive you.
Help yourself to the food.
-Really?
-Seriously?
Let's dig in!
That’s good, it's great to have friends!
That's good.
I’m full.
The grilled fish was delicious!
If I win the tournament...
....I will buy a boat and catch some better fish for you.
You want a ship?
Is that the reason you entered?
Part of it...
...I want to buy a newer model.
Then, go out to the sea again.
So that I can catch more fish at a time.
It would be great to live out on the sea.
I envy that kind of lifestyle.
The ocean is my world.
I’ve been living at the ocean’s side since I was born.
That’s why I know the ocean’s happiness, and when it’s sad.
I understand the sea very much.
Sorry for sayin' strange things.
No, not at all...
You even gave us a free dinner.
Well then, it’s time to go.
Really, leaving so soon?
Thanks for the food!
Let’s work hard.
Wait, Yugi.
I am not interested in your friends.
But Yugi...
...you won't run away.
You...!!
I’m not stupid enough to feed you and then let you go.
What do you mean?
I take care of this area...
...this is the place where I use food to reel in hungry Duelists.
I hold the advantage in the sea.
Damn.
You treat people like fish...
So that's why you were being really nice to us.
Just like choosing an opponent to test my power.
But, you are not good enough.
Yugi, let’s Duel.
I'll beat ya!
Alright.
I accept this Duel.
This is my area...
Duel Ring!
In this field's condition, I'm the navy head...
And you're only a tiny soldier.
Is that ok?
Yeah, it's ok.
Each player will bet 2 Star Chips.
Alright.
Yugi... you have fallen into my trap now.
Duel start!!
Yugi, do your best!
Don’t lose to that ocean bastard!!
My card is...
This!
What?
There’s no data for that card...
The monster isn’t even materializing!
What does this mean?
Well, what will you do?
This is my attack!
Do I have to fight against an opponent that I can’t see?
Hey, what’s wrong?
It's your turn!
So, all of my opponent's monsters are hidden, but they definitely are there.
This is why the data isn't there.
After the Devil Kraken's attack is increased from the Sea's Field Power Source...
...it's attack will be upped to 1560, and defense 1829.
But you don't know this quite yet.
That's the horrible thing about the ocean.
Shit, he can't attack!
No way...
That's unfair, Kajiki!
If the legendary Duelist's bothered by such minor details, he's not worth playin'!
Here, I can only hope.
My card is this!
Devil Kraken, go!
What?
What is that?
Tentacle Submission!!
Imp, defeated.
He can't take something like that.
It’s gone back into the ocean again!
This is the Sea Stealth Attack!
Sea Stealth Attack?
It’s just the beginning of the ocean!
Now, go back to your field.
As long as I can't see the opponent's where his attacks are coming from...
I can only use a defense right now.
Gremlin.
But, I won’t give up just yet.
Next turn...
...I will show you my strength.
I know what you're planning.
My next card is...
This!
The ocean's Giant Jellyfish!
He'll go in defense position.
I can't see it again...
What are you gonna do, Yugi?
Then, I'll have to use this combo!
Horn of the Unicorn!
That's it!
What?
That monster is going to hide in the ocean field.
That means that all of his monsters are hiding underwater.
Yugi planned to trap him in the ocean.
I see, there is another attack.
Gremlin, attack!
Alright!
Why haven’t your Life Points changed?
Yugi, you fell into my trap.
What?
This jellyfish, can conduct electricity!
Then, they can resolve that electricity, and use it against you on all of your monsters!
It’s my turn.
Devil Kraken, attack!
Tentacle Submission.
In the sea, I will always win!!
You are very good, Kajiki Ryota.
Your attacking technique and strategy are perfect.
In the ocean that’s hard to be controlled...
....what should I do?
I guess I can only keep attacking.
I will use this now...
Silver Fang...
...with this Full Moon Magic Card.
What kind of card is that?
What in the ocean can you attack with that?
I will let you experience the ocean’s heavy force!
Sea God Dragon - Leviathan!!
What?
What is that?
The ocean's Field Power makes it power-up!
Now raised to 2340 Attack, 1950 Defense Power!
Leviathan?
You can’t look down on the sea.
The aftermath of destroying an ocean isn’t funny.
Silver Fang, gone.
Now I am not being hurt by your monsters.
What?
Look at the field!
This is...!
Most of my field is underwater now!
Leviathan is showing you his anger!
That hit took over 95% of your field, under the water!
Also, you have no more space from your field to use anymore cards!!
You’re going to lose soon.
That means my opponent isn't just monsters, but now the whole ocean.
Your eyes are showing fear to the ocean.
Just like when I was a kid.
What do you mean?
My father...was the greatest fisherman in the land.
But in the sea...my dad...
I used to think the ocean gave people warmth and made them full of life...
But, I gave up that theory after that day...
Ryota, the ocean itself is a monster.
Monster?
I heard that we should not underestimate the ocean’s power...
It’s peace in the past was like a dream to me...
All of a sudden, it showed me it’s ugly and terrible side.
Dad...that!!
Ryota, you will die if you get swept under by the sea.
Dad!
When I woke up, I was alone on the beach.
Then, I couldn’t find my dad...
Do you understand this, Yugi?
I have to challenge the ocean for my dad.
And someday, I won’t be afraid of the sea anymore.
I will be the greatest fisherman.
That is what I'm here for...
So, I cannot lose.
Finish the game, Yugi.
It’s your turn.
I got it.
I will finish this with you peacefully then.
Yugi...
He actually has a soft-side too...
What an opponent...
Only 5% of the field...
...so I have to get that card.
Let's settle this!
Here comes, Giant Soldier of Stone.
This giant soldier can effectively use...
...the remaining 5% left.
So, his attack and defense go up from the land!
It’s a very good attack force.
But this monster can move freely in the ocean.
So it increases the attack’s area.
Megalodon!
Dammit!
It’s stopping him from moving!
Now the Giant Soldier of Stone can’t move.
Don’t even think about trying to increase your field.
Yugi, sorry but I’ve won.
No, Kajiki.
I return your earlier words. I was waiting for this moment!
What was that?
Giant Soldier of Stone, Attack!
What?
My monsters have already blocked him...
...how can he still attack?
This attack does not limit just to monsters...
...but the card I played on the field before.
The moon!
What!?!?
Giant Soldier of Stone, attack!
Rock Crush Sword!!
What?
The ocean is dissipating!!
Why the hell!?
The Full Moon card increased the tide.
The attack power of Leviathan...
...I can’t increase his attack from the moon.
Wha---What!?!?
When the moon is destroyed...
...the field power is decreased dramatically!
My monsters...
The circumstances are very obvious...
...that’s the truth.
Curse of Dragon.
Equipped with the Burning Land Magic Card.
Combo Attack.
Hell Flame!
All of the opponent’s monsters are killed.
I lost.
Awesome!
Yugi won!
Alright!
My water cards...
...lost on my own field.
Yugi, I lost.
You are very good!
You are also very good.
Now I only have one Star Chip Left.
I guess I start all over again.
Let’s do our best.
All duelists have their own hopes and expectations...
People who arrive on this island...
...should fill-up their stomachs first.
See ya!
Let’s go get some food!!
He seems to be....very optimistic.
Alright, let’s go!
Great, I am getting a little hungry.
Me too.
Didn’t we just eat?
Hey, let’s have some more food.
Just as Yugi starts to increase his gathering of Star Chips...
...a Star Chip thief appears
Yugi, are you really going to accept a duel with that guy?
Is there any chance you know who it is?
Is that, Kaiba-kun's little brother?
Is there some kind of connection between these brothers and Pegasus?
Next Time, "The Stolen Blue-Eyes White Dragon".
Duel Standby
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship