Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
"The Story That Concludes in the Light"
Partner, this is my final trump card as well as my mightiest warrior!
The Black Magician!
That's right!
Atem still had the Black Magician in his deck!
Black Magician...
It was reassuring when he was on my side...
But as an enemy, there's no stronger foe!
But I have to defeat him...
Or I won't win!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon a Monster in Defense Mode!
Black Magician's Attack Power with the equipped Book of Secret Arts is 2800.
None of my current Monsters can beat it.
I switch Curse of Dragon into Defense Position!
Turn end!
So he's got nothing else he can do but defend...
No, we don't know that for sure.
That Face-Down Defense Monster could be troublesome for Atem.
The Monster set on Partner's field...
And by using Witch of the Black Forest's Effect,
I can add a Monster with 1500 Defense Points or less
in this case Marshmallon, from my deck into my hand.
That's without a doubt Marshmallon.
When that thing is attacked while in Face-Down Defense Position,
it deals 1000 points of damage to the opponent.
And it's a Monster that can't be destroyed in battle.
My Life is at 900.
If I attack him carelessly, this match will end.
But, my partner...
Such a strategy won't work against me!
My turn!
Draw!
Magic Card! Thousand Knives!
He did it again!
The Pharaoh's really forming his own cards!
There is no doubt that the Pharaoh is now God of Battle.
As long as Thousand Knives is on the field with a Black Magician,
it can destroy one of the opponent's Monsters!
Go, Black Magician!
Marshmallon!
Naturally, the effect of Marshmallon in Face-Down Defense Position won't activate!
Then, Black Magician!
Attack Curse of Dragon!
Black Magic!!
Yugi!
Jounouchi, Yugi had the advantage, but he just lost all his Monsters!
Stay strong, Yugi!
Brother!
He changed the flow of this battle in an instant...!
The Black Magician is really frightening...!
He's strong...
But that goes without saying.
My other self and the Black Magician...
Is there even a blind spot in the formidable bond these two share...?
It's your turn now, Partner.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon the Blockman from my hand in Defense Mode!
I then set a card face-down... and end my turn.
Here goes! My turn, draw!
I equip Black Magician with the Black Sphere!
When Black Magician is equipped with the Black Sphere,
and its Attack Power is higher than the opponent's Defense Power,
the difference is dealt to the player as damage!
Here goes, Partner!
Black Magician, attack Blockman!
Trap, activate!
Soul Shield!
Soul Shield lets me halve my Life and negate the battle.
The opponent's Battle Phase is then forced to end!
The Black Magician's attack couldn't reach me!
Then my turn is over.
He made it out of that one somehow...
But now Yugi's only got 400 Life Points remaining.
But Atem-kun only has 700 of his Life...
It wouldn't be all that farfetched to think the next attack will determine the match.
Shit. I was talking all high and mighty to get Anzu to stay and watch this Duel,
but now I'm starting to feel like I can't watch it.
Yugi... Atem...
Fate is too cruel to force you two to fight each other!
My turn!
He's planning something.
Draw!
I have no choice but to make a gamble...
I play a Magic Card from my hand!
I activate Gold Sarcophagus of Sealing!
Gold Sarcophagus of Sealing?
I can choose a card and place it inside the gold sarcophagus...
If my opponent uses the same card, its effect is negated.
What card did he choose?
That box...
It looks exactly the same as the box Yugi kept his Millennium Puzzle in.
The box the Millennium Puzzle was laid to rest in...
The object that lead to Yugi and the other Yugi meeting each other.
A box of friendship.
I'll then activate Blockman's Special Effect!
Block Release!!
Blockman has the ability to split into the same number of sacrifices
as the number of turns passed since his Summoning!
So Blockman becomes two offerings!
I sacrifice the two Blockmans!
I'll defeat the Black Magician with this Monster!
Come forth!
Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction!
That's...!
Gandora...
That's...
The Monster that defeated Bakura's dark personality in the Memory World.
And it's the Monster that represents Yugi's parting with the other Yugi.
On the turn Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction appears on the field,
its effect halves the Life of the player
and removes all the Monsters on the field from the game!
Gandora's Special Ability!
Giga Rays of Destruction!!
Trap Card, open!
Black Illusion!
The Trap Card, Black Illusion.
Upon activation, it protects Black Magician from all Monster Effects on the field!
No way...
Even Gandora couldn't defeat the Black Magician...
But as a result of this effect, the opponent is permitted to draw another card.
Now, my partner!
Draw a card.
I set two cards on the field.
Turn end.
Yugi just lost all his Monsters on the field again!
This is bad, Brother!
It's all over for Yugi this time!
It's impossible.
It really isn't possible for Vessel Yugi to defeat the Pharaoh!
Yugi...!
No... Partner's flame of opposition hasn't disappeared!
My turn!
Draw!
My Black Magician will attack you directly, Partner!
Trap Card, activate!
Magician's Circle!
When my opponent attacks with a Magician Monster,
this card lets me Special Summon a Spellcaster-Type Monster from my deck!
That's a card meant to deal with Black Magician...
So Partner really did think up a strategy to battle against Black Magician.
I Special Summon Silent Magician from my deck!
But Magician's Circle calls out to my deck as well!
From my deck...
Come forth, Black Magician Girl!
Black Magician Girl!
The battle will continue, Partner!
Black Magician!
Attack Silent Swordsman!
Yugi's Monster only has 1000 Attack Points!
If this hits him...!
This isn't over, Other Me!
I swore to defeat you in this Duel!
Magic Card, activate!
Textbook of Magic!
I use this card to discard my entire hand and draw one card from my deck.
And if it's a Magic Card, I can activate it!
My hand is at zero!
I have no cards to discard!
This will be the last draw that determines both of our fates!
Magic Card, activate!
Treasure From Heaven!
Both players draw cards from their decks until they hold six cards in their hands!
I use this moment to activate Silent Magician's Special Ability!
Silent Magician's Attack Power increases by 500 points every time my opponent draws a card!
I had to draw five cards!
Thus, Silent Magician advances to Level Five and her Attack Power becomes 3500!
Then, Black Magician's attack will continue!
Atem's only got 700 of his Life!
If this Battle Phase is conducted, Yugi will win!
I activate a Quick-Play Magic from my hand!
Magicians Cross!
When there are more than two Spellcaster-Type Monsters on the field,
I can use two of my Magicians to launch a 3000 Attack Point attack!
I'm impressed, Partner.
You managed to defeat my trump card, the Black Magician.
But our Life Points are tied at 200.
This won't continue much longer.
The time to settle this has come!
Mm-hmm...
Partner, the card you used to turn the tables, Treasure From Heaven,
in turn gave me a turnaround.
You guided me to just the card I needed to settle this Duel!
I activate the Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead, from my hand!
Resurrect, God of the Sky!
Osiris!
What?!
He brought Osiris back?!
Osiris' Attack Power is determined by the amount of cards the player has in his hand.
I have five cards in my hand.
That means that Osiris
has 5000 Attack Points!
Partner... I win.
I knew, Other Me...
If I were you... I would call out a god...
That's...!
I now break the seal on the gold sarcophagus!
The sealed card is coming out!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Because I put Resurrection of the Dead in the coffin, you can't use it...
Therefore, on this turn... Osiris' Special Summoning...
...is negated.
Osiris is...
...fading away...!
Resurrection of the Dead is usually the card that gives Yugi the upper hand!
Yet he sealed it away himself?
This is Yugi's message... to the other Yugi.
The souls of the dead must not linger in the world of the living...
This was meant as a requiem to see that the Pharaoh's soul travels to the Afterlife.
Yugi's trump card... was also his way of saying goodbye.
My Partner... predicted my trump card...
You've... surpassed me.
Atem-kun doesn't have any Wall Monsters!
If Silent Magician attacks him directly... the Duel is over.
Yugi...
Now come...
Partner!
Silent Magician!
Direct Attack on the player!
I lose, Partner.
Stand up...
The winner shouldn't be on his knees.
If I were you, I wouldn't cry!
I-I'm too weak...!
You've always been my goal!
I always wanted to be strong... like you.
You're not weak...
You've always had a power that no one else could beat...
The strength of kindness...!
That's what I learned from you.
Partner...
The courage you showed when you accepted this Battle Ceremony...
...showed me the path I must take.
Other Me...
I'm not the "other you" anymore.
And you are no one but yourself!
You're the only Yugi Mutou in the world!
Yup!
What the?!
The eye on the door...!
The Eye of Wadjet guards the door to the Afterlife.
Through the Rite of the Duel, it has seen through the Pharaoh's soul.
After 3,000 years of being lost in the world of the living,
the time has come for the Pharaoh's soul to be welcomed into the next world.
Soul of the Pharaoh!
Say your name to the Eye of Wadjet!
My name is Atem!
- Yugi!!
Wait, Yugi!
Are you really going to go?!
Hey, you don't really have to go the next world, do you?!
D-Don't leave us!
Other Yugi!
I mean... Atem!
The place you have to return lies beyond that light...!
I know that!
I do understand that...
But to us, that light is nothing but a wall separating you from us!
Don't you... understand what that means...?
We've been friends for so long,
now all of a sudden you're just going to vanish right in front of us?!
I just don't get it!
Anzu! You don't need to get it...!
Just accept it and burn these memories into your brain!
The time you've spent with him... The feelings...
Burn it in so you never forget!
So for now... Let's just see him off.
To his future!
Guys...
I won't forget...
...anything about you!
Yugi!!
Even if you're "Pharaoh", even if you're "Atem",
you're still "Yugi"!
Even if a thousand years pass, we'll always be friends!
Yes!
We'll never forget you!
Yugi!
Other... Me...
What?!
An earthquake?!
The Stone Slab of the Underworld!
The Millennium Items!
Come on, Yugi!
It's too dangerous to stay here!
Run for it, everyone!
Hurry!
By delivering the Pharaoh's soul, the role of the Millennium Items has ended.
The Door to the Afterlife has closed forever.
So he's gone, huh...?
Yeah...
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Grandpa, I'm heading out!
Okay! Be careful!
Yugi!
Good morning!
- Mornin'!
Good morning, guys!
This isn't the story of a great Pharaoh.
You're late, Yugi!
Sorry about that.
Everyone has a story of their own.
And that story ends in the light.
And...
My story has just begun!