Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Hell Poet - Helpoemer"
That's...
Is my brother fighting in a Dark Game...?
If he loses a card from
his hand every turn...!
Shit...! This Malik asshole uses dirty tricks!
Jounouchi-kun's at a complete disadvantage now!
My turn, it would seem.
Draw!
Jounouchi only has the Monsters Panther Warrior and Rocket Warrior on his field...
Whatever... They're both Four-Star weak Monsters.
I can defeat them anytime...
But Panther Warrior loses 500 Attack Points every turn because of Plasma Eel's Effect.
And as long as the Plasma Eel remains attached to him, he cannot be sacrificed...
I'll let Jounouchi keep his Monsters and use them to bring him more sweet pain!
I set two reverse cards!
Turn over!
He's not going to attack...?
He used up his entire hand...
What is he planning?
I have only one Three-Star Monster in my hand...
I'll just have to draw
a High-Level Monster...
My turn! Draw!
Yes! The Insect Queen!
But she's a Seven-Star Monster that requires two tributes...
I can't Summon her right now.
I'll just have to make this guy last 'till next turn...
I Summon Baby Dragon in Defense Mode!
Those set cards are
Traps without a doubt...
Should I just pull back...?
Or...!
What's wrong? I have no hand right now.
Come on and attack me!
Perhaps my set cards intrigue you?
It must be futile!
Cuz they could be scary Traps and all~!
Those are obviously Traps...
He can't attack like this!
Jounouchi, just calm down and come up with a plan!
If I can defeat his Drillago right now...
...he'll lose his Wall Monster!
If I end my turn without doing anything, he'll get out without taking any damage...
But my Panther Warrior's Attack Power keeps dropping because of Plasma Eel...
If I'm scared of his Traps, I'll only give him a further advantage...!
I don't know what's
gonna happen, but...!
Don't listen to him!
No! He needs to attack!
If he takes a chance and strikes, Malik will be forced to open his Traps.
And if he does, he'll be forced to reveal his plan.
If he does nothing but wait, Jounouchi's Panther Warrior will lose 500 Attack Points.
He needs to choose self-exposure in order to get ahead.
I would do the same.
Rocket Warrior! Attack Drillago!
I compliment you for having the guts to attack me, despite the obvious Trap!
Reverse card, activate!
Card of Last Will!
What?!
Card of Last Will activates whenever one of my Monsters' Attack is decreased.
I am permitted to draw from my deck until I have five cards.
There's no need to play God against someone as worthless as you...
No way!
Are you serious?
Even if you set a trap,
I'm not gonna stop!
I sacrifice a Scapegoat!
Panther Warrior attacks!
Booyah!!
Sweet move!
But he's still got a set card...
I activate the Permanent Trap, Coffin Seller!
What?!
Now every time one of your Monsters is sent to the Graveyard...
...you will lose 300 of your Life Points.
What'd you say?
Your Battle Phase is over!
Relish the sound of Helpoemer's song!
He stole the Insect Queen...!
Damn it...! I lost my second-strongest Monster, not counting Psycho Shocker...!
So the power of Coffin Seller activated already?!
By the expression on your face, you must have lost quite the valuable Monster!
Shut the hell up!
What a terrible combo...!
You lose a card every time you attack...
...and if it's a Monster, you lose Life...!
This is not good!
Your turn's as good as finished!
So it's time Plasma Eel lowered Panther Warrior's Attack Power by 500 points!
My turn! Draw!
In addition, I'll show you
a terrifying combo...
I set a reverse card!
And now, I activate a Magic Card!
Premature Burial!
Premature Burial allows me to Special Summon one Monster from the Graveyard!
A Monster from the Graveyard?!
I pay 800 Life Points in order to Special Summon Drillago in Attack Mode!
I'll then sacrifice Drillago...
...and Summon the Legend Devil!
That... looks strong...!
Allow me to give you some information...
Legend Devil has a Special Ability.
At the start of every one of my turn's Standby Phases,
he gains 700 Attack Points!
Say what?!
700 points every turn?!
If you don't hurry up and beat him, his Attack Points are going to grow way out of your reach.
Turn end!
Shit...! A Monster that raises its Attack infinitely isn't fair!
Jounouchi-kun has the upper hand when it comes to Life Points, but he's still at a huge disadvantage.
He's playing me left and right here...
Isn't there something I can do...?
Something...!
If I can just draw that card...!
...I can destroy his Trap!
Don't let me down!
My turn! Draw!
This isn't...! I failed!
Nothing you try now
will make a difference!
In that case, I'll try the Rocket Warrior Combo again!
I Summon Little-Winguard!
Oh no you don't!
Trap Card, activate!
Scratch Wheel!
Rocket Warrior can't move!
As long as this card remains face-up on the field, the selected Monster can't attack.
And they can't change their Battle Position, either!
He's going to attack with his Legend Devil next turn...!
All I can do is defend myself for now...!
I Summon Little-Winguard in Defense Mode!
I'll also switch Panther Warrior into Defense Position and end my turn!
I activate Plasma Eel's Effect!
Panther Warrior's Attack Points go down!
I won't let this pain defeat me...!
No... This pain is just giving me more of a reason to kick his ass!
For Mai as well!
A Dark Game...!
If he loses, my brother...
...will become like Mai-san...
My turn! Draw!
I forgot to mention that!
On every one of my Standby Phases,
Scratch Wheel deals my opponent 800 points of damage!
What did you say...?
Furthermore, Legend Devil's Special Power increases his Attack Power by 700 points!
Go, Legend Devil!
Attack Little-Winguard!
Damn it!
You take another 300 points of damage due to Coffin Seller.
Taking Life away from
you like this is so fun!
I set a reverse card!
Damn you...!
Turn end!
Another Trap...?
If I activate Calamity of the Wicked,
every card you have on the field will be sent to your Graveyard.
You now have five
Monsters on the field...
That means thanks to the effect of Coffin Seller...
...you'll take 3500 points of damage...
And Legend Devil will
kill you instantaneously.
You have no way of winning.
Jounouchi can't even fight back now!
A deadbeat 'till the very end...
He can't even entertain us properly.
It's my turn!
If this keeps up, I'll get closer and closer to losing this turn.
I've got no choice
but to draw that card!
Please!
Your turn is nothing but a wasted
turn bringing me closer to victory!
The least you can do is let me enjoy your final moments of suffering, huh?!
You asshole...!
I won't lose...!
I won't lose to this psycho bastard!
I...
...won't lose!
Hey, Malik-chan!
It looks like your turn was a wasted
turn bringing me closer to victory!
What?!
Let me show you!
This is my trump card!
Magic Card, activate!
Quiz!
Let me show you!
This is my trump card!
Magic Card, activate!
Quiz!
Q-Quiz, you said?!
Now you have to guess the
Monster at the bottom of my Graveyard.
What?!
If you guess it right,
that Monster is removed from the game.
But if you guess it wrong,
that Monster is Special Summoned
to my side of the field!
Come on and give me
an answer already!
What's the name of the
first Monster to enter my Graveyard?!
The first card in his Graveyard...
So the first Monster to enter his
Graveyard was Wyvern Warrior...
No, that's wrong...
But it disappeared from the Graveyard when I activated Buried Offerings.
So that means the first Monster
sleeping in the Graveyard would be the
card sent their by Helpoemer's Effect.
You don't know, do you?!
Of course you don't!
And that's because...
...Helpoemer discards them at random!
There's no way you'd know!
So what's the matter, huh?!
Is the first Monster in his Graveyard
that powerful a Monster?!
Hurry up and answer!
You got five seconds!
Five!
Four!
Three!
Two!
One! Time's up!
Ya got no clue, right?
That means I get to
Summon my Monster!
It matters not.
Regardless of what Monster you bring back,
Calamity of the Wicked will send it
straight back to the Graveyard!
The answer is... this guy!
Come forth, Psycho Shocker!
Psycho Shocker?!
Now your Traps are useless,
my little Malik-chan!
Open your eyes nice and wide
and take a good, long look at
Psycho Shocker's Special Ability!
Trap Search!!
All my cards in Reverse Mode, including Calamity of the Wicked...!
All my Traps were destroyed?!
Psycho Shocker!
Alright! He turned things around!
You're doing good out there, Jounouchi!
Smart move! That was an excellent attack,
making full use of Helpoemer's Effect.
Jounouchi...! You bastard...!
How do ya like that, little Malik-chan?!
Psycho Shocker is one of the cards I won in Battle City containing a soul!
Here's my Puzzle Card and Rare Card.
Please take them.
Will you Duel me again someday?
Esper Roba.
I'm not Esper no more. I am just Roba.
I will challenge you with my true ability next time, fair and square.
That's how it should be.
I look forward to that day.
Hey Roba.
You have your brothers, and I have
my sister, and my reliable friends.
We are not alone, so we will be stronger.
That's right.
Guys who aren't alone
are much stronger!
I'll beat this final enemy
standing before me!
Yugi... Wait for me in the Final.
As I expected of you, Jounouchi-kun.
Throughout Battle City, you've taken
the steps to become a True Duelist!
Pride!
Spirit!
And strength!
You have all of these in your heart!
Malik! This is my Battle Phase!
Here I go!
I switch Baby Dragon and Panther Warrior into Attack Mode!
And then, I attack with Psycho Shocker!
Eat this!!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Hurting me this badly...!
Yes! The Monsters on
Malik's Field are gone!
If he can Direct Attack the player, Jounouchi-kun will win!
He can win...!
You can win, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi! If you win this,
you'll be able to enter the Final!
Big brother, I bet you'd be
really shocked if Jounouchi won this!
Don't underestimate a
God Wielder, Mokuba.
I can tell...
The gods won't smile
on someone like him...
Just you wait, Mai!
Once I beat this guy down,
I'll save you!
Let's finish you!
All three of my Monsters attack!
Wha...?!
Your boasting has gone far enough!
Dark Wall of Wind!!
What?!
His Monsters' attacks didn't work?!
Your Battle Phase is over!
Plasma Eel!
Now Panther Warrior is
as good as useless!
Dammit...
You went and got cocky...!
And I'm not done yet!
All that awaits you is a living hell!
I've been thinking about the
Penalty Game for when you lose...
I'll be sure to pay back the damage you inflicted onto me ten-fold!
And I'll deliver onto you
the ultimate suffering!
I really want to
watch my brother's Duel...!
But, Mai-san...
What should I do?
My turn!
Draw!
This card is the perfect
Penalty Game for you...
I Summon the Lava Devil - Lava Golem!
3000 Attack Points?!
Don't you need to sacrifice to
Summon an Eight-Star Monster?
Hey, hey! Don't misunderstand me!
I won't be Summoning this
Monster on my field!
I'll sacrifice the two Monsters on your field...
and make the Lava Golem your servant!
What did you say?!
I sacrifice Psycho Shocker
and Baby Dragon!
I Summon Lava Golem!!
Just what... the heck is going on here?
Rejoice! You get to control a
Monster with 3000 Attack Points!
Me control it...?
Wh-What the hell is that thing?!
Jounouchi-kun's been
trapped inside a cage!
What's going on?! Why would the enemy
give him such a powerful Monster?!
He forcibly Summoned a High-Level
Monster to his opponent's field...!
Big brother, what is that thing?
Provided that, of course,
the player can handle his red-hot body
melting around him every turn,
and taking 700 points of
damage every turn as a result!
I guess you could say
this Monster is quite a handful!
What?!
O-Ouch...! Hot, hot, hot...!
Damn, is that hot!
In addition,
now that Psycho Shocker is gone,
I'll play a reverse card on the field!
Hey, wait!
You just told me that's a Trap!
Big deal! Your Monster
has 3000 Attack Points!
I have no Wall Monsters to hide behind!
I'm defenseless!
It's a simple decision, is it not~?
Shit...!
Jounouchi...!
Think about this first, Jounouchi!
Calm down!
He sacrificed the two Monsters
on Jounouchi-kun's field...
...just so he could Sacrifice Summon this High-Level Monster, Lava Golem...
But there's no way Malik would just hand his opponent a 3000 Attack Monster like that.
He has to have a horrible strategy
hidden up his sleeve!
I just gave you a powerful Monster!
A "thank you" would be in order...
...or are you perhaps too scared to speak, trapped in that cage and all?
Damn it!
Big brother...
Damn it all! I can't stand this heat!
I have to do something about this!
And now Jounouchi, it's your turn!
If you don't act quickly,
you'll melt right down to the bone!
Malik...! You bastard!
What's the matter?
Attack me with that
3000 Attack Power Monster already!
A much hotter hell awaits you!
Jounouchi has been trapped by this creepy looking lava Monster!
But he can still attack Malik with that 3000 Attack Monster!
Oh wait, I guess he
really did set a Trap Card...
He continues to lose Life every turn that passes.
And his hand is reduced!
But don't give up, Jounouchi!
You still have one chance to turn things around in your hand!
Next time!
"Counterattack! Gilford the Lightning"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise