A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Driven to Desperation!
The Shadow of Temptation"
The morning of the battle is finally here...
Grandpa...
Yes?
Mornin'!
Good morning!
Good morning, guys!
It's finally here, Yugi!
Let's head out to our final battlefield!
Let's go!
Yugi, Jounouchi. We're gonna head on up to the balcony so we can cheer you guys on.
Yugi, Jounouchi. Do your best.
Good morning, boys!
Yugi, the time to settle things has come at last.
Jounouchi... I'm impressed you showed up, considering all that awaits you is a loss.
Keith, I don't know squat about you being the ex-U.S. Champion,
but I'll beat the shit outta a creep like you with my cards!
Guess you still ain't realized...
Without the card needed to participate in the tournament,
you'll lose before you even enter the Duel Ring.
Attention all Duelists participating in the tournament.
Sorry for the wait.
Please enter the Duel stage.
Pegasus!
Welcome, proud Duelists, to this sacred Dueling battlefield!
The Duelist Kingdom Championship Tournament shall now commence!
The one who survives the tournament shall be granted a prize deserving of a champion!
With a prize that big, I can save Shizuka.
And of course, the winner shall earn the right to challenge me.
Hey! Can you answer one thing, Pegasus?
What does the person get if they defeat you?
The one who defeats me, the creator of Duel Monsters,
shall be recognized as the "Duelist King" and the founder of Industrial Illusions.
In other words, the one who defeats me shall be awarded the title of the world's number one Duelist.
Recognized by everyone...
The world's number one...
I presume the Duelists among me would gladly accept both great fortune and fame.
Am I wrong?
Ain't that interestin'?
Yeah! Let's go for it!
I sincerely wonder who will win the tournament and challenge me.
Pegasus...!
I'm going to defeat you no matter what!
And get back everyone's souls!
The first round will now commence.
Yugi Mutou VS Mai Kujaku!
Please proceed to the Duel Ring.
Before we start, please show me the cards earning you the right to participate.
Very good.
You can do this, Yugi!
You...!
Jounouchi-kun!
You can see much better from up here.
Yugi! You better win!
Mai Kujaku... I must win this Duel so I can move on to battle Pegasus!
Beating strong opponents is a Duelist's greatest thrill...
I came to this island for the sole purpose of that thrill.
But after meeting you guys...
I began to question my way of living, and learned the meaning of friendship from you.
And I dreamed of the moment I could finally fight against you.
Yugi! Your very existence is what got me this far!
But right now, you're not even looking at me.
Seems his heart is already set on his fight against Pegasus.
That's the one mistake you mustn't make.
You can't win a Duel when you don't even have your enemy within sight!
Let's go, Yugi!
Okay!
Duel!!
What's wrong, Mai?
Aren't you going to use those special "Aroma Tactics"?
I don't need to use those against you.
Mai, I'm sorry, but you're no match against me!
There's something you can't see right now.
If you can't see that...
...you have no hope of beating me!
Harpie Lady in Attack Mode!
That's Mai Kujaku's usual strategy.
Be careful, Yugi!
Don't worry about it!
That's Mai's overused strategy!
You really think the same strategy she used on me will beat Yugi?
Also, I'll play another card this turn as well.
A Set Card, eh?
I'll just play a strong card and dispose of the Harpie Lady!
Dark Knight Gaia!
Attack the Harpie Lady!
What a big idiot!
Trap Card, activate!
Silver Screened Mirror Wall!
Spiral Shaver!!
What!?
Silver Screened Mirror Wall is a Trap Card that halves the Attack Points of a Monster that attacks it!
The moment you attack it, this mirror appears to stop your assault!
And after attacking the reflection of itself in the mirror,
the attacking Monster will have its Attack split in half.
My turn.
I place an Equipment Card on my Harpie Lady.
Cyber Bondage!
Get going, Harpie Lady!
Scratch Clash!!
Dark Knight Gaia has been annihilated!
I don't believe it...
My powerful card Gaia... was destroyed...?
Yugi, I didn't think you would fall for something so obvious.
Now it's your turn, Yugi.
Alright... Demon's Summon.
It has enough Attack Points to beat the powered up Harpie!
Now come on and attack me, Yugi.
I set a card face-down!
I face you with this card!
I'll show you the extent of my power, Mai!
Go, Demon!
Finish off the Harpie Lady!
Demon Lightning!
You just declared "attack", Yugi!
My Trap Card will reactivate!
Wh-What?!
And with that, the Demon's Attack Points are halved!
I get it! A Permanent Trap!
That's right.
The Trap still remains on the field.
But you noticed a bit too late, Yugi.
Normally once activated, a Trap Card will lose its powers...
Then the card will disappear from the field.
But there are some exceptions!
Yes. Out of the hundreds of Trap Cards,
Mirror Wall is one of the rarest Traps, a Permanent Trap Card!
So long as this card remains on the field, I can activate its effects again and again!
Each time you declare "attack"!
Yugi, that makes all of your Monsters' attacks completely useless!
What's wrong with Yugi-kun?
He seems to be playing rashly without thinking!
It's not like him to fall for the same trick twice!
Yugi... what's wrong with you?
You disappoint me.
To think the Duelist I've admired for so long was only at this level...
I can clearly see it!
From the moment you stepped into the Duel Ring, you've been crushed by an invisible pressure!
An invisible pressure?!
When Duelists face each other in battle, they can feel their fighting aura.
But I'm not feeling that aura from you right now!
Are you trying to say you can't feel any fight in me?
That's right!
You're only thinking about fighting Pegasus, aren't you?!
And you're looking right past me.
Man, you're more of an arrogant boy than a strong man!
You thought you already beat me before the Duel even began.
You're distracted by the thought of Pegasus watching us,
And you think of our battle as a mere nuisance.
Pressure... from Pegasus...?
Yugi boy... That lady is correct.
With the way your mind is now, you hold no chance of ever defeating me.
Mai! Say what you want after you beat me!
Just continue the Duel!
It's just like a weak man to try and intimidate his opponent.
But you're just bluffing to hide your own weakness!
Don't screw with me!
Right on the mark, eh?
And that's why you fell into my trap so easily!
That damn Mai...! She's always trying to provoke her opponents...
Yugi! Don't let Mai toy with you anymore!
Mai-san... Why are you acting this way towards Yugi...?
Could it be Mai-san's trying to help Yugi not lose sight of his Duelist ability...?
Win or lose, the cruelties of the world still remain.
But in the end, all you can rely on is yourself!
Mai-san won't forgive Yugi unless he fights her with everything he has... his full strength.
Now I'm seriously angry, Mai!
So you've finally woken up, Yugi?
Maybe now we can have a real Duel.
Here I come! This time it's the real battle!
Okay! I'll take you on!
That's it, Yugi...
As A Duelist, you must face me with 100% of your power and your pride.
Or there's no meaning to me defeating you.
Will he attack Harpie with Demon this turn?
But it's Yugi's Set Card that bothers me...
It's very likely to be a Trap...
And if it is...
This turn, I attack using this card!
Harpie's Feather Duster!
My Set Card was Hexagram Curse...
Had you attacked, you would have fallen for my Trap Card.
You read through it nicely, Mai.
I'm a very cautious person.
Maybe a bit too cautious at times.
It's your turn, Yugi!
As long as she has Silver Screened Mirror Wall...
I can't attack her, no matter how many Attack Points my Monsters have.
My attacks are sealed!
Demon to Defense Mode!
I also place a Monster in Defense Mode.
You stand no chance of winning if you're trapped like that!
My turn!
I use the Equipment Card Rose Whip to increase Harpie Lady's Attack Points!
So you plan to infinitely power up your Harpie while hiding behind Silver Screened Mirror Wall?!
I'll start by attacking that Defense Monster!
Whip Punish!!
Not yet, Yugi...! My Harpie Combo is far from complete!
Hey, hey! Will Yugi be alright?
Yugi! Mai's gonna create her Harpie Lady Army!
Be careful!
Yugi! Keep trying!
A Monster in Defense Mode!
As long as Mai continues to use that Trap Card...!
There's no point in trying to defend yourself.
I'll take you out nice and slowly.
My turn!
It's here!
With this card, my Harpie Combo is 70% complete.
Even though it's not complete yet, this is more than enough to beat you!
Here I go, Yugi!
This is the Harpie's strongest servant!
That's...!
Harpie's Pet Dragon!
Harpie Lady's cute, well-trained pet!
Harpie's Pet Dragon gains 300 Attack Points for every Harpie Lady on the field!
Now, eliminate that Demon!
Saint Fire Giga!!
Even the Demon...!
Yugi... there's something you've lost sight of.
What?!
And until you find that answer, you stand no chance of beating me!
Back when I fought against Jounouchi,
he asked me a riddle.
Yugi, now it's time for me to direct that riddle at you.
It's something you can see, but can't see!
Yugi, I wonder if you can find the answer to that.
Something you can see, but can't see...?
Mai, ain't that the same question I asked you?
Besides, do you even know the answer yourself?!
I do, Jounouchi.
Because of you, I've come up with my own answer.
Then I'll answer in place of Yugi.
And that answer is...!
The fiery, fiery spirit of friendship!
How 'bout that?!
Idiot! That's incorrect!
My answer's not such a cliché!
C-Cliché?
Then what the hell is the correct answer?!
'Sides, me and Yugi thought of it first!
What the hell are you doing?!
Jounouchi... You were the one who taught me that answer.
And you should know what that answer is.
How do you think a card amateur like you made it this far in the Duelist Kingdom?
Tell me that and you've got your answer.
But the way Yugi is now, he'll never find that answer.
Now's not the time to be confused by Mai's words...
I'll win this Duel with my own strength!
Alright.
The Black Magician card.
Harpie's Pet Dragon has 2300 Attack Points.
In terms of Attack Power, Black Magician is stronger.
But she still has the Silver Screened Mirror Wall Trap on her field.
I can't attack.
Then I'll play a Trap against a Trap!
I set a card on the field!
And Black Magician in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
Now then, Mai...
If you attack my Black Magician, Holy Barrier Mirror Force will destroy your Monster!
My turn!
With this card, my Harpie Combo will be 80% complete.
Yugi, there's no point in setting a trap for me...
My next card is the Equipment Card, Shadow of Temptation!
Shadow of Temptation...?
By looking at your magician, you'll know what it does.
What in the world?!
Black Magician took a fighting stance!
Right! Shadow of Temptation has the power to lure enemies into battle!
The Harpie's battle pheromones stimulates an enemy's battle instincts!
She switched him into Attack Mode?
S-So that means Yugi's Defense has been sealed?
Now, go on and attack the Harpie!
Black Magician!
And then I'll play this card.
Harpie's Feather Duster!
My Trap Card...!
And Harpie's Pet Dragon will attack!
Saint Fire Giga!!
Well, Yugi?
My Harpie Combo is perfect, is it not?
Th-This is bad, Yugi!
Yugi!
"Preview"
What you can see, but can't see.
Mai-san's words help Yugi take back what he's lost so he can begin his counterattack.
But with Mai-san's impenetrable strategies, he's backed into a big pinch!
Eh? What?
He's found some kind of trump card to turn the tables?
Next time! "The Legendary Strongest Soldier: Chaos Soldier Descends"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship