Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Noah, no matter how powerful the Monster you try and attack me with is,
and regardless of how many Life Points you have,
so long as I have the bonds I share with my friends, I won't lose!
You use your power to force people's hearts into accepting you.
We'll never be beaten by someone like you who uses such brazen methods!
So take this, Noah!
This is our power of cooperation!
"Darkness of the Kaiba Family"
Shizuka!
Big brother!
Mokuba!
Since our bodies are back to normal...
Yugi-kun won, right?!
What?! Yugi?!
That's right! Yugi took over your deck and fought Noah in a Duel!
Yugi took my deck...?
But I at least surpassed Seto in the end, didn't I...?
No!
Seto chose defeat
in order to save Mokuba!
And then I lost to Yugi, who took over Seto's spirit...
The "bonds of friendship", was it...?
But I've always... I've always been alone!
Is that why I lost?!
If that's so...!
It was because I didn't have any friends?!
I won't...
I won't accept that!
DON'T LOOK AT ME LIKE THAT!
If this is how it is, I'll just take over your personality and become you!
Wh-What's with... these visions...?
Who is... this man with that serious expression...?
Jounouchi-kun!
Kaiba!
Everyone's here!
Just what... is this...?
What the hell are you?!
Yugi!
Hey! You bastard!
Now you've really pissed me off!
Knock it off, brother!
This is a kid you're picking a fight with!
Now let us all out of here immediately.
And before you do that, give me back my real body! OOH-AH!
Your "real body"...?
Your real bodies aren't even here!
"Your"...?
What do you mean by that?
Still haven't figured it out yet?
Everything you see here is virtual.
There's not a real thing here.
What'd you say?!
Now I get it! That's why all the pain we get here feels real!
Correct.
All of your real bodies are being held in Virtual Simulator Capsules.
I saw something similar when Noah entered my body.
Is that what he meant?
I've been thinking something was strange for a while now.
It's peculiar that we could actually get hurt in Virtual Space.
I see.
So we all just lost consciousness back then...
I just transferred your minds to the Virtual Simulator.
What the?
I'm disappointed in you, Noah!
Impossible! That voice...!
Father!
Gozaburo!
Father, why are you...?!
You should have passed away!
Dead?
It's true that my body has been destroyed.
But my mind has lived on
and escaped death!
I used the same system I tested on Noah,
and became the ultimate being after being transferred into the computer, in a sense reviving as a virtual being.
Humph. No matter what form you take, you're still the same disgusting man.
I've been wanting to
see you so badly, Father!
I've been alone here for so long!
I no longer have any use for you.
Noah...
Alright, enough with the chit chat!
So why don't you enlighten us, Gozaburo?!
On the foolish plan you've got cooked up!
Humph, you're just as patronizing as always, Seto.
Very well. I will tell you everything.
It all started out with an honest desire to save my dieing son, Noah.
Noah was born to inherit my very mind, to be the runner of Kaiba Corporation and control the entire world.
as you can imagine, it created quite a problem for my plans when he went and died.
"Created quite a problem for my plans when he went and died"...?
How cruel...
But in the end, virtual is virtual.
It's nowhere near the same as living like a normal person.
But how many people would survive after this plan of yours was commenced?
About 3%, more or less.
Don't you think that's a bit too little?
I don't really care.
It has nothing to do with me, after all.
Shortly after, I realized something about the Virtual World and the Real World.
For someone such as myself who lived in in this reality, the Real World, the gap between the two of us was vast.
What are you saying, Father?!
I was just trying to make you happy!
Noah...
And then, Seto...
You appeared before me.
And you adopted me as a test for Noah!
And if Noah won, it would be the proof you needed that Virtual Reality surpassed Reality!
You adopted me in order to help Noah prove himself greater than I!
Humph. How wrong you are, Seto.
What?
You were meant to be
Noah's container!
Noah's... container... you said?!
Exactly. After realizing first hand the limitations of Virtual Reality,
I sought to bring Noah back to life in a body of his own.
And Seto, you were the one I selected for that task!
That's... not something a real human being would think of!
This man called Gozaburo...
Now I understand why Kaiba hates him so much!
Despise me, do you?
But that didn't go
as I had planned either.
I couldn't forgive you for snatching Kaiba Corporation straight from right under my nose.
So before killing myself, I transfered all of my memories into the computer.
It was at that moment that I decided you would no longer be a test for Noah.
I plan to steal your disgraceful body from you, and revive once again as the runner of Kaiba Corporation!
No way... So you're saying I was just being used...?
The situation has changed.
Thanks to Seto, that is.
If you have to hate anyone, hate Seto!
Scumbag!
But I no longer have any need for your body either.
Because, regardless of whether I have a body or not, I can easily hack into Kaiba Corporation's computer network.
Within a matter of seconds, the world would be in the palms of my hands!
Humph, what a joke.
You don't even have a body anymore.
What could you possibly do?!
Take a look at this!
Those are...!
An advanced group of artillery Kaiba Corporation built in our secret base after signing a certain contract.
Satellite missiles!
M-Missiles?!
Originally, this mobile floating fortress was built as the launching site for this type of weaponry.
It has weapons aimed at every major city in the world.
Father, are you saying that you were able to hack into the system that controls it?!
Why are you so surprised aver this?!
Was it not you, Noah, who gave me this idea in the first place?!
Father.
I made a simulation of something interesting not too long ago.
I calculated that if we used the entire financial resources and weaponry of Kaiba Corporation,
we could destroy the entire world in just 30 days.
I bet you didn't know that!
Understand now?
I plan to remain as a virtual existence.
Using computer mainframes around the entire world, I can gain control over the entire world with almost no effort!
What a fool...
As we spoke, I have taken control of this world's program.
All exits connecting the Real World and the Virtual World have been shut off.
None of you people will be leaving this Virtual World ever again.
What did you say?!
Seto!
Noah!
The two of you had better put aside your differences and get along well together.
You will live immortal, never feeling pain or hunger again!
You can almost view this place as a Heavenly paradise!
Kaiba Corporation belongs to me.
I won't give it to anyone!
Wait, Gozaburo!
There's an exit in this place?
Father was right.
All the exits have been closed.
I was planning to get a body and return to the Real World.
I was then going to run Kaiba Corporation in Seto's place.
No, I was just doing what Father wanted!
But... Father said he no longer needs me!
It was exactly the same when we came to his home...
He was just being used by Gozaburo!
If there's no exits, we'll be...
Is there really no other way to return to the Real World?
If not, I'll remain trapped in the body of a monkey forever! OOH-AH~!!
Hey, what's the deal, Noah?
You sure there aren't any other exits?!
Quite a shame, isn't it?
You may get off fooling that deadbeat over there, but you can't fool me!
Father has locked the program.
We can't create another exit from here.
Why don't you all give up on leaving and stay here in this world with me as my father suggested?
It's more fun than it looks...
Noah!
I can't believe you're still saying that!
You were abandoned by Gozaburo, you know!
That hurts, Mokuba.
Big brother!
No! He's not my big brother!
But...
Why the long face, Mokuba?
I-It's nothing!
He put us through so much...
But when I look at him, I can't help but think of how Big brother was back in the old days!
That's right!
There may still be one more chance to get back to the Real World.
What'd you say?!
Tell us!
If that one exit I
made myself is still active...
I hid it inside one of a game!
I'm almost positive my father wouldn't know about it.
Where is it? Hurry and take us there!
I guess it can't be helped.
Just follow me.
I won't let things end like this.
If this is how things will go, I'll get myself a body and return to the Real World, no matter what I have to do to get one!
How amusing!
Tch, weaker than I thought...
Kaiba, I have something to ask you.
About what Noah said.
How much of it do you trust?
Hm, here I thought you were going to ask something more serious with that look on your face.
I feel as if he's planning something else.
I know that well on my own without you telling me.
I don't think he's doing anything bad!
Partner!
I just don't think Noah would be plotting anything else.
Why?
But Noah said himself he was just being used by his father.
And knowing that, do you really think Noah would have a reason to try something?
That's true. You could be right about this.
Now isn't it about time we switch places?
Yup!
It's inside here.
Behind this gate lies Virtual Domino City.
Virtual Domino City?
Huh? Where'd everyone...?
Yugi?!
Big brother!
Where did everyone go?
Mokuba!
So this is where you were?
Noah! Where's the others?
They went ahead already.
Now, come this way!
As we speak, they're all lost in the flow of their own memories.
Guess who?
Grandpa!
Hey...!
What the heck is this?!
That's low, Malik!
Here I go!
Osiris, attack!
Super Conductor!
Thunder Force!!
He counter-attacks with Dragon Sword!
I can't win...
I can't... defeat Osiris...
This is...!
Here it is!
There's a door leading to the Real World in this game center.
I can't believe there's an arcade in the Virtual World!
It's kind of weird!
Sorry Mokuba, but I'll be taking your body.
Hold on a second!
What? We'll be caught!
Otogi! Take Shizuka-chan and run!
B-But what about you?
I've still got business with them!
Honda-san!
Just run away already!
Got you!
Okay, this way, Shizuka-chan!
Don't let em escape!
Hold it!
Hey! That's dangerous, you two!
So where do you wanna go, Jounouchi?
W-Well, I dunno...
Anywhere's fine, so long as it's with you.
Mai!
Jounouchi...
No...
From the very beginning, I've always thought of you as...
No! This isn't really happening!
Yugi-kun!
Anzu!
Big brother!
What was that just now?
Huh? That Noah bastard's gone!
Mokuba-kun's gone too!
Kaiba-kun as well!
Hey Noah... About what you said earlier...
Once we return to the Real World, you're going to need a body.
But your body is gone already, right...?
Yes.
And that's why I'll be taking your body.
If you promise me that you'll stop trying to hurt my big brother,
I'll be happy to ask
my brother a favor for you.
To get you a new body.
We won't be able to get you a real body or anything...
But with Kaiba Corporation's technology, we can make some pretty good-looking androids!
If anything, it won't be a monkey.
I mean, we're brothers and all.
I can't believe he'd call me his brother after all those horrible things I did...
What a simpleton.
Oh yeah, this isn't the time to be playing games.
Where's the exit?
My big brother and the others are there already, aren't they Noah?
Up there.
The exit should be in that game over there.
There's no way Gozaburo would know about this!
Now's my chance!
I finally got one!
A living flesh-and-blood body!
It isn't virtual!
It's a real body!
We're still trapped inside of Virtual Domino City.
Our only chance of escape, Noah, is nowhere to be found.
And we can't find Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun either!
Eh? Kaiba-kun headed by himself to settle things with his father?
While we search the streets for Noah, a hoard of Monsters appear!
Geez! Just hurry up and let us return to the Real World already!
Next time!
"Exodia Necross"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise