A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Eat this!!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Impossible...!
As great as I am...
I lost to that kid...?!
And the winner is... Jounouchi!
I DID IT~!!
Now then, excusing the interruption that just occurred,
we shall now begin the final round of the tournament...
...featuring Yugi Mutou versus Katsuya Jounouchi.
So the time has finally come...
Yugi.
"The Final Game of Friendship!
Yugi VS Jounouchi (Part 1)"
We shall now commence with the final round of the tournament!
The final round will feature Yugi Mutou versus Katsuya Jounouchi.
Grandpa!
Yugi! I believe in you!
That you'll surely save me!
Well then, bye bye, big brother.
Just clean it up. It's disgraceful.
I can't believe the Duelist Kingdom finals
would come down to Yugi-kun and Jounouchi-kun...
True... but a match is a match.
They've got to fight each other seriously.
But why...?
Yugi would give the prize money to Jounouchi after he wins...!
So why do they still have to fight each other?!
If they don't have a match, they can't get the prize money.
That's true and all, but...
Those two are best friends!
For those two to seriously fight each other...!
But that's why they're going to fight each other seriously.
That's what best friends do.
I just don't get it!
Jounouchi-kun...
Yugi, don't even tell me you can't Duel against me!
Well?
I know that, but...
I don't think I can...
Just fight!
Yugi!
We've fought a lot of difficult battles to make it this far!
No matter who the opponent is,
we made it this far because we fought on to the very end!
Am I wrong?!
Jounouchi-kun's right...
We've got to fight until the very end!
For the sake of everything we've fought for.
Now accept this match with me!
I understand, Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi...
The two of you have both done Well winning and making it this far.
This will be a battle to determine who earns the privilege of challenging me.
So go forth and fight on with everything you've got!
Yugi...
I wanna say something before we start the Duel.
You believe this or what?
I actually made it all the way to the final round, against you.
I made it this far thanks to you and the others.
Jounouchi-kun...
Right now, I'm feeling something...
That I really wanna fight you seriously.
I know you have incredible strength.
That's why I want to fight head on against this strength, against this power!
Let's go, Yugi!
The Duelist's flame is starting to ignite within Jounouchi-kun...
The flame that aches to fight against a strong opponent!
This is truly remarkable...
Despite the two having such a strong friendship,
they are able to cast away their feelings as a friend and can charge in head on.
This is truly the most fitting match for the final round of the tournament!
Jounouchi-kun, I'm not holding back!
I'm giving it my all!
Yugi, I'll beat you and that incredible power of yours!
And I'll do it in the name of our friendship!
And now...
Duel start!
Duel!!
I'll start things off!
Bring it!
Elf Swordsman in Attack Position!
Yugi and Jounouchi both have the same goal... to save someone precious to them.
So why...?
That's something completely different now.
Right now, those two are fighting their strongest as Duelists.
They're putting all that to the side.
And that's what makes them men!
But I wonder if Jounouchi-kun's usual head-on attack pattern
will be enough to take down Yugi-kun...
What a truly beautiful sight this is!
Right now, the Duel Ring is like a pen holding two wild beasts!
Now, it's your turn, Jounouchi-kun!
Here I come, Yugi!
I Summon Mage Knight Giltia!
Attack Position!
Battle!
The Magical Attack!
Soul Spear!
Elf Swordsman just got a beatin'!
What's wrong, Yugi?
Put out something more powerful than that!
Jounouchi's really gotten stronger.
Just like him, too.
But the Duel's just getting started.
When it comes to focus, Yugi-kun's got the advantage.
What do you mean?
I mean Yugi-kun's eyes.
He's hiding his fighting spirit,
while observing Jounouchi-kun at the same time.
The old Jounouchi-kun would charge in with raw power.
But the Jounouchi-kun in front of me is different!
He's fought many battles, and he's learned the importance of strategy.
He almost seems like another person!
Jounouchi-kun.
What is it?
In this game, each battle between Monsters is a risk.
Even if I play a Monster with higher Attack than yours,
I may only win one battle, and the lead can change at any moment!
Right.
I've learned quite a bit since I came to this island.
I'm fully aware of that.
The key to Duel Monsters is...
...a balance between Magic Cards and Monster Cards.
One who is unaware of this has no chance of winning.
And I've learned a lot from watching your matches, Yugi!
Then you should know not to use up all your good Monster Cards right from the start.
Yup. Thanks for that little piece of advice.
My turn!
Dark Knight Gaia in Attack Position!
Battle!
Mage Knight Giltia has been beaten!
Yugi, now that's what I'm talkin' about!
But I'm different than I used to be!
Armored Lizard, in Defense Position!
So it's a plan to lure me into attacking him?
Very well.
I'll take you on!
What the heck's that Jounouchi up to?
No, Jounouchi-kun seems to be planning something...
I see.
What's wrong, Yugi?
It's your turn.
Right, here I go!
Demon's Summon, in Attack Position!
I did it!
Demon Lightning!!
And I beat Armored Lizard!
I thought as much.
This is all a part of Jounouchi-kun's plan.
There's no way.
They're just being beaten left and right.
No...
I'm sure it's more than that...
Jounouchi-kun was trying to lure Yugi-kun out and make him lose focus
by playing a mediocre card from his hand.
He knew his opponent wasn't going to play a strong Monster from the start,
so he played Armored Lizard in order to force him to.
Jounouchi...
Just as I thought.
I figured you would wait for me to play something stronger...
I've been waiting for this moment!
For the moment you brought out the Demon's Summon!
Yugi!
A balance between Magic Cards and Monster Cards is the most important thing!
I'm gonna return that advice to you!
My turn!
I play the Flame Swordsman in Attack Mode!
What do you mean by that, Jounouchi-kun?
What in the world is he thinking?
There's no way he can win with Attack Points like that...
No, look at that...
I'll then use this!
The Magic Card Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand!
What?!
So he played that card, eh?
That card switched the Attack and Defense Power of every Monster on the field.
So that means...
So your Attack Power now becomes 1200.
And my Attack Power is now 1600!
Battle!
Here goes!
Fighting Spirit Flame Sword!
I just beat the Demon's Summon!
So the Armored Lizard really was bait to lure my Demon Skull out...?
Yugi, the only way to beat you is to take one Monster on at a time.
You really have grown, Jounouchi-kun.
That was a splendid combination of Monster Cards and Magic Cards.
I'm glad to hear you praise me.
Jounouchi really has gotten so much stronger.
Mmm-hm...
If he's grown this much,
he may actually have a chance against Yugi-kun after all.
Yugi...
They both know what the other is thinking,
and they know each other's strategies to a Tee.
This is truly worthy of praise.
Now then!
Let's get serious, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
I intended to from the start!
Then come at me already!
It's your turn, you know!
Very well then!
My turn!
Curse of Dragon!
Attack Position!
And then...
...with the Fusion card,
I polymerize Curse of Dragon with Dark Knight Gaia!
What!?
Dragon Knight Gaia!
Dragon Knight Gaia, attack!
The Flame Swordsman is beaten!
Yugi...
What a fierce attack...
Yugi-kun has been observing how Jounouchi-kun
plays up until now - his playing pattern.
But it looks like he's finally gotten serious.
Well, Jounouchi wouldn't want it any other way.
No, it's not just that...
This is almost like two wild animals fighting instinct against instinct.
Otherwise, there wouldn't be a need for such big attacks.
They both just want to win.
They can't!
It's Yugi and Jounouchi fighting down there!
Why do those two have to fight each other in the first place?!
Probably...
...just because they're Duelists.
That is correct.
Regardless of who your opponent is, once you enter the ring,
you must fight until the opponent falls.
That is what defines the world of Duels.
This Duel is only going to get more intense.
And no one can stop those two now.
Now, what're you going to do, Jounouchi-kun?
Try and beat my Dragon Knight Gaia!
Get a hold of yourself, Katsuya Jounouchi!
I've got to get serious!
I've got to focus on destroying Dragon Knight Gaia...
What happens after that doesn't matter now.
Dragon Knight Gaia has 2600 Attack Points...
And my strongest Monster, the Red-Eyes Black Dragon, only has 2400 Attack Points...
Even if I play it, my chances of winning will only decrease...
It's these moments that makes Dueling so exciting!
Jounouchi boy is rustling up all of his offensive power,
trying to think of a plan to destroy Yugi boy's Dragon Knight Gaia...
But even with all his might, such a task is impossible.
What tricks will you use to get out of this?
A head-on attack will only get him killed...!
I've got to use a Magic Card combo
to make my Red-Eyes more powerful than the Dragon Knight Gaia Monster...
But is there even a way to do that?
Jounouchi-kun...
Sorry, but once I enter the ring,
I will not lose, by any means necessary!
I'll use any methods necessary to block any attempt you try!
Now... What will you try next?
What do I do?
The Mimic Illusionist?
That's it!
Imitation!
And in my hand...
Graverobber!
If I use the both of these,
I can beat the Dragon Knight Gaia's 2600 Attack Points!
Did he think up a strategy?
Yugi, you know...
I think I might be a genius here!
I just...
...came up with a way to destroy your Dragon Knight Gaia!
What'd you just say?!
Jounouchi-kun came up with a plan!
I Summon Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Attack Position!
And then...
The Trap Magic Card, Graverobber!
It lets me steal a card from your Graveyard!
What?!
I'll be takin' the Demon's Summon!
You can't...!
Yugi, I'm gonna use the same strategy you did!
Also, the Mimic Illusionist!
It lets me copy one of the opponent's cards!
It's too early to be surprised!
The card I'm gonna copy is...
The Fusion card!
Fusion, you said?!
That's right.
It's the first time I've ever used it.
This guy's effect is really something!
I fuse the Demon's Summon with the Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
The Skull Dragon - Black Demon's Dragon!
What!?
Beautiful!
What a wonderful trick!
Black Demon's Dragon, rip Dark Knight Gaia apart!
Meteor Flare!!
I did it!
I beat Dark Knight Gaia!
I'm sure I said this before.
That I was gonna beat you!
Yugi. I finally understand the true fun in Dueling.
That's right. This is a true Duel, Jounouchi-kun.
What's going to happen in this Duel...?
The only ones who know that are those two.
I get the feeling we'll find out soon enough...
But one thing's for sure...
What?
Those two will keep fighting until one of them falls.
There's no doubt about that.
Yugi...
Jounouchi...
This is...
...a site truly worthy of my eyes to behold.
The fight has just begun.
Come on, Yugi!
Let's go, Jounouchi-kun!
"Preview"
Why?
Why do those two have to fight such an heated Duel?!
While viewing Yugi and Jounouchi pushing themselves to the limit,
I think I've slowly begun to understand how the two feel.
Yugi! Jounouchi!
No matter which of you win, your Life hasn't truly fallen!
Next time!
"The Final Game of Friendship! Yugi VS Jounouchi (Part 2)"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship