A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Showdown!
Dungeon Dice Monsters"
Since you accepted a game you don't know the rules to...
Yugi-kun, this will be your final day as a Duelist!
D.D.M. Ring, set up!
This is...!
A virtual holographic ring similar to the Duel Monsters one used for D.D.M.!
Now then, shall we begin?
These are the dice we'll use to play.
The players both choose a total of 12 dice to use as their pool.
My Dice Pool's already been chosen.
You can go on and choose whichever dice you like.
What's wrong?
Don't know which to choose?
I choose mine!
The stage for our game is called the "Dark Field".
A land of perpetual darkness deep below the Earth.
Place all of your dice in the shooter.
D.D.M....
What kind of game is about to start?
The dice you've chosen will be automatically dispensed.
They should all be fairly shuffled.
The dice sequence is an important factor of this game.
Now, take three dice.
We've become the Dungeon Master of this field.
The Dungeon Masters each receive three Life Points.
That means you lose if you take three hits!
Game start!!
He's fighting in a game he knows nothing about!
Otogi has this entirely in his favor.
Go, go!
O-
-to-
-gi!
Thank you, my dears.
Otogi-kun~!
What a low-life bastard!
You can't talk!
I'll take the first turn.
Each player rolls three dice on their respective turns.
I got two crests.
Every single die has a variety of crests on it.
This star-shaped mark in particular is the Summon Crest!
When you gather at least two Summon Crests among the three dice,
you're permitted to Summon a Monster.
Summon a Monster?!
And due to the dice I rolled,
I get to play one of mine on the field!
White Dice, set up!
Dimension Dice!
Gargoyle!
There's a Monster inside the die...!
A pathway appeared in the Dungeon after he rolled the die!
In D.D.M., the players use their dice to build a "Dungeon",
and they then engage in a game of wits.
In other words, the players create their Dungeon by rolling the die on the field.
You then invade the other dungeon with the Monsters you Summon,
and you proceed to launch a direct assault on the player.
I see.
Every time you Summon a Monster,
you also expand your Dungeon at the same time.
The more Dungeons you create,
you gain an edge over the opponent!
This is an excellent game!
Now then, Yugi-kun. It's your turn.
Otogi!
Don't you forget!
If I win this game,
you have to set Jounouchi-kun free!
If you beat me, that is.
I'm counting on you, Yugi!
I believe you're gonna win!
Hey there, you dog! Stop talking!
Yugi can do it!
Yeah, he'll make it.
In order to protect our friendship!
It's impossible for you to win this game.
Dice roll!!
The crests are all different!
The Summon failed.
The dice you chose were high level, meaning they're difficult to Summon.
As I explained earlier, each die has a variety of crests on them.
And the crests are...
...Summon...
...Movement...
...Magic...
...Attack...
...Defense...
...and Trap, totaling in six altogether.
You can see each of them on the dice.
And the Gargoyle I Summoned has three Summon Crests.
And thus, Summoning it is much easier.
But how easy a Monster is to Summon depends strictly on its Level.
Speaking of which, why don't you look at the dice you're holding?
These dice only have one Summon Crest...!
Right.
The less Summon Crests there are, the lower your chances of Summoning it.
But in exchange, the Monster's Level is higher.
The outcome of this game is determined
by how many Monsters you're able to Summon to the field.
If you only choose high Level dice, you stand no chance of winning!
Oh no...
The Levels of these dice are too high...!
That's not fair, Otogi!
You should start the game over now that he knows all that!
It's obvious no one can win in this situation!
Start it over!
The game can't be stopped now.
Got that, Yugi-kun?
My turn.
Dice roll!!
Good, I got two Summon Crests!
I can Summon a Monster from one of the three dice!
Dimension Dice!
I Summon Yaranzo!
The Dungeons are connected!
A passage is headed towards my side of the board...!
You must set the dice so your Dungeons link up.
Plus, I got a Movement Crest.
So I'll move my Monster one space.
And in case you don't want to use the abilities of the Crests you Summon,
you can stock them in your Crest Pool.
Now it's your turn.
Dice roll!!
No good!
I didn't get a match!
If you don't hurry and Summon a Monster,
you won't be able to defend yourself against my Monsters.
My turn.
Dice roll!!
Yet another match.
Dimension Dice!!
Lizard Dragon!
move forward one space!
Dice Roll!!
Yes! The dice matched up!
I can Summon something!
Take a closer look!
If the Levels aren't the same, your Summon will fail!
What?!
My turn.
Level 4 dice, eh...?
This game's starting to get boring.
Let's spice things up a bit.
Dice Roll!
Splendid!
Seems the Goddess of D.D.M. favors me!
The Summon's a success!
What's that?
You can look forward to the rest later.
It's now your turn.
Dice Roll!
No matter what I do, I can't match them!
It seems the rumored gaming master isn't as good as they say.
But it's way too early to start regretting challenging me!
The true fun of D.D.M. starts right now!
Dice Roll!
This roll of the die will be the end of your life!
Dimension Dice!
The 13th Buried!
Summon!
Just three more spaces...
Then he can attack me...
If I don't get a Summon Crest next turn...
...it'll be difficult to stop the enemy from attacking me.
Well now, what ever is the matter?
It's your turn.
Not that it'll help you any though...
It's way too difficult to Summon a Monster with your dice.
It's true Level 4 dice only have one Summon Crest...
But I've got no choice but to try!
Dice Roll!!
Yes!
I got two Summon Crests!
What?
He got two Summon Crests with Level 4 dice?
Dimension Dice!
Little Wizard!
A Level 4 Summon!
I activate my Movement Crest!
He moves forward, using a Magic Attack on the 13th Buried!
Magic Attack!
Lightning Rod!!
He did it!
Yugi!
-Yes!
-No~!
Because one of his Summons was a Magic Crest,
he got to use a Magic attack...
Otogi! The game's just getting started!
Alright!
He was able to Summon a Monster!
Now Yugi can attack him.
Look over there.
Otogi-kun's Dice Dungeon has almost reached Yugi's field!
And he's still got more Monsters on his side!
Let's see if that Little Wizard of yours is able to hold against my Monsters.
Here I go.
Dice Roll!
Good.
I got some Summon Crests.
Dimension Dice!
I Summon the Bomb Lizard!
The Bomb Lizard itself isn't all that strong,
By using Magic Crests,
it can bombard a Monster with a Level higher than itself!
So it has a Special Ability...?
If I don't strengthen my defense,
I won't be able to stop his assaults!
My turn!
These dice have three Summon Crests.
There's a good chance I can Summon a Monster!
Dice Roll!
Alright!
I can Summon!
Dimension Dice!!
I Summon Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress!
With this guy guarding me, my defense should be pretty tight!
I wonder about that...
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
Your Summon failed!
You still don't know the true feat of this game!
In this game, you collect various dice,
and use them together in a combo attack!
What?!
You can combo attack?
Among the many Crest abilities and other strategies,
using Monster abilities to combo attack is one of the most advanced!
I first use a Movement Crest to get Bomb Lizard into position.
And by using two of my Magic Crests,
he can attack a Level 2 Monster!
Yugi-kun...
Sorry to kill that Summon right after it appeared.
Otogi-kun, you're so cool~!
Yugi...!
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
My Summon failed?
My turn!
Dice Roll!!
I Summon the Level 3 Dark Assassin!
I then activate a Movement Crest!
Begin the siege, my Monsters!
Now then, it's your turn to roll the dice.
Or perhaps you wanna give up?
Well, it'll take a miracle for you to beat the one who made this game.
What?!
Otogi, you're this game's...
I am!
I was so close to being seen by the entire world!
As both the champion and founder of Dungeon Dice Monsters!
Yugi-kun!
I know all about your winning of the Duelist Kingdom tournament,
and the fact that you beat Pegasus and became the champion!
But did you know that the moment you earned that fame,
you also ruined my dream at the same time?!
What?
Dungeon Dice Monsters...
This game was my greatest masterpiece,
forged from all of my own ideas!
I sent an email to the Pegasus on his homepage,
hoping I could let the world see my Dungeon Dice Monsters!
And I got my answer only a few days later...
I got an email from Pegasus, who read my letter.
Hello, Otogi boy!
And he said he wanted to speak with me in person about it!
And so, I flew to Pegasus' private island, the Duelist Kingdom!
With only a brief sample of my ideas,
Pegasus created a model of Dungeon Dice Monsters,
and turned it into a perfect game!
And in his first time ever playing it,
he beat me, the creator of the game!
I win!
A-Amazing...
Otogi boy, the Dungeon Dice Monsters, or D.D.M., you created is a fabulous game!
I would like to spread this game around the world.
Thank you... very much.
He promised he would contract me after the Duelist Kingdom tournament ended!
But after you beat Pegasus in the Duelist Kingdom,
I lost complete contact with him!
My plan to spread D.D.M. around the world, Yugi Mutou,
was completely ruined because of you!
Even if it seems that way, you know nothing about him.
I know all about him after having fought him!
There's no way that perfect champion would lose to someone like you!
You must have pulled some treacherous tricks on Pegasus in order to win!
You've misunderstood, Otogi!
Like I'll believe that?!
It seems you won't understand, even if I try and explain myself.
Don't forget!
The condition that you must never play Duel Monsters again!
I'll take revenge on you for Pegasus!
My turn!
Dice Roll!
Yes!
I got a pair of Summon Crests!
I'll gamble on this!
Dimension Dice!!
I Summon Iron Golem Gorogon!
You were finally able to Summon a Level 3 Monster,
but you have a slim-to-none chance of getting to use his Ability!
He's no match against my Monsters!
If he uses a Crest to activate its Ability,
it'll be a troublesome opponent though...
My turn!
Yes!
Two Movement Crests and an Attack Crest!
I move Bomb Lizard and Lizard Dragon closer!
Are you serious?!
Lizard Dragon just reached Yugi!
This isn't good...
He needs to do something...
Here I come!
Lizard Dragon, attack!
Dragon Fire!!
Otogi-kun, that was amazing~!
Awesome~!
Shit!
Yugi lost one of his Hearts!
What the heck are you doing?!
Shut up!!
And now you only have two Life left!
A guy like you who cheated against Pegasus...
...has no hope of winning Dungeon Dice Monsters!!
Cheated?
I won't let you play Duel Monsters ever again!
I hope you're prepared!
I won't let you take away the Duel Monsters fame me and my other self earned!
I won't lose!
For Jounouchi-kun...
And to clear up this misunderstanding about Pegasus!
I can't afford to lose!
"Preview"
I can't believe Otogi-kun was the one who made D.D.M.!
He's taking revenge on Yugi for ruining his dream!
Without even fully knowing the rules,
Yugi begins his counterattack!
But Otogi-kun has completely taken over the entire Dungeon,
and has Yugi completely trapped!
Don't you lose, Yugi!
For your pride as a Duelist!
Next time!
"Yugi's Desperate Battle:
God Orgoth's Violent Attack"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship