Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
With a body already ridden with injuries...
Jounouchi-kun went on to have a Duel with Mai.
Even though he was using all his might to remove the darkness in Mai's heart...
...he lost his own soul in the end.
The man manipulating Mai and the Musketeers...
And the true enemy who captured the souls of Partner and Jounouchi-kun...
Dartz!
I won't forgive you!
"The Duel of Destiny!
Yugi VS Rafael"
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun...
Jounouchi...
You jerk...!
How could such a thing...
His soul is also...
Then who could have...?
It must've been Mai.
She was searching for Jounouchi and Varon.
She did this.
I can't be wrong!
That's just...
Damn! I won't forgive Mai!
Mai...
No.
The truly unforgivable one is our true enemy who's been controlling the Musketeers!
Yugi!
Mai!
Why would Mai...?
A Harpy's feather...?
No...
So you were the one behind this, Rafael!
I've been waiting for you, Nameless Pharaoh.
This is...!
Jounouchi-kun's Claw of Hermos!
You're the one who took down Jounouchi-kun and Mai!
The one who defeated Jounouchi was Mai Kujaku.
Mai did?
Then why is Mai also...?
Because Mai foolishly decided to rebel against Lord Dartz!
I've got no business with you, Rafael!
Where is Dartz?!
I've got no more need for the power of Doma or the Barrier of Orichalcos!
I want to use my own abilities to defeat Dartz!
That way I can take responsibility for my actions against Jounouchi and Varon!
Do not be conceited, Mai Kujaku!
In the end, you were nothing more than an additional offering on the list!
What?!
You act far too much on your own agenda.
And you've run out of chances.
Be good and disappear!
I'm sorry...
Sorry...
Jou...nou...chi...
Jounouchi-kun's feelings finally reached Mai.
But despite that...
Both Jounouchi and Mai probably hoped that this card would end up in your hands.
If so, you should hold on to it.
Rafael!!
Don't you feel any pain at all?
Doesn't your heart throb? Doesn't your chest ache?
Pegasus...
Haga...
Ryuzaki...
Mai...
Jounouchi-kun...
And my partner...
Just how many souls have you taken away?!
Even Amelda and Varon...
Even the souls of your companions were taken away!
Even despite that, you don't feel anything at all?!
I've said this before.
That nothing can be achieved while humans liter this world!
That's why destiny exists.
And in order to understand your destiny,
you can only accept it and offer yourself to it.
I also want to know the answer my destiny offers.
That's why I won't hesitate to offer my soul and my very life in the process!
Why?
Why would a Duelist of your caliber need to abide by the destiny set up by Dartz?
Isn't that the purpose of having souls unique to ourselves?!
Destiny has already begun to move.
The pages of this era have already begun flipping into the next chapter!
No one can stop the wheels of time!
What is... that?
What's that?
The stars... are disappearing!
Hang on, Honda!
Honda! Anzu!
Mokuba-kun!
Kaiba!
Damn deadbeat...
So you've lost as well...?
Jounouchi...
What happened to Yugi?
He set off for Paradias Organization alone.
What's wrong, Mokuba?!
Th-Th-That...!
R-Rats!
This way!
Quick, get up!
Just what is going on?
Very soon...
The great doors of Destiny will be opened by Lord Dartz.
Only then will our answers reveal themselves before us.
For the sake of that day, Pharaoh...
I will fight against you once again!
I did defeat you that day.
Those who lose to The Barrier of Orichalcos will have their souls taken away.
But your soul was not taken.
I do not know why destiny made this arrangement.
But compared to the destiny Lord Dartz speaks of...
...it becomes insignificant.
That is right. You will not be able to defeat me.
I will prove right now that is what destiny has determined!
Rafael!
Why must we be bounded by destiny?!
I too want to Duel with you again!
But it's because you are a True Duelist!
It has nothing to do with destiny!
No, our Duel was predetermined by fate.
And for that, I must get your soul this time!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Your destiny lies here.
Let your hands decide your own destiny.
Even if you pass that barrier card to me,
I will not use it again.
I know that.
This time I want him to use his own hands...
...to destroy The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Duel!!
I'll attack first.
My turn, draw!
Look out, Nameless Pharaoh.
I will unleash my battle tactics.
Continuous Magic!
Treasure of Guardian God!
Treasure of Guardian God...
By discarding the five cards he has in his hand...
...he can draw two cards from his deck.
He can also draw two cards in his subsequent turns.
This is a card that allows one to draw more cards!
Then, I Summon Backup Gardna in Defense Position.
I set one reverse card and complete my turn.
My turn, draw!
I Summon Queen's Knight in Defense Position.
Turn end.
If he really plans to use The Barrier of Orichalcos...
...when will he play it?
My turn, draw.
Nameless Pharaoh.
My companions are pleased to be able to see you again.
I send you greetings on their behalf.
Continuous Magic! Gravity Axe!
Due to the special effect of Gravity Axe...
I can Special Summon Guardian Grarl!
By the Effect of Backup Gardna...
Gravity Axe will be equipped onto Guardian Grarl!
Go! Guardian Grarl!!
Swift Cleave Attack!!
I end my turn.
My turn, draw!
I use the Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead,
to revive Queen's Knight in Attack Position!
Then from my hand, I Summon King's Knight in Attack Position!
I then activate the Special Effect of King's Knight!
When King's Knight and Queen's Knight are both on the field...
...one Jack's Knight can be Special Summoned from the deck!
Next, a Magic Card! Brave Attack, activate!
That card...!
Next I activate
a Magic Card from my hand!
Brave Attack!
Go!
Magnet Warriors!
I can't believe it!
The Magic Card that defeated the god, Dark Obelisk!
Yes, Brave Attack can combine all the Attack Points of my Monsters...
It allows my Monsters to defeat a single enemy!
I've been waiting for a chance to do so!
Have you already forgotten...
...that you lost the previous battle because you sacrificed your Monsters?!
Rafael.
I won't be swayed by your words any longer!
I believe in the bonds I have with my Monsters!
We share both pain and joy!
Go on, Knights!
Show him your combined power!
Open reverse card!
Guardian Force!
This card can only be activated when there are no Guardian Monsters in the Graveyard.
It can destroy a Magic Card that set up the incoming battle!
I can easily destroy such low level tricks.
Turn end.
Indeed, his tactics are impregnable.
And above all, if he decides to activate The Barrier of Orichalcos...
My turn, draw!
But, I can't imagine him using that barrier.
I didn't actually believe he'd play it the last time either.
Equipment Magic, Butterfly Dagger.
The Attack of the Monster equipped with it goes up by 300 points.
Guided by the Butterfly Dagger is my Guardian Monster known as Elma!
A new Guardian Monster...
I activate the Special Effect of Guardian Elma!
An Equipment Magic Card from the Graveyard can be equipped.
Equip Guardian Shield!
Furthermore, The Special Effect of Backup Gardna...
Butterfly Dagger is equipped onto Guardian Elma!
Guardian Elma!
Attack Queen's Knight!
Despair Confusion!!
Next, Guardian Grarl.
Attack King's Knight!
Swift Cleave Attack!!
Turn over.
He's strong.
He's strong enough even without relying on the Barrier.
My turn! Draw!
I only have one Five-Star Monster on my field.
From my hand, I activate Twinkle Five Star!
A new Monster is Summoned by using the five stars of Jack!
Appear! The Five Kuriboh Siblings!
So you've sent out the shrimps again?
By discarding one Trap Card from my hand...
I activate the Special Effect of Kuribu!
Come out! Kuriball!!
The Attack Power of Grarl...
This is the Special Ability of Kuriball!
In just this turn, it can cause the Attack of the targeted Monster to drop by 1500 points.
And because of the Special Ability of Kuriba...
The Five Kuriboh Brothers combine into one to form Kuribabylon!
It's nothing scary.
Guardian Grarl's Attack Power is also 1500!
The preparations for this fight aren't finished yet.
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Cyclone!
What?
This card can destroy one Magic or Trap Card on the field!
Destroy Gravity Axe!
Go, Kuribabylon!
Attack Guardian Grarl!
Elma!
What?
Activate the special effect of Guardian Shield!
Because the shield is destroyed...
It can prevent a Monster from getting destroyed during battle.
But...
I still take damage as per the enemy's strike.
He protects his Monsters at the expense of his Life...
I set one card and end my turn.
That's right... That is how you fight.
The determination not to send any Monsters into the Graveyard.
The Monsters and their respective player's mutual bonds to protect each other.
It goes to prove that you're not the kind of Duelist who would activate The Barrier of Orichalcos.
Your ideals regarding Duels...
...is surely not in line with The Barrier of Orichalcos!
For the sake of protecting your Monsters...
...you will not give in to the darkness in your heart.
Isn't that right, Rafael?
My turn, draw.
Pharaoh, you are right about what you just said.
But...
Even if that is correct, it's not sufficient to understand the answer to destiny.
Once you accept the darkness in your heart...
...and it becomes part of you when you give up everything...
Light appears in the darkness for the first time.
And a much larger destiny is born as a result!
Rafael.
We are very alike.
But we chose very different routes.
That's why you cannot utilize your strength fully.
If so, I'll show it to you.
The real strength behind this card!
Stop it, Rafael!
Activate this instant!
Barrier of Orichalcos!!
Yugi!
That is...!
Mai-san!
What on Earth happened?
Even Mai got...
The rooftop.
Rafael!
Yugi!
Yugi...
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
What was waiting for Yugi at Paradias...
Was Rafael, who had defeated Yugi previously.
Even though he's an enemy,
Yugi respects the way Rafael treats his Monsters during his Duels.
Yet, Yugi is bewildered when he activated The Barrier of Orichalcos.
In the end, he Summons Guardian Eatos which resulted in Yugi's defeat last time.
And then...!
Next time!
"Immortal! Guardian Deathscythe"
Duel standby!