Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
There are clues about my past here.
Who am I? Where am I from?
The answers are here.
"This Town Will Become a Battle City!"
Yugi?
There's a room in the basement, too...
That's...
The Ancient Egyptian king carved here...
There's no doubt in my mind that this is person is me!
Why? Why is there a carving of Yugi on that stone tablet?
The Millennium Puzzle?!
Anzu, I have just realized who I really am.
The soul of an Ancient Egyptian king who was trapped inside the Millennium Puzzle for thousands of years.
That is who I really am.
Can it be? Does Yugi's other soul really live inside of the Millennium Puzzle...?
After all this time, it's no wonder I've forgotten everything.
We have been waiting for you.
Who are you?
I am Ishizu Ishtar.
For 3000 years...
I have protected a piece of the Pharaoh's memories.
That's... a Millennium Item!
This Millennium Tauk grants the power
to see into the near future.
I knew you would be coming here.
And I knew a great battle would soon be waged in this town.
Yes, you came here yourself.
You chose your destiny of battle.
Destiny of battle?
To regain your memory...
you must gather all seven of the Millennium Items.
Tell me one thing first!
Are you my enemy?!
Or are you an ally?
My Millennium Item is not your enemy.
But, I can see...
The enemy who will soon appear before you...
is the one who possesses the last Millennium Item.
The last Millennium Item...?
And that battle...
will be a battle to regain your memory.
You'll understand when you leave today.
For it is there that you will choose your own destiny.
What do you mean?
The rest is something you must find out for yourself.
Yugi...  Destiny of battle?
Why was my soul
inside the Millennium Puzzle?
Why were my memories...
...sealed in the seven Millennium Items?
And, the other man carved in the stone...
...looks like him.
Could it be? The resemblance is too great.
The carving on this stone slab...
predicted our present-day battle!
Is the only way I can find the answers to find my lost memories?
"Collectible Card Games Division"
Main computer system activated!
System check positive - all checks green.
Big brother, I'm ready here.
It's okay to start anytime.
At last, the final test for the Next Generation Duel Disk.
Equipping the Duel Disk!
This new Duel Disk doesn't need to be thrown every turn.
When the card is set,
the card data is scanned immediately.
Our satellite system has sped up the process in which it connects with Kaiba Corporation's main computer.
Holograms of all Monsters can be materialized at any time and place.
Yugi, you are the only Duelist I recognize as a rival.
When this new Duel Disk is complete, our renewed battle will take place!
The Duelists depicted on that ancient mural...
I could care less if it is you, Yugi!
This is my era.  I'll only fight you, the enemy of my future!
Wait and see, Yugi!
Duel Robot, standby!
Duel Robot, standby OK.
Setting tactics level to max!
It's finally the last test of the new Duel Disk.
But even if it's Seto-sama, can he really beat the Duel Robot?
Idiot!  My big brother can't lose to a computer!!
But Mokuba-sama...
The Duel Robot has been equipped
with Seto-sama's cards that comprise his strongest deck.
So the three Blue Eyes White Dragons...
are in the Duel Robot's deck?
Yes, all according to Seto-sama's orders.
My brother wants to fight against
an enemy with the most powerful hand?
I am entrusting you with the Great War God Obelisk.
My deck has the first of the God Cards that Ishizu gave me.
The Great War God Obelisk.
This demonstration is more
than the final test of the new Duel Disk.
It's also a test to see what power The Great War God Obelisk holds.
I want to see if this card...
...is stronger than the ultimate deck consisting of three Blue-Eyes White Dragons.
Let's begin!
Main computer: auto-duel system, on!
On!
Duel Robot, activate!
Activate!
Brother...!
Solid Vision projectors...
Launch!
Duel! Bring it!
It is my turn.
Draw phase complete.
And next, Main Phase.
Card in Defense Position.
My turn!
I set one card.
I summon Minotaurus in attack mode.
Go, Minotaurus!
What, Cyber Pot?!
Cyber Pot, effect activate.
Destroy all monsters on the field.
Both players draw from their decks...
and all Level Four or lower monsters are set on the field.
Because of Cyber Pot's effect,
they have a lot more monsters.
It is my turn.
I sacrifice to low-level monsters
to summon Blue Eyes White Dragon.
Blue Eyes, you've finally come!
I see. According to the new rules...
To summon a powerful monster requires sacrifices.
Was that the purpose of the Cyber Pot?
I end my turn.
It's not attacking because of my set cards.
That's tactics level MAX all right.
It's truly is amazing.
Now it's my turn!
I sacrifice Cyclops to summon Dragon Killer!
Defense mode!
When Dragon Killer changes to attack mode,
it destroys an enemy's dragon.
Next turn it'll target the Blue Eyes.
So, what will you do?
It is my turn.
I set one card.
Lord of Dragons, Attack Position.
What?
Whenever this card is on the field,
Any magic, traps, or effects do not effect dragons.
Did it see through Dragon Killer's attack?
I'll just have to hold out playing defense.
It already has my brother on the defensive.
It is my turn.
Flute of Summoning Dragon.
Combo activate.  Combo activate.
When Lord of Dragons is on the field...
Up to two dragons may be summoned from my hand.
What's that?!
Big brother!
Three Blue Eyes White Dragons!!
Next, activate face-down card...
Polymerize the three Blue Eyes into Ultimate Dragon.
What?!!
The new rules say that a new fusion monster cannot attack.
I end my turn.
Beautiful...
Brother!
It's hopeless. Ultimate Dragon is unbeatable.
There's no way to defeat it!
If its attack succeeds, there'll be direct damage!
What?
Seto-sama programmed the Duel Disk
to simulate combat damage.
Big brother! It's too dangerous!
Stop the Duel!
Big brother!
Yugi!
Yugi, is this the fear you feel whenever you fight me?
But no matter how many times you felt it,
you ignored that fear and stood up to face me.
Yes, by believing in your cards.
The duelist's greatest enemy.
That is..
Something called fear that lives in their hearts.
That is the evil we must face!
My turn!
I'll bet everything on this card!
Come forth! The Great War God Obelisk!
I sacrifice my three monsters...
That's...
The God Card that he told me about.
This is my ultimate weapon.
The Great War God Obelisk!
Now, use your ability and increase your strength!
Absorb the soul power of these two monsters.
Not good...!
The attack counter increasing too fast!
Forgive me.
Ultimate.
I'll lay you to rest with the hand of God.
Obelisk, attack!
Obelisk!
God Hand Crusher!!
System malfunction.
Warning!
Ah! The Duel Robot...!
The main computer is going haywire!
The Great War God Obelisk...
It drained the player's life in mere seconds.
Incredible!
There are two God Cards left.
With them I can defeat...
...anyone, no matter how strong.
Then I will be the complete and true King of Duelists!!
Anzu...
What?
My partner doesn't know I came here to see
the stone slab today.
I don't want you to tell him about the stone,
or about what Ishizu said.
I want to get my memory back,
and my partner knows what that means.
I don't want him to worry about me, yet.
We created this deck together.
Half of it is the work of his soul.
The day he understands who I am...
will be the day this deck will display its true power.
I know that day will come.
Strange...
I'm picking up this hostile aura.
What is it?
What's with the scary look?
No, it's nothing.
Hey, Yugi!
Mai Kujaku!
Mai-san...!
Long time, no see!  How you doing?
Mai-san, you're doing as well as ever I see.
Nah, you know me...
Hey hey, Anzu. A date with Yugi?
Of course not!
A date. A date!
Mai-san, let go. Let go!
Anyway Mai, what are you doing here?
Huh? Why am I...?
You're here and you don't even know?
Someone told me I could find my future here.
The future, huh? Could be true.
A few days ago, some news got out on the internet.
"Go to where ancient Duelists and card engravings rest."
Some kind of message.
"Ancient Duelists and card engravings?"
The date is today, the time is right now.
They're supposed to announce a huge duel tournament here.
A duel tournament?
Yugi, you must have sensed it by now.
I can feel the hostility of duelists in the air.
Yes, the people here are duelists from all over the country.
Look closely.  You might see some familiar faces.
That's Insector Haga!  ...and Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Yes, and that's the duelist with "special abilities," Esper Roba.
Ryota Kajiki-kun, too?!
I see,
So that's why all these duelists are in town.
Yugi, that's...?
Kaiba!
Rumor has it that he's the one who spread
the information to come here.
Kaiba is hosting the tournament...?
Fellow duelists, listen carefully...
In one week, in this very same town...
Kaiba Corporation will host a Duel Monsters tournament!!
Duelists must meet two prerequisites.
He must have a deck of 40 cards, including one rare card.
Also...
He must have in possession this new Duel Disk.
- What's that?
- Kaiba Corporation's new device?
Duels will be played by Battle City rules.
And there is an ante rule.
The loser must give the rarest card in his deck...
to the winner.
A rare card ante?
That Kaiba sure has set a tough rule.
In other words,
The final champion will acquire the rarest cards of everyone.
All right!
Where's the arena?
Kaiba!
I knew you'd show up, Yugi.
The two of us will settle things once and for all in this battle!
The stage of the battle will be all of Domino City!
In one week, this town will become a Battle City!!
Battle City?!
Battle City, eh?
Yes, Master Malik.
Duelists from all over the country
have gathered in Domino City.
When all of your prey have gathered in one place...
...it's very convenient.
How interesting.
Assemble the Rare Hunters of
the Ghouls from around the world.
Our next target is Domino City!
Jounouchi wants badly to join Battle City,
but only those who receive
Kaiba-kun's Duel Disk get to participate.
Jounouchi's name is here too?
All right!
Jounouchi rushes to the Shizuka
in the hospital after getting his Duel Disk.
He's is ambushed by Ghouls?
Not good! If he doesn't hurry, the operation's gonna start.
Next time!
"The Ghouls' Attack:"
"Take Aim at Red Eyes Black Dragon"
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...