With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Showdown!
Call of the Living Dead"
Jounouchi! Can you stand up from your cowardly fear of Dueling?
What’d you say?
You're... a loser dog!
Loser dog?
Loser dog!
A dream?
Damn it all! I ain’t some loser dog!
It’s morning! Everyone, UP!
"Duelist Kingdom Tournament
2nd Day"
You’re pretty worked up aren’t you, Jounouchi-kun?
Of course! It’s now day 2!
Let’s gather up some Star Chips, and head for Pegasus’ castle!
Well, you don’t have to be so friggin’ loud!
So you’re all up, huh?
Morning, Anzu!
Huh? Where’s Mai Kujaku?
I got this from Mai-san, addressed to us.
“I’ll be paying back that Star Chip debt.”
Debt, huh?
Is that so?
So she’d rather be alone…
Everyone ready?
Yeah!
Alright then! Let’s get started!
"Jounouchi:
4 Star Chips"
"Yugi:
6 Star Chips"
I wonder how many Duelists are left on the island?
Well, 12 were kicked off on the first day.
And there's probably a bunch that fell victim to the Player Killers last night.
Then that would mean out of the original 42, only about half are left, right?
There’s still time, Jounouchi…
Don’t blow all of your Star Chips.
Although we can’t be easy going about it either.
There’s only a little bit of time left,
and I think the remaining Duelists are getting stronger with each win.
Even stronger?
Hey Yugi, don’t talk like that, or Jounouchi’s gonna get scared.
Who’s scared?
What was that for, asshole?
No fighting, now!
No matter how strong they are, I’ll crush them!
Yup, Just like that, Jounouchi-kun!
How bout them?
Let’s kill ‘em.
But they’re only two in that group that have Duel Gloves.
So the rest are the peanut gallery, huh?
Isn’t that…
Isn’t that midget the brat they call Yugi?
Yugi?
For now, let’s just tell this to bro.
Guess you’re right.
Found some prey?
Yes, two of them.
But there’s one little problem.
We might as well give it up…
We can’t win against them.
One of them is a brat called Yugi.
He beat Kaiba, and odds are that they’re heading for the castle.
Yugi?  Who’s that?
Besides, We’re all definitely going to the castle.
T-that’s right!
That’s why we banded together to help each other out.
Yeah! If we’re following our bro, we’ll definitely get to the castle!
That’s right.
You may look like half-assed losers to other people,
But you’re under the great Bandit Keith’s advice!
We ain’t scared of anything!
We’ll definitely get the prize money!
We’ve got Bandit Keith with us, after all!
Yeah!
W-What?
Don't screw with me, Pegasus!
I’m not doing anything of the sort.
This young boy will Duel with you in my place.
I'll use this card, ya damn brat!
Let me see... when you play that card, I...
W-What?
Tom wins!
Just you wait, Pegasus.
I'll pay you back for the utter humiliation I got from you.
What was the other guy like?
Well, he looked kinda weak.
Alright then.
Then he’s our target!
Have you seen any other Duelists around?
Maybe they haven’t entered the depths of the forest yet?
Damn, because there’re fewer people, finding the remaining Duelists is gonna be hard.
Pee time!
Wait here for a sec, would ya!
What?
Mother Nature’s calling!
Bro, just where are we going?
A hidden stage.
A hidden stage?
I found the special stage Pegasus made by chance in this cave.
Kotsuzuka, You run a Ghost Deck, right?
Y-Yeah.
Lemme see it.
The attack force in this deck sucks.
R-Really?
But don’t worry…
We’ll make the best Ghost Deck possible with these cards!
Up ahead is the Graveyard Field.
Graveyard Field?
You’ll wait for the prey there.
You’ll definitely win with this Ghost Deck.
I gotcha. Leave it to me, Ghost Kotsuzuka!
I’m counting on you to get us to Pegasus’ castle!
You’re such a wuss.
This is fake!
Pegasus has one hell of a sense of humor!
Wait for me!
I feel so much better!
What’s with you?
Y-You…
Wake up, dammit!
Y-You’re…
So you finally woke up, huh?
Where are we?
This is your grave!
Duel Standby!
What the hell is this?
A-A cross?
Welcome to the Graveyard Field.
I hope you’re ready.
I'm gonna bury you alive!
A-A GHOST~!!!
Jounouchi-kun’s taking too long.
Yeah…
Did he get lost?
Was he challenged to a Duel?
It’s possible.
Jounouchi's probably worried, since he's low on Star Chips,
and was probably scared after what we said.
At any rate, let’s split up and look for him.
Ok then, Bakura and I will go this way. Yugi and Anzu, go that way.
Now then, It’s time to Duel!
This is your graveyard.
He’s scared.
What’s with him? He passed out while standing up!
What a weakling.
Wake him.
Get up!
When you laid eyes on the Graveyard Field, you lost all of your will and passed out.
Graveyard Field?
This place is given power from the Demons.
You can’t escape.
Just so you know, I didn’t pass out because of the Graveyard Field.
It’s because your face creeped me the hell out!
That’s right, Kotsuzuka!
In this cave, you really do look like a ghost!
Shut it! I can't help that I was born this way!
Listen up! We’re betting 4 Star Chips on this fight, alright?
I got dragged into a random Duel…
What’s the matter? You gonna fight or not?
In this place I don’t know the first thing about…
So you got cold feet?
You got the face of a loser dog wimpin' out before the fight even starts!
"Cluck, cluck, cluck!"
Loser dog?
You’re a loser dog that’s too scared to Duel!
I’m in!
If I run from here, I really will be a losing dog.
I’ll take you on!
Duel!
Kotsuzuka, hurry up and bring out your Ghost cards to crush him!
Ghost cards?
So that’s how it is?
So you just noticed?
This Ring is 100% Graveyard.
Here, Ghost Cards are at their strongest!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
It doesn’t look like he went this way.
Let’s look that way.
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Nothing.
This is too weird.
If he was in a Duel Ring, we would have seen it.
Where did he go?
Here I come!
-I’ll Summon this Ghost card—
-Just a sec.
That card's no good.
Take the card from the far left!
The far left…
Armored Warrior Zanki?
This isn’t a Ghost card!
I slipped that card into your deck.
Why? This card won’t get the Field Power Bonus!
Just do as I tell you.
I’m not wrong about this.
But…
Kotsuzuka, just do as he says!
We’ve gotten as far as we have because of his advice!
Hey, you jerks!
Would the peanut gallery please SHUT UP?!
-Ok, I’ll do as you say...
-Hey, are you even listening to me, dammit?!
Armored Warrior Zanki in Attack Position!
Then, I’ll play this!
Axe Raider, attack!
Gale Cut!!
Alright!
Armored Warrior Zanki is defeated!
It was killed…
That’s good.
That was a worthless Warrior card...
If that was one of my Ghost cards, it would have won for sure.
YES!
He can take a nice nap in the graveyard!
Alright freak, hurry up and play your next card!
The next is gonna be a Ghost card—
Not that one, Kotsuzuka.
The second card from the left!
This is... Earth-Crawling Dragon?
This isn’t a Ghost card either!
It’ll be killed the second it enters the field!
Relax. I’m thinking of how to get you to win this.
You’ve gotta trust me, cuz I’m a legend where I come from.
O-Okay.
Defense…
So you’re running, Huh?
All talk, no action.
Okay, Axe Raider!
Crush it!
YES!
Next up is the farthest card on the right!
Ehhh?
This time, don’t put it in Defense Mode.
If he can’t see it, he might not attack.
You gotta believe in me.
Otherwise, I’ll stop giving out my wonderful advice.
So, what’ll you do?
Murder Circus in Attack Mode!
I choose this card!
Flame Swordsman!
Battle!
Fighting Spirit Flame Slash Sword!!
Yes! Murder Circus is destroyed!
I can do this!
I can win!
Now that I think about it, Yugi always saved me from the brink of defeat.
I can’t believe I didn’t catch on to my own weakness.
But now, I’ll win on my own!
Just watch, Kaiba!
I’ll show you I’m not a loser dog!
Bro...
Relax.
Your victory is assured.
You guys really like talking secretly, huh?
If that’s the case, how about you come and play me?
Is that so? Well then, let’s show him what you’re made of, Kotsuzuka.
Oh, now I get it! You were intending on turning the tide with this!
You really are amazing!
Now show him your trump card!
Prepare yourself!
This is my sure-kill Magic Card!
Call of the Living Dead!
Call of the Living Dead?
All of the cards in his Graveyard return as Zombies!
Zombies are Ghost cards,
and use the power of the grave.
What? What are those things?
That’s Jounouchi’s!
So this is Jounouchi’s sister?
Even if he is an airheaded dumbass, he wouldn’t forget that!
Something must've happened to him!
Look!
A cave!
What the hell is this?
Be careful, this isn’t a normal cave!
Those are coffins, right?
But these aren’t real.
Stop playing around, you two.
They’re disturbing.
Don’t worry. They’re fakes.
Damn this thing!
Stop!
Pegasus and his crazy ass jokes!
Jounouchi-kun…
What are those?
Thanks to Call of the Living Dead, all of my Monsters return as Zombies!
Zombies?
And on top of that they’re Ghosts now, so they get the Graveyard Field Power Bonus!
Dragon Zombie, attack Axe Raider!
Fight back, Axe Raider!
No way!
It revived right after a clean hit right into it!
They can revive as many times as they want with Zombie Power!
What'd you say?!
Go, Dragon Zombie!
Zombie's Deadly Breath!!
This looks… bad.
"Preview"
Jounouchi is cornered by Ghost Kotsuzuka’s Zombie cards.
No matter how many times he defeats them, they come right back to life!
And they even power up!
And even the Time Magician, the card that’s gotten him out of countless problems, fails him!
Don’t Give Up, Jounouchi!
You’re not a loser dog!
Next Time: "Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship