Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
We're undertaking this four-way Battle Royale in order to determine the match-ups in the Semi-Finals.
Yugi, I know you want to face that worthless deadbeat,
but I will not allow such scrutiny!
Your awaiting fate is to fight me in the Semi-Finals!
In order to ensure this, I have to get rid of the annoying deadbeat and Malik!
So you better get ready to Duel me!
"Their Respected Opponents"
My turn!
I Summon Dark Jeroid!
This guy also has a Special Power...
The moment it is Summoned, one Monster on the field has their Attack Power decreased by 800 points.
Now... Which Monster should I choose?
Come attack me, Malik.
And fall victim to my Trap...!
The moment you do, Destruction Ring will leave your Life Points practically dead!
A Trap, is it? It's written all over his face!
Well let's see... His Majesty's Gilfer Demon has 2200 Attack Points.
Even with Dark Jeroid's Special Ability, he'll only drop from 2200 Attack to 1400.
Still 200 Attack Points higher than Dark Jeroid.
Then I think it's rather obvious!
I'll go after Jounouchi's Gearfried!
Figures!
Dark Jeroid's Special Ability activates!
Gearfried's Attack Power drops by 800 points!
Die!!
Fooled ya.
Not so fast!
Reverse card, activate!
Devil Dice!
This is gonna lower your Monster's Attack Points!
Tch! This man depends on luck too much!
Shut yer trap!
Here goes!
It rolled a two!
Your Dark Jeroid loses half it's Attack!
Nice move!
Too bad for you, Malik!
Your Monster's the dead one here!
Iron Sword of Gearfried!
What?!
Th-This can't be...!
His body's shrinking!
What in the world...?
I just activated my reverse card, Shrink!
This Magic Card cuts the Attack Power of the selected Monster in half!
Jounouchi, your Gearfried's Attack shrank to a low 800!
H-He's so small...
Dark Jeroid destroys Gearfried!!
Dammit, Kaiba!
Why'd you go and butt in...?!
Jounouchi-kun!
I knew that damn Kaiba had something up his sleeve...
I didn't realize he was this low a bastard!
But it's just part of the game's strategy.
Even so...!
And Kaiba-kun still has two set cards on the field. They can't let their guard down.
That's my big brother!
He activated his reverse card right in the pits of despair!
Listen well!
All enemies that oppose me serve only one purpose!
To make me win.
Wh-what was dat?!
Don't get worked up, Jounouchi-kun.
We'll win this!
Here I go! My turn!
Mai-san?
Mai-san!
Who is that...?
I don't know you...
My brother's going to save you, Mai-san!
I believe in him!
In the meantime, I'm by your side, Mai-san.
That way my brother can focus on Dueling.
Keep it up, big brother!
My turn!
Draw!
What are the other players' positions this turn...
Kaiba has two reverse cards out on the field.
And Blade Knight in Attack Mode.
Malik has no reverse cards, but he does have his Dark Jeroid in Attack Mode.
And Jounouchi-kun has just one reverse card...
He's clearly at a disadvantage.
Wh-What is it? What the hell are ya all starin' at?!
Humph! Who gives a damn
if my field is empty?!
My Gilfer Demon is the strongest Monster on the field...
But what's bothering me are those reverse cards Kaiba set.
They must be Traps.
I can't carelessly attack.
Who should I aim for...?
Well, in that case...
He's my only target!
Yugi must be thinking of his promise to fight Jounouchi in order to become a True Duelist.
So he's gonna hit Malik or Kaiba!
But look at Jounouchi-kun.
Jounouchi-kun's got his eyes focused in only one pace.
He's been staring at Malik the entire time.
Yeah, Jounouchi's been aiming for Malik.
He wants to save Mai-san with his own strength.
Damn it!
I will save Mai...!
I'll save her with my own hands!
Jounouchi...
As a Duelist just like her...
...just like she fought alongside us up until now... I really want to save her.
She saved my butt a ton of times, when I think about it.
That's for sure.
Oi! What's that mean?
Anzu, don't tell Yugi this.
But why?
The two of us promised to fight each other fair and square the day we become True Duelists.
True Duelists?
To be honest, I'm not sure if I'll be able to call myself that, even after all of this.
But there's one thing I do know for sure.
If I can't save Mai with my strength alone, I'm not qualified to become one.
Big brother...
So in order to keep
my promised with Yugi, I...
I'll beat the hell out of Malik with my own hands.
And I'll rescue Mai from her suffering!
Is that so...? He said all that...?
That's something Jounouchi-kun would say, alright... Just like him...
He thinks it's his fault that he couldn't protect Mai-san.
He...
I attack with Gilfer Demon!
The Monster I target is...
Yugi!
Hold it a second!
Before you do that, Yugi...
I wanted to ask you what a True Duelist is...
Jounouchi-kun...?
I attack with Gilfer Demon!
The Monster I target is...
Yugi!
Hold it a second!
Yugi... I wanted to ask you what a True Duelist is...
Jounouchi-kun...?
Is now a good time
for him to be asking that?
Well I do know one thing...
A True Duelist wouldn't go and interrupt someone else's turn.
So true.
I've been looking for the answer through all of Battle City, and made it this far.
Yugi, it's because I wanted to fight you fair and square!
With each guy I fought in the city, I got a little closer to the answer.
More like the answer a deadbeat found on the path to mediocrity.
Yugi... Because of you, I don't back down from any opponents.
You taught me to never give up, no matter how strong the opponent is, and to trust in my cards all the way.
Honda!
Wh-What do you want?!
You guys taught me about the strength of trust, too!
Wh-What's gotten into you all of a sudden...?
You're freaking me out...
And all the Duelists I fought...
STOP!
I won this duel.
It's been a while, Jounouchi-kun.
So you finally showed yourself, Insector Haga!
I was looking forward to meeting with you.
Attack, my Queen!
Queen's Hell Breath!!
Haga, this match is over already.
What?!
Trap Card, activate! Graverobber!
Graverobber, you said?!
Yup. And the card I'm taking from your Graveyard is...
Ya see, I really can't stand bugs!
All right! Insect Queen is done for!
Fortress Whale is fried to a crisp!
I play the Magic Card Revival of the Dead!
I revive a Monster this turn!
What's wrong?! Now hurry and come!
After all that boasting you did before, show me how you fight!
I can't afford to lose here!
I have my sea to fight against!
I can't give up until the very end!
Magic Card activate!
Hurricane!
What?!
After all, I can't let this card stay in the Graveyard.
Don't just stare! Now come and get me, Jounouchi!
They all showed me my own weaknesses I didn't know I had.
They've helped me to grow as a Duelist.
Mai! Your opponent's not decided yet!
No matter who my opponent is, I'll win!
Yugi! Jounouchi!
The next time we meet, it'll be in the Semi-Finals!
Jounouchi, I'm not a soft Duelist like you who needs another's power to win!
You were damn right about that, Mai...
You taught me
something important, too...
Only one person can win Battle City and gain victorious glory!
This is a Battle Royale!
We're all your enemies!
I'm bored to tears over here!
Just get on with the
goddamn Duel already!!
Yugi! If you're a True Duelist, take down your enemy! Take down me!
Stop playing favorites just so you can keep your promise with me in the Semi-Finals!
Jounouchi-kun...!
I'm the weakest one here in the current situation!
Just look around you and you'll see that I'm the one with no reverse cards!
Jounouchi...
Jounouchi-kun may have more Life Points at the moment...
One attack from Gilfer Demon would send him close to the top!
It's a basic strategy of this game to take down the weakest guys first, Yugi!
Don't waste your next turn!
Just attack me!
Jounouchi-kun...
Even if I lose this match, I'll still get to the Final and fight you!
If you believe in me, attack me... Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun, this is your card.
Yugi...
Right now I can't take Red-Eyes back.
Jounouchi-kun, I'll wait for you.
I'll take care of your Red-Eyes until then!
Mhm-hm!
I understand, Jounouchi-kun!
Let's face each other in the Final!
Attack, Gilfer Demon!
Aim for Jounouchi-kun!
Direct Attack!
Gilfer Flame!!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Brace yourself, Malik...
I'm taking you down with me!
Mai... I'll save you,
no matter what it takes...!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi's almost out of Life...!
It's my turn!
Draw!
Mai...
Why did you do this for me...?
You don't have the time to stand around staring!
You better win!
Jounouchi...
Wh-What...?
Those tears for your little sister...
I hope it shines with a bright light...
Mai! I'll get your light back!
I Summon Axe Raider!
Is he going to attack Malik...?
Or...
The guy I'm attacking...
Kaiba!!
You!!
He's going after Kaiba?
Wasn't he after Malik?
What's the deal?
Doesn't he want to save Mai-san?
Why would he change his attack target so far into the game?
Or did he just bluff his wanting to attack Malik so he could go after Kaiba?
I knew it!
You really are a nobody, Jounouchi!
He's gonna beat himself while trying to beat my big brother!
Here goes!
Axe Raider! Attack Blade Knight!
Bring it, deadbeat!
Kaiba's got a trap!
I know!
Take this!!
Hurricane Cutter!!
Trap Card, activate!!
Destruction Ring!!
Destruction Ring?!
The Monster the Destruction Ring attaches to is destroyed,
and the Monster's Attack Points are taken out of the controller's Life Points!
But I have no desire to blow up alongside this common deadbeat!
I activate my face-down Instant Quick-Play Magic Card, Defense Ring!
It negates all damage
inflicted by a Trap Card!
Jounouchi! This time it's really game over!
Jounouchi-kun!
This means Jounouchi's Life Points are at zero...!
Called it! Jounouchi's the one who lost!
Nope!
Not exactly!
My Life hit zero...?!
What in the world...?!
I activated Graverobber!
Graverobber is a card that steals one card from the opponent's Graveyard.
Now if ya don't mind, Malik-chan,
I'll be taking that Spell of Pain you tossed in the Graveyard off your hands for a while!
Using this card, I can transfer all damage I receive to another player!
Damn good work, Jounouchi!
It's just like you to turn your enemy's strength against himself!
You can get things done when you put your mind to it, Jounouchi!
I guess!
Good thinking, Jounouchi-kun...
If he had attacked Dark Jeroid with Axe Raider,
Malik would have only taken 500 points of damage to his Life Points.
But by attacking Kaiba and making use of his Trap,
and then using Graverobber at just the right moment,
he was able to activate Spell of Pain and take Malik down in one blow.
That was an excellent strategy, Jounouchi-kun!
Later~!
You are going to deeply regret this...
Now Malik's in the first round of the Semi-Finals.
And me, too...
Now Jounouchi's got no Monsters, reverse cards, or anything for that matter out on the field.
What do you think's gonna happen next turn when my brother goes to attack?
Punk...!
Yup. My field's wide open.
It's just as I planned though.
Turn over.
It's just as you planned, you said?
Don't make me laugh!
My turn! Draw!
There's no way a loser like you who relies on nothing but luck had any sort of plan!
Blade Knight! Direct Attack Jounouchi!!
Be gone, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Let's meet in the Final, Yugi!
I'm fine with this.
This Battle Royale was nothing more than a game to decide our opponents in the Semi-Finals.
Yo! Sorry to keep ya waitin'!
You're about to sleep in darkness as well!
Well, I'm kickin' your ass, Malik!
The Duel is over!
The Duels for the Semi-Finals has just been decided!
Very good.
Kaiba...
First match of the Semi-Finals!
Malik Ishtar versus Katsuya Jounouchi!
Second match!
Yugi Mutou versus Seto Kaiba!
This Duel was fated, Yugi!
I sure hope you're ready!
Jounouchi-kun... Wait for me in the battlefield of the Final round!
I'm going to be there after I settle things with Kaiba!
Duel Gate, open!
We're finally headed to the battlefield of the final matches!
You may as well refer to it as a gateway to a world of darkness!
Stop fooling yourself! Even with that Ra card of yours, I'm gonna beat you to a pulp!
Let us head to the final stage!
Launch the gondolas!!
Malik's fighting Jounouchi in the first round of the Battle City Semi-Finals.
I really want him to win so Mai-san will wake up, but...
He's facing one of the God Cards, The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Kaiba-kun knows of Ra's terrifying abilities...
Is there any way for Jounouchi to fight against them?
Malik just activated a Dark Game!
Next time!
"The Semi-Final Match of Darkness: Jounouchi VS Malik"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise