Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Yugi!
It's alright! Yugi's fine!
The other Yugi...
I thought he'd always existed within Yugi...
Like a split personality the Millennium Puzzle merely brought out...
But is that just what I wanted to believe?
But...
Other Yugi...
Did you come from inside the Millennium Puzzle?
"The Lost Memory of the Pharaoh"
We thank you sincerely for choosing Japan to host your exhibit. Welcome to you all.
We appreciate your welcome.
No...
I've always wanted to meet the Egyptian archaeological expert.
Thank you for taking great care with this Ancient Egyptian exhibit.
"No matter what, we should never sing about the eras where successive generations are filled with hostility."
Hmm?
Please excuse me. It's a very old joke often told in Egypt.
I sincerely hope this Ancient Egyptian exhibit will be a success.
Yugi!
Hold up, Yugi!
Yugi...!
We shall now introduce Ishizu Ishtar-san, who has come all the way from Egypt
in order to display an Ancient Egyptian exhibit at Domino Museum.
Hello, citizens of Japan.
Ishtar-san plans to display some of the greatest pieces of Egyptian history.
I have come to put the Ancient Egyptian exhibit on public display in Japan's Domino City.
So what exactly do you plan to display in the exhibit?!
Good question.
This is a very special exhibit that will display a mural of the eighteen Egyptian dynasties and the many kings that ruled them.
This will be the first time these items have been toured abroad.
Big brother, it's amazing! It's the first time this has been shown around the world!
How boring. I have no interest what happened in the past.
Really?
It looks kind of interesting.
This exhibit...
What is it?
You have an Ishizu Ishtar from the Egyptian government who would like with speak to you.
Ishizu Ishtar?
We sincerely hope that everyone enjoys the exhibit until the last day of its display.
I ask that all of you come visit the exhibition as soon as possible.
"Domino Egypt Exhibit"
Wait right here. I'll go alone.
Yes, sir.
Welcome. It's an honor
to meet you, Mr. Kaiba.
I am aware of Kaiba Corporation's remarkable strides in the high-tech gaming industry.
Head, everything is going as instructed.
No one shall enter this building.
You sure have a funny way of greeting the president of an official company.
If I am being doubted from the get-go, I may as well take my leave right now.
Pardon me, but I hope you will understand my reasoning for doing this.
This is merely a military strategy to protect the artifices from certain individuals disputing over them within the Egyptian government.
Strategy?
I suppose you could say you caught my attention.
Then please come this way.
We, the Bureau of Egyptian Archeology, were formed back in 1857.
You could say we exist as an organization formed to protect ancient artifices from grave robbers.
Currently, we are observing excavations such as this around the entire world.
If you are searching for someone to dig up mummies for you, I hate to disappoint...
But my only interest lies in building high performance silicon chips for electronic game design technology.
I'm not the least bit interested in a bunch of rocks from thousands of years ago.
You told me on the phone earlier...
Wouldn't you be interested in getting some rare cards, Mr. Kaiba?
My only interest in being here is the rare cards you told me about.
You aren't about to tell me that was some sort of trick to lure me here...?
Then let us cut to the chase.
I understand you do hold an interest in Duel Monsters.
What if I were to tell you that the cards you cherish so much holds their origin in Ancient Egypt.
What?
Pegasus J. Crawford...
The game designer that created the present form of Duel Monsters.
Pegasus...!
Yes.
What if I told you that he created Duel Monsters after a trip to Egypt?
Although, this fact is not very well known.
Please come with me. I think it is about time for a change of scenery.
Thanks.
You risked your life in that fire to put the Millennium Puzzle back together.
But it was Jounouchi-kun and Honda-kun that saved us.
I guess you're right.
We have good friends.
Yeah...
What's on your mind...?
Yugi!
Where are you going, Yugi?
Don't go, Yugi!
YUGI!
I am about to show you two palettes in the room up ahead.
The palettes originated from the Mortuary Temple of the king that ruled during the eighteenth dynasty of Egypt.
This holds the origin of Duel Monsters.
Wh-What in the...?!
They look exactly like Duel Monsters!
That is correct.
Pegasus created Duel Monsters after seeing this palette.
I will now explain the details of the past existing of both humans and the "Monsters" we've come to know them as...
The Ancient Egyptians, like many cultures,
thought misfortunes were caused by evil spirits, fear and the suffering that existed within people's hearts.
As a result, the Pharaoh and his magicians used spells to trap the spirits.
Using stone tablets as a source, the spirits were sealed within them.
However, over time the evil power began to grow within the sealed tablets.
Soon after, a group of priests began to rebel against the king and his magicians.
They used the evil spirits sealed within the stone tablets,
and a war broke out as a result.
Please look at this other palette.
This is what I wanted
to show you here tonight.
Please look at this
palette long and carefully.
Just as Mr. Pegasus did long ago.
I'm certain that, just as he did,
you will find some form of inspiration from this image.
That's...!
Yugi!
And the image carved above him is the Black Magician!
And the one standing beside the king...
He is known as the "White Beast Handler".
And the creature carved above him is without a doubt...
The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
The young Pharaoh controls the Magician of Black Magic...
And one of his own priests, The White Beast Handler, confronts him using the White Beast.
This palette depicts a Duelist battleground that took place several millenniums ago.
The Millennium Puzzle along with another similar item is depicted in this battle between the king and the priest.
Legend states that when all seven of these items join together, an unimaginable power will be born.
That story is still told even today.
But the most important thing...
...is the battle between the evil priest and the righteous king.
And that battle continues on even now.
I don't believe it...
I...
...don't believe in this palette!
Mr. Kaiba...
I don't know what you are thinking, but this is reality.
Then come.
Please accept the truth with an open heart.
R-Ridiculous!
Come!
Th-This place is...!
I call upon the divine sun god Ra!
I Summon you to become my servant and protect us!
Deliver onto this evil priest and his followers divine judgment and punishment!
O God, deliver unto them your holy judgment!!
What...
...is this...?
The vision you are experiencing is a Duel that took place 3,000 years ago.
Just who are you?
I want to know!
Why?
"Why...?"
It's just...
I have no idea myself.
I knew you would ask me this one of these days.
But I have no intentions of lying to you.
I don't know my own name or where I came from.
I have no memories of my past.
Just who am I? I have no clue.
The palette describes the history of the eighteenth dynasty that I have been studying.
The names of the eighteen Pharaohs that ruled during that dynasty are recorded here.
In other words, they are the identities of the kings.
Kings?
However, no one knows anything about this king.
The name of this king was destroyed and all records of him were lost.
I shall Summon another servant by the will of God!
I shall then polymerize this servant with that of another spirit in order to protect our royal highness!
Come forth! Servant of evil!
God! Bestow onto them your almighty vengeance!
In other words, this is the only king to be completely erased from Egyptian history.
A nameless Pharaoh from 3,000 years ago.
I won't listen to any more of this bullshit!
I've had enough of your nonsense!
Then...
Let me show you one last vision.
What?!
In the name of the divine sun god Ra, we shall dominate this fortress!
By the spirits of those who reigned supreme and have left this world for the underworld!
The kings! And ourselves!
"King" is a title that is most fitting to us!
I will now pay tributes to God in order to realize this!
O God!
Become our strength!
Sacrifice these servants and show your divine form before us!
Summon!
Servant of divine judgment!
The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
This will now be our true victory!
O God, grant us your power!
We are God!
This is what I believe.
Perhaps fate itself leads the souls
of the king and priest depicted here to battle in present day.
Even now, after 3,000 years pass.
What bullshit!
This is nothing but crazy talk!
I overestimated you.
Well then...
Allow me to move to our main subject of the evening.
I take it you are still interested in the rare cards I mentioned over the phone.
What if I were to tell you that Pegasus himself has hidden them away?
What?!
Look closely at the top of the mural.
The three depicted atop the palette, from left to right...
The Great War God Obelisk.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon.
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra.
The Three Illusionary Beasts.
In our present day and age, they have come to be known as "God Cards".
God Cards?
Pegasus created the three rare cards after viewing this palette.
You probably have heard rumors of them.
It is said that whoever acquires these three rare cards
will become a legend among the world of Duels, and be granted the highest ranking Duelist's title...
The title "King of Kings".
Yes, I've heard of them.
The God Cards, as they're called, can be used for either good or evil.
If used by an evil person, they can supposedly take the lives of both the opponent and the player.
They are prohibited cards.
Also known as the ultimate weapons.
That is right.
They are cards that scared even Pegasus.
So much so that he himself requested that we, the Bureau of Egyptian Archeology,
seal the cards away in various locations within the Valley of the Kings.
However, before long they were stolen by a certain individual.
By whom?
The Ghouls.
Ghouls?
Rare Card Hunters operating in secrecy around the world.
Sealing rare cards by stealth or force...
...selling them on the back market for profit...
I've even heard rumors recently that they have begun making counterfeit bootlegs of the rarest cards.
However, before the worst can occur,
we must get the God Cards back.
The sole purpose for us hosting this Ancient Egyptian exhibit is so we can search for the whereabouts of the cards.
I believe that this palette has the ability to attract Duelists.
So you're making this town into a Duel Monsters battlefield?
I see now. They are bound to gather here in flocks to seek out the large gathering of Duelists.
My Blue-Eyes as well...
Finally...
This card.
That's...!
The Great War God Obelisk!
This is the only card out of the three that was not stolen.
In order to retrieve the other two, I am entrusting you with the Great War God Obelisk.
You're entrusting me with this card?
Are you sure you can trust me that much?
What will you do if I retrieve the rare cards...
...and refuse to give them back?
I trust you.
Mr. Kaiba!
What is it?
We have been fighting this battle for 3,000 years now.
No matter what...!
I certainly plan to go after these Ghouls.
But there is one condition.
What is it?!
Please do not speak of this king and priest battle crap, or any other occult nonsense for that matter, in front of me again.
I have no interest in what happened in the past.
I'm sorry.
I shouldn't have asked you in the first place...
Let's forget about this conversation.
There's one thing I know for sure.
As long as you have the Millennium Puzzle,
I can exist in this world.
Enough already...
But I...
Enough already!
I want to be with you forever.
I don't care if I don't get my memories back.
Me too...! I'll always...!
I...
I'll give you all my memories!
The God Card, The Great War God Obelisk, eh...?
Calling the millions of Anzu fans out there!
Sorry to have kept you waiting!
I, Anzu Masaki, will be performing a Dance Battle at the local game center!
I'll overcome the jerk Step Johnny with my Dance Moves!
"Let's settle this with a Duel"?!
"Just leave this to me?!"
Yugi, I always knew you were a dependable man!
Next time! "The Fiery Dance Battle"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...