Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Jounouchi-kun managed to turn the tides
with a major counterattack against Malik!
But jut as he managed to
back him into a corner,
Malik went and Summoned Ra!
And Ra's third Hidden Ability...
Is Jounouchi-kun's life spirit going
to burn up along with all his
Monsters on the field?!
Please! Endure it, Jounouchi-kun!
Victory's right in front of your eyes!
"Jounouchi Dies"
Stop screwing around...!
If I lose, I'll never see Mai...
...and Yugi...
...EVER AGAIN!!
Jounouchi-kun!
BURN!
'TILL THE LAST OF YOUR
LIFE IS BURNED AWAY!
Jounouchi!
This isn't good...
If this goes on, the pain will
shatter Jounouchi-kun's mind...!
Big brother...!
This Malik jerk's gone way too far...!
Jounouchi could really die up there!
Ra's third Hidden Ability...
I finally saw it with my own eyes!
Not bad at all for a deadbeat!
You have my respect!
That's enough.
Return to me, phoenix!
I can see the remainder of his soul
rising to Heaven with the smoke...
WHAT!?
Jounouchi!!
Jounouchi-kun!!
I-Impossible!!
He's still alive!?
Yugi...?
Jounouchi-kun!
This is our final match!
Final match...?
Oh yeah... I withstood the attack
from Malik's Ra back then...
On the next turn, Resurrection of the Dead's
effect disappeared, and Ra vanished
from Malik's field.
That's right! And on your next turn,
you Summoned Gearfried
and defeated Malik!
Yeah...!
Yugi! We kept our promise!
Let's Duel, Jounouchi-kun!
H-How...?!
Are you telling me Jounouchi's willpower
was stronger than God's attack!?
My... turn...
This can't be happening...!
Hell yeah!
Nice endurance, Jounouchi!
Ra disappeared from Malik's field!
And if he attacks Malik,
Jounouchi will win!
Jounouchi!!
He beat God...?
Now play a Monster, Jounouchi-kun!
Draw...
Yugi...
I...
Gearfried... The...
I won...
A... ta...
Big brother!!
Jounouchi-kun!!
Resisting to the very end...!
We will now enter into a time count!
Wait, Isono!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!!
Jounou-
Hey...!
Jounouchi...
...isn't breathing!
That can't...!
Because Katsuya Jounouchi is no longer
able to continue, this Duel is now over!
The winner of the first
Semi-Final match is Malik Ishtar!
Jounouchi-kun!
-Jounouchi!
Big brother!!
Isono!! Call the medical team!!
Have them take him to the Battle Ship!!
Sir!
To think someone like him
pushed me this far...!
But now he's...
Jounouchi-kun!
Oi! JOUNOUCHI~!!
Hey...! Wake up...!
Wake up, Jounouchi!!
Answer me, brother! Big brother!!
Big brother...!!
Jounouchi...! You jerk!
Open your eyes!
YOU BASTARD!!
Calm down, Honda-kun!
Damn this...!
A doctor...! Is a doctor here yet?!
They're on their way right now!
DAMMIT!!
It's a lie...!
IT'S A LIE!!
Jounouchi...
In your death...
I'll accept you as a Duelist
as you come to your end.
Yet another!
Another sacrifice to the darkness!
Another being has
vanished from this world!!
Shut up! Jounouchi-kun isn't dead yet!!
Big deal~
He shall be very shortly.
Malik.
Jounouchi's death wasn't in vain.
For me, at least...
Malik... You showed me everything
in your Duel with Jounouchi.
I've seen all of Ra's Abilities.
And the key to defeating God...
...lies in this card.
Then I wish you the best of luck.
Hurry! Carry him to the Medical Room!
-Big brother!
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Just hang in there!
-Don't die!
-Hang in there!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Stay strong!
Jounouchi!
The second Duel of the Semi-Finals
will take place in one hour!
Yugi!
Overcome your friend's death...
and return to this Duel Arena!
I'll be waiting for you, Yugi!
Doctor, how's Jounouchi doing?
His vital signs have
improved slightly...
But to be frank, he's in a
very dangerous condition.
"Dangerous condition"...?
Is Jounouchi... going to die?!
NO~!
Big brother~!
Big brother~!!
Huh? Isn't this Domino City...?
Come on! Jounouchi!
Old man Sugoroku!
Gosh, we've been looking
all over for you!
What in the world
are you doing here?!
Walk!
H-H-Hey...!
W-Where are we going, exactly?
What do you mean, "where"?
Isn't it obvious we're going to the
Domino City District Duel Tournament?
District Duel Tournament?
If we don't hurry up,
the tournament will start without us!
You're right about that.
So pick up the pace, Jounouchi!
You're going to be disqualified
if you don't get there in time!
R-Right...
Oh yeah, that's right...
I entered in the
District Duel Tournament...
Hey, doctor...
You've got to do something!
This man, Honda,
makes only one request!
Please!
I'm begging you, doctor!!
Please save him! Please!!
E-Even if you say that...
I don't even know
what is causing this!
I can't do anything like this...
What did you say?!
You're a doctor!
It's your job to cure sick people!
Cut it out, Honda!
The Power of Darkness is what
is causing his death...
Modern medicine can't
do anything for him...
The only hope we have...
...is that this boy has the willpower
necessary to pull through this.
Besides, even if I did know what
was wrong with him,
I don't have the equipment
here to treat him!
We need to transfer him to
a proper hospital immediately!
We can take him on the Battle Ship!
I-I'll go ask them!
M-Me too!
Mokuba-kun!
Thank goodness you're here!
I heard you...
But we can't take him
there on this ship...
What'd you say?!
Bastard! You're still saying shit
like that at a time like this?!
Who gives a damn about these
Duels when someone's life is on the line!?
That's not it!
We can't fly!
We can't fly...?!
The ship's engine is broken...!
What!?
It happened when we escaped
from Noah's mobile fortress...
That struggle destroyed it...
Luckily we made it
to Alcatraz in one piece...
Now the engine won't even start...!
No way...!
But don't worry!
We should at least be able to call
Kaiba Corporation for a helicopter!
Thank you for the trouble, Mokuba...
Just don't tell my brother, alright?!
Jounouchi-kun...
Jounouchi-kun...!
Don't die...!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi-kun!!
Partner...
Jounouchi-kun...
If you die...
I... I'll...!
I can't... fight anymore...
Jounouchi-kun...!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
I understand.
We'll fight each other then, Jounouchi-kun!
The promise I made that day
was supposed to be my main
objective in Battle City...!
My lost memories...
The God Cards...!
They should have been nothing compared to the promise I made with my friend!
Despite that... I...
Did I sacrifice Jounouchi-kun
for things like that!?
Other me...
The only thing keeping me going now...
...is my hatred for Malik!
But...!
After that...
What will I have left then...?!
Here goes!
Flame Swordsman!
Attack Holograh!
Booyah! I win!!
YEEEAHH~!
That's right...
The District Duel Tournament...
Looking back on it, that may have
been the first step I took on my
way to becoming a True Duelist.
But you know...
But Yugi...
Please, Jounouchi-kun...
Please...!
Don't die on me...!
I wanted to ask you
what a True Duelist is...
Jounouchi-kun...!
This is...
The Millennium Tauk!
It's the Millennium Item
Ishizu-san gave us!
This belonged to you originally.
But Ishizu said the
Millennium Tauk is losing its power...!
So why is it glowing...?
Yugi! Our Battle City isn't over yet!
Right!
DUEL!!
That vision just now...!
The Millennium Tauk should have
lost its powers, but it showed me...!
Our future...!
We will now begin the second
Duel of the Semi-Finals!
Will the participating Duelists please report
to the stage atop the Duel Tower!
Jounouchi-kun...!
I'll believe in this future!
And I'll fight...
...as a True Duelist!
This is Mokuba!
Please respond, Kaiba Corporation!
Can't you hear me?!
Send a helicopter to Alcatraz!
Damn it all! What's the deal?!
It's possible there is temporary disturbance
due to the explosion that missile caused.
This is Mokuba!!
Please respond, Kaiba Corporation!!
Big brother...
Yugi...
Yugi-san...
Jounouchi-kun...
I'm headed to the Duel Ring
where Kaiba's waiting.
Yugi!
So you stay here and keep fighting!
As a Duelist!
I want you guys to stay here
with Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi!
Wait, Yugi!
Are you saying Dueling is more
important than Jounouchi!?
Why do you have to fight
at a time like this!?
Not just Jounouchi...!
Mai-san...
Bakura-kun...
Even that man named Rishid...
Every one of them have fallen
one after the other!
We've got nothing left to lose!
Anzu...
I fight because I
promised Jounouchi-kun.
Promised...?
The Millennium Tauk showed
me a vision of the future...
If I run from this battle...
...that future will never come true!
Anzu...
You remember the Egyptian slab in
the Domino Museum, don't you?
Yes...
That's...
Why? Why is there a carving of Yugi on that stone tablet?
Anzu, I have just realized who I really am.
The soul of an Ancient Egyptian Pharaoh -
a king who was trapped inside the
Millennium Puzzle for thousands of years.
That is who I really am.
My soul was supposed to
have been lost long ago...
But I am alive,
existing right here in front of you!
I came back to find what I've lost...
As long as people continue
to search for answers...
...they have a reason to live,
a place to return.
Jounouchi-kun will come back!
I'm certain he'll return to us
as his usual, energetic self!
I believe in that future!
Win this, Yugi!
I will!
Along with Jounouchi-kun!
Good luck!
But if I lose Yugi, too...
I'll...
Jounouchi-kun...
I will fight...
In order to make my
promise to you a reality.
So don't you lose either!
I will fight as a True Duelist!
For that day!
Believing in his future with Jounouchi,
Yugi meets Kaiba atop the Duel Ring.
They head further down the road paved by everyone in Battle City.
It becomes a battle of fate as they fight for the truth.
Yugi pits the Osiris he holds against the Obelisk Kaiba-kun holds.
It's become a battle of the gods!
A fierce battle is starting, with their pride on the line!
Next time!
"The Sky Colosseum:
Yugi VS Kaiba"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise