Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
I Summon Gear Golem the Moving Fortress in Defense Mode.
Another Defense Monster?
Yugi!
There's no need to fight him anymore!
You're fighting a rigged Duel set up by the Ghouls!
That's where you're wrong, Jounouchi-kun.
I will continue fighting fairly until the end.
To defeat him!
A true duelist, no matter what the opponent is like, must not underestimate.
Yugi...
I won't let you Summon Exodia!
"Turn the Tables: Chain Destruction"
You're amazing, Yugi... You caught on to his strategy in only three turns!
Yugi, You taught me something again...
A Duelist's confidence... and a thing called pride.
Kid, I praise you for seeing through my plan.
However, the next card I draw will be the fifth piece... the Left Arm of the Sealed One.
On my next turn, Exodia will be complete! What can you possibly do in one turn?
Brother, this Duel can't be approved.
Wait a while, Mokuba.
But as the head of the Public Comity... we can't do anything?
I know more about Exodia's terror than anyone else here.
Exodia?! Then all the more reason!
Yugi beat you with that, right? Is it alright to let him take advantage of it?
It's fine!
He won't be taken down by an opponent like this.
But if he loses, I can no longer acknowledge this man as my true rival.
My turn! I set one card.
Illusion Beast Chimera, attack!
Chimera Impact Dash!!
My turn is over.
Your turn over already?! What's wrong? Did you try your best already to destroy the Defense Monster?
I see it, I can see my victory.
Once I draw this card you're finished.
Dammit. Even if he figured out his plans, he still can't do anything.
Do something, Yugi!
My turn.
This card I draw...
Now!
Trap Card activate!
What?!
Time Seal!
This skips the opponent's Draw Phase!
That's an annoying trap. I can't play cards until the next Draw Phase. By that time, my win will still be the same.
Ah! At least he still thought of something to survive this turn.
This is a Duel with the person who stole Jounouchi-kun's Red Eyes.
And in this Battle City...
I have to fight to get my lost memories back.
I can't afford to lose here!
I'll use this card to determine my fate.
I believe in the deck I built alongside my partner.
This card is the road to my future!
Lightforce Sword!
This Magic Trap Card seals one of the cards in your hand for three turns.
I'll use it to stop your Exodia!
What?!
But, if it doesn't hit the Exodia in his hand, I'll lose.
Go! Lightforce Sword!
What?!
Exodia's Right Hand...!
He did it! Yugi sealed one of his card's parts!
Next, I use Chimera as a sacrifice. To Summon the Demon's Summon!
Attack Gear Golem the Moving Fortress!
Demon Lightning!!
Yes! He turned the favor! Finish him off, Yugi!
Now even if you draw the last card part on your next turn, you can't complete Exodia!
My turn.
Draw Card.
What's wrong? You drew the same card you had out earlier, didn't you?
Why don't you enlighten us?
What's wrong with this bastard? Was the shock too much for him?
I knew you'd stop me from playing Exodia right from the start!
What'd you say?
You really think I don't know how to seal Exodia away?
Take this! Sealing Swords of Light!
What?!
It's Sealing Swords of Light!
With this, none of your Monsters can attack for three turns.
Before you even get a chance to attack me, the Lightforce Sword will break and I'll Summon Exodia!
You haven't fought this kind of Duelist before, have you?!
Dammit! It wasn't easy taking the lead the first time...
Big brother! Yugi's seriously gonna lose!
No. The real battle has just got started.
Now then. If you're my true rival, show me your abilities, Yugi!
My turn. I draw a card.
I'm through.
Where'd that confidence you had before run off to?
Thinking of a plan for when the Lightforce Sword wears off?
You're not gonna make it in time!
I have three sets of the Exodia Parts in my deck!
That means, I can still draw two more copies of the Right Arm.
I'll get my victory before your sword even wears off!
What's so funny?!
Sealing Swords of Light is a troublesome card indeed.
But it's not like it's unbreakable.
Then go ahead and try.
Will I break the Sealing Swords first...?
Or will you draw the final part needed before I can?
Either way, this match... will be decided in just three turns!
My turn. Draw Card!
It's Exodia's head?
But it makes little difference...
There's no need for me to rush since he can't attack me.
Yugi!
Don't worry, Jounouchi-kun. I'll get your Red-Eyes back.
My turn! I set a card!
Also, I Summon Magnet Warrior Alpha in Attack Mode!
So you go and Summon a useless Monster? It's still in vain...
It's quite the opposite.
Let me tell you your Exodia Deck's greatest weakness.
What?!
Exodia is made up of the five different "Sealed Cards" in your hand. It's a very special card.
In order to increase the drawing rate of the card parts,
you have to continuously play cards from your hand.
The Exodia Deck's greatest weakness is...
...you wind up playing no Monsters on the field!
Look! Your field's wide open!
My Monsters' Attack Power added together exceeds 4000.
If I attack you with both of my Monsters, you'll be wiped out!
You bluff...!
That so? We'll see about that...
You're about to experience this battle strength first hand!
Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun, watch carefully.
This Duel's match is determined by whoever believes in themselves more.
My turn.
Another double?!
It's true that I have no Monsters on the field...
But, the Sealing Swords of Light's Effect hasn't worn off yet...
So, what's wrong?
Who knew that kid would know the weakness?
I can use the double Exodia parts in my hand for Defense.
So in the small chance he's able to destroy the Sealing Swords next turn...
he still can't successfully attack me...
I shouldn't be at a disadvantage!
Exodia the Sealed One in Defense Mode!
Looks like you're playing fake cards in your deck from the start to the finish of this Duel!
I've been waiting for this moment!
Trap Card, open!
Chain Destruction!!
What the?!
This card destroys all cards identical to the one Summoned,
from both your hand and your deck!
What?!
Disappear!!
The Exodia cards need to be gathered together.
Even if you have other parts in your hand, you can't create Exodia!
Impossible...
My... Exodia...
It's impossible for someone like you who uses fake cards to Summon Exodia!
Trap Card, activate!
Dust Tornado! Destroy the Sealing Swords of Light!
My turn!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Chimera revives!
Chimera, attack the Monster on his field!
Impact Dash!
So now you've got no Wall Monsters left.
Go, Demon! Magnet Warrior Alpha! Direct Attack!
His Attack Points are added to it, increasing them by 2500!
Thunder Magnet Sword!!
You did it, Yugi!
He did it! Yugi won!
So Yugi won the first battle of the tournament just as expected, huh?
I'm looking forward to this.
Go inspect Battle City.
Okay! As the Battle City's chief chairman, I will go tour the place!
You guys! If you detect the God Cards, immediately contact my big brother!
You did it, Yugi.
As per the rules, I'll be taking Jounouchi-kun's Red-Eyes and your Puzzle Card.
This card's a fake!
I lost...
My... ultimate deck...
Help me!
He's here... He's here...!
Yugi! This guy's acting weird!
He's coming...!
The wadjet symbol of the Millennium Items?!
Malik-sama...!
We haven't met in a long time, Yugi.
The great Duelist who defeated Pegasus.
The man you faced was the weakest of the Rare Hunters.
Us Ghouls have much more strength than that!
H-Hey...
What's this guy talking about?
Whoops. I didn't mean to surprise you.
The man speaking with you isn't the one before you.
I'm in a place a bit further away.
I've implanted a bit of myself in him.
So I can control him whenever I want.
For example... something like this...
What the?! This guy's creepin' me out!
Who are you?!
Like you, I'm one of the ones chosen by the Millennium Items.
I'm controlling everything he does, with the power of the Millennium Rod!
Millennium Rod?!
An enemy will soon appear before you.
And that person will wield a new Millennium Item.
In any case, I was merely introducing myself.
My name is Malik.
Malik!
Malik! What are you Ghouls after?!
To gather the three legendary rare cards that have revived in this modern world.
God Cards?
According to the Ancient Egyptians, three stone slabs were said to possess the Power of Darkness.
Obelisk The Great War God!
Osiris the Sky Dragon!
And the Sun Dragon Ra!
The one to gather all three God Cards...
...and who takes the title of "Pharaoh"...
...will be granted a power strong enough to control the world!
Gain the power to control the world?
We Ghouls have obtained two of the God Cards already.
And the remaining one is in the hands of someone in this town.
Yugi. The Game has just started.
A Rare Hunter with a God Card is already lurking in your town.
And if you meet him, Yugi...
...even with your skills...
...it'll be instant death...
We'll see about that.
I'd never hand the title of "Pharaoh" or the power to rule the world to the likes of you!
And even if the Rare Hunter holding a God Card appears before me...
I won't lose!
I'm looking forward to testing that theory.
I need to find my lost memory in this battle.
Malik.
The power of your Millennium Rod called me into battle!
I will defeat you!
Very well, Chosen Ones.
The Millennium Battle has begun!
I look forward to it...
He's out cold. The power to control people, huh?
Just where the hell's this Malik bastard hiding, anyway?
Jounouchi-kun, this is your card.
Yugi...
Right now I can't take Red-Eyes back.
If I take that card now...
I'll feel I'm just getting farther from the True Duelist I'm trying to become.
And he wouldn't approve either.
A True Duelist?
Yugi.
You've always been the one closest to what I consider a "True Duelist"...
When I was at Duelist Kingdom Dueling with you, I felt I was fighting for something.
But I think I lost that feeling...
Jounouchi-kun...
Even when you face an opponent using cheap tricks, you always fight them fairly.
And you taught me another lesson as a result.
What I was missing was a Duelist's pride.
It's true that Red-Eyes means more to me than any other card in the world.
He's been my fighting partner for a long time now.
And that's why I can't take him back now!
No, the way I am now, Red-Eyes wouldn't let me.
So anyway, Yugi...
I'll leave that card with you.
I put together a new 40-card deck for today's tournament.
I've still got my Puzzle Card, so I'm still qualified to participate.
And I still have the Time Magician.
This is the last rare card I have to bet.
I want to become someone I can respect... a True Duelist.
No, in this Battle City, I'll become one!
Yugi, when I win this tournament,
and when the time comes where I can call myself a True Duelist...
When that time comes, please fight me.
I understand.
We'll fight each other then, Jounouchi-kun!
Thank you, Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun, I'll wait for you.
I'll take care of your Red-Eyes until then!
Mhm-hm!
There, there! I finally found them!
Yugi, Jounouchi!
Alright! This tournament's just getting started!
Who wants to fight me?!
Wait for me, Red-Eyes... I'll will get stronger!
And Yugi, at that moment...
Let's meet again.
Oi~! Yugi!
Wait. Yugi, Jounouchi?
Wait for me!
"Preview"
Jounouchi's opponent in the premier round
is the one who defeated the Dinosaur Ryuzaki, the psychic Esper Roba.
He's a Duelist holding the ability to see the opponent's strategies!
In order to become a True Duelist, Jounouchi chose to fight someone stronger than him.
But is he really alright?
If he loses here, he'll be out of the contest.
Next time! "Esper Roba: Terror of the Psychic Deck"
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...