Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
''Shine! The Sage's Jewel"
Brother, let's go rest over there.
Good idea.
It's probably just
another ridiculous trap.
Th-This is...
This is our home.
This is... the day when me and Mokuba were adopted...
Every object is composed of atoms.
An atom is composed of the atomic nucleus and electrons.
Seto-sama, you have been adopted by the Kaiba's.
Until you catch up with Gozaburo-sama, there will be no time for you to sleep.
Or did you and Mokuba-sama change your minds and want to leave this place now?
I know...
Seto... what are your visions for the future of Kaiba Corporation?
What will you do when you inherit Kaiba Corporation?
I want to... build Kaiba Land!
"Kaiba Land"?
My brother wants to build a game paradise for underprivileged kids like us.
"Game paradise", you say?
How ridiculous!
It's too boring for words!
Are you trying to tell me
this is your dream?
Games are not boring!
Games purify our souls and leave room for new development that challenges the mind!
They are the products of human wisdom!
So what?
"S-So what"?
Can they make the world turn?
The reason I want you to inherit Kaiba Corporation is so you become a ruthless dictator of the world!
Hey... confiscate all of their toys and games.
Yes...
Until you learn what it means to be that ruthless dictator,
I won't let you touch games or toys!
This is stunning.
I can't believe that after gathering all the toys and games in you guys' luggage, there's almost nothing left.
Class will begin shortly.
Big brother...
There's no way my brother is wrong!
What might the problem be?
Um... Please...
Give this to my big brother.
He forgot to
take his reference book.
You forgot this.
You have no time to sleep.
We are starting in one hour.
I know...
Big brother... please don't let them steal our most important treasure.
Use these cards to help you relax.
Mokuba...
They're all trashy cards...
Mokuba...!
Mokuba, I'll get the real one some day.
That's some outstanding brotherly love you two have there.
Seto... You sure had it hard early on in your life.
What do you want with us?
Why are you showing us all of this?
In order to refresh your memory.
I want you to remember what you did to Gozaburo Kaiba!
What?!
Sooner or later,
judgment will come for you.
Noah, just who the hell are you?!
I'm eagerly waiting
for that time to come.
Anzu...
Although we've been moving forward in this darkness,
we seem to have forgotten about one important thing.
Something important?
This is a game we're playing.
As long as we have a stronger Monster Card than the one guarding the door, the doors will keep opening.
This is the first most important rule.
First most important rule?
I get it! If we wanna get out of this maze, there should be a second rule!
Most likely...
That must be it.
I did think it was a bit strange.
In each room we enter, there's a set of doors with the Level Stars ranging from one to four.
Right... that guides us on how to get out of this endless loop.
We just went through a One Star door.
So this time...
Let's go through the Two Star door.
Go, Elf Swordsman!
Good job!
Wait for me Anzu!
It's so cold. Please save me, Yugi.
Unfortunately for you, no matter how loud you cry for your friends,
we're the only ones in this world!
Now, it's your turn.
My turn.
Since I used Offerings for the Dead last turn, I can't draw during this turn.
You only have one card in your hand.
If you don't hurry and send out a Monster, my cute Flying Penguin is going to attack you directly!
Call me to the board!
The Deck Master can be played as a Special Summon.
Let me cover for you.
Wait! You don't have enough Attack Power to beat this guy!
If the Deck Master is defeated, the player will lose the game instantly!
That's correct!
Without Black Magician, Black Magician Girl's partner, she's nothing but a little cosplay-girl!
It's alright.
I'm going to need your strength later on!
No way!
I'll Summon a Monster in Defense Mode and end this turn!
It seems like you don't have any Wall Monsters in your hand.
My turn!
Go! Flying Penguin!
Penguin Sword!!
Heh, just a weak little angel, was it now?
Because of Helping Angel's Effect, I get to pick one card from my deck.
Well, I can tell this turn is over.
Anzu Mazaki, 16 years old, the card you picked is the only one you have.
And your life-saving chain is only a useless magician.
You have no other way to beat me.
Let me help you out
by using your body...
Who'd let someone like you...
I have to bet
everything on this draw!
Please lend me your strength, Yugi!
No! Attack Power, 1550?
It can't defeat his Monster.
Wait... Maha Vailo is a strong magician with a hidden ability.
A hidden ability...?
Right, this card...
Which card is the most like me?
Umm... since you have so many cards, there must be something.
Yeah, you're right.
I think it's Black Magician.
I'd like to say that, but he fits my other self better.
But for me...
Yeah, this one.
Maha Vailo?
Yeah... this may not be the best Monster,
and it doesn't really have the strongest Attack Power,
But it has a hidden ability.
It can use this power at will.
Maha Vailo's hidden ability...
I remember now!
My turn! I'll Summon Maha Vailo!
Next I'll use a Magic Card!
I equip it with Magician's Spell Book!
It's a pity that my Flying Penguin has 2200 Attack Points.
It seems you're still a bit inferior.
No... Maha Vailo has a hidden ability!
When equipped with an Equipment Card, it receives a 500 point power up!
What?!
Maha Vailo...
Holy Lightning!!
''Yu-Gi-Oh Episode 103 Subbed'' originally Encoded by Nealhon
Thanks Kamesennin2 for helping him with the subtitles!
I did it!
Thank you!
Yugi!
That was Anzu's voice just now...
What's wrong?
N-Nothing!
When she calls my name, Anzu doesn't really want me.
The one she's really calling...
I know very well who she wants...
The Level Three Star door?
There!
Okay! Do it, Dark Knight Gaia!
Wait, Partner!
Gaia!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force... exactly what I thought.
Look at the top of the door!
Is that covered card there a reverse card?
No doubt about it.
So... how about this?!
Okay, we got him!
No...
Not yet! Berfomet!
Then Fusion!
Go... Chimera!
Alright, this is the last door!
There are five set cards.
In order to get this far, we've used a lot of cards.
If you waste the few cards we have left,
we may not get out of this labyrinth.
There are only five cards left in my deck.
A Four Star Monster
and five covered cards.
This will be tough.
Wait! He's our last trump card!
Then... I'll use this! Heavy Storm!
Good, the covered cards are gone!
Play that card.
The Four Star Ladybug of Death!
We did it!
Good thinking!
The Four Star Ladybug of Death is a card with the Effect to destroy Level Four Monsters.
Let's hurry!
Anzu!
Anzu! Anzu!
I know I was too careless to look down upon you,
but I'll make you regret what you just did.
My turn.
I'll play Volt Penguin in Defense Mode!
I'll also play a reverse card to end this turn.
I doubt there are many Monsters that have an Attack Power over 2550.
But I'd better finish this fast just in case!
My turn!
I'll use Maha Vailo to attack!
Holy Lightning!!
My chance is soon at hand!
Instant Magic, activate!!
Revenge Sacrifice!!
Maha Vailo!
Revenge Sacrifice can destroy the
Monster and present it as a sacrifice.
Now I'll Summon a new Monster to take care of you!
I Summoned Guardian of Ice - Defender Iceberg!
2450 Defense Points!
Can you overpower this Monster and attack me?!
My turn!
I'll cover one card.
And I Summon Penguin Torpedo.
Because of my Deck Master, it gets a power-up!
This Penguin Torpedo can attack the player directly!
Anzu!
Well, it's your turn.
My turn.
You're at your limit!
Let me out!
Although I can't attack, the opponent won't be able to attack very easily.
Black Magician Girl...!
So you finally came out to play, ya piece of garbage.
But if it gets destroyed then I win!
My turn!
Reverse card, activate!
Ocean of Regeneration!
This card is able to revive a Water-Attribute Monster from the Graveyard for one turn.
Go! Direct Attack!
Oh no!
With that, the 16-year-old Anzu Mazaki's life is like a fading candle flame!
Anzu!
Anzu!!
Anzu... Anzu's gonna be defeated.
I've made it here.
But I can't help at all?!
Damn it all!
No... I believe in the power of Black Magician Girl.
Please listen to me.
There should be one card that can save us in your deck.
I didn't pick that card for my deck.
I didn't choose Black Magician!
Yes, you did.
It's the first card that you picked.
The Sage's Jewel?
Right... that is the card that will grant us a miracle and give me the power to win!
But, it'd be too coincidental to draw that card during my next turn.
It's time I activated
my Deck Master Ability!
My sleeping comrades...
please lend me your power.
The Black Magic Secret Technique!
Soul Circle!!
Wh-What the hell?!
My Deck Master Ability borrows the power of our comrades sleeping in the Graveyard and draws five cards from your deck!
I got it!
What?
I'll let you see my power!
Black Magician!
Black Magician!?
Black Magician?!
Impossible!!
The 16-year-old Anzu Mazaki doesn't have that card in her deck!!
When I'm on the field and The Sage's Jewel is played, I can call my master, Black Magician for one turn.
WH-WHAT'D YOU SAY!?
Here goes!
Double Black Magic!!
Damn you! I was so close to getting a new, young and sexy body~!
I... I won.
Anzu!
Yugi!
I knew you'd come save me!
Yugi! I was so scared!
Anzu... you're okay now.
Yugi...
This sure was unexpected.
No, I should say it was... refreshing entertainment...
I somehow got away from that old, perverted penguin.
I managed to reunite with Yugi,
but I wonder what
happened to the others.
Jounouchi's started his Duel already?
The opposing Deck Master is Judge Man.
What kind of Duel is a... "Trial Duel"?
Be careful, Jounouchi!
He's a dangerous foe to deal with!
Next time!
"Deck Master: Judge Man's Judgment"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise