J-Jounouchi...
That's low! Let go of Anzu!
Jounouchi!
Namu-kun!
That's...!
Mokuba!
Good of you guys to come.
We are the warriors of the Ghouls.
Mask of Light.
Mask of Darkness.
We are a Tag Team assembled for the sole purpose of getting the God Cards back!
Shining Abyss! Defense Mode!
The Magic Card Mask of Brutality!
What?!
Within one turn, they were able to play a Monster with 2600 Attack Points!
These guys have the advantage when it comes to a Tag Duel...
And in our case, Kaiba is fighting alone.
Can I really save Jounouchi-kun and the others in this situation?
The Sealed God Cards
My turn.
My card is...
Mask of the Accursed.
Mask of the Accursed?!
To start, I'll use this guy...
I equip it on Yugi's Magnet Warrior!
The Monster equipped with Mask of the Accursed
cannot attack or defend.
And the controller of this Monster will take 500 points of damage at the start of their every turn.
I'll then set another card face-down!
Turn over!
Trap Card?
This Light guy hasn't played a single Monster...
Is his strategy to play cards that work along side the Mask Cards?
All Partner needs to do is play a High-Level Monster to finish you off!
Now, Yugi!
It's your turn!
So ya get to take 500 points a damage!
Draw!
Red Lord of Hell - Gilfor Demon...
A 6 Star Monster with a good Special Ability!
Because of Mask of the Accursed, he can't attack or defend, but...
if Yugi sacrifices his Monster,
he can Summon a High-Level Monster, as I would if I were him.
But...
I have a bad feeling about this...
Alright!
I sacrifice the Magnet Warrior!
Trap Card activate!
Permanent Trap!
Mask of Sacrifice Sealing!
Mask of Restrict
What?!
You fell for it, you fell for it!
Mask of Sacrifice Sealing is a Trap Card that restraints the opponent players from sacrificing any Monsters!
Meaning as long as this Permanent Trap remains on the field,
ya can't sacrifice any Monsters!
What?
We're sealed off from Summoning High-Level Monsters?!
That's right.
You guys can't Summon the God Cards or any other powerful Monster for that matter!
The God Cards have been sealed!
Damn you...!
We can't play any strong Monsters on the field?
I set a reverse card and
and play Kuriboh on the field in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
With our sacrificing sealed, we can't win.
Kaiba, we only have one way to win!
I know what you're about to say.
Fight along-side each other, right?
What nonsense.
Kaiba!
No good?
If this keeps up...
It's my turn!
It'd be better to leave Yugi's Magnet Warrior on the field.
Cuz he's losing Life because of it.
What bothers me is Kaiba's reverse card.
You don't have to worry, Partner.
Got it.
First, I set 1 reverse card!
Also, I attack Kaiba's Blood Vorse with Shining Abyss!
Think I'll let you?!
Trap Card activate!
Destruction Ring!
Ring of Destruction
Alright!
This card will destroy Shining Abyss!
And both players receive damage equal to the destroyed Monster's Attack Points!
I won't let ya!
Counter Trap Card activate!
What?!
Cursed Transfer!
This activates when the opponent activates a trap card!
It transfers its effects to the opponent!
But Kaiba's not the only one who will lose Life Points...
His companion Mask of Darkness should also lose some too...
Kaiba!
They've got a way to stop it!
Be quiet, Yugi!
As I told you last time, I don't need help from you!
Destroy Blood Vorse!
The Magic Card Defensive Ring!
Ring of Defense
This card negates any damage done from a trap!
How 'bout it?!
You damned fool!
Our Tag Combination is far more than these measly tricks!
What?!
I'll be using that Effect!
Spell Transfer
Kaiba!
Your Defensive Ring is wiped out!
I'll then use it to escape damage!
Kaiba...
These are the fusion tactics of Light and Darkness!
You guys can't win against our combination!
Shining Abyss!
Direct Attack Kaiba!
Die, Kaiba!
Let's see...
How are you?
Big brother?
It's me, me!
Honda.
Honda-san?
You still haven't taken off the bandages?
I can take them off anytime, but...
Then we'll head to Battle City after you take them off.
Eh, but...
"But"...?
My big brother was there during the operation, right?
I'd like my big brother to be here when I take off the bandages, too.
So you feel insecure without Jounouchi here...?
I get it!
Let's go to where Jounouchi is!
Let's cheer for Jounouchi together!
And he'll give you the courage you need!
Thank you, Honda-san!
But he's not the only one who'll give you courage!
Anyway, you should get ready to go!
I'll go get us some tickets for the train!
Looks like the worst is over.
Now sleep well.
I wonder just who could have done something so terrible...
I wish we could find the culprit right away...
but I can't look for the criminal by myself.
Hold it, let me go!
I said let me go!
You guys really think you're gonna get away with this?!
Wait a minute!
What are you gonna do with me?!
Where'd you put Jounouchi and Namu-kun?!
HEY!
These Ghoul guys...
Just what are they planning?
They captured us,
yet we don't have any rare cards...
This Millennium Talk grants me the power to see into the near future.
I knew you were coming here.
And I knew a great battle would be held in this city shortly.
Yes. You came here of your own will. You chose this fate of fighting.
Ishizu-san mentioned a new fight...
She wasn't just talking about the game?
Is this all related to the other Yugi?
Just when did we get ourselves mixed up in this fight?
Wh-What the...?
Yugi...!
I activated the Magic Card Multiply with Kuriboh.
It's the Magic Card Multiply and Kuriboh combo!
Your attack won't reach Kaiba!
He used Multiply on such a weak Monster?
They're all weaklings!
So I was saved by your Kuriboh...?
Yugi! Mind your own business!
Kaiba, this Tag Match must be played with a team of two...
However...
The issue is you and me.
If either one of us falls, it's all over.
Are you saying I can't win with my power alone?!
Right now, the Ghoul opponent's before us have flawless team strategy.
They help each other in times of peril.
That attack of teamwork is unmatched by anything else.
If we don't combine our power in this Duel, we have no chance of defeating the Ghouls!
Cooperation...?
With your teamwork...
It's impossible for ya to beat us.
But with these weakling Monsters all over the field,
our attacks won't reach those guys.
It's quite a problem.
It's alright, I got a plan.
Just a bit more...
Ow, ow, ow~!
I need to go on a diet...
Let me go!
Who's there?!
What are you doing!?
Mokuba-kun!
Anzu!
Are you alright?
Y-Yeah...
Why are you here too?
I was looking for you guys,
then suddenly...
Me and Jounouchi were assaulted too...
Why'd this happen?
They probably captured us so Yugi and my big brother couldn't run away from their Duel!
Those damn Ghouls are after my big brother's and Yugi's God Cards!
God Cards?
Yeah!
The three God Cards are legendary rare cards!
They're probably attacking my big brother and Yugi right now!
That's what they're after...
I see...
But maybe that's not all...
You know something, Anzu?
N-No!
Not much...
I can't talk to Mokuba-kun about all this...
That we're being dragged into a battle that has lasted 3,000 years...
My turn!
Draw!
Blue-Eyes...!
I can't Summon a High-Level Monster without sacrificing though...
But...
But they have the Permanent Magic on the field Mask of Sacrifice Sealing...
Forget the God Card, I can't even Summon Blue-Eyes!
I can't stand it...
I set a reverse card!
Minotaur in Defense Mode!
Battle Ox
Turn over!
Looks like your big plan was a failure, Kaiba!
They have Shining Abyss on their field with 2600 Attack Points.
In a Tag Battle, you can protect your partner with a Monster on your field.
Right now we can only rely on the multiplied Kuribohs.
We're sure to get a chance!
Seems ta be my turn!
Good, good, good, good!
Aside from those weakling Monsters guarding you, you guys can't do a thing!
I'll get rid of em with this card!
Mask Card!
Mask of Dispell!
What?!
The Multiply Magic Card's being engulfed by the Mask Card!
With Multiply's effect gone,
there's only 1 Kuriboh!
Even more, this card takes an additional 500 points from your Life Points on the start of your every turn!
Without Multiply,
We can be directly attacked by their Monsters...!
It's just a matter of time...!
What should I do?!
Also, I use Masked Spellcaster - Cursed Boogy to attack Kuriboh!
Grand Tiki Elder
He's annihilated!
Now that little Wall Monster a yours is gone!
The Magnet Warrior I have on the field can't attack or defend because of the Mask...
And the only Wall Monster I had is gone...!
Now, Yugi!
It's your turn!
Don't forget ya lose 1000 points from your Life Points due to the 2 Masks!
My turn!
Draw!
A Trap Card?
This won't help...
If I use the Magic Card Hand Obliteration,
Card Destruction
All players discard their hand,
And then draw the same number.
But...
If Kaiba has a card in his hand that can turn the tables,
I'll also be forcing him to discard it...
No good...
We still can't increase our teamwork...
What's wrong, Yugi?
Seems like you have some High-Level Monsters in your hand.
Meaning you can't play any Monster Cards this turn.
But it can't be helped if we're holding these powerful cards in our hands...
If we can't sacrifice to Summon them, these cards are a nuisance.
Wouldn't they be better off in the Graveyard?
Kaiba's Reverse Card on the field...
I see!
Kaiba wants me...
Those two seem to be quarreling friends!
These guys don't have a hint of teamwork in this world!
Yugi...!
Did you realize?
I set 1 reverse card!
Turn over!
Yugi!
Seems like you couldn't play a single Monster in Defense Mode to help you!
I'll... bet on this!
My turn!
I'll use this Magic Card!
Ritual Card!
Masked Beast Ritual!
Curse of the Masked Beast
Masked Beast?!
I sacrifice a Monster of Light and Darkness on both of our fields!
I Summon Masked Hellraiser!
3200 Attack Points?!
Yugi has no wall on his field!
Hellraiser!
Eliminate Yugi!
What?!
kaiba's Monster got in the way?!
The Tag Duel rules state that when the opposite player is being directly attacked,
you can protect your Tag Partner with your own Monster.
Did you forget?
These two didn't have any teamwork...!
Kaiba!
Don't misunderstand me.
This is payback for that Kuriboh favor earlier...
But now Kaiba's Monsters're all gone!
Now you can't protect yourself against the Masked Beast's attacks!
Is that so?
Here I go, Kaiba!
Reverse card open!
Hand Obliteration!
What?!
Hand Obliteration?!
All players must discard their entire hand!
Now I sent the Red Lord of Hell - Gilfor Demon into the Graveyard along with my hand!
I discard my entire hand as well.
You need a sacrifice in order to Summon High-Level Monsters.
But in this specific case, there's another way to Summon a High-Level Monster onto the field without sacrificing.
My turn!
Reverse card open!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Monster Reborn
That's...!
Kaiba!
Thanks to Hand Obliteration, I was able to Summon Blue-Eyes from the Graveyard!
Blue-Eyes?!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Is here!
Preview
He was able to Summon Blue-Eyes, but...
There Monster's Attack is still much higher!
You're saying to still attack, Yugi?
I see!
You're gonna prove the power of cooperation to Kaiba, right?
If you guys master it, you won't have to be scared of these Rare Hunter's plays anymore!
Way to turn the tables!
Next
Time
Cooperate !
Next time!
Cooperation!
Duel standby!