Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Kaiba! Sorry about your loss, pal...
Why don't you Duel me?!
How 'bout a battle for third place?
My journey on the path to become a True Duelist won't end after one measly loss!
The Virus Combo right from the start?!
Now the only Monsters in my deck are Monsters with hardly any Attack Power!
But this Duel's just getting started!
"Blue-Eyes White Dragon VS
Blue-Eyes White Dragon"
Well, Kaiba?
I didn't get this far in Battle City for nothing, ya know!
Good move, Jounouchi!
He's not gonna lose, even if Kaiba-kun's his opponent!
Jounouchi-kun has indeed grown
much stronger as a Duelist.
Yup! Jounouchi-kun's gotten really strong!
If Malik hadn't set that Dark Game up in his Semi-Final match,
Jounouchi-kun would have won for sure.
Return to me, phoenix!
WHAT!?
H-How...?!
Are you telling me Jounouchi's willpower
was stronger than God's attack!?
My... turn...
Draw...
Yugi...
I...
Gearfried... The...
I won...
A... ta...
If Jounouchi-kun's attack had connected that moment,
he would have beaten Malik.
Yeah.
When Battle City ends, I'm going to fight
Jounouchi-kun just as we promised!
I'm looking forward to that moment!
Yeah! It's gonna be a really good Duel!
I'm going to defeat Malik
for that sole purpose!
You're right.
And I'm definitely going... to win!
I can't believe my brother's Virus Combo didn't work!
Jounouchi's not too shabby!
It seems as though you've gained
a fragment of wisdom on battle conduct.
But it appears to be shallow at best.
What was that?
Even if you managed to survive this turn,
your deck only contains Monsters with 1500 or lower Attack Points thanks to Deck Destruction Virus of Death!
You won't be getting far in this Duel relying on luck alone.
It's true. I can't use my main attack force with high Attack Points like Panther Warrior or Rocket Warrior.
But even so, I can't just give up
and run away with my tail
between my legs!
I'm going to beat you!
And then I'm going to fulfill my promise with Yugi!
Go for it, Jounouchi-kun!
I guess only death cures stupidity.
Very well! I'll give you a thorough lesson on the difference in our strength!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon
Blade Knight in Attack Position!
Attack the Swordsman of Landstar!
Take out the garbage!
Oh no! It was killed!
Things changed in a second!
Maybe it really was just luck earlier?!
No... Jounouchi-kun won't be taken out this easily.
I'll also set a reverse card face-down...
...and end my turn.
This Duel's only getting started!
Let's get on with it!
What in the world
did those two see before?
What in the...?!
The Millennium Rod is...
...glowing once again!
What...?!
What in the hell is happening?!
Why did it only respond to them...?
I'm the owner of the Millennium Rod!
Rod! Show me what you showed them!
And you are...?
My turn!
Draw!
Here I come!
I Summon Little-Winguard in Attack Mode!
What the hell is he doing?!
Won't 1400 Attack Points lose against Kaiba's Blade Knight?!
He needs to play Defense Mode and protect his Life Points right now!
What are you trying to pull?
Is the deadbeat commoner trying to think up a common strategy?
You could say that.
Then I'll play this thing.
The Equipment Magic Card, the Legendary Sword!
It increases the Attack and Defense Power of the equipped Monster by 300 points!
Good! Then it will have 1700 Attack Points!
It'll be stronger than Blade Knight!
I equip Legendary Sword
with little-Winguard!
Reverse card, open!
Magic Absorption!
What?!
The moment your Monster's Attack Points go up,
those points are absorbed by Magic Absorption and injected into my Monster!
My Legendary Sword...!
Use all the tricks you like.
They won't work against me!
You're only capable of producing the strategies of a commoner! A deadbeat Duelist!
All you ever do is call me deadbeat and commoner over and over again!
I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
It hurts me to admit it, but Kaiba-kun is really strong!
True. But keep watching.
Jounouchi's not giving up that easily!
To be more accurate, he doesn't know how to give up!
What's your problem, little girl?
That's not something you can just pick up off the ground.
Hand it over!
Why is the Millennium Rod...?!
It's you...!
What!?
Other me!
This can't...
The Millennium Puzzle is reacting to something!
Is Malik up to something again...?
Anzu!!
You don't think he's after Anzu...?!
Now that I think about it, she's been missing for a while...
Keep fighting, Jounouchi-kun!
I thought I could win using that Equipment Magic...!
But Kaiba used it to power up his Monster
Now their Attack Points...
It's my turn! Draw!
I'm going to show you such a menacing defeat...
So bad that you'll never even think of challenging me to a Duel again!
I activate a Magic Card! Enemy Controller!
This card cuts my Life Points
by 1000 points...
But, by using the input command, I can control one of my opponent's Monsters on the field!
Kaiba-kun took a huge risk by lowering his Life Points by 1000!
Is he planning to finish this in one strike?
Left! Right! A! B!
I have gained control!
I have seized Little-Winguard!
I'll then activate
a Magic Card from my hand!
Cost Down activates!
This card lowers the Monster Level of a Monster in my hand by two!
You can't mean...
Now I only require one sacrifice to Summon an Eight-Star Monster!
Let me show you.
This is how vast the gap in our power is!
I sacrifice Little-Winguard!
Come forth! Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
Normally I'd consider him a waste
on a deadbeat like yourself,
so you should be appropriately honored
to be finished off by the Blue-Eyes!
Oh shit!
Jounouchi doesn't
have a Monster on the field!
Go, Blue-Eyes!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Hold your horses!
Reverse card, open!
Scapegoat!
What?!
Don't go killing me off that soon!
God! You're really fluttering in the wind right now, Jounouchi!
He's a mess, but at least he made it out with his Life this turn.
You won't be damaging me until you defeat all these Scapegoats!
Then I'll beat them down one by one!
Go, Blade Knight!!
What?! The Blade Knight's Attack Power just went up!
It's one of Blade Knight's Special Abilities.
When I have one card in my hand or none at all, it gains an additional 400 Attack Points.
The Blue-Eyes holds 3000 Attack Points.
And the Blade Knight has 2300.
And you, who can't Summon any Monster with over 1500 Attack Points...
...can hope for nothing short of a miracle!
It's true that my Scapegoats are gonna be destroyed next turn if I don't do something!
Turn end.
Something...! There has to be something I can do...!
I'm begging you!
My turn! Draw!
A let down...!
Can't be helped... I'll have to endure this turn!
I set one reverse card!
And I Summon Ultimator in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
What a pointless struggle.
Let's just see if it's pointless or not!
I see!
So what you're telling me is
you've left a piece of your memory
within this little girl?
I will no longer
let you do as you please!
Sure about this?
You haven't gone
and forgotten, have you?
This body belongs to you
as well, you know.
I'm aware!
But this is the only thing
I can do to stop you!
So that means you're
willing to push yourself this far?
But you know, our dear
elder sister's gonna be pretty sad!
And Rishid as well...
What do you suppose he will do
once he learns he wasn't able
to protect you?
Rishid...!
And that's why...
...I say you're too soft!!
And the situation
changes in a second!
You would've been better off
if you had just stayed idly inside
and didn't come out!
My oh my,
what an agile body you have!
Still...!
As if a bunch of memory fragments...
...could ever hope to oppose me!
You're the one who should
disappear without a trace!
VANISH!!
Cease this at once!
Huh?!
Well, well... If it isn't my
cherished older sister...
Sister!
Malik! Hang in there!
Sorry...
I'm already...
Malik!
Forget about me!
Just... defeat him...
Malik!!
What's the deal, elder sister?
I'm the one he tried to kill here.
Heh! This isn't the least bit fun!
Perhaps I should dispose of you as well...
You have no way to protect yourself
the way you are now!
Stop this!
Man oh man! I've got irritations
up my ass today!
Malik, I'm not going to allow you
to cause any more problems!
And how do you plan on doing that?
Should we settle this here and now?
Oh, forget it!
It'd be pretty boring
to do things like this.
I've already thought long and hard
about the stage I'm going to kill you on.
We'll start the show in due time.
Wait patiently while
you've still got your head!
Other me! Anzu's...!
Anzu!
She's alright.
She is simply unconscious.
Why did Anzu
come here in the first place?
Yugi... I have a favor I must ask of you.
From me?
My little brother...
Please save Malik!
My turn! Draw!
The Magic Card, Life-Shaving Card Treasure!
Its effects allow me to draw until I have five cards in my hand.
So it's a Hand Reinforcement card?!
In exchange for the hand enhancement, I must discard my entire hand after five turns.
But I won't be needing to worry about that in this Duel!
Jerk! What the hell's that supposed to mean?!
It means this will be over long before that happens!
I Summon Kaiser Sea Horse
in Attack Mode!
Weaklings should go away!
And then Blade Knight!
Destroy the last remaining animal, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
All Jounouchi's Monsters were destroyed in a matter of seconds!
He won't be able to block against Kaiba-kun's attacks next turn!
I end my turn.
And now you don't even have a wall to protect you.
Continuing this Duel is a waste of time.
How about you surrender already?
Who the hell's gonna give in?
I can't give up in a Duel until the very last second!
So long as I
have cards in my deck, anyway!
That's called reluctance,
you deadbeat!
Shut up!
My turn! Draw!
I've still got a chance!
Using the effects of Pot of Greed,
I'll draw twice from my deck!
Please! This time...!
Yes! I did it!
I activate my reverse!
Graverobber!
Kaiba!
I'll be taking a card
from your Graveyard!
What?!
And that card is...
Enemy Controller!
This card lets you control the opponent's Monster by inputting a command and paying 1000 Life Points.
But I'm gonna use a wee bit different
command this time around.
Up! Left! Down! Right!
A!
Using this command, I can destroy the Monster I attach the cable to!
You can't...!
Blue-Eyes "Blows Up"!
And this ain't over yet.
I'll activate Resurrection of the Dead!
What...!?
And the one I'll revive is, of course...
Come out! Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
This is the ultimate combo with Graverobber and Resurrection of the Dead!
Great move, Jounouchi!
That was an amazing strategy!
You might even win now!
Big brother...
I'll use Blue-Eyes
to attack Blade Knight!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
How dare you...
I then Summon Falcon Knight
in Defense Mode!
And this is the last one!
I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
Whacha think?! We don't know what's gonna happen till the very end of the Duel!
That's why we fight 'till the end without giving up!
Someone like you
dares to use my Blue-Eyes...!
I will not forgive this humiliation!
Blue-Eyes...!
If Jounouchi plans to try and control you, I'll destroy you with my very own hands!
If you go to sacrifice a Monster when Kaiser Sea Horse is in play,
and the Monster you are about to Summon is a Light-Attribute,
its Special Ability counts it as two tributes!
So I can sacrifice two tributes for the Light-Attribute Monster, Blue-Eyes!
You can't...! Not another one...!
I sacrifice Kaiser Sea Horse!
Come forth, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
How do you like it, deadbeat?!
He played another Blue-Eyes?!
They'll destroy each other!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Damn, what a guy...!
Did he go nuts just because he didn't like the fact that I was controlling his Blue-Eyes?!
My turn's not quite done yet.
Did you think you were the only one capable of reviving the dead?
What?!
Resurrection of the Dead...
Revive, my Blue-Eyes!
Return to the side of your true master!
Kaiba also had Resurrection of the Dead in his hand?!
It's far too disgraceful for a fool like yourself to be using the Blue-Eyes!
Now that Blue-Eyes is back in the hands of his real master...
...you'll taste his terror!!
Kaiba-kun managed to turn the tables as he stole back his Blue-Eyes.
Even though Jounouchi tries to fend him off,
Kaiba-kun drives him into a pinch yet again!
But not giving up is one of Jounouchi's strong points!
Enduring several of Kaiba-kun's attacks,
Jounouchi draws the card that has saved him in countless crises! The Time Magician!
Can he beat Kaiba-kun with it?
Next time!
"The Path of a True Duelist"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other