Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Hidden Power:
The Purpose of the God Cards"
Calling all Duelists.
We will now be taking a 20 minute break.
Please report to the Bing Machine after that time.
We will then hold the lottery for the second round of the tournament.
Just 20 minutes, huh?
Let's get going.
What are you guys doing?
Mokuba!
Where's Kaiba-kun's room?
It's right here, but what do you want with my brother?
Kaiba! You're in there, right?!
Open up!
What the heck are you doing?
You can't bother my big brother!
-Kaiba! Open up!
-Stop it, Jounouchi!
-Oi!
-Kaiba!
Kaib-
So it's the deadbeat?
Even you should know how important the time before a battle is for a Duelist.
What?!
Oi, Jounouchi!
Now isn't the time to fight!
Kaiba-kun!
Yugi.
Kaiba-kun, I have a favor to ask.
You want me to land the Battle Ship?
Bakura-kun still hasn't woken up!
And he's bleeding a heck of a lot.
He was already pushing himself too much leaving the hospital and coming on board!
And what do you expect me to do about it?
Please land the blimp and take him to a hospital so he can be looked at!
Shizuka-chan's-
-right!
Whatever the reason may be,
he is responsible for Dueling with those injuries in the first place.
I beg of you!
People's lives are more important than these Duels!
Right!
That's our Shizuka-chan!
You should listen to her!
Hey, Kaiba!
Don't you have even the slightest bit of human blood flowing in you?!
We cannot land this ship now.
What did you say?!
Wait up, Kaiba!
Jounouchi-kun!
Please send the medical staff to room number six.
We have a team of doctors on board the Battle Ship with training better than any local hospital!
He's in good hands.
Shizuka-chan! That was well said back there!
When you told Kaiba-kun, "People's lives are more important than these Duels!",
I literally felt my heart move!
I was sooo moved~
N-No way...
I guess we've got no choice but to leave Bakura with Kaiba's supposed skilled medical team.
That's true.
Well then, I'm gonna go search for Bakura's missing Millennium Ring.
Yeah, we'll give you a hand.
No, you've got to focus on the coming Duels.
Duelists have a lot on their minds right now, right?
Honda-kun...
But...
Don't worry about it!
We're not doing anything but cheering you guys on.
Let us handle the tedious stuff!
So Shizuka-chan, shall we go look together?
Otogi, come with me.
Eh? No...
I-
The Millennium Ring's hard to spot!
It'll be too hard on my own!
Let's go search together!
So they can be useful sometimes!
Yup. But don't you think Honda-kun's acting a bit weird?
It's not up here anywhere.
Let's go search some place else.
While I've got the chance,
I have something to tell you.
It's been bugging me ever
since we met in Domino City.
What has?
Don't you think that
you are getting too close to Shizuka-chan?
I was wondering what you could be thinking about,
but Honda-kun, what exactly are you to Shizuka-chan?
Are you her lover or something?
Well...
I'd understand if her brother Jounouchi-kun was upset,
but I don't think that
you have the right to question me.
What'd you say?!
After all, I'm free to do whatever I like with Shizuka-chan.
Instead of dragging me all the way out here and tossing around uncanny accusations,
why don't you play this fair and square by confessing to Shizuka-chan yourself?
Although, even if you do, I think it's clear who the winner of this competition is.
You asshole! You askin' for a fight?!
Wanna try it?!
Good! Let's do it!
Damn you, Otogi!
Are you trying to kill me, bastard?!
Sorry! Hold on tightly!
Anybody there?!
Anybody up there?!
Help us!
-Hey! Somebody please help us!
-Anyone there?!
Shit... No one's gonna be up there now...!
Honda-kun!
Shit...!
My hands just went numb...!
Honda-kun!
You can do it!
Damn it..!
Honda-kun!
I... can't... take it anymore...!
Th-Thanks...
We're saved!
Thank you! We owe you our lives...
What's your name-
What's wrong with you, Honda-kun?
He's gone... The man cloaked in white who saved us...
The man cloaked in white?
You're... Shadi!
Based on my investigation in the Duelist Kingdom,
I learned that the seal on the Millennium Puzzle had been broken.
It seems that you have learned the identity of the other "you" residing within it.
Right, my other self is the soul of a Pharaoh sealed within it.
That is correct, vessel to the Pharaoh's soul.
How did you get here?
Never mind...
You're always appearing to me in incredible ways.
I am a guardian of the Millennium Items.
And currently, all seven items are gathered aboard this ship.
Huh?
Adding to that, the God Cards are here as well.
All the requirements needed to open the door
to the Pharaoh's memories are gathered aboard this Battle Ship.
Really?
But listen carefully, vessel holding the Pharaoh's spirit.
Both the Millennium Items and the God Cards
may only be used by those chosen to wield them.
If one who is not chosen tries to use them, they shall suffer God's wrath.
God's... wrath?
Yes.
Once in the past, Pegasus traveled to Egypt in the hopes of bringing back his dead lover.
Soon after, he discovered palettes containing the images of strange monsters.
Being tempted by those palettes,
Pegasus returned to Egypt several times.
He sought out the stones depicting the truth behind the Pharaoh and his Royal Priests.
This was the beginning...
The Duel Monsters game revived soon after that.
Of Duel Monsters?
This was the beginning
The Duel Monsters game revived soon after that.
Of Duel Monsters?
Pegasus studied the palettes for years
and learned of the existence of three "God Cards"
He then finally decided to locate these God Cards himself.
Why can't we find the God Cards?
I am most certain that the God Cards exist! They are not a myth!
Why I can't I find them?
My Duel Monsters shall not be complete until I create the God Cards!
You are... Shadi!
The three God Cards have been sealed by the Tomb Guardians and their Power of Darkness.
You won't find them
no matter how hard you try!
Oh my God!
But with my power,
I can show you them.
Really? Please!
Show me those palettes!
It's hard to believe there's a village down here!
Come on.
No! It seems somebody is here!
Th-This is...
They can no longer see us.
Oh! Unbelievable!
It's here!
We are about to open a door to history here!
Oh, three God Cards...
Cross over 3,000 years of time and revive once again!
Oh! Th-That's...
Jesus! At long last I've finally found the three God Cards!
Oh, great! At long last I can finally complete my Duel Monsters!
Pegasus then went back to America
to design the images he found in the pit.
Even I had no idea of the terror to come...
That moment I was thinking...
Whether or not those chosen by the Millennium Items
could control the gods as well.
What? all the people involved in the God Card expedition have all died?
Y-Yes.
Jesus! At long last I've finally found the three God Cards!
Oh, great! At long last I can finally complete my Duel-
Even for Ancient Egyptian language, these words are something special!
If I can't decipher their meaning, the cards can't be completed.
What's the matter?
And others involved grew delusional and had panic attacks.
I don't think it's all just a coincidence!
I must insist that you stop the production of the God Cards!
The development of Duel Monsters
is our company's opportunity to become a big hit!
We shall create a new page in history!
Are you suggesting we waste such an opportunity?!
So you're implying this is "God's wrath"?!
In that case, I will take the full brunt of that wrath!
Whether it be the power of the gods or the power of darkness,
I can control both with no trouble!
But now I'm a bit tired.
Th-This is...!
Listen to me, Pegasus!
Duel Monsters is not just a mere game.
It holds the power to destroy the entire world.
It's a Dark Game!
No!
Even if it is a Dark Game, I have to bring Duel Monsters to life!
If my soul is to be devoured by the devil himself, then so be it!
You cannot control all three cards at once.
Unless you are to seal them away in Egypt.
NO~!
Unbelievable!
That overwhelming heat, power and pain...
There is no way that was a mere illusion!
Even though Pegasus had completed the three God Cards himself,
he himself had experienced the extremely horrible power of the cards firsthand.
He decided to seal the cards away himself.
I know that you have come to return these cards to their rightful place.
Pegasus J. Crawford.
Then Pegasus received a visit from that woman.
And by that, you mean Ishizu-san?
O Vessel of the great Pharaoh's spirit, please deliver my words to him.
That's not necessary.
Just tell me directly, Shadi.
I am most sorry.
All seven items are present aboard this ship.
All you need to do now is win the Duels and open the gate with your own power.
All participants of the tournament, please report to the main lobby!
I'm counting on you, other me!
Right! I'll gather all three cards!
It's true!
There was a man cloaked in white!
He was really scary, eh Otogi?
But I really didn't see him myself...
Oh come on, stop trying to scare me.
Who'd believe that story anyway?
But, there really could be a ghost!
Come on, not you too Shizuka...
What's up, guys?
Yugi! You freakin' scared me!
Here's the story, Yugi...
Malik...
Here, dear sister!
Shadi!
A horrible fate awaits Malik...
I am Dueling in order to prevent that horrible fate.
"Preview"
The one chosen to be Jounouchi's opponent in the second match
is the one who brainwashed us
and forced a fight between friends!
Malik!
We won't ever forgive him!
Jounouchi! Pay him back tenfold in the Duel!
Compared to the energetic and impatient Jounouchi, Malik is calm and gloomy.
What?
A giant temple appeared on Malik's field!
Next time!
"Jounouchi VS the Trap Deck"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise