A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Final Duel!
Yugi VS Pegasus!"
Alright!
I'm counting on you, my deck!
Grandpa, at last, the fight
against Pegasus will begin...
I'll win for sure and get your soul back!
Listen. In important, stressful situations,
a Duelist's heart will begin to lose grip.
You begin to lose sight of yourself,
and before you know it, you begin
walking down the path of failure.
Yugi, if you are able to face your
heart in these times of pain...
You'll be able to win for sure.
I understand, Grandpa!
Yugi.
Yugi, it's finally about to start.
Guys!
You made it this far.
You have to win!
For your grandfather and Mokuba-kun!
And for Kaiba-kun as well.
It is time.
Challenger Yugi Mutou,
please enter the Duel Ring.
Here I come, Pegasus!
Yugi! We're counting on you!
You can do it!
Show him your power, Yugi!
At long last,
the final showdown has arrived!
My cards, we're about to face the master
of the kingdom, the strongest Duelist!
Let's fight as one!
Yugi boy, you are indeed
a splendid Duelist.
I commend you on surviving
the fights in this kingdom ﻿
and earning the right
to challenge me to this fight.
Pegasus!
Before we Duel, you will
swear to me right now!
That if I win, you'll return
my grandpa's soul to me!
Yes, it's a deal.
That's not all!
The souls of the Kaiba brothers
sealed in the cards as well!
Well, isn't this odd...
Is Kaiba boy not your enemy?
Right now, you're my only enemy.
I...
But then, what can I do?
You don't have to steal.
I promise.
I will defeat Pegasus!
I swore to Mokuba...
That I would allow him to
see his brother once again.
I see. An oath, was it?
The Mind Scan...?!
Okay, I swear.
If you should win this match...
I will set them free from
the prison of lost souls.
Hey, it's finally starting!
Yeah! I can almost see their fighting spirits clashing from all the way up here!
Yeah! We finally made it this far!
Will Yugi-kun be alright?
The odds of winning against an opponent
who can use the ﻿power of the
Millennium Eye to read his mind...
You dumbass! Yugi won't lose!
He'll be the real king of this island!
He'll kick that Pegasus bastard's ass!
That's right! That's right!
Right, Honda?
I just brightened the mood!
What's with the depressing attitude, Honda?!
But just think about it!
This battle can't be called fair.
He's taken those three hostage
to lure Yugi this far, after all.
But didn't Pegasus capture his grandfather's
soul just for this Duel.
Pegasus is a Duelist himself.
Even he wouldn't do anything that low.
Yeah...
Besides, you're
the one most worried here.
Their Duel is about to begin!
Hey, let's go to the upper balcony
so we can see it better!
Yeah, good idea.
Jounouchi-kun and Anzu-chan
aren't worried at all...
But you may be right, Honda-kun.
Pegasus isn't to be underestimated.
If the Duel gets dangerous for him, there's
no telling what measures he'll take.
Honda-kun, where are you going?
I can't do anything
about his grandfather's soul,
but if I can at least save Mokuba and
Kaiba, Yugi may stand a better chance.
Mokuba, huh...?
Yugi Mutou, you have come to Duelist Kingdom
in order to challenge the king.
Please show me the Honor of the
King's Left card as your entry.
Yeah. This is it!
Honor of the Kings Left!
Indeed.
If you hold that card...
..and you are able to
defeat the king of Duelist Kingdom,﻿
Pegasus J. Crawford,
in a game of Duel Monsters...
Pegasus will hand you 60%
of Industrial Illusion's stocks.
In other words, if you wish it,
you will become the ﻿new president
of Industrial Illusions.
Are you serious?!
Huh? Where's Honda?
Dunno... He wandered off on his
own somewhere and took off.
He probably had to use the bathroom.
Anyway, the Duel's about to begin.
That is a truly amazing present!
For the one able to defeat me, of course
there should be a reward of such mass.
Or you're just confident there's no one
alive that can defeat you.
Yes.
However, it takes
great risk to gain such honor.
That card, Honor of the King's Left...
There is no image on the card.
And do you know why, Yugi boy...?
An image will appear on the card
once you are defeated.
In other words,
my soul will be sealed in the card?
Just like Kaiba.
That is correct.
I'm prepared!
That courage is magnificent!
What did he say?
If Yugi loses,
he'll end up just like Kaiba-kun?!
He...
Even though he knew what would happen, he
still went ahead and challenged Pegasus?
He's betting his own soul?
Soul?
Can he really do that?
Dunno... But he definitely did something
to Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun.
Yugi... don't lose!
If you lose, I...
You have to win!
Yugi!
It's too bad, Pegasus.
I have no intention of becoming
a part of your card collection.
I am not going to defeat you
merely for the sake ﻿of adding
another card to my collection...
My most important goal lies in getting
control of Kaiba Corporation.
This fight will decide
the future of Kaiba Corporation.
That is correct.
I would like it if
Mr. Pegasus could dispose of Yugi.
All we need now
to complete the contract is to
find the key Mokuba hid away.
Kaiba Corporation, Mr. Pegasus,
will then become yours.
All the pieces are in place.
All that remains is to win this Duel.
Now then, the Duelist Kingdom
Championship Match will now begin!
Cut and shuffle each other's cards.
Okay.
Duel!
Yugi boy... with the power of
the Millennium Eye at my disposal
you have no chance of defeating me.
I won't lose!
I can't lose!
Bakura may just be right
about all the stuff he said...
If I find them, it will be a big help,
but this castle's so huge...
It's time to change shifts.
How's the kid doing?
The same as usual.
We shouldn't have to worry about him escaping, but don't let your guard down.
Of course. He's the only one who knows the location of our precious key, after all.
Mokuba...
Huh? It's a dead end?
That's strange.
What?
This is...
Here I go! My turn!
I set a card face-down.
Then I play this Monster Card
in Defense Mode.
Does his Millennium Eye really allow him
to see my entire hand and set card?
It is my turn.
I set a card face-down.
Furthermore...
A Monster Card.
I'll lay Archery Mermaid in Defense Mode.
Turn over.
Archery Mermaid?
Just a Normal Water-Attribute
Monster Card?
And he didn't even
play her in Attack Mode...?
Yugi boy, I know very well.
The two cards you
have face-down on the field...
...are Ruiz and...
...Horn of the Unicorn.
I'm positive that in the next turn, you will use this to Combo Attack me with Ruiz...
If that's a Water-Attribute Monster,
my set card should be the best choice!
Pegasus' set card does worry me...!
...but I can't let this chance slip by!
Alright!
I'll give it a try!
I switch my set Ruiz to Attack Mode!
I also activate my Set Card,
Horn of the Unicorn!
His sword becomes an electrical sword and
his Attack Points go up by 700 points!
Attack the Mermaid!
You've just made a grave error.
I activate my Trap Card!
I knew he'd do this...!
Mermaid's Tears!
What?!
Mermaid's Tears is a Trap Card that activates
the ﻿instant the opponent activates a set card.
It seals the enemy's attack.
Ruiz is electrified by his own electricity
in the bubble of ﻿water,
and because of it,
his Attack Points drop back down!
My turn.
I switch the Mermaid to Attack Mode!
Arrow Shot!!
Ruiz is killed!
It's almost as if he knew what Yugi's ﻿reverse card was going to be!
So this is Pegasus' Mind Scan...?
What's Honda doing?
He still isn't back yet?
Now that you mention it,
he's taking a long time.
Geez! What the hell's
he doing at a time like this?
As I thought, with Pegasus' Millennium Eye,
he can see right through me...!
That's right, Yugi boy.
Pegasus is not only the creator of the ﻿cards,
but a king without bounds!
How do I fight against
the power of his Millennium Eye... ?
You appear to have
wasted a turn, Yugi boy.
There are many variables
in this game, from ﻿the cards to choose,
to the right timing...
The player's road to defeat
is lined with a great ﻿number
of little mistakes, one after another.
Let me tell you one thing.
I never make mistakes.
Pegasus gives off a sense of absolute ﻿confidence in this game.
If I can't break free of that, I can't win!
That Pegasus bastard...!
All humans make mistakes!
Does he think he's God or something?!
Since Pegasus was the one
who created ﻿Duel Monsters,
he's almost like a god.
The creator knows his world inside out.
Bakura! Are you trying
to say Yugi can't win?!
That's not it!
I don't think so, but I also don't know
how anyone can defeat Pegasus...
No! I believe in Yugi!
Croquet-sama worries far too much.
There's no way a motionless brat's just gonna run away.
You sure it's all right to act like that?
Of course it is.
That was nothing!
Mokuba!
I set a Monster in Defense Mode
face-down and end my turn!
It's me.
Oi, what's the meaning of this?!
This is the head of security.
Can you hear me?!
He's not responding!
The B1 Area has had its lock opened.
What the hell is he doing?!
You guys, go look for him!
We don't know what's going on,
but there may be an intruder.
Hey! Can you hear me?!
If it is an intruder, Pegasus-sama
must be told immediately.
Pegasus-sama is currently Dueling.
I understand. I grant you permission.
I'll let you guys handle it.
Understood.
Yugi, concentrate!
Don't back down, Yugi!
Not good! I've been found already...!
It's my turn.
I set a card face-down on the field.
Dragon Egger in Defense Mode.
I'll also switch the Mermaid to Defense...
...and my turn is over.
This way's no good either...!
Wh-what do I do...?
It's my turn!
Yugi boy is like
a small animal struggling for breath
as I crush it with my hands.
For I know every single card
in your entire hand!
Mind Scan!!
And the card you just drew is...
Demon's Summon, isn't that right!?
That gaze that
pierces through my cards...!
This feeling's
not just my imagination!
We're counting on you, Yugi!
Yugi!
He's reading my mind...!
But there's nothing
I can do to stop it...!
Pegasus was really reading through Yugi after all!
And Pegasus plays the same ﻿card he used to beat Kaiba-kun.
None of Yugi's attacks are working, and even Demon's Summon has become a Soon Monster!
Yugi's in trouble!
Bakura-kun and Honda have gone missing...
Just what's going on in this Duel?!
Next time!
Attacks Impossible!?
The Invincible Soon Army"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship