Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Hurry up!
If we don't hurry up,
their Duel's gonna start without us!
Hey, we're goin' the right way, ain't we?
If we just follow the hoof prints, we won't go wrong!
I must witness this Duel with my own eyes.
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Yugi vs Rafael - The Impregnable Guardian Deck"
Oi, Otogi!
Step it up on the accelerator!
That's right!
We ain't gonna catch up
with Yugi at this pace!
All right then! In that case, get ready to fly!
Hang on tight, you two!
Otogi! You bastard!
Don't leave us behind!
Rafael!
So you came.
We had a deal.
Hand over Professor Hopkins!
I have already set the professor free.
He should have already gotten home by now.
What did you say?
As our death match is about to start, there's no need for an escape route!
I'm very honored, Yugi Mutou, to be able to Duel with you.
As a True Duelist.
Don't make me laugh.
How can you be a True Duelist?!
If you were a "True Duelist",
you wouldn't be using the power of the Duel Monsters for your own evil intentions!
So we are evil...?
Let me ask you then, Nameless Pharaoh.
What is your definition of "justice"?
My definition of justice?
We are both comrades walking on paths we believe in.
In our hearts, we have our own version of "justice."
The path that we of Doma are walking towards...
Is it for good or evil?
For that matter, it shall soon be decided by huge historical changes.
Historical changes?
That's right.
Amidst the changes, there is only one thing we can do.
We can only bet on the justice before our eyes and our lives at this moment.
Dueling with full strength... with death in mind.
Duel!!
What the...?!
Be careful, Other Me!
He's not normal!
Got it, Partner!
That murderous aura...
It's like I'm being stalked by a wild beast...
This guy is strong!
I shall attack first.
My turn!
I activate the Continuous Magic, Treasure of Guardian God!
By discarding five cards I have on hand, I can draw two cards from my deck.
In my coming turns, I can draw two cards instead of one!
A card that allows one to draw more cards...!
Even at the expense of discarding five cards...
Is he aiming to get The Barrier of Orichalcos?!
I Summon a Defense Position Monster.
I set another reverse card, and I end my turn.
Now, I have no cards in my hand.
So Yugi, are you relieved now?
I do not have The Barrier of Orichalcos in my hand.
His hand is at zero...
Once I destroy his face-down Defensive Monster,
this Duel will be under control!
My turn!
Good...
I polymerize Illusion Beast Gazelle and Berfomet from my hand!
To Summon Winged Phantom Beast Chimera to the field!
With the attacking power Chimera possesses, it can easily destroy any ordinary Monster!
Go, Chimera! Attack his Defense Monster!
Chimera Impact Dash!!
What?!
Backup Gardna has a Defense of 2200!
So Chimera's Attack Points can't touch him!
An ordinary attack won't do!
Give me your strongest attack!
That again...?
It's my turn.
Equipment Magic, Gravity Axe!
I activate the special effect of Gravity Axe!
Come forth, Guardian Grarl!
Guardian Grarl is a Monster that can be Summoned when Gravity Axe is on the field.
And because of the Effect of Backup Gardna,
I can attach the Equipment Card, Gravity Axe, to Guardian Grarl!
3000 Attack Points!
Go, Guardian Grarl!
Swift Cleave Attack!!
Chimera was beaten this easily...
Due to Chimera's Effect, I can Summon Berfomet!
What's wrong, Yugi?
This won't do any damage to my Guardian Deck.
Guardian Deck...?
That's right, my Monsters will risk their lives to protect me.
Likewise, I'll protect these Monsters as well!
You say you will protect these Monsters?
The professor is sleeping very soundly.
He doesn't seem to have any injuries, either.
Anzu, take a look at this
I thought I might find some information on the Internet.
After some searching...
Eh? There's information about them online?
A news article ten years ago?
About the incident that caused a luxury liner to sink?
There was only one survivor.
I didn't remember that until now.
When I became the U.S. Champion, rumors had it that...
The first in the U.S. wasn't me.
But someone who used the legendary "Guardian Deck" and who never appeared in public.
The name of that young Guardian Theme user was Rafael!
If that's the case, this young boy is...
I can't be wrong!
Rebecca!
Please let me go, Anzu!
Yugi will surely win.
Let's believe in him and wait for him to return.
Anzu...
Can you even begin to grasp how strong the bond between myself and these Monsters is?
You wouldn't be able to comprehend it!
That sounds so shallow, Rafael.
A Duelist who believes in his guardian cards...
It's natural for anyone to believe in their own deck!
Yugi...
Look carefully.
These cards...
They're worn out from overuse.
Naturally, to ensure I can't differentiate them from my other cards,
I've pasted new covers on the back.
But this does not change the fact that they have supported me for a very long time.
These cards hold a true power - They rescued me from the abyss I was in.
Yugi... No, Nameless Pharaoh.
Ever since I knew of your existence,
I have held some strange feelings towards you.
We are both people being manipulated by fate.
People manipulated by fate...?
This place greatly resembles the place where I lived with my Monsters.
It's like a no-man island floating on land.
Here, Big Brod'er!
What have we here?
Hurry up an' open it!
Isn't this Guardian Eatos?!
I've wanted this card so badly!
Julien and me worked really hard to find this!
Sonia!
Big Brother, happy birthday!
Happy birf'day!
Sonia, Julien, thank you!
Wh-What's happening?
Wait!
Come back here!
What's up with the ship?
I've caught you!
I caught ya!
What's wrong?
Big Brod'er?
What's that?
Big Brod'er!
Big Brother!
Sonia!
Julien!
Big Brod'er!!
Sonia!! Julien!!
Papa! Mama!?
Sonia! Julien!
That accident happened too suddenly.
Fate took away all that I had in a single moment.
Eatos... Was it you who protected me?
"If I'm alive, maybe my family is alive somewhere too."
With that in mind, I strove to stay alive on that no-man island.
Have you ever been unable to speak to anyone for three whole years?
Have you ever endured the loneliness of being unable to touch anyone?
What kept me going and prevented me from going crazy from all the loneliness...
...were these cards.
They were my friends and family at the same time.
That murderous aura surrounding him...
Can that be coming from the Monsters that want to protect him?
Rafael!
If you love your cards so dearly,
why are you helping Doma?
Nameless Pharaoh.
You should be able to understand.
Humans can't fight against the "fate" that exists in this world.
I've experienced that!
I realized that there are ignorant people in this world.
Those who do not
know the existence of "fate."
Young lad, he who leads the Duel Monsters into battle...
Once thy seeith clearly, thou shalt return to my side.
I returned back to this world miraculously.
But what was waiting for me in my former world...
...was endless despair.
The whereabouts of my family remains unknown.
All that was left were my relatives, who took my Dad's inheritance.
And those who wanted to share in my fame.
To think that I had stayed alive to return to such a place...!
Nameless Pharaoh...
Why did your soul revive after thousands of years?
Why was my whole family wiped out in seconds...
...leaving me alone to live in this malicious world?
You can't answer my questions.
There is but one way to answer to "fate."
Rafael...
Why were you the only one to survive?
Do you want to know the answer to that?
Then come to me.
I shall guide you.
The answer to "fate..."
If you want to know the answer, you'll have to accept your own destiny.
You can only watch carefully to see where your fate will bring you.
Does that mean that you're also fighting your own fate?
But fate will only allow
one of us to stay alive.
But I have no wish to disappear!
Me as well!
That hurts~!
I thought I'd die~!
Hey, look there!
Has the Duel started?
My turn!
The Magic Card, Twinkle Five-Star!
The Twinkle Five-Star card can only be used when there is a Five-Star Monster on your side of the field!
The Five Stars will Summon the Kuriboh Brothers to the field!
I Summon the Kuriboh Siblings!
Are these the Monsters that protect you?
Don't be careless, Rafael.
I activate the Special Effect of Kuriba!
The Kuriboh Siblings will combine to form a Summon!
Kuribabylon!
In addition, I activate Pump Up from my hand!
This card can double the Attack Power of a Monster for a full turn!
Kuribabylon, attack Guardian Grarl!
I activate the Magic Card I placed in the Graveyard!
Rescuer from the Grave!!
A Magic Card that can be activated even when it's in the Graveyard?!
Rescuer from the Grave...
By removing five cards in the Graveyard out of the game, the battle with your opponent is invalid.
I've said this before.
That I'll protect these Monsters!
In order to have this defense...
That was why he discarded his hand in the start...
He's truly strong!
It's my turn.
Honestly, I'm quite disappointed.
In that turn earlier, both our Monsters had the same Attack Points.
Given that situation,
your precious Monsters would have gone into the Grave.
Yugi...
I won't forgive anyone who belittles his Monsters.
I set two cards face-down.
Then I activate a Continuous Magic,
Purity of the Cemetery!
The effect of Purity of the Cemetery is that, for every Monster sleeping in your Graveyard,
you will be dealt 100 points in damage every turn.
This effect is destroyed once there is a Monster in my Graveyard.
Is this guy really intending not to get any of his Monsters sent into the Graveyard?
And let me tell you one more thing.
I'll never use The Barrier of Orichalcos in this Duel!
Even if I don't use that card,
I'll still be able to defeat you.
Your little servants are now in Attack Position after the attack was nullified earlier.
Guardian Grarl has an Attack of 3000 points!
There's a difference of 2700 points.
If this attack hits, it will be vital damage to you!
Go ahead, Guardian Grarl!
Swift Cleave Attack!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Each betting on the 'justice' that they believe in,
The violent battle between Yugi and Rafael continues.
Rafael, who has a strong bond with his Monsters...
Risks his Life Points in order to save them.
But is he really intending not to use The Barrier of Orichalcos at all?
And the truth about Doma and their aim is revealed...
Next, "The Truth about Doma"
Duel standby!