Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Mai VS Malik:
The Dark Duel"
The lottery for the Duelists participating in the third round of the tournament will be held in fifteen minutes!
How's his condition?
There was no severe psychical damage done to his body.
However, he remains unconscious.
Most likely, he fell into a coma due to extreme mental shock.
Mental shock...
Bakura-kun's still sleeping after he fell in his Duel...
Too many people have been hurt in this tournament!
But it doesn't make any sense...
I took damage from the God Cards just like he did.
Why just him...?
'Cause you're thick-skinned.
Shut up!
But I guess we won't learn who this man really is 'till he wakes up.
Was this man really a member of the Ghouls?
This guy insisted on being Malik's shadow until the end...
But Malik's the one I'm really mad at!
Making this man act as his "shadow" and then abandoning him!
Not only does he brainwash people...
He's rotten to the core!
When things got tough, Malik betrayed him and left him alone.
When you think about it, you can't help but feel bad for this man.
All alone...
After the Duel, I stood up in time, so I won...
That's it!
This guy and me... I think I know what determined our match.
I had a dream.
Of you guys...
I had friends waiting for me...
But this guy must have been all alone...
Jounouchi-kun...
Thank you, guys...
You gave me strength.
Jounouchi, you don't have to thank me, just pay me back for the Beef Bowl I bought you!
Why bring that up now?!
Come on, big brother!
Friends, huh...?
Oh yeah, isn't it time for the lottery drawing for the third match?
Oh yeah!
Let's leave the rest
to the doctor and head out.
Okay!
Hey! Hey, Jounouchi!
Can I ask you something?
Hm? What is it?
The dream you saw...
I was in it too, right?
With everyone...
No.. well...
How do I put it...?
My body feels really tired...
I can't stand up.
W-Well... You know...
My dream took place in our classroom!
So of course you weren't in it!
You're too old to be in High School!
Next time... Oh, that's it!
You can be a lady zombie!
It'll be a dark and serious character!
W-Well, I'm off...
That idiot...
There's no way I could tell Mai something as embarrassing as me dreaming about her in a classroom!
Ow, ow, ow~!
Jounouchi!
Wh-What the heck was that for, Anzu?!
I should be asking that!
You don't get woman at all!
You're the worst!!
Alone, huh...?
What's wrong with me...?
Until I met these guys...
I always fought by myself...
Without anyone's help...
I stood alone!
That was my pride and my belief...
There can only be one winner...
Who needs the bond between friends in such a cruel and lonely world?
After all... I'm a Duelist!
And now... we will decide the match-up for the third round of the tournament!
What's going on?
Malik and the eight Duelist
aren't even here!
Hang on a sec!
Hey, Kaiba!
Malik entered using a fake name!
Ain't he disqualified?
And what about it?
And that's why I call you a dead-beat "Joe Blow"!
What was that?!
This isn't a competition based on names!
In this tournament, the only thing anyone cares about is the amount of skill you wield!
If I defeat Malik, I can take Ra away from him.
And if I have two God Cards,
defeating Yugi will be a simple matter.
Begin!
Alright, let's begin the lottery for the third round match-ups!
Ultimate Bingo Machine, go!!
I bet my brother goes next!
My only target is Malik.
This draw is gonna decide the contestants for the fourth Duel as well.
Third match! The first Duelist is Number 4, Mai Kujaku!
Do your best, Mai!
Now let's start the lottery for her opponent in the third match!
Bingo Machine, go!!
Mai! Your opponent's not decided yet!
No matter who my opponent is, I'll win!
Yugi! Jounouchi!
The next time we meet, it'll be in the Semi-Finals!
Mai...
We'll cheer for you...
Don't come!
Mai-san!
I fight alone!
I don't need you guys cheering me.
I don't recall ever claiming to be a part of that little group of friends you're running over there!
Mai...
Jounouchi, I'm not a soft Duelist like you who needs another's power to win!
Wh-What the heck does that mean?!
I dare you to say that again, dammit!
Big brother!
Fine then!
Will you please hand me that key?
One by one...
I'll sacrifice them to the darkness.
Rishid...
The seal you carved in your face kept my hatred in check...
So long as you exist,
you threaten to return me to the darkness.
Now it's your turn
to be in the dark, Rishid!
You can die and join my old man on the other side!
The third match of the tournament!
Mai Kujaku's opponent is...
Malik Ishtar!
Both participants, please report to the Aerial Duel Ring!
You've got quite the luck...
I'll keep you alive a while longer...
Malik...!
The man they say owns Ra...
The darkness is hungry...
Interesting! So I get
to add a god to my deck!
I'll beat this man...
and his Ra will be mine!
Woman, I'm going to sacrifice you to the darkness!
Now why don't you show me if you're worthy of holding Ra in your deck.
Mai Kujaku VS Malik Ishtar!
The third match shall now commence!
Here goes!
DUEL!!
I'll be going first!
Card Draw!
My turn!
I Summon Dunamis Valkyrie!
Attack Position!
My turn is over!
Now isn't that a nice rare card...?
Now then... I think I'll start things off with a sharp sword...
My turn.
My card is Revival Slime.
Defense Position.
The Magic Card, Slime Breeding Machine.
Thanks to this card, a Slime Token will be created on each of my turns.
Now, woman...
If you don't attack me quickly, my field will become crowded with Monsters...!
So you intend to show me this soon, huh...?
It's started already?!
Mai!
You guys...
Mai-san, you can do this!
Beat Malik!
Why did you all come here?!
I thought I told you I can fight by myself?!
We know that!
You'll win regardless of what we do!
But we're your friends, so cheering you on is only natural, ain't it?!
Do what you want!
Yugi! Look at the ring!
That's...!
It's Revival Slime and
Slime Breeding Machine!
My turn!
Mai! Watch out!
That Monster is...!
Yugi, you're violating principles!
What'd you say?
Regardless of what kind of strategy he uses,
it's against the rules to give me any advice!
Mai-san!
You sure about that, woman?
You'd be much better off listening to what he has to say.
Don't look down on me!
I don't need anyone to help me!
I've gotten this far by fighting alone!
Mai...!
Dunamis Valkyrie!
Attack Revival Slime!
Angel Dust!!
Revival Slime is destroyed!
What?!
Don't be in such a rush.
All you did was activate Revival Slime's Regeneration Ability!
Regeneration Ability?
Let's enjoy this thoroughly...
We've got plenty of time...
My turn!
Magic Card! Pot of Greed!
Thanks to Pot of Greed's Effect, I get to draw two cards.
And thanks to Slime Breeding Machine, I Special Summon a Slime Token!
Furthermore, I set one reverse card!
Big brother, that card...
It's probably the Trap Card that redirects the enemy's attacks to Revival Slime.
Defender Slime!
He's right...
He'll just use the Revival Slime's Regeneration Ability to revive itself!
He needs three sacrifices to Summon Ra!
I won't let you!
My turn!
Magic Card! Harpie's Feather Duster!
Permanent Magic and Traps won't work against me!
Alright!
Good job, Mai.
You got rid of that combo that caused me a lot of trouble in a mere turn!
Dunamis Valkyrie!
Get rid of that scrawny Monster!
She did it! Mai scored an early lead!
Rejoice...!
Rejoice to the Heavens as you grasp on to the last ray of light and hope!
That way when everything you hold dear crumbles in despair before you,
the resulting shock will be ten-fold!
I set another face-down card on the field!
My turn is over!
My turn.
I Summon Melchid the Four-Faced Beast.
I then sacrifice both Revival Slime and Melchid the Four-Faced Beast...
...to Summon Masked Beast Death Guardius!
That's...!
From the Duel against the Mask guys?
Go, Death Guardius~!
Attack Dunamis Valkyrie~!
I'm not gonna let you do that!
Trap Card, activate!
Silver Screened Mirror Wall!
Now your Monster's
Attack Power is cut in half!
Dunamis! Pay him back!
Angel Dust!!
She did it!
This is all going in Mai's favor!
No...
Dunamis!
The moment Death Guardius is destroyed,
its Effect instantly activates, known as the Mask of Remnant!
Thus, I shuffle my deck...
...and I gain control of Dunamis Valkyrie.
And allow me to dispose of that nuisance of a Trap.
The Magic Card, Remove Trap!
Shit! Now she's got
no Monsters on the field!
If he attacks her now, she's gonna take a huge amount of damage!
No, it'll be fine!
If things continue to go the way they've been going so far, Mai's got this Duel in the bag!
He's right!
If he Summons Ra,
I have no chance of winning.
I've got to finish
this before that happens.
I'm gonna get serious, now!
I'll show you the
power of my Amazoness Deck!
I look forward to it.
What's with this guy?
He's up there acting all carefree...
This is one creepy guy!
Mai! Don't let your guard down!
Shut up!
You're pissing me off!
What's with her all of a sudden?
I see. Your friends, huh?
Then you fools can watch...
...as I destroy this woman right before your very eyes!
It's about time we
end this little petty farce...
Woman, I plan to sacrifice you!
That's enough of a warm up!
Warm up?!
He isn't...!
Now let the Dark Game begin!
Wh-What is this?
These dark clouds...
...are completely surrounding us!
Starting right now, I'll make you experience the world's most terrifying game!
This weird fog-like presence...
These aren't normal clouds!
I'm sure that this dark cloud...
This is the same as what happened when Yugi fought Pegasus!
A Dark Game!
That's right, Yugi...
So you figured it out...
What's gathering around us is hatred...
darker than the darkest night!
Malik! Stop this!
This darkness is nothing less than a reflection of my heart, and my deepest hatred!
Yugi...
This darkness is eagerly awaiting its chance to devour you...
The darkness is hungry!
And I shall sacrifice
this woman to calm it!
Mai! This Duel is dangerous!
If you lose, you'll lose your life as well!
Surrender the Duel!
Yugi, are you trying to insult me?!
Once a Duelist accepts a Duel,
if they show the enemy their back, a part of their heart dies!
You should know that better than anybody else!
Mai!
Yugi! Jounouchi!
I'll win this Duel
no matter what happens!
So that I can fight you guys next!
Nice...
I'm gonna turn this woman
into a living platter!
And I'll spice it up with her pride!
Livestock like her will make for a mouth-watering dinner!
Yugi, don't bother.
Don't bother anymore.
Nothing we say to her will stop Mai now.
Mai...
Don't you dare lose, Mai...!
Here I come, Malik!
The Dark Game begins!
Be careful, Mai!
We have no idea what the Dark Game he's casting is...
My turn!
I set a card on the board!
Then...!
I Summon Ally-Slaying Swordmistress!
Wh-What on earth is this light?!
Mai Kujaku...
You can see this because you are participating in the Dark Game.
The light illuminating your Monster...
That light is the very light
of your existence.
The essence of my existence?
Rather than me explaining it, you'll understand quicker if you see it for yourself.
This is a game of dismay and fear.
And you will feel emotions beyond anything you've ever experienced in this Duel!
This man... has the eyes of a madman!
Even so...!
Ally-Slaying Swordmistress!
Attack Dunamis Valkyrie!
Well done!
You succeeded in reducing my Life...
...but Dunamis Valkyrie was originally your Monster!
Therefore, the Effect of Darkness shall activate and affect you!
Effect of Darkness?
That's right.
Every single Monster on the field holds within it a piece of human memory... of both you and me!
And of course, once that Monster is destroyed, the very piece of our memory within it shall disappear!
But that's impossible!
Yugi, what the heck's Malik talking about?
Has Malik already used his Power of Darkness on Mai?
Now then...
I wonder who will disappear from your memory first?
Anzu!
She shall be the first to vanish from your memory.
Anzu...!
Anzu's going to
vanish from my memories?
Mai Kujaku...
I already caught a glimpse of what you hold dear in your heart.
And I already know how to break it.
Using this eye, I can see the truth behind one's desires.
This causes my opponent
even more suffering!
No... It's the most suitable power to get under your skin...
I can see it...
The vision of you crying out like a child, "I'm lonely! I'm lonely!"
Mai Kujaku...
What you fear more than anything else...
...is the loneliness of your friends disappearing right before your very eyes!
That's... not possible!
Then try to think of her!
That girl's face!
I can't remember!
Now, dear woman...
You've taken your first step towards true loneliness!
Oi! Mai!
What's wrong?!
Mai!
Mai Kujaku...
You shall suffer true loneliness and despair before you die a miserable death!
And that is why they call it...
a Dark Game...
"Preview"
Thanks to the Dark Game Malik made, Mai-san won't answer my call!
And even her memory of Jounouchi leaves her!
Don't lose, Mai-san!
If you beat Malik,
your memories will return!
Huh? Mai-san's Monster took Malik's card from him!
That card is...
It couldn't be...!
Next time!
"Capturing the God Card"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise