Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Judge Man tried to
cheat me in gambling,
but the manly Katsuya Jounouchi won't lose to some fake lawyer scumbag!
The Goddess of Luck smiled on me till the very end!
But I can't afford
to stay here wasting time.
One of the two remaining Big Five guys may be after Shizuka!
Wait for me, Shizuka!
"A Man's Passage to the Stage: Honda's Death for Honor"
This place doesn't
seem very dangerous.
No, we don't know when one of them will appear.
We can't let our guard down.
Otogi!
But it's true!
You're so dense! How come you're always saying stuff that scares Shizuka-chan?!
Uh... But I'm glad both you and Otogi-san are with me.
Ain't ya?!
If ya stick by us, you don't gotta be scared of nothin'!
There you go with that easy-going attitude again...
Oi, cut it out already, will ya?!
But you're too relaxed, Honda-kun!
What was that?!
Stop it already, you two!
Anyway, I'm worried about my big brother and the others.
Well...
They're probably Dueling someone...
If you can beat us,
we'll let you leave this Virtual Space.
But if you to refuse our challenge...
unfortunately for you people, we will not permit you to return.
The Big Five...
If there's five of them...
They may not just be after Duelists like Yugi-kun and the guys,
but there's a good chance they'll try and Duel us as well.
Otogi!
But we'll be fine
if we stick by Honda-san!
Huh? Why?
Because Honda-san taught my big brother how to Duel!
I didn't know you Dueled as we-
Without a doubt, if those guys come and try an' Duel us,
I'll school em in a second flat!
If Yugi, Jounouchi and I all beat one of the Big Five, only two remain.
I'm sure Kaiba-kun will be fine...
...but if they go after the others...
Damn it!
Jounouchi-kun!
Wait up!
What's...
...this?
What the heck is this thing?
It looks like... a door.
Well, it certainly looks like one...
But it's awfully suspicious.
We'd better be careful.
But it could be an exit.
-Shizuka-chan!
-Don't!
Did we return
to that mobile fortress?
No, I don't see
the Battle Ship anywhere.
If you look closer,
it's another room altogether.
But it must mean we've at least escaped the Virtual Space...
Yeah, maybe the others
got out already?
Thank goodness!
I've been awaiting you!
So we... didn't escape?
By the looks on your faces, you probably thought you had escaped.
I am a member of the Big Five, known as Soichiro Ota!
Looking like that...
What the hell do you want?!
I am simply taking the form of a robot known as Machine Sergent.
Before that annoying Seto Kaiba took over the company,
I was the renowned President of Military Affairs for Kaiba Corporation!
They called me "Demon Warlord of the Factory"!
Now, shall we begin our Duel?
Now then, my opponent shall be the first one to have entered this room.
You!
Me?
What should I do, Honda-san?
Wait, let me be your opponent!
It's rude to force a woman to be your opponent!
No, let me do it!
You've never had a real Duel in your life, have you?
This isn't the time to try and act cool in front of Shizuka-chan!
Well, if I don't do it now, when the hell will I get to?
Trying to protect her, eh?
How utterly pointless!
Regardless of who becomes my opponent, none of you stand a chance of beating me!
Dammit...
He sure is overconfident...
The pain felt in this world is about the same as the Real World.
If I don't step in, they'll take the damage in this Duel as if it were real life injuries.
No matter what he says, I can't let Shizuka-chan Duel him!
I won't let Shizuka-chan
take part in this Duel!
Then tell me what
you think about this.
Of what?
The two of us will take you on.
That'll give you a shot at two bodies.
In that case, I'll take the liberty of raising the stakes for a much more entertaining Duel.
How about the
three of you Duel against me?
What?
I'll be alone on my side,
while your side has three.
In return, I'll be taking the bodies of all three of you if your side loses.
The two of us should be just fine!
Unfortunately for you,
the situation has changed slightly.
We require all three of your bodies.
Then Yugi and the others...
They won!
Weaklings like you
should stick together.
You should really be thanking me.
Bastard! How dare you say that!
You don't know, do you?!
Honda-san taught my
big brother how to Duel!
Shizuka-chan!
Honda-san, Otogi-san, I'll do my best!
"Your best"...?
No way are we gonna let you Duel!
You need some Duel Disks!
Awesome!
Shizuka-chan, you had better forget about this...
It'll be fine!
After all, you'll be with me!
Shizuka-chan...
This isn't good at all...!
Now build your deck!
Simply touch the cards you desire.
Let's see...
Honda-san!
First choose a total of 40 cards.
You can't just choose a bunch of strong Monsters.
You have to pick them in combination with Magic and Trap Cards, got it?
Yes!
Okay... This one...
And this one...
This looks like a warrior
suited for a woman.
These cards...
When your done choosing your cards, pick one to act as your Deck Master.
I'll be using Swift Black Ninja as my Deck Master!
I'll.... um...
...choose Goddess of
the Mind's Eye-sama!
You don't need the
"-sama" honorific!
I'll choose Rate Metal Knight!
Looks like all is set.
Then let us begin!
What the?!
There are a set of specific rules I will be strictly enforcing.
You are free to
aid each other in attacking,
but you are forbidden with discussing your strategies with each other.
You will each take your turns one after the other, followed by me.
I take it you are fine with the "ladies first" policy?
Honda-san, you set the deck in the Duel Disk, right?
Yeah, that's right, Shizuka-chan.
Duel start!!
You can do it, Shizuka-chan!
My turn!
Draw!
Umm... Let's see...
This one!
Demon Tamer.
She's a cool hands-on-fighter like the kind my brother uses.
I Summon Demon Tamer in Attack Position!
Attack Position, you said?!
Did I mess up or something?
If it goes like this, he'll attack her.
Honda-san!
This is alright... isn't it?
Of course it's alright!
I'll do something about it!
Like hell this is "alright"!
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
I can't let him go after Shizuka-chan!
I Summon Commander
in Attack Position!
Now he'll go after me instead...
Turn end!
Honda-kun used Attack Mode on purpose to try and lure him from attacking Shizuka-chan...
My turn! Draw!
Come on, Otogi...
Play some weakling in Attack Mode!
That way there's a 2-1 chance of him not attacking Shizuka-chan!
Come forth, The 13th Buried!
Defense Position!
Otogi! You jerk!
So you mean to abandon Shizuka-chan?
Turn end!
Very well. My turn.
Draw.
I Summon Giga-Tech Wolf!
Attack the Demon Tamer!
Bastard! You were aiming for Shizuka-chan from the very start!
And the force from the attack will assault the player!
-Shizuka-chan!
That was Shizuka screaming just now!
Yeah...
You think it was the Big Five...?
Shizuka...
Shizuka...!
Shizuka!!
-Shizuka-chan!
Shizuka-chan...!
Don't move!
What?!
You are forbidden to leave your side of the field during a Duel!
What the hell's with you?!
I'm alright...!
Shizuka-chan...!
The damage in this Duel...
So it really is felt as real pain!
I can't let Shizuka-chan
be damaged anymore!
My turn's far from done!
What?!
I activate my Deck Master Ability, Support Bombardment!!
I discard three Machine-Type Monsters from my hand!
In order to inflict 500 points of damage to each and every one of you!
Shizuka-chan!
I'll then place a set card
and end my turn.
You okay, Shizuka-chan?!
Yes!
My turn!
I should play it in
Defense Mode... This one...
Nice! You're getting the hang of this, Shizuka-chan!
Right!
I will Summon the Merciful Nun!
Attack Position again!
I get it! She must have set in on the Duel Disk wrong!
Shizuka-chan, when playing Defense Mode, you have to set it on the Duel Disk in horizontal position!
Don't help her any more than that!
Bastard! Let her do it over!
You are forbidden to change the position of your card until your next turn!
Turn end.
This is bad...!
If he uses that
Final Artillery Attack again...
I have to do something...
My turn! Draw!
Attack Seal, huh?
Good. This is nice.
Using this Magic Card, I can switch Shizuka-chan's Monster to Defense Mode!
I activate Attack Seal from my hand!
I won't let you!
Trap Card, open!
Force Field!
It will seal away Attack Seal!
Shit...!
I couldn't do anything...!
Turn end!
Big brother, that's...!
That's the Kaiba Corporation factory I had destroyed!
The military factory...
Ota, I would like for you to show your obedience.
Sir?
Destroy the
military base at Alcatraz.
Wh-What did you say?!
The factory?!
I've put my entire life into running that factory!
And you're telling me
to destroy my factory?!
No, my factory.
Cursed Noah...
Just how far
do you intend to mock me?
Just how many visions are you going to show me?
It's at the point where I'm no longer feeling anything from them.
Stop wasting your time already!
How about you
just come before me already?!
One who moves based on emotions alone is nothing but a puppet controlled by their own mind.
Seto, I'm simply playing around with you in order to prove this.
My turn. Draw!
If I don't raise our
attack force considerably...
Otogi, forget about a way to counterattack and play a card to protect Shizuka-chan!
Yaranzo in Defense Position!
Otogi! How could you?!
That's not gonna protect Shizuka-chan!
I place a card face-down
and end my turn!
My turn!
I sacrifice Giga-Tech Wolf!
To Summon Machine King!
Machine King's Special Ability increases its Attack Power by 100 points for every Machine-Type Monster on the field!
Meaning the Commander as well as itself being Machine-based Monsters on the field,
his Attack Power goes up
by 100 points!
And on to battle!
Machine King, attack the Merciful Nun!
Go, Commander!
Honda-kun, wait! I'll-
I'll protect Shizuka-chan!
Honda-san!
If I used my Defense Monster, none of us would've been damaged!
Really?
Tell me sooner!
That's Dueling common sense, isn't it?!
I'll then activate Treasure from Heaven from my hand!
All players must draw from their decks until they hold six cards in their hands!
Now then, I've gathered the materials I needed to launch another attack.
He's still...
...got another attack left?
Using my Deck Master Ability, I discard three Machine-type Monsters from my hand.
Support Bombardment!!
I'll then place a card face-down on the board and end my turn.
My turn.
Draw!
Let's see...
I Summon Lady Panther
in Defense Position!
Moreover, I'll switch Merciful Nun to Defense Mode as well!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Command Angel
in Defense Position!
My turn!
I Summon Dark Assassin
in Defense Position!
What's wrong?
Declare "turn end" already!
Now that we've
got enough Wall Monsters,
you can't attack us anymore!
And you can't use your Deck Master Ability unless you have a hand, right?!
So you can't use Support Bombardment anymore, am I right?!
That's right, Otogi.
So this is what
you were planning for!
And now that we've got this many Monsters on the field,
we can sacrifice them to Summon High-Level Monsters!
How naive!
I still have a Trap Card on the field!
What?!
Trap Card, activate!
Backup Soldiers!!
Backup Soldiers, you said?!
When I hold five or more Monster Cards in my Graveyard,
this card allows me to add up to three Monster Cards with 1500 Attack Points or less to my hand!
And I'll revive Giga-Tech Wolf, Mecha Falcon and Ground Attacker Robot!
Now then, I'll take the three I just got back from the Graveyard and discard them there once more.
I activate my Deck Master Ability, Support Bombardment!!
You brought them back just to discard them again?!
Bestow upon them
the Support Bombardment!!
Turn end!
My turn.
I've been waiting for this!
I activate the Continuous Magic, Clockwork Knight, from my hand!
It transforms every Monster on the field into a Machine!
What'd you say?!
Turn them all into Machines?
This will increase my Monsters' Attack Power greatly!
And in reverse, your Monsters all have their Attack Power decreased!
And thanks to Machine King's Special Ability, it gains 100 Attack Points for every Machine Monster on the field, its Attack Power goes up!
And because of Clockwork Knight's effect, its Attack goes up even further by 500 points!
3400?!
Don't worry!
Regardless of how strong his Monsters are, they can only attack one at a time!
And if we leave them in Defense Mode, we won't take any damage!
Well now, we'll see about that.
I activate the Instant Quick-Play Magic from my hand, Leakage!
O-Oi!
They're all switching
into Attack Mode?!
This card forces all Monsters on the field into Attack Mode.
And for one turn, all your Monsters are unable to attack, or activate Flip and Special Abilities!
That's not even possible!
If he attacks us now,
we don't stand a chance!
None of your Monsters can even move!
Machine King, attack the Merciful Nun!
This time you can do nothing to protect this young lady!!
Shit! What'll we do?!
If we can somehow Summon a Monster not affected by any of this...
We do have one...!
Fire!!
Go, Rare Metal Knight!
Wait, Honda-kun!
If your Deck Master is beaten, you'll...!
His Deck Master Ability allows me to cover a card!
And Rare Metal Knight's
Attack Power goes up!
YOU REALLY THINK THAT EFFECT WILL BE ENOUGH!?
Honda-kun!
I just used the
best trick I had up my sleeve...
I'm sorry, Shizuka-chan...
When I said I taught Jounouchi how to Duel... I was lying...
As you can see,
I'm just an amateur...
Otogi, I'm leaving Shizuka-chan to you!
Because you lost your Deck Master, it's game over for you!
Honda-san!
Honda-san!!
NO!!
Honda-kun...!
One down!
Turn end.
No way! It has to be a lie that Honda lost to the Big Five!
In shock, Shizuka-chan
becomes unresponsive.
But once a Duel starts,
no one can stop it!
If things keep going this way, Shizuka-chan and Otogi-kun will lose as well!
Stand up, Shizuka-chan!
If you don't want Honda's sacrifice to be in vain, you've got to stand up and fight!
Next time!
"Saint Jeanue: The Trinity Attack"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise