With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Cut through the Darkness! Sealing Swords of Light
Bastard... what did you set?
Can it be another trap card?
You still don't see?
It's not me that will go to the darkness of hell..
It's you with your hostility!
Impossible.
- What you are saying is...
- It's not a lie!
In this darkness, each turn that passes the flame will increase...
and take you down.
Four turns left.
W-What are you saying?
The so-called "darkness" will be swallowed by a mirror of evil.
People with weak hearts will be consumed.
Brat! Do you know of your situation?!
It's your turn!
Now... draw a card!
Yugi... he's using words to battle with his opponent?
Mai... is that really his trump card?
Yeah.
In the darkness the Player Killer has the advantage.
But Yugi's words are now distracting him.
Good job, Yugi.
What's the problem? Can't you even draw a card?
You brat...
I've drawn my ultimate card!
Appear! Supreme King of the Dark Realm!
He's my trump card!
Unfortunately before you play your trump card it will be destroyed!
Yugi!
Supreme King of the Dark Realm! Destroy his Curse of Dragon!
Evil Shock Wave!
What?
Card-Hunting Reaper is destroyed!
- All right!
- Yugi, you did it!
What is that?... Damn Yugi...
To force me to attack, he used the Hexagram Curse's card
He was prepared even for this?
What a pity. My monster here is intact.
My turn.
I'll now use my trump card!
Let's go! Sealing Swords of Light!
Stop it!
Yeah! Now we can see the enemy!
The darkness was dissipated...
Damn...
Three turns left!
You're finished!
But that's not all...
Because of the Sealing Swords of Light, your monsters now for three turns...
are all sealed.
In other words... your attacks are sealed.
This is bad...
Yugi will attack my monster in the next turn...
But the only card he has on the field is one Curse of Dragon.
On my side on the field I have three monsters...
Barox, Dark Chimera, Supreme King of the Dark Realm!
Although the Sealing Swords of Light is in effect,
the darkness field power source won't disappear...
With only the Curse of Dragon, even if,
for example, Barox is defeated, it won't change anything!
It's your turn! Hurry and draw a card!
But.. what if...
...he uses a more powerful monster to attack me in the next turn? If that's the case...
I just drew a good card!
Yugi! Your plan to defeat me in three turns is over!
The Chaos Shield card!
That card puts all your monsters in defense mode...
And increase its defense through an impenetrable shield!
And I will use the Castle of Concealing Darkness
together with the Chaos Shield, activating a combo!
This is terrible!
He is using the castle in the air to make the shield cover
all his monsters below and increase all of their defense power!
Damn!
No way!
This isn't your ordinary enemy.
Combo complete!
I got it.
With this all of his monsters have more defense points than normal...
With this Chaos Shield, the attack of your monsters are useless!
Do you still think that you can beat me in three turns?
What do you say, brat?
When the darkness was dissipated and we thought that the enemy was down,
he got an amazing defense power...
The Player Killer of Darkness fought perfectly protecting himself...
Yeah.
And on the other hand, Yugi-kun has his offensive strategies,
but the enemy's defense is too high.
He can't just attack...
Hey, there isn't a way?
This wouldn't help him!
This strong defense... how will you break it... Yugi?
Now.. it's your turn!
You didn't realize...
...that you have exposed your weakness?
W-What weakness? Stop saying things that make no sense!
Really?
What are you saying?
Since this duel started...
I have been analyzing your strategy!
So what?
I said in the beginning...
that you were an incurable coward.
That is now proven.
Shut up!
I've already told you! I'm not a coward!
No! You are really a great coward!
I AM NOT A COWARD!!
Hey!
Don't forget...
Now you only have two turns left.
I'll tell you one thing...
I had already calculated that you would use some kind of shield...
Since the start...
Don't joke around! Do you want to feel the fire again?
Yugi, stop it!
Don't provoke him anymore!
Calm down....
Yugi is using his words as a weapon to get out of this pinch.
Believe in him.
You're just bluffing and spouting bullshit!
It's not a bluff...
You don't do anything if you're not sure that you are in a safe place.
So I could imagine that I would be dealing with a coward that hides behind a shield.
Called me coward again?
If you don't want me to say that... then defeat me!
You just have two turns left...
What will you do then? Will you continue? Will you not continue?
You sure talk a lot, brat!
Very well...
You will be toasted to death when this duel is finished!
He escaped that pinch for now...
...but the duel starts now.
Let's go! My turn!
It's here! Dark Knight Gaia!
Idiot! Do you think that with his attack points you can destroy my fortress?
Also I activate my magic card that was set!
What?
And the card is...
The Fusion card!
Dragon Knight Gaia! Attack Mode!
Dragon Knight Gaia?
I end my turn....
With this you are finished!
Impossible! I will lose? In this situation?
Dragon Knight Gaia's attack can do nothing against my Chaos Shield
that is protecting my monsters against all attacks.
He really is bluffing...
What is that smile?
But if I can get past the next attack,
in my turn the Sealing Swords of Light will disappear...
Then I will deactivate the Chaos Shield and his monsters will be destroyed, with my victory.
But to be safe...
My turn!
My card is Metal Guardian!
I put him in defense mode to protect my monster army,
and he receives a field source power up!
This is perfect! My monsters are now 100% protected against any attack!
I knew it... What a fool...
What did you say?
You only thought of how to protect yourself... You're too weak!
Bullshit!
After the Sealing Swords of Light disappear in the next turn,
I'll be invincible and will crush you!
It's too late.
You are already caught in my trap.
What?
The more you try to protect yourself, the more you can't escape!
Don't joke around! I'm warning you!
Is that really it?
Now... it's the last turn!
This is the end!
My card is... Catapult Turtle!
And also...
I'll put the Dragon Knight Gaia on the Catapult!
The Dragon Knight Gaia's attack...
will increase to 3200 due to the catapult's speed.
That's its strength!
It's useless...
My monsters are all protected by the Metal Guardian.
If I survive this turn, the darkness will once again seal your attacks!
Who said that I would attack your monsters?
My target is...
The castle!
Idiot!
The defense of the Castle is 3200
and the Dragon Knight Gaia's attack is the same 3200,
so the battle's damage will be nothing!
Now... let's shoot it!
Go! Dragon Knight Gaia!
Oh? Yugi's Life Points have...
He used it all in a suicide strategy...
Bakura! Don't be so calm!
And what will he do if this attack didn't destroy the castle?
Yugi...
Ah... it's still floating!
All you did was talk! What did you mean by "shoot it"?!
Your useless attack did nothing but destroy the floating ring of the castle.
Brat... You have too much pride of yourself!
Now... I'll put all my monsters in attack mode...
In the next turn I'll attack with all of them!
This is the end of this duel.
You don't have a next turn...
What did you say?
It's mysterious, isn't it?
If the floating ring was destroyed... why is the castle still floating?
The Sealing Swords of Light caught not only the monsters but the castle as well...
It can't be...
That's right!
Now that castle has been held by the effect of the Sealing Swords of Light...
When this turn ends... what do you think will happen?
I-Is that really it?
Yeah.
When the effect of the Sealing Swords of Light disappear, the castle will...
Wait!
Turn end!
Run! My monsters!
It's useless... Due to the Chaos Shield, they can't escape!
He did it!
It's Yugi's victory!
Amazing!
I.. I lost? Impossible...
It doesn't matter how the duel ended!
Brat! Go to hell!
What?
That's bad!
Yugi can't move!
This is punishment for making fun of me! Fire!!
- Yugi!
- Yugi-kun!
What?
I'll show you the true power of darkness!
S-Stop it!
Yugi... it's good that you are ok.
But what was that light before?
Maybe because of the fire the 3D virtual system had a problem?
Yugi... You did a good job.
Mai...
These chips are yours.
What is it? Take them!
Mai-san?
I can't take these Star chips... I have to leave the island.
Mai-san... you said that, didn't you? That to duel with Yugi was your dream?
That's...
Man! It won't change anything being here talking.
If you don't want them, then I'll keep them all.
Wait a minute! That's unforgivable!
But you don't want them, right?
Give them back!
Here they are!
Jounouchi...
If your pride won't let you fight with these Star chips...
You can just throw them in the sea.
That's your decision to make.
But if it was me I wouldn't. Neither the Stars nor the dream.
Now then... let's sleep!
As always all you say is shit!
Shut up!
Now.. now..
Yugi!
I'll borrow these Star chips...
As I'm in debt... I don't have the right to fight with you.
But.. when I get that right...
When that happens... I'll challenge you!
Fair and square!
Mai-san...
I'll be waiting...
Ah... Who can it be?
Landing a helicopter on the island in the middle of the night?
Ah? Kaiba-kun?
Jounouchi challenges Kaiba-kun who came to confront Pegasus...
It's a good way to test the Duel Disks?
Don't lose, Jounouchi! Show us how much you improved since you got to this island!
Next episode: Clash! Blue Eyes vs. Red Eyes
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship