Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Just you wait, Honda!
I'll get your body back really soon!
These Big Five creeps keep attacking us with different Deck Masters,
But me and Yugi working as a team makes us invincible!
But now that we've backed him into a corner,
how can he be laughing?
"Beat It! The Five God Dragon"
I've been waiting for this moment!
For the third turn of which Altar of Mists was activated!
What?!
We've just won this Duel!
I activate the Effect of Altar of Mists!
I add Dragon Revival Ritual from my deck to my hand!
Dragon Revival Ritual is the necessary Ritual Magic Card used to Summon Five God Dragon.
What did you just say?!
However, you must also sacrifice five Monster Cards consisting of the Earth, Water, Fire, Wind and Darkness Attributes.
There's no way you'd conveniently have all five of those Monster Attributes on hand at once!
I see you still haven't realized.
Take a close look behind me!
Behind you, you said...?
Psycho Shocker!
I get it!
Their Deck Masters!
If I remember right, Judge Man was an Earth-Attribute!
Deepsea Warrior was a Water-Attribute!
I'm pretty sure the Machine Sergeant was a Fire-Attribute.
Penguin Nightmare was
a Wind-Attribute!
So then Psycho Shocker...|N is a Dark-Attribute?!
You're all right!
So here goes!
I Summon my Deck Master!
Android - Psycho Shocker!!
Deepsea Warrior!!
I Summon my Deck Master!
Penguin Nightmare!!
Judge Man!!
I Summon my Deck Master!
Machine Sergeant!!
I activate Dragon Revival Ritual!
I will now polymerize our Deck Masters consisting of Earth, Water, Fire, Wind and Darkness Attributes!
I then Summon the Five God Dragon!!
The Five God Dragon!
Shit...! This thing caused us and Mai so many problems...!
It's up to you...
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!!
This thing's gonna
mop the floor with us!
This Monster cannot attack on the turn it's Summoned.
What the heck?
Don't scare me like that.
But it does have the Effect
to destroy every Monster, Magic and Trap Card on the opponent's side of the field on the turn it's Summoned!
That's low! Stop trying to throw our guard off!
I must apologize for that.
To make up for it, let me give you a little forewarning.
Monsters of the Earth, Water, Fire, Wind and Darkness Attributes cannot damage the Five God Dragon!
Then that means almost all Monsters' attacks won't work on it?!
There's not a single soul who can defeat the Five God Dragon, the very unity of ourselves!
However, we learned the hard way in our previous battle.
As such, we're taking every needed precaution in this match.
I place a set card!
Turn over!
What's the matter, Jounouchi?
It's your turn, you know!
This ain't about what's wrong...
How the hell do we beat a Monster with 5000 Attack Points?
Huh, Yugi?
Just do your best, Jounouchi-kun!
A chance will come sooner of later!
Yeah, you're right.
Heh, I better pull myself together.
I can't rely on Yugi all the time.
My turn!
Draw!
I don't have a Monster to Summon...
But I'll do what I have to do
until the very end!
I'll place three reverse cards face-down on the field!
I'm counting on you, my Deck Master!
I Summon my Deck Master,
Flame Swordsman!
Jounouchi! You'll lose if your Deck Master is beaten!
And if you lose, you'll end up looking like me, ooh~!
Big brother!
I just did everything I could.
Looks like I'll be relying on you in the end after all...
I guess all I can do is leave this to Yugi...
Turn over!
Let me handle this, Jounouchi-kun.
We've still got a way to win.
My turn, draw!
I Summon my Deck Master!
Black Magician!
Not just Jounouchi, but even Yugi Summoned his Deck Master?!
What in the world
are those two thinking?!
But if they don't have any Monsters on the field,
they'd just get Direct Attacked, and Yugi and Jounouchi would be done for, ooh-ah~!!
There's no method in existence that can beat the Five God Dragon!
How about you spare your dignity and just surrender now before you lost miserably?
Yugi...
Only shame awaits those who talk big without the efficiency to back up their words.
What did you say?!
It's not like you guys are the only ones who can fuse their Deck Masters!
What?!
Fuse?!
D-Don't tell me he's about to play Master of Dragon Knight again!
No! He shouldn't be able to play Master of Dragon Knight without the Blue-Eyes!
I fuse our Deck Masters together!
Black Magician and Flame Swordsman!
As a result, I Fusion Summon the knight of black fire, Black Flare Knight!
B-Black Flare Knight, you said?!
This card is able to attack on the same turn it is polymerized!
Then go ahead and try your luck!
That Monster is a Dark-Attribute.
I'm sure I told you they don't work on the Five God Dragon!
That aside, you actually plan to attack a 5000 Attack Power Monster with a Monster only holding 2200 Attack Points?
You bet I am!
What was that?!
Wouldn't that mean he'd be killing himself for nothing?!
It's suicidal!
No, Yugi-kun's got this right!
I know he's planning something!
I don't really get what he's hoping to accomplish...
But I trust Yugi!
I use the knight of black fire, Black Flare Knight, to attack the Five God Dragon!
Have you lost your mind, Yugi?
Why?! Why hasn't your Life changed?!
Regardless of how many Attack Points a Monster has that's attacked by this card,
even if that Attack happens to be higher than its own,
the player will not receive any damage!
It's all a part of the knight of black fire's, Black Flare Knight's, Special Effect!
What?!
And that's not all.
The moment this card is destroyed,
I can Special Summon Illusion Knight - Mirage Knight from my hand or deck!
And so what if you can?
Even if slightly higher, this Monster still hardly holds enough Attack Power to scrap the Five God Dragon's foot!
Unless this is also
a Special Effect Monster?!
Illusion Knight - Mirage Knight, attack Five God Dragon!
The Illusion Knight cannot be destroyed in battle!
And during Damage Calculation, the Attack Power of the Monster being attacked is added to its own!
Meaning the 5000 Attack Points of the one being attacked, Five God Dragon, will be added to the Illusion Knight's own!
I-Impossible! 7800 Attack Points?!
And let me give you some last bit of information.
Illusion Knight - Mirage Knight is a Light-Attribute!
The only Monsters that can successfully attack the Five God Dragon are creatures of light!
From darkness to light!
I've been waiting for this moment!
We beat the Five God Dragon!
That means the 2800 points in difference will be subtracted from your Life Points!
Your Life is now at zero!
We've just won this Duel!
What?! Why didn't your
Life Points drop to 0?!
What the hell is the deal?
Did you cheat again somehow?!
It seems my strategy was one step ahead of yours.
Take a nice, long look at my field!
What!?
Bargaining with Demons!
Correct.
It's a Trap Card that can only be activated when a Level 8 or higher Monster on my side of the field is destroyed!
This Trap negates all damage I received to 0 at the cost of half of my Life Points.
So that's why your Life Points didn't drop to zero?
And that's not all.
When this Trap is activated, I can Summon Berserk Dead Dragon!
Huh? The Illusion Knight
returned to normal.
Once the Battle Phase ends, the Illusion Knight is destroyed, and Black Magician and Flame Swordsman are Special Summoned.
Oh no! Once that Big Five guy takes his next turn,
Yugi-kun's and Jounouchi-kun's Deck Masters will be wiped out!
Does that mean they'll lose, ooh-ah?!
That can't be!
Please! Keep trying, big brother!
Say "keep trying" all you want...
It's Yugi's turn right now, ya know!
We're countin' on you, Yugi!
I activate the Magic Card, Magical Silk Hats!
Also, my Deck Master Ability!
Separate Magic!!
By paying 1000 Life Points, I am permitted to use the Effects of the Magic Card, Magical Silk Hats, once again!
Turn over!
Nice one, Yugi!
Now we've at least got a chance.
No, we've just delayed the inevitable.
We can't relax just yet.
Heh, relax! We're fine!
He can't handle this!
I get that feeling way
more than you think.
But reality often steals away the last bit of hope we hold dear.
My turn! Draw!
Let me explain.
Berserk Dead Dragon holds a Special Ability that allows it to attack four Monsters every time it attacks.
E-Every time it attacks?
Four Monsters?!
Yugi has the Black Magician hidden under four Magical Silk Hats on his side.
And Jounouchi-kun has the Flame Swordsman hidden on his!
So if he attacks either Yugi or Jounouchi, who both have four hats on the field...
It's a 100% failure rate!
That means...
On this turn, either Jounouchi-kun or myself will be defeated.
No! We still don't know that!
What the hell are you talking about?!
Are you an idiot?!
He's always sucked at math, ooh-ah~!
Then allow me to show you first hand!
No, after your friend's loss, that is.
I use Berserk Dragon to attack all four of Yugi Mutou's silk hats at once!
Is this the end...?
Don't give up, Yugi!
Flame Swordsman!
Protect Black Magician! Protect Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
That's way too reckless, Jounouchi-kun!
If he does that, Jounouchi will lose!
Don't do it, big brother!
Let me be the monkey, OOH~!!
Jounouchi-kun!
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Big brother!
How?!
Impossible!
Huh...?
Why?!
Why is the Flame Swordsman still alive?!
Because this thing saved my butt!
One Dollar Silver Coin...?!
That's right! This activates only when I receive battle damage after you attack a Monster with 1000 or less Attack Points!
This Trap Card makes
all the damage invalid!
1000 Attack Points...?
Now I get it!
Flame Swordsman has 1800 Attack Points.
But you reduced his Attack Power by 1000 points in order to use his Deck Master Ability!
That's why your Trap was activated!
Great job thinking so far ahead like that, Jounouchi-kun!
Now we're even!
Now what're ya gonna do, Big Five guy?!
Damn it all! Just how much are you gonna piss me off?!
My turn's over!!
Huh? Its Attack Power dropped.
Berserk Dead Dragon's Attack Power drops by 500 points at the end of your turn!
Oh wow! That sucks for you, man!
My turn!
Draw!
Magic Card, open!
I activate Knight's Title!
This automatically turns Yugi's Black Magician into a Warrior-Type!
And now for Flame Swordsman's Deck Master Ability!
I transfer 700 of its Attack Points!
He's got 3200 Attack Points!
So he's stronger
than Berserk Dead Dragon?!
That's all I can do for you.
The rest is up to you, Yugi!
Okay!
Turn over!
Thanks, Jounouchi-kun! I couldn't have won this Duel without you!
Hey! What's the meaning of this, Ouka?!
I thought you said Jounouchi would hold him back!
Isn't he making Yugi more powerful?!
T-This wasn't supposed to...!
It's my last turn!
Draw!
Here goes! I use the Warrior of Black Magic - Black Magician's Knight, to attack Berserk Dead Dragon!
Berserk Dead Dragon is beaten!
Big Five! Your Deck Master was destroyed!
That means we've won this Duel!!
We lost...!
They did it! Yugi and Jounouchi won!
You did great, big brother!
Honda-kun! Now you can get your body back!
Thank you, Yugi!
Thank you, Jounouchi!
Now return Honda-kun's body just as you promised.
If this is the case, we'll be taking your bodies by force!!
That's not fair, you jerks!
What's the meaning of this?
You're really sad, Big Five!
Noah-sama!
Your job here is done.
They disappeared...!
That's so cruel...! After they won the Duel, too...!
N-No way, ooh...
I'll never look like a human being again, ooh-ah~!!
Is this the end for me, ooh-ah, OOH-AH~!?
I'm so sorry, Honda-san...
That may not be so bad after all, ooh~
Noah-sama!
I can't stand looking at losers.
Don't you agree, Mokuba?
Losers will never win, regardless of what they do!
Honda's body is gone!
That can't be! When did it happen?!
Noah-sama, just once more!
Please just grant us one more chance!
We just want a real human body, no matter what it takes!
We beg of you, Noah-sama!
Just give us one more chance!
Did you fools really believe you'd get real bodies if you won that Duel back there?
What did you say just now...?
Let me put it another way...
There's not a real thing here in this Virtual World!
I can't believe it!
-YOU DECEIVED US!!
-HOW DARE YOU, NOAH!?
SCREW YOU TO HELL!!
It's because you guys
were to stupid to realize!
Even though we defeated the Big Five, we're still trapped inside this Virtual Space!
In this case, we've got no other choice but to go talk to Noah directly.
Kaiba-kun has already started to fight against Noah!
Noah explains the secrets behind his Creation of Heaven and Earth Deck.
And how Noah is related to Kaiba-kun...!
Next time!
"Noah VS Seto: Duel of the Creation of Heaven and Earth"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise