Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
My turn.
I use Swordsman of Landstar as a sacrifice to summon Android Psycho Shocker!
Come and attack.
At that time I'll use a trap to deal with you.
Trap Crush!!
What?!
That's too bad.
My Psycho Shocker
Can destroy all the Trap Cards on the field.
"The Courageous Bet:
Spinning Roulette Spider"
This is bad.
Psycho Shocker has an Attack Strength of 2400.
My monster's Attack Strength is only 1500.
If he attacks me my Life will decrease by 900.
I can get you soon.
Next I'll use this.
Equip Card "Amplifier"
I equip this on Psycho Shocker.
Psycho Shocker's Attack gains another 500 points.
Also, his attack increases by 300 points every turn.
What?
Psycho Shocker, attack.
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Shit.
Defense increases Attack; my basic points therefore decrease.
Yipee!!
You did it!
Well done, Big bro.
Amazing!
I just know my brother is great.
Wonderful, amazing.
Amazing.
Shit, what should I do now?
Jounouchi-kun, it's your turn.
You can always surrender.
Surrender? Are you kidding?
I will definitely continue.
It's my turn.
Please give me a card to turn the table.
Baby Dragon.
Alright, I'll use this guy.
You don't even have any super powers.
No matter what card you draw,
You can't defeat my Psycho Shocker.
In my next turn you are finished.
How 'bout this?
Summon Baby Dragon.
Baby Dragon?!
It's useless to use this monster Jounouchi.
I thought you had a better idea, but it's just a Baby Dragon.
It can't defeat my Psycho Shocker.
You are right.
But my turn is not over yet.
Time Magician.
What?
So you plan to make your Baby Dragon
grow into Thousand Dragon to increase his Attack.
But my monster still has a better Attack Strength.
Time Magician can do more.
Through thousands of years,
Your android will become nothing but rotten iron.
Here I go!
Time Roulette!
Got it.
Alright!
Time Magic!
Baby Dragon changes to Thousand Dragon.
Your Psycho Shocker will be destroyed by a
thousand's year time and become nothing but scrap.
Nothing changed.
What's wrong?
It is not working at all.
My Psycho Shocker's body is protected.
It won't get rotten even after thousands of years.
It is incredible.
It's over.
Don't give up, Jounouchi-kun.
Psycho Shocker, attack his Thousand Dragon!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Thousand Dragon is defeated.
Shit, it is too close.
Honda-san...
How's Big brother?
You said Big brother is going to win right.
Yes.
He was attacked a little.
Did he lose?
No.
He will win in the next turn.
Thank goodness. I know this battle
is very important to Big brother.
Honda-san...
It's time to rest.
I'll come here later.
I am sorry.
See you later.
Suck it up, Jounouchi.
Shizuka-chan is cheering for you.
Thank goodness. You seem to be getting better.
By the way, nurse.
What's wrong?
Can you check the duel to see who is winning?
Guess who?
Grandpa!.
Hey, be careful.
You scared me.
Hello?
Ahh, Honda.
Are you with Jounouchi?
Am I supposed to be with Jounouchi?
Can you leave him a message for me?
You have only one hand card,
what else can you do now?
You are about to lose, Jounouchi-kun.
Won't you give up?
I am sorry, Roba.
I never give up that easily.
Magic Card, Scapegoat.
You use Scapegoat to protect you?
You are only wasting your time.
Don't struggle.
Give up now, won't you?
Jounouchi-kun.
Roba is right. Give up, you are already lost.
There is nothing you can do, Jounouchi.
I end my turn.
C'mon!
Good decision, Jounouchi-kun.
Don't give up until the last moment.
If there is the will, then there is hope.
Everything is okay.
Good.
Please come in.
Let's see Jounouchi's condition.
Don't miss the moment of victory.
It's okay.
Thank you, Honda-san.
But, you don't need to comfort me.
The nurse told me the truth.
Big brother is losing, right?
I'm sorry, I didn't want you
to get you worried, Shizuka-chan.
Yes, I know.
But I want to know the truth.
Big brother is playing hard.
I want to support him, too.
When I hesitated about the operation,
Big brother's encouragement gave me strength.
It's my turn to support him.
Though I can't do much, I can at least be with Big brother in spirit.
Shizuka-chan.
But I appreciate your kindness, Honda-san.
Thank you.
Y...Alright, let us both cheer for Jounouchi.
Yes.
It's OK if you don't give up.
You just need to wait for your failure.
It's my turn.
I Summon Reflect Bounder.
Reflect Bounder's special ability is that
It can rebound monster's attacks.
Which means, Jounouchi, even if you Summon a monster, I can still strike you back.
Damn you.
Plus, Psycho Shocker's Attack gains another 300 points.
Do you understand?
You have no chance to turn the table.
What is waiting for you is failure.
Prepare yourself! Now I will attack another of your monsters!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Also!
Great Wicked Light Beam!!
Two Scapegoats are destroyed.
Now you have only two Scapegoats.
I only have to Summon a monster on my next turn,
And let the three monsters attack together.
I can defeat you.
I hate this, but he is right.
I am bound to win.
It's useless to struggle more.
Just surrender now.
Damn it!
Jounouchi-kun...
You shall lose to me, Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi, I am sorry.
I may not be able to keep my promise.
Shizuka-chan is watching you.
Jounouchi!
Anzu...
Honda called, they are watching your duel through the Internet.
Honda and Shizuka-chan are cheering for you.
Honda...
You must work hard, Jounouchi.
Shizuka...
You cheer for me even when in the hospital.
It's now your Big brother's turn.
Just wait, I will not lose.
What are you doing? Hurry up and surrender!
Are you kidding?
What?
He's alright.
Look at his eyes.
Jounouchi's eyes are burning with high morale.
Thanks to Shizuka...
...My last card is...
This is my last chance, I will use it now!
Jounouchi-kun, believe in your card.
Here I go! It's my turn now.
It's here!
Magic Card, Roulette Spider.
Wh...What?
Roulette Spider, This Magic Card is my last card.
By putting this card on the field,
my Life Points will decrease by half.
It doesn't matter to me.
What is he trying to do?
Roulette Spider will cover the strongest
monster on the field and begin to spin.
When it stops, it will attack the target that it has pointed to.
What is he talking about?
It's just like a game of roulette.
The targets on the roulette board
include any monsters on the field.
If it is pointed at the player's own monsters, it will be attacked too.
In the end, you have to stop the roulette.
Psychic bastard.
What?
What card is he using?
First dice rolling cards, then Time Magician, now this betting card? Is he playing a Gamble Deck or something?
Go, Roulette Spider SPIN!
Give it a try, psychic power kid.
If it is pointed at me,
Psycho Shocker will have about 3200 Attack Points.
What's wrong?
STOP!
It's pointing at my Reflect Bounder.
That means...
Don't do it Reflect Bounder!
It's no use! It rebounds Psycho Shocker's 3200 Attack Points!
They kill and destroy each other.
Psycho Shocker and Reflect Bounder, both are destroyed!
B-Both are destroyed? T-That's impossible!
Let me explain, Psycho Shocker had 3200 Attack Points.
Reflect Bounder had 1700 Attack Points.
Their difference was 1500 points.
They will be decreased from your Life.
I won this duel.
He did it!
Alright! Jounouchi won!
It's great, Big brother.
I can't believe he won.
Sometimes it depends on luck.
My Big bro lost the game.
Damn it!
But it really was a great duel.
I... Lost...
Hey, Esper Roba lost.
He was defeated by an outsider duelist.
I won.
Give me your Rare Card and Puzzle Card.
You and all of them...!
You despise me!!
Roba, I don't despise you.
But sometimes I do have better luck.
Other people won't look down on you.
Shut up. What the hell do you know?!
Don't force yourself, Roba.
Damn, I promised myself that I would never lose!
No matter what it takes.
People respect me as long as I win.
Roba...
As long as I am strong,
they won't despise my brothers.
I win these card games to protect my brothers.
Stop it.
In Battle City, if you don't stand up you lose.
Here.
Stand up.
Leave me alone!
I don't need your sympathy.
It's up to you.
Stand up, Big bro.
W...What? What is the voice?
Stand up. Stand up, Big bro!
It's you.
This is the last message.
Big bro!
Sorry, Big bro lost...
I'm Sorry...
It's ok.
You had a great duel.
Don't worry.
We will play the game honestly hereafter.
Is this the truth of the universe?
I am so moved.
Jounouchi-kun... I won't lose either.
Here's my Puzzle Card and Rare Card.
Please take them.
Please duel with me again.
Esper Roba.
I'm not Esper no more. I am just Roba.
I will challenge you with my true ability next time.
I will wait.
I will wait for you.
Hey Roba.
You have your brothers, and I have
my sister, and my reliable friends.
We are not alone, so we will be stronger.
Yes.
Later.
It's great, Jounouchi.
I did it, Yugi.
I did it, Shizuka.
"Preview"
Yugi joined Battle City to regain his lost memory.
Be careful, Ghouls people is watching you.
Black Magician appears before Yugi, claiming to be the real one.
The real Black Magician user is Pandora, and he is after Yugi.
Wait a second, what kind of duel ring is this?
Next Time: "The Black Magician User,
Pandora"
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...