The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
I expect that you will transfer all
that you have from Kaiba Corporation to me.
We understand what you are saying,
but... we have a condition...
Defeating that boy named Yugi will be very easy.
What?!
Mokuba! Release Mokuba!
If you win the duel, I'll think about it.
Where's the opponent for the duel?
He's already waiting... Look!
Kaiba?!
Back from the Dead!
Magical Silk Hat
Yugi... you will now fight with Seto Kaiba!
Against Seto Kaiba's spirit, that is!
What did you say?
What do you mean?
I already told you.
Seto Kaiba is not among the living anymore.
What?!
It's a lie! My brother didn't die!
It's not a lie! He died because of his hate for Yugi Mutou!
Now, that one standing up there is only Kaiba's spirit.
Impossible!
So, what are you going to do, Yugi? Fight or not fight?
Very well. I will reveal that person's true self!
Seto Kaiba died?
Yes. That's what I heard.
Oh no! That is something so unlucky....
So this is an impostor?
It doesn't please you?
Well, well... it's all right...
I'll just watch this as entertainment.
Excuse me but, I don't really understand the point.
Yugi-boy will surely come here.
And then he will be in my hands.
Yugi...
I am dead...
It's a lie!
When I lost to you, I lost interest in everything..
...even my life...
Absolutely unforgivable...
Now I stand at the door to hell!
And I will drag you into that hell along with me...
Do you think you can faze me with this spirit talk?
Say what you want after you beat my deck...
Even if you have Kaiba's face and tone,
you can't have his deck.
We'll see about that...
My brother would never get killed so easily!
Yugi, don't listen to him! He's just a fake!
That's right!
Yugi...
The opponents you will fight on this island...
are not just the ordinary ones...
This is the first one that the Industrial Illusions
sent to this island in order to defeat you.
You will lose your heart to Kaiba's spirit.
That'll be your downfall.
When that happens.... Kaiba Corporation will belong to Mr. Pegasus.
We'll bet three stars!
Very well! I will bet three... all that I have!
Duel!
First it's my turn.
Cyclops in attack mode.
What is the problem, Yugi?
Now, it's your turn.
Cyclops... that's really a card that Kaiba has in his deck...
My brother has that card in his deck too.
Even so, that doesn't mean that is Kaiba's deck!
No... I don't think this fake could have Kaiba's deck...
This is a fake too!
I'll use this card to battle!
Black Magician in attack mode!
Black Magic!
Cyclops is defeated!
As usual you are strong... strong...
This guy...
Yugi... somehow is getting very fazed...
Yugi... I can easily read your mind...
What you are thinking now is:
"Maybe that is really Kaiba's deck...", am I right?
That's right. This is the exact same deck as Seto Kaiba!
The dead Kaiba is linked to this deck.
Kaiba is not dead!
I don't believe in such a thing!
Well, well... Am I not right?
You're wrong!
Believing is the best thing you could do...
What do you mean?
You don't have it, do you? Exodia?
Can you win without it?
Against Seto Kaiba's deck?
What?!
Jumped?
We will not need to lock him up now...
Voice verification. Your name is?
It's Seto Kaiba.
Verification complete.
Seto-sama, it's been a while.
While I was absent... what happened?
A board meeting happened...
What was the issue?
50% of the company that was held by the Big 5...
will be transferred to the Industrial Illusions,
of Pegasus J. Crawford, under a certain condition.
A condition?
Pegasus J. Crawford has organized the Duelist Kingdom tournament...
If Yugi Mutou is defeated, the transfer will be complete.
Damn Pegasus...
He intends to take over the Kaiba Corporation..
But Yugi has the great Exodia.
So for him to lose...
According to the database, Yugi Mutou doesn't have Exodia.
What did you say?!
Any other questions?
I haven't seen Mokuba. Where is he?
He was invited as a special guest in the Duelist Kingdom by Pegasus.
Mokuba has the key to the company's secret files room.
So he took Mokuba hostage...?
Pegasus!
What will you do?
I'll surely free Mokuba, but now...
I need to stop Pegasus's plan to take over the company.
Yugi has to win no matter what!
It's a matter of time for him to find that I'm using this computer.
It's a fight against time! I'm counting on you.
Understood.
First, let's use the network to find the battle places...
Target: Duelist Kingdom!
Next, it's your turn!
So, here I go...
Now, the dead one came from hell to reclaim his revenge on you!
Are you ready, Yugi?
Look! The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
What?
B-Blue-Eyes White Dragon?
It can't be... that's really my brother's deck!
So? Are you surprised?
T-That's is really...
The real Kaiba's deck...
So that means... that Kaiba is really...
I know what you're thinking!
"Kaiba is really dead, isn't it?"
Am I wrong?
No one can imitate Kaiba's deck.
This one here is really my deck...
And here it is...
My Blue-Eyes White Dragon, full of hatred,
that revived to get revenge on you!
It's a lie! Someone say that this is a lie!
Shall we go together to hell?
Searching complete. Duelist Kingdom has been located and targeted.
Which duel rings are being used now?
Actually there are twelve duel rings scattered in the island.
Okay... In these 12 places, locate where Yugi Mutou is battling...
Searching... please wait a moment...
Access denied?
Yes. The data of Yugi Mutou's duel is confidential.
Impossible!
I see... Pegasus... you have something planned, huh?
Yugi's duel data is something that you want to be a secret?
What's next?
Very well... I'll surely find where Yugi is!
This time, let's force our way in...
The method?
This one...
The duels that happen in the island have their data
transfered by this satellite and recorded at the Industrial Illusions's main computer...
The Millennium server.
If we can use this and enter the Millennium system...
we will be able to find Yugi's secret data in the records.
Hacking? Their security system will not let anything in.
This entire system runs off of a virtual system...
I was the one who designed it.
What would I do if I wasn't able to operate with this virtual world?
But, without information, you can't do a search.
I can do that.
If Yugi is in a duel,
there's a high probability of a Black Magician appearing in the battle field.
Listen... Search for a Black Magician...
Understood.
Black Magician's data and searching program linked together.
Okay... now hack in the Millennium system!
Understood. First step, from the control room link with the Illusion Satellite 2.
Change Security wall's virtual purge to stealth mode.
Understood.
Stealth Mode has been reached.
Start purge!
Purge complete. Illusion Satellite 2's security wall has been activated.
Okay... now use the path created to do a landing in the Millennium system.
Understood. Begin landing.
Reached the Industrial Illusions!
It seems they didn't find us.
Second step! Hack in the main computer, Millennium!
Understood! Start hacking in the Millennium system!
I will not attack this turn.
Instead of that, I'll make sure that your monster has nowhere to run...
Is that a magic card... or a trap card?
Black Magician in defense mode!
And then, Curse of Dragon in defense mode.
As I have predicted...this will be interesting.
I activate the Trap card! Seal Defense!
What?
With this all monsters in your side will be in attack mode.
Yugi!
That's bad...
As long as the Seal Defense card is on the field...
my Life Points will only decrease...
Go, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Burst Stream of Destruction
Curse of Dragon is defeated!
Yugi!
Not in this room... how many left?
There's still one... room 146.
There is no one dueling?
No... that's not it.
Enter the room 146.
Understood.
What happened?
It Froze!
Reboot it!
Rebooted.
Re-access room 146!
It Froze!
Unknown reason.
Okay... wait...
This is it...
The Freeze is a camouflage...
it seems that I'm getting a response to something that is happening inside.
It seems that there's a Black Magician in the field inside.
There's no doubt... Yugi's in there.
Which method will you use?
The key-hole destruction program! We will explode the door!
Understood.
That is...
That building is the materialized form of the stored memory.
Actually, Yugi Mutou's duel data is stored inside it.
However, there's a need of a password in order to enter it.
Damn Pegasus...
A place like a prison where you can't leave once you entered?
It's a good joke, but it won't work!
Get inside!
The password?
Alcatraz!
No! I have no chance of winning?
Yugi...
Kaiba's spirit will be happy to see you losing!
My brother isn't dead! Isn't dead!
Yugi! Didn't you tell me?
That my brother would come back!
I... I believe... I believe in those words...
I'll wait for my brother forever!
Mokuba... I understand...
I believe...
Kaiba is surely alive.
I believe! I will not lose!
Magical Silk Hats!
I play this combo alongside Black Magician!
One of these silk hats is hiding the Black Magician.
Now... attack! Use your Burst Stream!
But the chance of success is one in four...
What is it? If you are really a vengeful spirit...
and want to really see me dead, attack!
Amazing, Yugi! That way he has a chance to escape from Blue-Eyes's attack!
Yugi!
Door unlocked. Alcatraz accepted.
Now the real thing starts. Pegasus, I will show you my, Seto Kaiba's, true power!
Let's start the battle!
What foolish trickery... just to buy time...
Say what you want... now, attack!
So, I will destroy each one of them! Burst Stream!
Somehow Yugi escaped Blue-Eyes's attack!
But he didn't get out of the pinch.
Kaiba-kun's deck has 3 Blue-Eyes cards.
At this rate, Yugi will...
Eh? Blue-Eyes is disappearing?
Someone must have helped Yugi.
Finally the real identity of the fake Kaiba is revealed!
There's no reason to be confused anymore! Beat him up, Yugi!
Next, Blue-Eyes White Dragon Strikes Back!
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship