A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Dragon Knight Gaia, attack!
The Flame Swordsman is beaten!
I fuse the Demon's Summon with the Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Black Demon's Dragon, rip Dark Knight Gaia apart!
Meteor Flare!!
Yugi. I finally understand the true fun in Dueling.
That's right. This is a true Duel, Jounouchi-kun.
The fight has just begun.
Come on, Yugi!
Let's go, Jounouchi-kun!
"The Final Game of Friendship!
Yugi VS Jounouchi (Part 2)"
A very superb Duel!
Yugi boy has technique,
and Jounouchi boy has power.
But, right now Jounouchi boy's tactics went up, and he's pushed Yugi boy into a corner.
So, Yugi boy, what are you going to do?
Next is Yugi's turn.
Yugi won't give up so easily.
The battle has just started.
But Jounouchi-kun
is feeling the same way.
This Duel will probably get more and more intense.
What's wrong, Yugi?
You want to give up already?
No. This turn I'll use this card.
Black Magician in Attack Mode!
Yugi's Black Magician finally came out.
But you can't fight against my Black Demon's Dragon!
I know.
In front of a strong Attack Monster,
if you put it in Attack Mode, it'll become the target.
That's what you said!
But, Jounouchi-kun, I've also said a Duel is a combination of both Monster Cards and Magic Cards.
Don't tell me...
Magic Card...
Magical Silk Hats!
Magical Silk Hats...
That is...!
Yugi used it before.
You finally decided to use
your best techniques, Yugi boy.
So, Jounouchi-kun. Which Silk Hat did Black Magician hide in?
I knew he would eventually use them, but...
this is really annoying.
Which Silk Hat
is the Black Magician hiding in?
Alright, let's battle!
In that case, I'll blast 'em one by one!
Go! Black Demon's Dragon!
Did I get him!?
It seems you missed him, Jounouchi-kun.
There's only three left.
Damn... Which Silk Hat is the Black Magician hiding in?
Hey! Any one else notice that Jounouchi's been taking more time to think?
He's probably changing his plan.
In this turn, he is probably planning a trap.
You said you would destroy
my Monsters one by one, Jounouchi-kun.
So, what are you waiting for?
If I destroy Black Magician, then you'll have no success later.
But ending this Duel that quickly would be a pity.
I'll use this!
The Warrior Monster, Garoozis,
in Attack Mode!
What are you trying to do?
His Attack is 1800. Black Magician's Attack is 2500.
In my turn, I want to give you a step to win.
What did you say?!
I want to continue fighting with you!
Even if destroying Black Magician is easy, it's not fun!
So finish him off!
Come attack it, Yugi!
Did Jounouchi make
a mistake or something?
No. He's luring Yugi-kun to attack.
Jounouchi-kun plans to force out Black Magician, who is hiding in the Silk Hats.
What's wrong? Come. It's your turn.
Jounouchi-kun, I'm sorry,
but I can't accept your invitation.
I put this card in a
Silk Hat and end my turn.
And I end my turn!
What did he put under it?
It's your turn, Jounouchi-kun!
It's impossible to trick him.
You insist on hiding the Black Magician under one of the Magical Silk Hats...
And he hid another card under it.
It probably is a Trap Card.
Jounouchi-kun probably thinks the card I hid is a Trap Card.
Will you still have the courage to attack?
Damn it. Even if I keep thinking, I'm not coming up with anything...
Looks like I'll have to take a bet.
Black Demon's Dragon, battle!
Meteor Flare!!
This is why the Mind Scan brings me ecstasy.
I can know exactly what they are thinking.
The problem is the last two Silk Hats.
No matter who attacks, there will be a significant change in the current situation.
Such amazing thinking between the two...
Didn't think Jounouchi would be able to think about Yugi's play...
Yes. It would be impossible
if he hadn't progressed so much.
But, he's now become a great Duelist.
What is this? It's making me nervous...
Two Silk Hats remain!
One of them is Black Magician.
The other is a set card.
From now on, the attack will be sure
to reach something.
Yeah.
The other Silk Hat has a Trap Card, right?
Attack and you'll see.
I intend to do just that!
But whatever happens, I won't run away!
That's because the Duelist I'm fighting with right now isn't any normal Duelist!
Yugi, here I come!
Black Demon's Dragon, attack a Silk Hat!
Meteor Flare!!
Hexagram Curse!
The Hexagram Curse...?!
His Attack has decreased!
This is bad. Just in case, I change Garoozis to Defense Mode.
Next is my turn, Jounouchi-kun.
Defeating Yugi really isn't an easy task.
But, Jounouchi is doing pretty good against him.
That's right. Even if the attack just now didn't work, both their strengths are equal.
Since they are both using their most powerful Monsters,
Yugi has the advantage, possessing
more regeneration spells, but...
But what?
It would be useless to try to think too much into a Duel that has reached this much depth.
He really isn't letting me win so easily...
What should I do?
Impressive! The Jounouchi-kun in front of me right now isn't scared of his opponent.
Furthermore, he's not acting so carelessly any more.
This is the capacity of a Duelist,
to think calmly and quietly.
Jounouchi-kun, you're the ideal opponent for me to go all out with!
This is now becoming a fight of willpower.
I look forward to the end result of this Duel.
But this is no time to be admiring him.
It's time to finish this.
I'll defeat this Black Demon's Dragon, no matter what it takes!
Come if you dare!
It's my turn.
Are you ready, Jounouchi-kun?
The Book of Secret Arts!
Using this Magic Card, I can increase Black Magician's Attack by 300 points!
Battle!
Black Magic!!
Black Demon's Dragon has been defeated.
Bravo, Yugi boy!
Yugi... You're strong...
Too strong.
Just as I thought, I can't win against you...?
Jounouchi-kun, this is the proof of our friendship.
We can't worry about the outcome.
We must fight with all our strength.
That is our Duel.
Isn't that right, Jounouchi-kun?
Jounouchi, you did great getting this far, but you can't go on anymore.
But then again, we still don't know what will happen.
What do you mean?
The result still hasn't been decide between them yet.
Their enthusiasm for the Duel still hasn't disappeared.
I've worked hard for this day, but I still can't beat him...
Damn it! What should I do?
Big brother!
Shizuka...
I wanted to see
your face one last time!
You promise?
I promise.
That's right...
She's still waiting for me.
Yes... Whatever happens, I must not lose!
What did he draw?
The real battle starts now, Yugi!
Baby Dragon! Attack Mode!
And I set this card.
Could that face-down card be the Time Wizard?!
If it is, it will attack as Thousand Dragon instead of the Baby Dragon.
Then I must kill it first!
Battle! Black Magician, attack Baby Dragon!
Black Magic!!
I won't let you proceed!
I activate a Trap Card!
What!?
Garoozis! Chained Boomerang!
Oh no... Because of Baby Dragon...
I thought it was the Time Magician...
Yugi boy made an error.
He understands his opponent too much.
He messed up, even if it's just one card.
This is what makes this Duel
so complex and interesting.
The time to put an end to this
has finally arrived, Yugi.
That's right, Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi.
What is it?
Whoever wins, no anger towards him!
Of course.
Yugi... Jounouchi...
I've come such a long way.
And I think I've gotten pretty good.
But the battle isn't over yet.
It's not over 'till I win!
Everything will be at stake on this next move!
Even if I'm beaten in this Duel, I still won't regret it!
Yes! I drew the best card for our match!
What!?
Don't tell me...!
Let's go!
Time Magician!
The Time Magician!?
I never thought I'd use this card in our final match.
Right, use this one too.
I think it'll give you a hand when you're in trouble.
Really? Thanks a lot.
He's helped me out of a ton of pinches before.
Yugi, without it,
I wouldn't be Dueling you right now.
This Time Magician is the most appropriate card
to put an end to our Duel!
Watch this, Yugi!
This is my best card!
Time Magician! Time Roulette!
Yeah! It's hit!
Time Magic!
And because of Time Magician's influence, Black Magician will age!
The Black Magician...
became an old man...
Jounouchi won!?
This is unbelievable...
Will I actually defeat Yugi...?
No, this isn't a dream or an illusion...
Yugi, don't be mad at me...!
I won!
Battle! Thousand Nose Breath!!
Makiu Evil Rain!!
What!?
This is...!
What does that mean...?
It's my turn...
How can the Evil Rain be activated?
Jounouchi-kun, because of Time Magician's influence, Baby Dragon wasn't the only Monster affected.
What do you mean...!?
The Magician who now received
a thousand years of life and experience...
became a sage mastering all the arcanes!
The Great Black-Robed Sage.
He enables me to add a Magic Card of my choice from my deck into my hand during each of our turns.
During your turn, the effect of Makiu
was activated which caused the rain to fall.
And now, during my turn, I'll be able
to add a new Magic Card to my hand.
Jounouchi-kun, it's my turn.
Thanks to the power of the Great Black-Robed Sage,
I can now use a Magic Card!
Resurrection of the Dead!
I resurrect The Evil Dragon -
Black Demon's Dragon, in Attack Mode!
Yugi...
Come, Yugi!
Battle!
They really didn't hold back...
Yes. This is what it means to be a True Duelist.
I seem to be able to understand now... The meaning of the battle between the two's strong link with one another.
That was superb. A very good Duel, Yugi boy.
I will defeat you for sure.
Here Yugi, take this.
It's yours now.
Jounouchi-kun, the prize money is yours.
My goal is to defeat Pegasus and save Grandpa, Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun.
Use the prize money for Shizuka-chan's operation.
Yugi...
You can do that, right?
Accept, Jounouchi.
This way, Shizuka-chan's eyes can be cured.
Thanks... Yugi, you have to win...
against this Pegasus...
It's finally Yugi and Pegasus' battle!
Pegasus uses the Millennium Eye to look at his opponent's cards, but you can't lose, Yugi!
Please save Grandpa, Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun!
Eh? Where's Honda?
Really...! Where did he go
at such an important time!?
Next time: "Final Duel! Yugi VS Pegasus!"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship