Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Jounouchi VS
the Trap Deck"
We will now hold the lottery for the second round of the Battle City Finals!
Ultimate Bingo Machine, start!
The first Duelist in the second match will be Number 2!
Katsuya Jounouchi!
Good! Who's my opponent?!
And his opponent is...
Number 7, Malik Ishtar!
It's Malik!
Malik... the Duelist who holds the third God Card...
Also the man who brainwashed Jounouchi-kun
and forced us to fight each other!
Malik, I'm gonna beat you with my own two hands!
We will now begin the second round of the tournament!
Katsuya Jounouchi VS Malik Ishtar!
Listen up, ya brainwashin' bastard!
Daring to insult the bond between me and my friends...
You asked for a serious beat-down, you asshole!
It's been a while since I've seen that!
Jounouchi staring someone down!
Yeah! Jounouchi-kun's full of spirit!
Right! He's never lost a fight when he's done that!
Although that's only for fistfights!
Eh?
Knew it...
But that Malik guy also has an incredible presence.
I think it's safe to say he's quite skilled.
Be careful, Jounouchi...
I don't know why, but I'm a bit nervous.
Oh yeah, this is your first time seeing Jounouchi Duel.
Yes.
Just do your best to cheer him on throughout the game, Shizuka-chan!
I will!
I think you've shuffled the deck enough already...
Get into position already, you two.
Bastard! I swear to God, I'm gonna kill ya!
I hereby declare a K.O.!
On your eleventh turn, Malik,
you're gonna lose to me!
Eleventh turn?
He's a bit full of himself right now...
Wow, that's awesome brother!
I can't believe you've planned that far ahead!
I think for the moment, he's just spouting nonsense...
That's...!
His Millennium Item!
Is that damn Malik trying to use it on Jounouchi-kun again?!
What the hell is he doing?
At least for the moment it looks like he's decided to Duel fair and square.
That man is without a doubt Malik!
You've done an excellent job using the fake Millennium Rod, Rishid.
Everyone here has been completely fooled by it.
And even if you fail to eliminate Yugi,
I still have a big puzzle that I have to resolve before you do.
Before I discover the answer o that puzzle, I need you to pose as me.
And that big puzzle is...
Beside the nameless Pharaoh on the palette stands a priest...
Blue-Eyes...
...and that Millennium Rod look-alike in his hands.
I must know how they are related...
And the Obelisk he wields...
The God Cards can only be controlled by those chosen by the Millennium Items.
But he is exceptional.
Rishid, using my name, you must learn the truth behind his memories.
If you win this Duel, you will earn the chance to fight Kaiba.
When that time comes, you must use the power of the Millennium Rod
to find out the truth behind how this man can participate in the Millennium Battle!
Big brother...
Does this Malik guy really hold the third God Card?
I am at least certain he's the leader of the Ghouls.
But I won't believe it, until I see it myself.
Jounouchi...
You're my lab rat...
Don't lose until you make him play his God Card!
Rishid...
Jounouchi's Duelist level is not very high.
He's no match against you.
I am well aware that I am Lord Malik's double...
I will bury any enemy who dares to stand in our way!
Here goes, Malik!
-Duel!!
I get to go first! Draw card!
Alright! Go for it, Jounouchi!
Don't you dare lose!
By the way...
Did Jounouchi-kun take his Red-Eyes back, Yugi-kun?
No.
What the heck? That idiot didn't even take his trump card back for the match?
Then that means Jounouchi-kun's deck hasn't powered up at all.
Jounouchi-kun insists he won't take that card back until he becomes a real Duelist.
He's seriously trying to act cool!
It's true I don't have the Red-Eyes in my deck...
But even so, I'm gonna win!
I'll beat Malik for sure and get his God Card!
Oh yeah!
Then that'd make me a wielder of a God Card!
That was close!
I almost lost my most important cards!
Man, big brother...
Nice catch!
Damn, so the wind is also an enemy on this Battle Ship?
Calm down, Jounouchi-kun...
Concentrate... Concentrate...
Okay! My turn! I play this!
Iron Knight Gearfried in Attack Position!
Great! He played a nice card!
I'm not gonna give you the chance to attack first!
Turn end!
My turn.
Field Magic, activate!
Temple of the Royal Family!
A temple just appeared on his field!
This has now become a sanctuary for the Pharaoh's treasures!
All beings other than the Tomb Guardians must humble themselves before this sacred ground!
Humble themselves?
Right, and due to this card's Effect, you are limited to one set card per turn.
What?
Powerful traps are set to pass judgment against thieves and robbers.
My turn will now come to an end.
So Jounouchi, do you have the courage to step into this sacred ground
and face this trap-filled territory?
Malik didn't play any Monsters?
Take him out!
It's useless.
Why?
Purposely stepping onto a ground full of traps is nothing but suicide!
He can't attack carelessly!
Shit!
More than that...
What's bothering me is that arc at the top of the Royal Temple...
What's sleeping inside it?
Rishid... Seems you've gotten your "Trap Hell" started.
This ain't good...
You can do this, big brother!
Don't be scared, Jounouchi!
Just kiddin'!
It takes more than a couple of traps to scare the manly Jounouchi!
I have my sure-kill Magic Card, Hurricane, in my hand.
If I play it, all Magic and Trap Cards on the field
will return to our hands.
He's planning on activating his Trap Card the moment I attack with a Monster.
So I just won't attack...
While he's waiting for me to make a move, I'll Summon as many Monsters as I can.
And after he's played every Trap Card he's got in his hand...
I'll activate Hurricane!
And then when he has no cards out on the field...
I'll have all my Monsters dog pile him!
My plan is perfect!
My turn! Card Draw!
Summon Little-Winguard!
I'll end my turn right there!
Seems he's got this under control.
What's he gonna do?
I'm getting more and more anxious!
My turn.
I set two more reverse cards.
My turn is over.
Four reverse cards on the field!
So he's got some kind of Trap strategy with no Monsters?
Just like I planned, he set all of his Trap Cards on the field!
My turn!
I'll then Summon another Monster!
Come out!
Falcon Knight!
Yes! Now the total Attack Points of these Monsters is over 4000!
If I activate Hurricane on this turn,
I can wipe him out!
Malik! You fell into my trap!
Magic Card activate! Hurricane!
Smart! Now all his cards have been removed from the field!
Jounouchi-kun wins!
What?!
What's the matter?!
Jounouchi, you are the one who fell into my trap.
Hurricane's Effect... just disappeared...!
Why?
You may have thought that my Trap Cards were activated by a Monster's attack.
But I was waiting for you to activate a Magic Card.
What did you say?
I knew that you possess the Hurricane.
You didn't play any set cards
as per the Effect of Hurricane,
because they would have been futilely sent back to your hand.
So you read my strategy this far...?
Human beings are foolish beyond words.
They don't bother doing anything they deem useless effort.
But such thoughts only put your life in danger.
Jounouchi, such tactics are child's play to me, the great Malik!
This is the Trap Card you deserve!
Judgment of Anubis!!
This card activates when the opponent uses a Magic Card.
Every Monster on their field is destroyed,
and your opponent then receives half of their Attack Points as damage to their Life Points.
What did you just say?!
The total Attack Power of your Monsters was 4200.
Therefor, you receive damage of 2100 to your Life as judgment.
My Monsters were all destroyed?!
Jounouchi... this is only the beginning of the true traps you will fall into.
He worked so hard to Summon three Monsters, too...
Trap Cards are scary because they can turn the situation around in an instant.
But what's also bad is the mental damage they inflict on the player.
In the worst scenario, Trap Cards can cause so much stress
that the player loses all focus and concentration.
If that happens, the player becomes so nervous they can't even fight.
Really...? So that must be a part of Malik's Trap strategy!
Will... Will my brother be alright?
Yes...
He'll be fine.
Right, Yugi?
Yeah! It'll take more than this to make Jounouchi-kun run away!
There's no way he'd lose to the pressure of his traps!
You can do it, brother!
Don't mind, Jounouchi!
So then... Your turn is not yet complete.
Listen up, Malik...
This past turn, I set you up in a trap to test your ability.
But it seems that I may have underestimated you a bit.
I'm glad!
Cuz you're the 21st Duelist to force me to play seriously!
So I'm gonna play for real now!
I'm gonna raise my Duelist level to max!
"Duelist level to max"?!
Thank goodness! He still hasn't gotten serious yet!
I think he's lost it...
Man, Jounouchi...
Well, you have to admit that he's pretty impressive.
He doesn't seem the least bit flustered.
Maybe he's just too stupid
to feel the pressure?
Alright then, Malik!
It's your turn, so lemme have it!
My turn. Draw.
I'll set two more cards face-down this turn.
Turn end.
Reverse again?!
That's cheap, ya jerk!
All you do is set Trap Cards all the time!
Don't you have the courage to fight me fair and square?!
You coward!
A Trap deck is a brilliant strategy.
You have no right to call me a coward just because you cannot comprehend it.
Then allow me to show the true way to play Duel Monsters!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Wyvern Warrior!
Attack Position!
There's no doubt in my mind that those five reverse cards are all Trap Cards!
If I'm not careful when I attack, I'll fall right into his traps!
Whatever is the matter?
Did you not say that you were going to show me how to Duel?
Shit... I can't...
I can't attack him.
I play a reverse card and end my turn!
Good, that was the right move!
You'll only fall for Malik's trap if you move now.
Be patient and wait for a chance!
Now it's your turn!
In that case, I will simply end my turn without doing anything.
Damn it all! So his plan's to just sit by and wait for me to attack?
I won't fall for something like that!
Then my turn is over as well!
Then I will simply draw on my turn.
Turn over.
Big brother, his strategy is easy to read.
But the match will never end if none of them attacks.
No, it doesn't seem so.
Looks like the idiot has been completely overwhelmed by the pressure.
Malik!
Not good!
Jounouchi, don't lose your cool!
That's what Malik wants!
Shut up!!
My turn!
I Summon Rocket Warrior!
I can't take it anymore!
My pride as a Duelist won't let me back down from a challenge!
Just like I promised, I'm gonna show you what a true Duel is all about!
Rocket Warrior, transform into your Invincible Mode!
Attack the player!
Don't do it, Jounouchi-kun!
Trap Card, activate!
Will of the Wadjet Eye!
Due to the Effect of this Trap, the Monster who sees the Wadjet Eye
shall be under the control of the player for one full turn.
What?!
Rocket Warrior!
Attack Wyvern Warrior!
I had a feeling you'd do that!
Magic Card, activate!
Monster Box!
His Monster is hiding in that strange box on the field...
And now the Rocket Warrior loses its attack target!
Over there! Rocket Warrior!
Did I hit it?
What?
Too bad!
My Monster's unscratched!
Plus I found the weak point
of your Trap Tactic!
Your deck's mostly
Magic and Trap Cards.
In other words, you don't have a single Monster.
So no matter what Traps you have,
if I can get rid of em,
since you have no Monsters to guard you,
beating ya would be a piece a' cake!
That's easier said than done, dude!
Jounouchi, are you sure about that?
You have already fallen
deep into my Trap Hell.
What?!
Rishid, hurry up and finish this.
Stop playing along with him...!
Just like you said, my deck is made up mostly of Magic and Trap Cards.
But what if a Trap Card exists that can take the place of a Monster Card?
A Trap Card that takes the place of a Monster Card?!
If that was true, then my deck would truly be unbeatable,
with none of the weaknesses you speak of.
I've never heard of anything like that!
Allow me to show you!
This is the card that shall deliver onto you God's punishment!
Watch!
You have already activated the Trap Card this turn!
What'd you say?!
The Trap Monster Card!
Embodiment of Apophis!
This card is a Trap activated when the opponent attacks.
And its Effect Summons the Monster servant of the gods,
Embodiment of Apophis!
No way!
So that card activates as a Trap Card but Summons as a Monster Card?!
Jounouchi-kun attacked this turn with his Rocket Warrior!
The Trap activated that same moment!
And it Summoned a Monster!
I can Summon three Monsters this turn!
Come forth! Apophis!
He Summoned three Monsters at once...?
Amazing!
So is this where it ends?
So this is Malik's Trap Strategy!
This is what he was after all along?!
Jounouchi...
Like a rat in a trap, you set foot on my trapdoor into Hell.
Now prepare yourself to fall to the very depths.
"Preview"
These Trap Monsters drag Jounouchi into a major pinch!
Is there any way out?
It's not like Jounouchi to surrender now!
The winning Duelists carry the dreams of the losers!
Jounouchi stands up once again after Mai-san's words!
Yeah!
You have to try your best for Roba-kun, Kajiki-kun and Insector Haga!
Next time!
"The Inherited Card: Psycho Shocker Counterattacks!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise