Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Ninja Master Magnum Arrives"
This is as far as we go by car!
Now, get out! Get out!
Wha? We're gonna walk the rest of the way?
That stadium's the location of the finals.
Let's hurry!
Kaiba and some other guys must be there by now.
Mhm-hm!
So this stadium must be the center of the Amusement City Kaiba Corporation's building.
That's Kaiba Corporation for you.
They do everything in a big way!
But with all these finished buildings around, it's almost like walking in a ghost town.
It gives me the creeps!
You have no hope of winning the finals if you're scared this easily.
Well, sorry!
By the way, Mai...
Huh?
There's something I've been meaning to ask you for a while.
Why'd you do that back in the Duelist Kingdom?
Stand up, Jounouchi!
Save those tears for if you lose the Duel!
Moron!
It's just a runny nose!
Shit...
It won't stop coming...!
Here.
Just clean it up. It's disgraceful.
Jounouchi, don't give up on your desires so easily.
Those tears for your little sister...
No, a runny nose, right?
Well, whatever it is.
Don't give up on them.
It's sure to come true.
Th-This is...
Why'd you give me that back then...?
Why did I give you my card?
I guess I can tell you now...
It's obvious that it's because we're friends, right?
Wow! Awesome!
Hey! Jounouchi!
It's the Jean-Claude Magnum Ninja Series!
Oh man, I wish this movie would hurry up and open!
I'm a huge fan!
God... You didn't listen to a word I said...!
Wh-What the hell?
Hey you! That's dangerous, ya know!
This ain't a movie or somethin'!
Sorry. I sure am sorry about that, boy.
J-Jean-Claude Magnum...!
Y-You're the real deal!
Hello! How do you do?!
M-Me... Y-You no... Very Very Fan de!
[I'm a very big fan of yours in very poor Engrish]
It's been a long time, Mai-san.
Mai-san, I came to pick you up, just like we promised.
What are you talking about?
Are you mistaking me for someone else?
That's awesome, Mai!
You know a Hollywood star?!
I told you he's mistaken...
No!
Mai-san! Have you really forgotten our promise?
Promise?
Yes. A promise.
Direct Attack Mr. Magnum!
Whip Banish!
My Life has been drained to 0!
Seems even a Hollywood star can't beat me in a Duel.
Huh?
You plan to use your "ninja arts" to assault your Dueling rival?
Mai Kujaku, I have been completely subdued by your strength.
Please marry me.
Mai-san!
I'll listen to your sick jokes after you beat me in a Duel.
So if I beat you in a Duel, it'll be okay to marry you?
Though it's about 100 years too soon for you.
Don't forget!
It's a promise!
So I did meet you once before...
Today, I plan to beat you and bring you back to Hollywood.
Huh!?
Don't go deciding that on your own!
What're you talking about, Mai?
A Hollywood star just proposed to you! You're awesome!
Don't waste this chance!
Skip the Dueling part and just marry the guy!
I have no reason to marry him.
But it'd be freakin' cool to have one of my friends the wife of a Hollywood star!
My god...!
He's such a kid!
Fine. I'll accept this Duel.
Oh! So if I win the Duel, you'll marry me.
You plan to beat me?
Mai-san!
Shouldn't we forget about this and head for the location of the finals?
Our spots in the finals could be taken over if we don't get over there.
But he...
...doesn't seem to plan on letting us go if she doesn't accept the Duel.
Well, that's true enough.
It's alright!
It's Mai-san we're talking about! She'll finish this up soon!
Right!
Go for it, Mai!
Weren't you suggesting I lose before?
Eh? Well, you see...
Ah, that's right. Lend him your Duel Disk.
Eh!?
No problem.
A Duel Disk!
But only members of the highest ranks are permitted one!
And I am among those highest ranking members.
As you can see, I have already obtained five Puzzle Cards.
So that means if Mai-san loses, she won't be able to enter the tournament finals?
What I am pursuing is not the usual tournament prestige or glory, rather it is you.
You've already won your place!
You don't need anymore Puzzle Cards.
That's right, Mai!
No, I want to show him that not everything can go the way he wants it to!
Now! Duel start!
My turn.
First up is the Ninja Commander Ikusa in Attack Mode!
A Ninja Monster...
Shadow Clone Art.
What?
Another Ninja just appeared!
As long as the Ninja Commander remains in face-up Attack Mode,
I can Special Summon one Ninja Soldier from my hand in Attack Position.
I can't believe such a conceited Hollywood star would play such weak and boring Monsters
on his first turn, and still brag about it.
Boring?
Here goes! My turn!
Draw!
Go! Amazoness Swords Woman!
Amazoness Slash!!
What the heck? Magnum seems really weak!
He doesn't seem like a star at all.
I'm counting on you! Don't ruin my image of the ninja hero!
Just as I expected of you, Mai-san.
You certainly have powered up since our last encounter.
My turn. Draw card.
Ninja Commander Ikusa in Attack Mode!
I then Special Summon Ninja Soldier Katana!
You're just as repetitive as ever, whether you're acting or Dueling.
And you're just as harsh as ever, Mai-san.
But that strong personality really turns me on.
Hey, big brother, Mai-san sure is lovely!
She's beautiful.
And she's cool!
Really?
I never really thought of her in that way...
I wonder if Mai-san has a boyfriend.
No way!
She's only interested in Dueling!
And no man alive can put up with that arrogant personality of hers!
That idiot!
What ever is the matter?
Mai-san, it's your turn.
I know that without you telling me!
Amazoness Swords Woman! Take care of him!
Amazoness Slash!!
Mai-san, I have been waiting for this moment.
What do you mean?
My turn.
In order to Summon Ninja Master Shogun,
the Ninja Commander and the Ninja Soldier must both be in the Graveyard.
I'll sacrifice my remaining Ninja Soldier,
and Summon Ninja Master Shogun!
Ninja Master Shogun?
Does he have some kind of Special Effect?
Allow me to tell you.
When the Ninja Master is Summoned using the Commander and Soldier,
he holds the Ability to Special Summon two more Ninjas from my deck in Attack Mode.
And the Ninja Commander Kabuki I just Summoned in Attack Mode...
...allows me to Special Summon Ninja Lady Soldier in Attack Mode.
Big brother, will Mai-san be alright?
Don't worry. This isn't enough to stop a Duelist like Mai.
That Monster's nothing!
An opening!
I use Ninja Master Shogun to attack Amazoness Sword Woman!
Fireball Art!!
My ninjas, now that she has no more Wall Monsters, sneak in for a Direct Attack on Mai-san!
Mai!
What the hell am I doing?!
I have to concentrate!
Mai-san, please do not think badly of me.
It mortifies me to attack my loved one.
But love is a battle!
Please accept this burning feeling throbbing inside my chest!
I just let me guard down.
What the heck are you doing?! This ain't like you, Mai!
If this keeps up, Mai-san is seriously gonna have to marry this guy!
I set one reverse card.
Turn end.
It's my turn!
Concentrate, concentrate...! If I can't enter the finals because of this,
it won't be a joking matter!
I Summon Cyber Lady - Cyber Bondage!
According to the law of battle,
when you wanna beat your enemy, you start with the boss first!
Harpie Lady!
Scratch Clash!!
Reverse Trap, activate! Ninja Art: Smoke Bomb!
The Trap Card Ninja Art: Smoke Bomb
protects me from one of your Monsters' attacks for the duration of the turn!
Is that card for real?
I set a one reverse card,
and end my turn.
Draw card.
Can you hear it, Mai-san? Our wedding march, I mean.
Don't you mean the march of grievance at your funeral?
You're still lovely even when you're mouthing off.
But my victory has been decided.
Equipment Magic-
No...
Ninja Art: Great Kite of Ninja!
Great Kite of Ninja is one of the "Ninja Secret Arts" that can only be used with Ninja Master Shogu.
No Monster or Magic Cards can touch it!
No way!
Also, due to it's Special Effect,
Even if the opponent has a Wall Monster,
by sacrificing one of your own Monsters,
you can directly attack your opponent!
I sacrifice Ninja Soldier and Katana!
Direct Attack Mai-san!
Lightning Art!!
My turn comes to an end.
Let's just skip this meaningless Duel,
and start talking about our honeymoon.
This Duel's not over yet!
If this goes on, Mai-san will become his bride!
That card's not fair!
Yugi ,is there no other way?
If Mai-san draws the Harpie's Feather Duster from her deck, she may be able to do something...
Mai, do you have the Harpie's Feather Duster in your hand?
I would've used it if I did!
Then use your coercive personality to overcome the impossible and draw it out!
Goodness sake...
It's my turn!
So, how'd it go? Were you able to draw Harpie's Feather Duster?
Doesn't look like it!
Is there no other way, Yugi?
Forget about the Ninja Master!
As long as there's no sacrifices for the Ninja Master,
he can't attack with the Great Kite of Ninja!
I get it!
M-Mai! Just stay calm!
Why don't you calm down?!
Listen up!
As long as there's no Monster sacrifices for the Ninja Master,
he shouldn't be able to use the Great Kite of Ninja!
Hey! This is an official Duel, you know!
Advice is strictly prohibited!
But there's still three Ninjas!
And Mai-san has only one Monster!
It's not looking good for Mai-san!
So eventually it will be...
Anyway, just do your best, Mai!
You don't have the time to waste here!
What about the tournament finals?!
I know!
Your friends are with you!
Friends, huh...?
The Magic Card, Kaleidoscope - Magnificent Replication!
I'll use this card to make clones of my Harpie Ladies!
Scratch Clash!!
Oh yeah!
D'oh! Goddamn boy!
Boy? You talking about me?
Yes.
A mature woman like Mai-san doesn't fit a child like you.
Can I ask you to stay out of us adult's romance?!
What do you say?
I deserve to be with Mai too!
I was speaking hypothetically. Hypothetically.
I'm both rich and powerful and a Hollywood star.
Judging from your appearance, you're a student.
It's easy to see that who is qualified.
You're so damn arrogant!
Hollywood this, Hollywood that...
And your movies earned, like, nothing in the box office and aren't even well-known!
They are almost all B-level films!
But, didn't you just say you were Magnum-san's fan?
W-Well, that was before he started talking.
No matter what you may say,
if I play a Monster next turn for a Sacrifice Summon,
Everything is over.
I set a reverse card. My turn is over.
It's my turn.
Yes!
Now Ninja Master can directly attack Mai-san!
Mai!
I activate the Magic Card Early Burial!
What?!
You have no longer have a Monster to sacrifice.
It's my turn now.
I'm gonna strip you of your stardom right now...
While seemingly perfect, Ninja Master has one major weak point.
As long as the Great Kite of Ninja remains in the sky, Ninja Master can't be attacked.
At the same time, he can't count as a Wall Monster to defend.
Meaning right now you don't have any Wall Monsters on the field to protect you.
Harpie Ladies! Direct Attack the player!!
Triple Scratch Clash!!
Oh no, Mai-san!
The match is over, mister Hollywood star.
There's no "happy ending" in real life.
What's so funny?
Maybe the shock of losing was too much for him?
When a drama is close to the end,
there is always a huge turn-around that shocks you.
Stop talking nonsense!
You don't even have any Life lef-
That is...
What's going on?
The duel is over, so why didn't it disappear?
That's not a solid vision! It's real!
That's right.
Hollywood Illusion!!
Let... let me go! You cheapskate!
Even if I couldn't win Mai-san in a Duel,
I will be taking Mai-san with me by force!
Wait, you asshole!
Brother...
Come on, bring Mai-san down immediately!
Hold on a second!
Let me go, damn you!
I said let me go!
Mai!
Oh, Mai-san!
Stunt man, hurry up and save Mai-san! What the heck are you doing?!
Mai!
Let go, Mai!
Jounouchi...
But
Don't worry! I'll catch you!
Are you alright, Jounouchi?!
Mai-san, I'm glad you're okay.
Come on.
You're always relying on your stunt doubles!
But... my love is sincere.
Then you should at least save the woman you love with your own hands!
To me, this "boy" looks like more of a hero than you.
I have... lost.
Big brother!
Hey, you alright?
Is it really alright to blow such a big chance?
There's tons of men out there who'd love to have a nice woman like me!
You mean "there's not many men who can handle a feisty woman like me.", don't ya?
Stupid!
Ouch...!
Brother, are you alright?
I'm fine, I'm fine!
Now let's hurry!
The stage of the finals is right over there!
"Preview"
We finally arrived at the stadium under construction.
But... is this really the stage of the tournament finals?
But participants in the tournament finals show up one after another.
Namu-kun? Even Bakura-kun?
And, Malik finally appears before us.
And finally, a giant blimp appears before us.
Eh? The true stage of the finals is this blimp?
Next time! "The Battle Ship Takes Off!"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...