With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
To remember about the past.... I'm not like this...
What a long dream I had...
That's right. A terrifying Dark Bakura was in mine.
By the way.... there were two Yugis... that was really a dream?
That voice is...
Pitch Dark Duel!
Castle of Concealing Darkness
All my Harpies... were defeated...?
It's the rules!
Give me all of your Star Chips!
You've been disqualified! Get lost!
Mai-san!
Yugi!
Are you okay? What's happened?
This saves me a lot of trouble.
My prey came right to me!
Who's that brute-looking guy?
Be careful! He's a Player Killer,
a Duelist hired to take Duelists' Star Chips and kick them off the island!
Player Killer?
Yugi!
I'll disqualify you, just as I did this woman!
Duel with me!
Disqualified? It can't be...!
Mai-san!
Yugi, this is as far as I go.
I can't realize my
dream of dueling with you.
Mai-san...
Losers can shout all they like!
You jerk!
Jounouchi!
Let me go.
I'll kick his lousy ass!
Wait.
You can't solve the problem even
if you beat him up.
But...
There is no other way.
Mai...
Jounouchi-kun, Bakura-kun's right.
I will take care of the things here.
Yugi...
Yugi!
Rest assured, Mai.
I'll beat this block-head and get back your Star Chips!
Now on this island, us Player Killers
are searching for Duelists to hunt.
Yugi Mutou.
It's my foremost mission to defeat you.
I'm really lucky.
Since a suspicious person appeared,
I knew there would be such a thing.
I've grown fed up with Pegasus and his ridiculous stunts!
Fool, this is the order of the Industrial Illusions.
Pegasus-sama...
wouldn't give orders for just anyone.
To defeat you,
the great Pegasus-sama feels he doesn't need to waste his time.
Today is the end of you.
I give these words to you.
I won't lose.
Only I can defeat Pegasus.
Then just try it while you have the chance!
You have no chance of beating me,
as long as this darkness exits.
Darkness?
Be careful, Yugi!
This guy is...!
When the darkness falls on this island,
Duelists cannot rest in peace.
Let your guard down for a second, and the darkness will swallow you!
You'll suffer the same fate as that woman over there!
Listen closely, block-head!
Taking advantage of people in the darkness
is the cowardly act of a thief.
What did you say, you damn kid?!
I'll teach you what happens when you try to scar the honor of a Duelist!
Damn you...!
In this duel
I'll wager all six of my Star Chips!
Don't screw with me!
I will bet all eight of the Star Chips
I stole from that woman.
What?
You lack two of them.
Let's use this to make up for the difference!
What?!
Yugi!
This'll be your compensation!
When you lose this duel ,
Flames will attack you from the hell of darkness!
That's cheap!
I can't believe he's going this far...
Yugi-kun...
I'll let you have a rest for this moment.
I can launch the fire whenever I feel like it!
Don't you ever think of escape.
This is not a good idea.
It's not the time to joke.
Yugi, you don't have to accept these conditions!
Yes, don't do it Yugi!
This isn't even a Duel!
Okay, I accept your challenge.
Yugi!
I will defeat you.
I will shatter your arrogance,
and show you up for what you really are!
See if you live long enough to beat me!
Here I come, Yugi!
Duel!!
Yugi...
It's none of your business.
With your honor as a Duelist on the line,
defeat him!
I'll let you experience the terror of darkness.
My card is the Castle of Concealing Darkness!
It powers up from the Darkness Field!
This, this is...
Watch! The darkness is moving.
What did you say?
This card makes the darkness descend.
So what'll you do now?
In this way
I cannot even see the cards of
my opponent and the monsters.
It's a great view.
I can see your side very well.
But you can see nothing!
Be careful, Yugi!
My Harpies were beaten by this Darkness!
What did you say?
Yugi, you can't gain a power up from the Field Power Source.
But, my Dark Monsters can.
Okay, it's your turn.
Play your card.
My darkness will kill your card here.
I cannot even see what strategies
my opponent uses in the darkness.
Elf Swordsman in Defense Mode.
I use this card... to attack!
What did he just play?
Dark Absolute.
Elf Swordsman was beat down!
Yugi!
Dammit, that attack is way too low!
You have to trust Yugi-kun!
But...
We can only do this now.
You are just at your wits' end.
To eliminate the darkness of my opponent,
I have to destroy the Castle of Concealing Darkness.
But the Defense Power of that castle is 2500.
It can be regarded as an invincible air fortress.
I don't have any card in my hand that can beat something like that.
Shit! What do I do?!
Okay, it's your turn.
There must be some strategies for an attack.
I play Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress in Defense Position!
It's my turn to add a card for another attack.
I call forth a Dark Monster!
There's another Dark-type!
I still can't see what it is!
Yugi, you've already become prey
and can't run away from the darkness.
Predators are waiting to bite you with their fangs in the dark!
I don't even need to play something stronger than you!
Mai-san, isn't there a way to stop him?!
If I knew that, I wouldn't have lost.
I see.
When the darkness is overwhelming, counter it with light.
Okay, I'll try my luck!
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress, attack!
Fireball Barrage!
I've seen it.
It's a pity.
You can never defeat my monster in the dark.
Dark Absolute!
Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress is blasted apart!
It's true that it's hard to find the opponent in the darkness.
Moreover...
although the light gave me a small glimpse,
the darkness will soon come back,
and I won't be able to see their identities once again!
Yugi, you understood.
I am invincible in the darkness.
That's not true!
All you're doing is running away to the darkness!
You're nothing but a coward!
Yugi!
If you want to live, you best learn your place.
You should understand the situation you're in.
Your life is now being grasped in the palm of my hand!
And the result of this duel as well!
Hey, what are you laughing at?
I see. Now I get it.
Know what ?
Your savage heart.
You just told me how to break it.
Don't bullshit me!
When the sun rises in the day,
the darkness will vanish.
At that time, you'll be alone.
Meaning...
And what I'll see at the end of this game...
...is a loser dog with his tail between his legs!
You bastard...! Take back what you just said...!
I found a way to beat the darkness!
What?
This card is my trump.
Your life ends in five turns!
Impossible.
Prepare yourself.
I'll show you what true darkness is!
What ?
What does he intend to do?
I don't know.
But he's not pretending to be confident.
The real darkness?
Don't make me laugh, kid!
You;re just trying to bluff your way out of your current situation!
I have the darkness on my side.
No matter what you try, you have no chance of winning!
No true Duelist gives up a fight
when someone else claims they're going to lose.
What did you say?
I think...
You at least have the pride that most Duelists have.
Then I'll grant you that much.
I'll show you what my trump card is.
What?!
What did he say?
And the card is...
The Sealing Swords of Light!
Sealing Swords... of Light?
These holy swords have the power to
block the enemy Monster attacks for three turns.
Even if they try to hide in the darkness,
in front of the holy swords of light,
they will be exposed from the darkness.
They will be trapped in the light...
having the fate of being destroyed by my card!
I-Impossible...
There's no way a mere card can destroy my darkness!
We'll have our answer in five turns.
It's my turn.
Curse of Dragon in Defense Mode!
And...
I'll cover one more card on the field.
And my turn is over with that.
That card has to be the Sealed Swords of Light...
I'll say it once more.
You only have five turns left!
You dare look down on me!
You damn brat!
Mai-san, is it really alright for him to tell his opponent what his card is?
Maybe...
In this Duel, Yugi is using...
...as another form of weapon other than cards to battle the darkness.
A weapon other than cards?
What's that?
I think that must be words.
Words?
You're right.
If the Player Killer is hiding behind the darkness,
Yugi can see nothing and his attacks won't reach.
But there is one way to reach him.
That's...
His voice... so his words, right?
I see.
Yugi-kun is using his words as a weapon...
That's his true trump against the darkness.
Yugi, show me how you fight...
Yugi!
I've never seen a Duelist as stupid as you!
I'll make you regret ever thinking of doing something so foolish!
My card will send that trump card of yours straight to hell!
The Card-Hunting Reaper!
The Card-Hunting Reaper...!
It'll eliminate that set Magic Card you have on the field!
Reaper of the Cards!
Destroy his Magic Card, the Sealing Swords of Light!
-Yugi!
That card's his trump!
If that card's destroyed, Yugi'll be caught by the God of Death!
Kid!
You're finished once this hits!
Fall into hell!
Card Eraser!!
The sickle stopped moving...
Not able to attack?
What's the meaning of this?!
Wh-What's so funny?
What did you do?!
I really did...
...say that the Sealing Swords of Light was my trump card...
...but I never said it was the card I played on the field!
What?!
The card I placed on the field...
...was the Hexagram Curse!
A Trap Card!
And when your Death God attacked this card,
it fell right into my trap.
When you play a Magic or Trap Card,
the Card-Hunting Reaper is the thing to watch out for.
I figured you had this card in your deck somewhere.
But it's been sealed now.
Now I can play all the Magic Cards I want!
He did it!
Sweet!
That's our Yugi!
To be able to make such judgments, even in that situation...
But he still can't let his guard down.
You bastard!!
You dare deceive me!
What a shame.
You've wasted your turn.
It's my turn now.
This time I'll really play my trump card!
And I'll set one more Magic Card!
You set two Magic Cards on the field?!
Wh-What the?
One more...
What card is it?
Facing the despicable attack of the Player Killer,
Yugi fights the battle with words.
But Yugi's got a flame ring set up at his feet!
It's too dangerous to irritate him!
The Sealing Swords of Light can reveal the Monsters on the field.
Take the chance, Yugi!
Before the darkness shows up again,
defeat the enemy with an invincible card!
Next time!
"Render the Darkness! The Sealing Swords of Light"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship