Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
The Ghouls Attack:
Their Aim is the Red-Eyes Black Dragon
Battle City?
That means, tomorrow, Domino City will become a Duel Monsters battle arena?
Yeah.
There will be a lot of powerful Duelists coming to the city.
That Kaiba...!
He didn't tell me, who was number 2 at the Duelist Kingdom?!
Unforgivable!
Oi, Jounouchi! You aren't thinking of attending, are you?
Of course I am, Honda!
But, what about Shizuka-chan's surgery tomorrow?
The surgery is only temporary.
Even so, I should still be able to make it if I quickly get back here.
Yugi, you'll be attending too, right?
Of course~! But one of the rules in Battle City is the Ante Rule, so I can't afford to lose.
Ante? What's that?
It's betting cards.
Betting cards?
Yeah. The winning player can take one rare card from the
losing player.
What?! Rare card?!
That means... if I lose, this will be taken away?!
Will you be alright? Because that card is worth everything to you.
Just kidding! Don't worry. Red-Eyes is my Goddess of Victory.
He and I have an unbreakable bond of destiny.
If I keep on winning,
I'll get rare card after rare card...
Hold it! When a person gets greedy, bad things will happen!
Ah, that's right! There's another requirement to attend this contest.
Eh? What's that?
The new Duel Disk.
Kaiba-kun's new version of the Virtual Card Battle Machine.
New Duel Disk?
That means...
Damn!
Jounouchi...
It really suits you to be on your knees.
Like a loser dog unable to stand up after a single loss.
The Duel Disks bring back such bad memories.
We don't have it at my place, but that new card shop that opened recently is selling it.
Great! Anyways, let's go buy it first!
I remember it was somewhere around here.
Ah, could it be a shop around the corner?
Great! Let's hurry and go buy it!
Yeah!
Anzu, you know this shop too?
Yesterday, I came with the other Yugi.
I see.
Anzu, thank you for yesterday.
My other self seems to have regained some spirit.
Hey, what did the other Yugi say?
Oh, Battle City stuff.
Oh.
So he really didn't tell him anything about that drawing or that Ishizu woman,
or anything about yesterday at all.
But, I still think it's kinda strange.
I'm certain the other me wouldn't accept the Ante Rule.
He's got no interest in winning rare cards or betting ours.
That's because these 40 cards are picked out from thousands of others.
That's why all our rare cards can't be replaced.
That's why he believes they can't be used for betting.
Although...
I keep thinking the other me is looking for something.
Aha! There it is!
These are really cool!
Seriously...
Honda, take a look at this one!
Amazing!
Yugi will realize soon what the other Yugi is looking for.
Their hearts are too close together to hide anything.
We're comin' in!
Welcome!
Um, are you selling the new Duel Disks?
Oh, You guys are Duelists looking to attend tomorrow's tournament?
There's been a lot of customers like you the past few days.
Then, may I ask what your names are?
Yugi Mutou.
Yugi Mutou...
Aha!
Ah, amazingly strong!
Eh, what is it?
Kaiba Corporation has the whole country's Duelist's information
About the Duelist's level and number of rare cards.
And Duelists above level 5 can receive the Duel Disk for free.
Kaiba-kun has...
Really? This way, he could control the contest's standards?
Yugi-kun's Duelist level is at the amazing level 8.
Congratulations! This is yours.
Th-Thank you!
Dude, I'm Katsuya Jounouchi!
Let's see... Jounouchi-kun, huh?
Ah~ Level 2, Nobody~ What's this "nobody"?
WHAT?! NOBODY!!!?
THAT KAIBA BASTARD!!!
Calm down.
Calm down?! Then what do I do?
Eh, that is...
Level 2 is not qualified to participate.
Why doesn't the runner up in Duelist Kingdom qualify?!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
He has such a powerful rare card, this guy...
I refuse to believe it!
Jounouchi-kun...
The system seems to have malfunctioned.
If you take a look carefully, your at a level 5!
You meet the standards.
Really?
What the...? It seems so.
Then there's no other choice. I'll take the Duel Disk then!
Well then, take this.
Thank you very much!
This is great!
That's a relief, Jounouchi-kun!
Thank you for coming!
Sorry for interrupting.
Ah, it's me. I've found new prey.
It's this late already...
Sorry, but I need to go to the hospital. So then...
I hope Shizuka-chan's surgery will be successful.
Thank you. See ya!
Bye bye!
It's finally time?
Then Jounouchi's heart must be really muddled.
His mom also went to the hospital.
When he was still small, his mom took his sister and left the house.
Really? When she's in surgery, he can't avoid seeing his mom.
Alright!! Tomorrow I need to help connect family relationships!
What? Isn't that a bit too enthusiastic?
That's because Shizuka-chan is Honda-kun's type.
In order to get the new Duel Disk, I was slowed down.
Wait for me, Shizuka.
What is it?! I'm in a hurry right now!
Are you Katsuya Jounouchi?
What the? You know my name?
We bet everything on the name of the Ghouls. We can't afford to let you pass.
Ghouls?!
I think I've seen the name in the newspaper before.
They're a group that Duels with Duelists around the world,
taking away their rare cards; A thieving organization.
Katsuya Jounouchi.
I challenge you to a Duel right here and now!
How can I let you guys go?
Fine then... The rules will be the Battle City's rule.
Of course with Ante as well.
If you lose, I'll take your Red-Eyes!
Damn it...
There's no time...
There's no other way.
Let me take care of you guys.
Duel!!
Shizuka, please calm down.
Once I think about the surgery I get nervous.
Just now I got a phone call from Big brother!
He says he's coming.
Katsuya is...?
My turn!
I Summon Panther Warrior in Attack Mode!
My turn.
I put this monster in Defense Position.
I'll quickly finish you off.
My card is Scapegoat!
This can Special Summon 4 monsters at once.
I sacrifice one of them.
Panther Warrior, Attack!
Come on now, what's wrong?! Hurry and come at me again!
My turn.
Due to Angel's Charity's effect,
I draw 3 cards, then throw away 2.
Next, I put this monster in Defense Position.
What's with this guy?
He challenged me to this Duel, but all he's doing is protecting himself?
Big brother, hurry up and come!
I don't know why you keep defending, but I'm not going to loosen up!
Wyvern Warrior!
Next, I sacrifice 1 Scapegoat!
I use Panther Warrior to attack your set card!
Yes!
This way, the defending monster is gone.
I think the Battle City rules allow you to attack the player directly.
Go, Wyvern Warrior!
Direct Attack the player!
How's that?!
My turn.
Angel's Charity!
What?!
I draw 3 cards, and discard 2 cards.
Next, I put this monster in Defense Position.
Using the same cards again?
I see! I know!
Just now I was thinking what you were planning.
But the truth is, you're just too weak!
I am just too strong, so all you can do is defend.
Now I can easily finish this off.
Let's see... the new rules say,
In order to summon a 7 star monster, what do I need to sacrifice?
Scapegoat can't be used as a Sacrifice Summon.
Panther Warrior and Wyvern Warrior are on my field....
Forget it! I got more than enough sacrifices!
I Summon Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
So that's it! In order to summon a 7 star monster I need 2 sacrifices?
Let's go!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Black Fire Bullet!!
How's that? Red-Eyes' strength!
No wonder you guys want it.
I can't give you this card,
But I'll at least show you his coolness.
Next, we'll determine the winner!
What's so funny?!
You won't have it much longer!
What?!
Draw card.
I have met my unlucky curse.
Come out, Exodia!
What?! Exodia?!
I-Impossible!
Apart from Yugi, there's someone else who has the Exodia card parts?
Indeed, the Exodia card parts is usually a rare card that is very hard to retrieve.
But, I have 3 of each in my deck.
Because of us Ghoul's tactics,
Getting a few rare cards is not a problem.
That's lowly!
We Ghouls don't care what method we use.
What'd you say?
You bastards!
Shit!
I'll take your Red-Eyes Black Dragon now!
Red... Eyes...
Please open the door, Shizuka!
Shizuka, Shizuka, open the door!
Shizuka, I'm begging you!
No, No! Big brother didn't come, I'm not taking the surgery!
Yes. Jounouchi-kun's mom?
Eh?! Jounouchi-kun didn't go to the hospital?!
How's that possible?! He was going there last night!
Yugi!
Anzu!
Honda-kun.
Yugi, did Jounouchi really disappear?
That idiot. What's he doing.
Honda, whats up with that?
Borrowed it off my senpai.
If we need to search the streets, using it will be faster.
If Jounouchi-kun doesn't go to the hospital,  Shizuka-chan won't take the surgery!
Don't tell me, that guy was in an accident?
I think the doctor who's doing the operation needs to go to America to operate on someone else tonight.
If they don't start before noon then they won't do it.
There's no time.
Alright, let's split up and search!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
If you're here, please reply!
That guy, he really disappeared.
I'm sorry, Shizuka!
Hey! Jounouchi!
Honda? What's wrong?
What's wrong?!
What're you doing here?!
You should be at the hospital!
Jounouchi, what happened?
Last night when I was heading to the hospital, the Ghouls appeared.
Ghouls?
A dark organization that hunts people's rare card.
I lost the Duel and Red-Eyes was taken away.
What?!
Jounouchi, who cares about a simple card?
More importantly, you have to get to the hospital soon!
It's unforgivable!
To me, Red-Eyes is the most important card for I need to win!
But, he was...
Let it go!
If you don't go to the hospital, Shizuka-chan won't take her surgery!
At important times like this, you should go and be there for her!
Shizuka-chan will then have more courage!
Shizuka...!
It's useless, right now I can't comfort Shizuka.
I...
I enjoy watching you and and Yugi using cards.
I watch you guys play cards and your bond gets stronger and stronger!
But, because of a lost card, you want to lose your relationship with your only sister!?
There's no time!
That is...!
Honda-kun and... Jounouchi-kun!
Shizuka! Open the door! Please!
If it's like this, I think it's not possible.
Doctor...!
Please wait!
K-Katsuya...
Mom, let me talk with her.
Shizuka! Shizuka!
Shizuka! Take the surgery!
Open the door!
No! Big brother is a liar!
Why didn't you come?!
Why?! Why weren't you beside me?!
I was afraid, so afraid.
Sorry.
When I was coming yesterday, I bumped into something sad.
My brain was all empty, only thinking of myself.
I am a terrible person.
But my friend helped me out.
He kept on looking me, telling me about your situation.
He let me know no matter how painful, how hateful it is,
I still can't forget those who need me, those who I worry for.
The most important thing is the relationship between people.
I'm sorry, Shizuka.
I have forgotten about this.
I hope you won't be like this.
No matter what time, we need to be together.
Shizuka.
Big brother!
Shizuka!
I'm sorry, Mother!
Thank you, Katsuya!
Really?! The surgery was a success?
Yay!
Thank you, Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun, tell me what happened.
Yugi, this upcoming Battle City is very terrible.
You've got to be careful. Those guys...
Whats wrong, Jounouchi-kun?
Nothing, nothing much.
Then, I'll see you at Battle City!
Yeah! See you.
Ghouls?
What kind of people are they?
Yugi.
I'm not gonna involve you in my troubles anymore.
I'll get Red-Eyes with my own two hands!
It's finally here! Battle City's opening!
At Kaiba-kun's luxurious opening session,
Powerful duelists all gathered and readied for battle in Domino.
Eh? The first battle in Battle City is the rare card hunter who stole Jounouchi's Red Eyes and Yugi?
Do your best! Yugi!
Defeat Jounouchi's enemy!
You must get Red-Eyes back!
Next time! Fierce Fight! Battle City Begins.
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...