Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
With an aura of calm determination,
Rafael, one of the three Musketeers of Doma, was waiting for me.
His battle spirit has told me just how strong of an opponent he is.
You say we are both comrades who are fighting against fate, Rafael?
But I will not lose!
Justice that allows you to destroy this world... Such a thing does not exist!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Truth about Doma"
I'll never use The Barrier of Orichalcos in this Duel!
If this attack gets through, it will be vital damage to you!
Go ahead, Guardian Grarl!
Swift Cleave Attack!
What?!
Too bad.
The Special Ability of Kuribi is that it can make the opponent's Attack zero.
Hence ending the Battle Phase for one turn only.
I see. I've been underestimating your charming little servants.
I have the feeling that both of them are on par at the moment.
But Doma's got this "Barrier of Orichalcos" card...
Thing is, when's the guy gonna activate the thing?
Good.
Once we cross up ahead, we'll reach Death Valley!
Just hang on, Yugi!
T-This all right!?
There's nothing "all right" about this at all~!
I've heard it from my grandpa.
That Yugi has two different personalities.
The original Yugi, and the Yugi who holds the spirit of the nameless Pharaoh.
Yup. The other Yugi is very dependable.
And he's incredibly powerful when it comes to Dueling.
So I have no worries about him winning his match.
Anzu, you like the Yugi who used to be King, right?
Why are you saying that all of a sudden?
If so, we won't become love rivals.
Because the one I like is the original Yugi.
When I first met Yugi...
He purposely lost to me in our Duel in order to get an important message across.
Darling is really very kind.
No matter what the situation may be, he's always very considerate to others.
Yeah...
Just like you said, everything's going to be all right.
"King" Yugi and Darling...
As long as the two work together, nobody can defeat them.
My turn!
At this moment, the magical effects of Purity of the Cemetery are activated!
You should have three Monsters in your Graveyard.
Thus, you will be inflicted 300 points of damage to your Life Points!
The other me, please don't be anxious.
We still have a chance against him.
Ah. I know, Partner.
I activate the Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
I can draw two cards from my deck
The one card that can get me out of this predicament...
...is still asleep in my deck!
And that is...
I activate the Kuriboh Brothers'
Special Ability!
To Summon Kuribabylon!
And then I use Kuribabylon as a sacrifice!
The Kuribohs that were Special Summoned by a Magic Card's effect
cannot be used as a sacrifice to tribute for another Monster.
He activated that Combination Effect for the mere purpose of a Tribute Summon.
And the Monster that I'm Summoning...
Come out! Black Magician Girl!
Black Magician Girl...
Master! Defeat that Evil God!
Otherwise, both of our worlds will enter a path of doom!
I did not forget the promise I made back then.
As long as Doma is not defeated...
Peaceful days will not return for both this world and the Duel Monsters world!
Take a look, Rafael!
This is my trump card!
The Monocle of Timaeus!!
This is... Timaeus!
Timaeus!
Combine with Black Magician Girl!
And create a new power!
I Summon Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Wh-What was that card just now?
He suddenly took that card from his hand an' combined it wit' the Monster on the field!
I knew it. These guys got their hands on some really special cards!
Go forth! Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Attack Guardian Grarl!
Impossible!
This Monster's Attack Power is lower than Guardian Grarl's!
Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl's Special Effect!
It calls for me to discard one card from my hand to the Graveyard.
All damage I receive is reduced to zero and the opposing Monster is destroyed!
What?!
Go on!
Black Dragon Burst!!
So this is the power of the Legendary Dragons...!
I did it...!
Not yet...
Reverse card! Self Sacrifice!!
Wh-What in the world?!
Self Sacrifice is activated when one of my Monsters is destroyed by battle...
By paying 1000 Life Points, I can return the selected Monster back to the field using this card.
So my Guardian Grarl... goes unscathed.
This guy...
...didn't hesitate to use his own Life in exchange for his Monster's revival...
Why would he go to such lengths?
Nameless Pharaoh...
We will not lose to you and your team.
Do you know the reason behind that?
It's because we of Doma hold a strength you guys don't.
A "strength" that we don't have?
Yes.
The strength to accept the darkness we possess in our hearts.
The darkness... in your hearts...?
Just like how we have light in our hearts, we too have darkness within.
If this world works like a scale - a balance acting as its foundation...
Each opposite side would balance the light and darkness of our hearts.
And this would be obvious reasoning.
If your link is with the "light in the heart,"
then us of Doma are bonded by a strong belief in the "darkness in the heart."
Believing in the bonds of the darkness within your hearts...?
You are right.
"Darkness in the heart" will forever be ahead of "light in the heart."
It lies in the deepest part of despair.
For people like you who pretend to be righteous all the time,
you could never come to terms with the depth of such logic!
The depths of our despair and sorrow is unparalleled to anyone's on this Earth!
That kind of thinking is wrong!
Revenge and destruction...
Even if you accomplish these things, then what?!
You'd only be left with a vast emptiness!
That's right.
If you do things half-heartedly, then you will most likely find only emptiness.
But...
What if even "emptiness" is not remaining?
What?!
Let me tell you our Doma's true purpose.
And that is "nothing."
We desire to bring the history of mankind back to "zero"!
What did you say?!
Damn!
What're they babblin' 'bout? I can't hear a single thing!
You said you wanted to return the history of mankind to zero?
Doma has always served as the "observers of history" from the beginning.
Observers?
From the first day "history" as we know it was first created, there has stood an organization behind all of it.
And that's Doma!
Doma has always been guiding people on their paths.
Always trying to lead them.
At other times, Doma would give human society a push.
Sometimes, unjust methods are used just to guide history.
However, humans have rebelled against Doma's ideas.
Yet none of them know
where it is they stand.
Just like that, about 1000 years of history passed and people made the same mistakes over and over again.
Yugi...
Why do you suppose that of all the living things on Earth, only humans are blessed with "wisdom"?
That's because it is the fate of human beings to act as guardians and protect this planet.
Humans are guardians?
In spite of that...
Just open your eyes and look around you!
At the ends of this horizon, there are humans who are stained with selfish desires.
And they are decaying this planet.
Endlessly shedding meaningless fresh blood.
The foolishness of humans has gone far beyond that of Doma's expectations!
Not long from now, humans will destroy this world.
Thus, Doma has adjusted its aim.
Doma has chosen to no longer guide the history of mankind.
But lead it towards the path of "reset."
You mean to reset the history of mankind?!
Don't talk nonsense!
Are you going to decide that based on your judgment alone?!
This is not our judgment.
But the judgment of the lord that is of the highest ranked in Doma.
The lord who manages this Earth and gave it paradise in the past...
The person who's managed this world in the past?
Nameless Pharaoh...
There should be "darkness" that lies dormant within the deepest thresholds of your heart.
Have you ever thought about that?
What kind of King were you in the past?
The things you have done when you obtained absolute power and authority.
The things... I've done...?
Can you dare say that you were a good king?
Don't tell me that city was my...
Impossible!
I... I don't believe in such things!
There is no darkness within my heart at all!
Then you should use the "light" within your heart that you believe in and prove it to me!
Nameless Pharaoh.
It's my turn.
I set two cards in reverse on my field.
Then I activate a Magic Card.
Exchange?
Exchange is a Magic Card that allows you to trade one card in your hand with your opponent.
We only have one card in each of our hands.
Thus, we can only trade those cards.
Necromancy...
This is a card that allows Monsters to be revived from your opponent's Graveyard.
I have not even one Monster in my Graveyard.
So this card has no use to you even if you hold it.
Now.
Give me your card.
Please accept it...
Yugi... This is your card of fate.
My "card of fate"?
Impossible...!
This card is...
What?
What cards did they trade?
Th-This card is...
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Yugi, you are holding a fragment of the Orichalcos you took from Gurimo.
As I said earlier...
In this Duel, I will not be using the The Barrier of Orichalcos.
You're the one who will be using it!
You should know the power of this card.
If someone who doesn't have a determined heart uses this card,
That person will become a prisoner in the darkness of his heart.
But for a strong Duelist like yourself, you should be able to control it well.
If you deny having any darkness in your heart,
prove it to me by being able to control that card!
Other Me!
You must not use that card!
Partner...
I can feel the evil energy from that card...
I understand, Partner.
Even if I don't use this card...
My turn!
At this instant, the effect of Purity of the Cemetery's Continuous Effect is activated!
You have five Monsters in your Graveyard!
As such, you will be inflicted 500 points of damage to your Life Points!
Go! Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl!
Attack Guardian Grarl once again!
Trap Card!
Crystal Seal!
What!?
Black Magician Girl!
Monsters that are sealed by the crystal...
Not only can they not attack...
They are also unable to be sacrificed.
But if the trapped Monster's Attack Power changes,
this seal will be destroyed.
The terrifying power of the Legendary Dragon...
As long as I can remove that threat entirely,
victory will surely side with me.
Black Magician Girl...
I will definitely save you...!
I set one Monster in face-down Defense Mode!
With this, my turn is over!
No matter what happens, he won't use the The Barrier of Orichalcos?
But...
My turn!
Magic Card!
Rod of Silence!
Rod of Silence can increase the Defense Power of a Monster equipped with this card by 500 points!
Then I activate the effect of Rod of Silence!
It can guide Guardian Kay'est onto the field!
Guardian Grarl, destroy Yugi's Defense Position Monster!
Swift Cleave Attack!!
Big Shield Gardna...!
My attack has not ended yet.
Guardian Kay'est, Direct Attack Yugi!
Pure Water Beam!!
With this, I end my turn.
Yugi, I guess we will know who the victor is in the next turn.
We're not through yet!
Right this very moment, thanks to the effects of Purity of the Cemetery,
your Life Points will fall another 600 point values!
If this carries on, you will have no chance of winning.
You were unable to prove the "light" in your heart.
And you will be defeated by me.
I... will be defeated here?
I promised them that I'd save both our worlds...!
I... must not... lose in a place like this!!
I activate the Magic Card, Treasure from Heaven!
Because of this card's effect,
both players can draw until they have six cards in their hands!
It's pointless, Yugi...
If I can use this card...
Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl's Attack Power would rise to 3100.
And she can be revived.
The only move that can change my predicament...
You can't! Other Me!
Partner!
You can't use this card!
But...
He's just waiting for you to use the card!
But if things keep going this way, I'm bound to lose!
Partner, this is my battle!
One that bets my
way of justice and my beliefs!
Other Me...!
I'm going to activate this card from my hand!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
That is...
What is that light?
Yugi! It's Yugi!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
After being pressed into a corner,
Yugi finally decided to use The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Dragon Knight Black Magician Girl becomes a Dark Monster, and her Attack Points go up!
Which should be able to break the seal of the crystal...
Ah! Timaeus!
Rafael was waiting for this the whole time!
I beg you! Please don't lose, Yugi!
If you lose, this world will...
Next!
"The Darkness Within Yugi -
Timaeus Disappears"
Duel standby!