A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Magic Card, Chaos Ritual!
I now sacrifice my two Monsters, whose total Levels equal 8 to activate the Chaos Ritual!
One soul shall merge with light!
The other soul shall merge with the darkness!
Between light and darkness, the gateway to chaos is opened!
What!?
The Chaos Soldier descends!
It's the legendary strongest warrior...?
Chaos Blade!!
I've beaten Harpie's Pet Dragon!
"Brutal: The Heavy Metal Deck"
The first round of the tournament...
Yugi Mutou VS Mai Kujaku.
The winner is Yugi Mutou!
He advances to the final round!
Alright!
You did it, Yugi!
Thanks, guys!
And my other self as well!
Congratulations, Yugi boy.
That was a splendid Duel!
Th-That bastard!
Pegasus...!
In order to get my grandpa, as well as Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun back...
I have to make it to the final round!
And defeat you!
We will now continue with the second round of the tournament!
Keith Howard. Katsuya Jounouchi. Please enter the Duel Ring.
A-Alright.
It's my time to shine.
Listen up, Jounouchi.
Calm down.
Try writing something three times on your hand.
Back off, would you?!
You're making me more nervous!
Do your best, Jounouchi-kun!
You better win!
Right.
You bet I will!
Like I said, write something three times on your hand!
Man, shut up already! You're pissing me off!
What?! You're stomping on my act of friendship?!
W-Will he be alright?
Dunno...
Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun.
Jounouchi-kun...?
Yugi, I'm gonna win... no matter what.
And when I do...
And when you do, we'll both play at our best!
Right.
I won't run away or hold back.
We'll have a fight at our full strength!
Mmm-hm!
Go on, Jounouchi!
You can do it!
That Keith bastard's not there.
I'm sleepy~
Keith! You gotta get your ass in the ring too!
Huh? What's this?
This little baby's gonna seriously Duel against me?
Against the great Bandit Keith?!
I told you this already.
That I'd kick your ass with my cards.
Ho~? You're gonna kick my ass?
Now then, please present your entry card.
Here ya go.
Kid, show him yours, too.
He's so arrogant...
Huh?
Please present your card.
R-Right.
H-Huh? I was sure it was in my jacket pocket...!
H-Huh?
D-Don't tell me... Jounouchi lost his card?
It's Jounouchi-kun we're talking about, so it's possible.
That idiot!
Hey, hey, hey!
Don't that mean he can't even Duel, Pegasus-san?
J-Just wait a minute! I know I've got it!
Indeed...
Anyone without the entry card will be disqualified.
N-No way...
There's no way he has it.
Cuz this card is the same card I stole from you.
Now I've reserved a spot for my great self in the final match, without even having to fight.
Jounouchi!
Did you drop the card somewhere?
It's possible I dropped it on my way to the ring.
I'll go check the hallway!
Five minutes!
What?!
The second round of the tournament finals will commence in five minutes.
We will wait for you no longer than that.
In the case you cannot present the entry card to me...
...you will be instantly disqualified!
That's not fair! He can hardly make it to his room and come back in five minutes!
The rules have been determined.
We will not make any exceptions!
Run and run some more, Jounouchi!
Shit...
After making it this far...
You think I'll give up after making it this far?!
Hey, don't ya think your clock is a bit slow?
It's correct.
But more importantly, in the case you're not in the arena, you'll be disqualified as well!
What?
Jesus... What a damn pain in the ass...
Shit...
Where'd it go?
I already gave Jounouchi-kun one of my cards...
This is the only one I have left now...
Yo!
Shouldn't we just disqualify him now?
He ain't comin' back.
What'd you say?!
Why are you so sure about that?!
It's real simple!
He's just a baby who don't know shit about cards.
He may be a moron,
but he's at least intelligent enough to know he stands no chance against me in cards.
He gave up on the Duel before it even began!
He said he's looking for his card, but he's just looking for a place to hide!
He's probably off crying somewhere in the castle...
...and won't be comin' back any time soon, don't ya think?
There's no way that's true!
What?
Jounouchi-kun's not the kind of man who would run away!
He'll be coming back for sure!
And then he'll fight you!
Somehow, I really doubt that.
Just one minute remains!
No way!
He won't make it in time.
Shit! What are you doing, Jounouchi?!
Jounouchi-kun...
I can't find the entry card anywhere...
I came to this island, and won several times, even if it was just luck...
Yet...
To come this far and have my dream crushed...
Why am I so freaking stupid?!
Shizuka...
I hope you can forgive me...
Stand up, Jounouchi!
Save those tears for if you lose the Duel!
Moron!
It's just a runny nose!
Shit...
It won't stop coming...!
Here.
Just clean it up. It's disgraceful.
This handkerchief... is already wet...
I heard about your little sister from Anzu-chan.
Jounouchi, don't give up on your desires so easily.
Those tears for your little sister...
No, a runny nose, right?
Well, whatever it is.
Don't give up on them.
It's sure to come true.
Th-This is...
Wait!
Mai Kujaku!
I don't need it anymore.
Mai...
Why did you do this for me...?
You don't have the time to stand around staring!
R-Right.
Jounouchi!
W-W-What is it?
You better win!
Of course!
Man, why do you think?
Isn't it obvious it's because we're friends?
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
So he came back to admit his loss, eh?
The entry card!
Satisfied now?
Im-
I'm holding his card!
Indeed. You are hereby permitted to participate in the tournament.
Making us worry like that...
Well, Keith. Let's get this Duel started already.
You little...!
It sucks, but I'll take you on!
All that awaits you is a living hell, though!
Then I'm gonna beat you in hell!
You little brat...!
We will now commence with the second round of the tournament finals!
The Keith Howard VS Katsuya Jounouchi Duel will now begin!
-Go! Take him down!
-Go get him!
Beat him, Jounouchi-kun!
Duel Start!!
-DUEL!!
We will now commence with the second round of the tournament finals!
The Keith Howard VS Katsuya Jounouchi Duel will now begin!
Duel Start!!
Beat him, Jounouchi-kun!
You better prepare yourself.
The former U.S. Champion, the great Bandit Keith's,
gonna send you to hell with the strongest deck!
That don't impress me in the least!
I made it to the Best 8 in the Intercity Championship!
Man. You sure are full of yourself, brat.
My turn.
First I'll play this guy in Defense Position.
It's started.
This is going to be a tough Duel.
What? He's won several tough Duels and made it all the way here.
Jounouchi!
We're with you on this!
Go get 'im! You aren't an amateur anymore!
Do your best, Jounouchi-kun!
Thanks, you guys.
Just you watch.
I'm going to win no matter what!
And I'll use the prize money to heal Shizuka's eyes!
I'll place a Monster face-down in Defense Position and end my turn!
I know your deck's filled with a bunch of weaklings!
Disappear!
Pendulum Torture Machine in Attack Position!
A Machine Monster?!
Go!
Eliminate that Defense Monster of his!
Ultimator!
Do it!
Splitting Blade Death!!
Jounouchi...!
No, that's just fine.
Huh?
Jounouchi-kun used the Ultimator to lure his opponent into using Attack Mode.
So he can play a Monster stronger than his opponent on the next turn.
So Keith uses Machine Monsters...?
But why...?
Come on, it's your turn.
Not even playing any set cards?
You're just asking for a killing!
Go!
Mage Knight Giltia in Attack Position!
Good!
Jounouchi has more Attack Points on his side!
Here goes!
Soul Spear!!
What?!
His attack didn't work?!
No way!
Why?!
Wh-What's going on here, Yugi?
You fell for it!
My Machine Monsters are equipped with a special Fullmetal Anti-Magic Armor!
Magic Attacks won't work on them!
So that's it!
That's why he uses Machine Monsters!
Now all his Magic Cards have been sealed away!
Shit!
Do something already, Jounouchi!
My turn!
Land Ironclad TM-1 Launcher Spider!
Another Machine Monster!
What's with all these uncute Monsters he keeps playing?!
Do it!
Shit!
How's that, kid?
You're no match for me the way you are now!
He's strong...
As expected of the former U.S. Champion...
He keeps busting out more and more powerful cards one after another...
Wow...
The power of Machine Monsters is unreal!
D-Do you think he can win, Yugi?
I'm guessing Bandit Keith's entire deck is made up of
Machine-type cards, a Heavyweight Power Deck.
Making all Magic Attacks ineffective,
he then backs his opponent into a corner with his overwhelming Attack Power.
But such powerful attacks always have some kind of weak point.
There's got to be a way to counter them!
None of my cards have a high enough Attack Power to beat them...
I set a card on the field face-down!
Then a Monster in Defense Mode!
Probably just another weak Monster!
Even if I beat that shitty card in Defense Mode,
that brat's Life Points won't decrease.
There's another way!
I've got a way to trap this idiot and end the match quickly.
I set a card face-down on the field.
Then I'll play this guy in face-down Defe-
Whoa...
My hand slipped.
I'll put this Monster face-down in Defense Mode and end my turn!
I saw another un-cute creature for a second there...
What was that just now?
You couldn't hide that from me, Keith.
That wasn't a Machine Monster just now...
It was a Dark-Attribute Monster called Devil Zoa.
It's not protected from magic!
The Flame Swordsman!
Good!
I drew a good card!
With this...
Alright, here's your chance!
Go, Jounouchi!
It's strange...!
Uh, what is?
Flame Swordsman in Attack Position!
Devil Zoa has 2600 Attack Points...
...and only 1900 Defense Points...
And so...?
I see!
I'll then use a Magic Card!
I was thinking that it wasn't immune to Magic Attacks...
...but Devil Zoa still has more than enough Attack Points.
No one thinking logically would play it in Defense Mode.
Salamandra!
The Flame Swordsman's Attack Power goes up by 700 points!
Then he showed the card while playing it in Defense Mode on purpose...!
Jounouchi!
Battle!!
You idiot!
Trap Card, activate!
What?!
Magic Reflection Armor - Metal Force!!
It's body turns to metal and both it's Attack and Defense Power go up!
Metal armor?!
But this is no ordinary metal armor!
The Magical Reflection Armor takes the Attack Power of Magic Attack thrown at him,
and throws it back at you, with its own Attack Points added to the total!
What'd you say?!
Flame Swordsman!
I can't believe you fell for such an obvious trap!
You seriously are still an amateur!
Jounouchi-kun...
It's my turn.
Kid, this match is done.
What?!
For starters, that Monster you have in Defense Position...
I'm gonna take care of it with this card.
That's the Defense Seal!
This is too obvious!
It may be just a weak Monster,
but it's suiting to be the end of you!
Not good!
If Jounouchi-kun gets hit with Metal Devil Zoa's attack, it's all over!
Jounouchi!
And now it's game over for you!
Metal Devil Zoa!
Attack the Axe Raider!
Metal Devil Zoa disappeared?!
That's...!
What the?!
Ta-daa~!
Trap Card, activate!
The Skewer Pitfall!
What?!
A Trap Card, you said?!
Awesome!
That was awesome, Jounouchi-kun!
Now the Metal Devil Zoa will be destroyed,
and a quarter of it's Attack Power is subtracted from Keith's Life Points!
What's wrong, Keith?
You ain't much of a U.S. Champion if you fall into "such an obvious trap"!
This damn brat...!
I can't believe it...
For our Jounouchi to hold his own against the former U.S. Champion like that...
Duels have a certain rhythm to it.
Those who can direct that rhythm are the ones who win in the end!
Jounouchi-kun is learning how to lean that flow towards him!
Right.
Now it's Jounouchi-kun's turn to take the lead.
Alright!
Go, Jounouchi!
My turn!
I'll first set a card face-down!
Keith, this is a Trap Card, so you best be careful!
He's got the upper hand now!
But he shouldn't get this cocky...
Don't you underestimate me!
You're a hundred years too early to fool me with an obvious bluff like that!
And then I'll return Axe Raider to Defense Mode.
Then this guy, in Attack Position!
The Beast-Warrior, Garoozis!
Attack the Pendulum Torture Machine!
Battle!
Shit...
What's wrong, Keith?
This is shameful for the ex-U.S. Champion!
Shut the hell up, you brat!
Launcher Spider!
Blow the Garoozis to smithereens!
There ain't even a corpse left.
You're naïve, Keith!
You just activated my Trap Card!
What?
Chain-Equipped Boomerang!
The card I activate it with gets a power-increase of 500 points!
Go, Garoozis!
Axe Crush!!
He did it!
It's only a slight difference, but Jounouchi-kun took the lead!
I can't believe Jounouchi has gotten this strong now!
Im certain Jounouchi-kun's wish to save his little sister reached the cards!
Go take him down, Jounouchi!
You're the strongest today!
Why...?!
Why am I losing to this amateur...?!
It's a shame, Keith.
Looks like the one who's gonna see a living hell...
...is you!
"Preview"
Not bad, Jounouchi!
You can do it! You can win!
With your Time Magician/Baby Dragon combo...
...you can easily destroy Keith's Machine Monsters!
Eh? The Time Magic was beaten?
The Time Machine can bring back a Monster destroyed in the previous turn?!
You can do it, Jounouchi!
Don't give up hope!
Next time!
"Time's Up! Red-Eyes Black Metal Dragon"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship