Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The power of the resurrected Great Wicked God Zorc is way too great!
The way things are going, we can't win!
We decided our only shot
was to retrieve the Millennium Items that were scattered to the desert...
But Isis ended up a victim in the process!
And Shimon soon followed, who tried to fight with Exodia!
I won't waste your sacrifices!
"Summon! The Three Illusionary Beast Gods"
Because of the curse released from the black box of the Cursed Necro Twins,
my Graveyard has been destroyed.
Thus, the Monsters from my Graveyard, along with my Magic and Trap Cards,
now wander the field as lost spirits.
But rest assured, Yugi.
None of these guys can attack, defend or activate their effects.
I've got a bad feeling about this...
But I can't afford to lose!
I end my turn!
It's my turn!
Draw!
Stop right there!
I use this moment to activate Necro Soldier's Special Effect!
If this card is on the field when my opponent is in Standby Phase,
another Necro Soldier will appear!
Additionally, the Special Effect of this Necro Soldier on the field will also activate.
Another!
No way...!
He got three Necro Soldiers at once!
Its Attack and Defense are zero,
but the Monster's going to be trouble...
But...
On this turn, my Silent Swordsman raises to Level Five!
Continuing from my hand, I Summon Silent Magician LV. 0 from my hand!
Marshmallon!
Silent Magician!
And Silent Swordsman!
Attack the three Necro Soldiers!
Yeah! This'll get rid of the Monsters on Bakura's field!
Why?!
The Silent Swordsman stopped its attack!
A Permanent Trap!
I activated the Narrow Corridor.
What?!
What's The Narrow Corridor?!
Because of this Trap's effects,
The opposing player can't attack more than two times during a turn.
Too bad, huh?
Go ahead and Summon all the Monsters you like.
Because you can't attack more than two times.
And...
Look, Yugi!
Yes. The Monsters you destroyed have remained on the field as wandering spirits.
So he increased the Monsters on his field to get me to attack...!
It's my turn! I draw!
When the opposing player draws,
Silent Magician advances to Level One!
Its Attack Power increases by 500 points!
Perfect timing to have drawn this...
Yugi! I just completed the final step in the ceremony of death.
Ceremony of death?
I activate the Continuous Magic Card, All Killing Death Card, from my hand!
All Killing Death Card?!
Correct.
When this card is on the field,
On your End Phase, the player has to discard as many
cards as there are Monsters on the field, including the wandering spirits,
from the top of your deck into the Graveyard.
For every Monster on the field...?
To the Graveyard?
That means...!
But if we're discarding cards from our decks, you also have to take a big risk!
You still don't understand, Yugi?!
Such a pity!
Since I, you know, don't have a Graveyard to discard my cards to!
Meaning this effect, Yugi...
...will only be activating for you alone!
A Deck Destruction Combo that only activates against me!
You said it!
Shit...! This combo is really bad news!
Yugi...!
And the Monsters will only continue to increase.
I Summon the Necro Mannequin in Defense Mode!
I then activate my dormant Permanent Trap, Necrecycle!
When I have a Necro Mannequin on the field,
I can Special Summon a Necro Mannequin once per turn.
The amount of Monsters increased!
Now, Yugi!
How many Monsters do you suppose I can gather on the field?
Instant death!
On your next turn, Yugi,
I plan to teach you just how strong the fear behind that meaning is!
Turn end!
Pharaoh!
I will handle-
No!
Let me handle this.
Pharaoh!
But...!
Believe in me.
And believe in the future carved out for us by the friends we lost.
We must not let their deaths be in vain.
Zorc! I will not let you do as you please anymore!
Using the power of the Gods, the Three Illusionary Beast Gods, I shall topple you!
Come to us, Three Illusionary Beast Gods!!
Obelisk the God of War!
Osiris the Dragon God of the Heavens!
Ra the Winged Dragon God of the Sun!
Three Illusionary Beasts, I summon thee!
There's no way of knowing how this match will end now, Bakura...
Tch... Went and Summoned the Three Illusionary Beasts, eh?
Yugi! This is shaping up to be the last turn.
There's no longer any need for us to limit the scope to this mere table!
Quite literally, the fate of the entire world
is going to be decided with the results of this game.
I have no more need for this body.
I'm going to return to my original body!
You fiend...
So you really are Zorc!
Come, Yugi!
Let us go!
To the battlegrounds!
I wouldn't have it any other way!
Great Wicked God Zorc! I swear to defeat you with the power of the Gods!
Come, divine Gods!
Do not believe you will conquer the powers of darkness!
Those are...
Obelisk!
Osiris!
Ra!
A battle of gods is about to begin!
Go forth, Obelisk the Great War God!
Pummel the Wicked God using the anger of the very Earth itself!
The power of the gods...!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Deliver upon the Wicked God Heaven's Judgment!
I-Incredible...!
And Ra the Winged Dragon God of the Sun!
Use your rage to burn the Wicked God to cinders!
Finish him!!
Three Illusionary Beasts, attack together!
God Hand Crusher!!
Thunder Force!!
God Phoenix!!
Destroy him!
Did they get him?
That's God!
So the Wicked God has been...!
Was Zorc beaten...?
The sky...!
Our God was victorious!
They did it!
We did it, Prince!
No...
He's coming...!
What in the...?!
The sun is...!
What terror...!
What is that...?!
Is Zorc creating a solar eclipse?!
The darkness is completely consuming the world...!
Three Illusionary Beasts!
Defeat Zorc before this land is engulfed by the darkness!
The darkness lies in my hands!
The sun...!
Osiris! Ra!
Futile!
My darkness is now far greater than that of the light!
Let my darkness slaughter the Three Illusionary Beast Gods!
Dark Slasher!!
Obelisk!
Osiris!
Ra!
No way...!
The Gods...! This can't be real...!
Impossible...!
He defeated the gods?!
The Gods were beaten...!
It's all over now!
Your Gods are now nothing
more than statues!
I will smash them into pieces along with your hope!
Prince!
My turn!
Draw!
This moment, Silent Swordsman advances from Level Five to Level Six!
But the Trap Effect of my Necrecycle will continue!
Allowing me to Summon another Necro Mannequin!
Now the total number of Monsters has increased to 11!
Dammit...!
As long as he's got Necrecycle, the number of Monsters will increase every turn!
And because of the permanent effect of The Narrow Corridor,
Yugi is only permitted
to attack twice per turn!
Even supposing you manage to destroy some of them,
the Monsters will not truly leave the field.
Because of the effect of the black box from Cursed Necro Twins,
they will simply remain as wandering spirits.
So what'll you do, Yugi?
Even so...
I'll use Silent Swordsman LV. 6 against a Necro Soldier,
and the Silent Magician LV. 1 to attack a Necro Mannequin!
Go!
You're pretty damn merciless!
What pointless massacre!
Now then, this is a ceremony, Yugi...
Including all the Monsters on the field,
you'd better discard the appropriate number of cards from your deck.
There's 11 Monsters on the field!
Hey! If he discards 11 cards, he's practically splitting his deck in half!
Now you've only got 17 cards left in your deck.
But isn't it for the best?
Huh, Yugi?
Since you chose the red box from the Necro Twins,
your Life will increase by 200 points for all those 11 cards you sent to the Graveyard.
Turn end!
It's my turn!
I draw!
I Summon Necro Wall in Defense Mode!
The Special Effect of
Necro Wall allows me to
Special Summon a Necro Wall Token for every Undead-Type Monster
on my field during my End Phase.
What?!
No way!
I have two Undead-Type Monsters on my side of the field.
Which means I can Special Summon two more Necro Wall Tokens.
That leaves us with 14 Monsters.
I'll finish my turn on that note.
My turn!
Draw!
I'm using my Silent Swordsman LV. 7 and my Silent Magician LV. 2
to attack your two Necro Wall Tokens!
Sweet! His tokens don't enter the Graveyard! They're just simply destroyed!
So they won't come onto the field as ghosts either!
I'm then activating a Magic Card from my hand!
I activate Aria from the Other Side!
It lets me select one Magic Card that has been removed from the game.
I can then activate it!
The card I'm choosing is...
Spirit Sword of Sealing!
I'm using Spirit Sword of Sealing to seal away Silent Swordsman LV. 7!
You're sealing the Silent Swordsman?
But by doing that, he managed to reduce the number of Monsters on the field by one.
I end my turn!
Then get on with discarding them, Yugi...
11 cards from your deck.
11?!
That leaves the amount
of cards in your deck...
...at just five.
On your next turn, your deck will be completely destroyed.
It's my turn!
Draw!
I could just end my turn right away and let your turn come...
But I plan to snuff out the remaining life you have during this turn!
I Summon Necro Pot in Attack Mode!
Go attack Silent Magician!
He's nuts!
Silent Magician has higher Attack Points!
That one left me with only 200 Life Points remaining!
Just kidding.
I activate Necro Pot's Special Effect!
If this Monster is destroyed in battle,
your opponent must send one card from the top of their deck
to the Graveyard for each multiple of 300 Battle Damage.
That totals four!
Yugi...
Send four cards from your deck to the Graveyard!
Did he say four...?!
That means Yugi's deck only has...
...one card?!
I guess this truly is "the end".
Because Silent Swordsman was removed from the field,
you managed to spare
yourself a single card.
That ends my turn!
Now then... There's 14 Monsters on my side of the field.
And only one card left in your deck.
There's nothing left for you to do.
Yugi!
You're damn weak!
Can't you do anything
without the king around?
Yugi!
Don't listen to what this guy says!
If you call yourself a Duelist, don't give up until the very end!
But I'm already...
Other Me...
I thought I had always been fighting by the Other Me's side...
But maybe I was always just chasing your shadow...?
Other Me!
It's no use...
I can't give up!
I promised you!
That I would find your real name!
That I would save you!
That's why...
I won't give up!
My turn!
Draw!
Everything rides on this final card!
That's the spirit!
Yugi!
What can a single card do for you?
I sacrifice the Monsters on my field, Marshmallon and Silent Magician...
...and Summon Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction!
What?!
Bakura-kun, there's only one card
resting in my deck that can break your "Undead Locked Dead" Deck...
A card that can break through my Undead Lock...?
Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction's Special Magic Attack!
Giga Rays of Destruction!!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Even the power of the Three Illusionary Beasts weren't enough to defeat Zorc.
Yugi, you're the only one who can save the fallen Pharaoh!
He finally beats the Dark Bakura using Gandora, the Dragon of Destruction's Effect!
But at the same time, Zorc begins destroying the city.
Kaiba-kun!
What are you trying to do?!
Next time!
"Zorc VS Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon"
Duel standby!