Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Rafael.
Looks like it's time for us to settle our scores once and for all.
I recognize you as a True Duelist.
But I don't agree with your talk about fate!
I, for one, will never use The Barrier of Orichalcos again.
But for someone like you who treasures the bonds you have with your Monsters,
do you really intend to use it?!
"Immortal! Guardian Deathscythe"
Why, Rafael?
Why must a Duelist like you do this?
I want to do all I am capable of in this Duel.
And take your soul away!
I want to prove that the fate that Lord Dartz showed me is real.
Rafael...
That guy is the one that defeated Yugi...
What?
That guy...
Nameless Pharaoh, I'll show you...
The true power of The Barrier of Orichalcos that allows you to fight alongside the darkness in your heart!
The darkness of the heart...
Will you really not forget the bonds you have with those Monsters inside this barrier?
Here I come!
Guardian Grarl, attack Kuribabylon!
Resolute Assault!!
Reverse card open, Rope of Life!
What?
When a Monster is sent to the Graveyard due to battle...
I can discard my entire hand to activate this card.
There are zero cards in my hand, thus I'll Special Summon Kuribabylon!
I'll set one card, finishing my turn.
Yugi...
Is he alright?
He has only 1000 Life Points left.
1000 points is enough!
I'll believe in him!
But the power of The Barrier of Orichalcos is much more than this...
Yugi, the title of Duel King that you've tainted... Are you able clear it?
My turn, draw!
Activate Kuribabylon's Special Effect!
Separate into the Five Kuriboh Brothers!
Activate Kuribe's Special Effect!
Combine to become Kuribandit!
Next, I activate a Magic Card, Curtain of Black Magic, from my hand!
Half my Life Points is used to activate this card...
I can then Special Summon one Black Magician.
Good! It's the Black Magician!
But because of that, Yugi's Life is now only 500.
I-It won't be a problem!
I use Black Magician to attack Guardian Elma!
Black Magic!!
Reverse card open!
Guardian Formation!
What!?
This card can be used when Guardian Monsters are under attack!
I can change the position of one Monster!
As long as there are monsters in front, Monsters at the back cannot be attacked!
How despicable! Hiding in the back like that!
His deck has the strength to use the power of the Barrier effectively.
Next I can activate an Equipment Magic specially from my deck!
Saint Sword of Goddess!
Turn end.
Saint Sword of Goddess... Is that Monster coming out soon?
My turn, draw.
Nameless Pharaoh, I will once again show you a nightmare.
Come! Guardian Eatos!
Guardian Eatos...
When there are no Monsters in my Graveyard, Eatos can be Special Summoned without tribute!
What is that?
This overwhelming pressure... like it holds absolute control over everything...
Turning Eatos into that form... are you really alright with that?
Is this really the time for you to be worrying about such things?
This is bad!
Yugi was defeated by that Monster!
That woman can absorb the Attack Power of the Monsters in the opponent's Graveyard.
What?
How did it turn out like this? If it keeps up like this...
Is there no other way?
Activate Kuribandit's Special Effect!
By sacrificing Kuribandit, I can draw five cards from my deck.
From those cards, I'll add non-Monster Cards to my hand and send the Monsters into the Graveyard.
By doing that, the Monster's Attack Power will be even higher!
But if he can draw a card that can go up against Eatos, it's worth a try.
Yugi, can you draw it?
I've gambled my chance on this draw.
Gambling for the last hand, are you?
You won't be able to defeat Eatos with that!
Activating Eatos's Special Effect!
Soul of the Sacred Sword!!
Her Attack Power... is 7000?!
Looks like you did not manage to draw the card you wanted.
Go! Guardian Eatos!!
Forbidden Gospel!!
What?!
It's a pity, Rafael.
The card that I wanted was neither a Magic Card nor a Trap Card.
But this!
Electromagnetic Turtle!
When this card is in the Graveyard, the player can end the turn at any time.
Absurd!
There was such a card in the Graveyard?
That's our Yugi!
What is going on?
So fate wants me to continue this battle?
Turn over!
I don't want to see Eatos in that evil form.
So you were wrong after all!
You shouldn't have used The Barrier of Orichalcos!
Only someone like you who half heartedly believes in the darkness in your heart would think that way!
My turn, draw!
Summon Big Shield Gardna!
Next, I change Black Magician into Defense Position.
Then I'll set one card, ending my turn.
My turn, draw!
Its no use, even if you change your Monsters into Defense Position!
Yugi has two Monsters on his field, but Rafael has four Monsters in play!
This is bad, if he Direct Attacks..!
My Guardians...
Now it's time to decide the outcome of fate!
First, Guardian Eatos will attack Black Magician!
Opera of the Spirits!!
Yugi!
Reverse card open!
Magical Silk Hats!
She missed!!
Yes! Now he has only two Monsters in Attack Mode!
And he can't Direct Attack, either!
Even so...
If Black Magician is destroyed...Yugi will have no Monsters on his field.
Rafael, if the destiny you speak of is really what is guiding you, then all you have to do is guess!
Guess where my Black Magician is located!
One chance out of three...
The one that can overcome Black Magician's Defense Power is Grarl...
In that case...
Go Elma!
Liberation of Thunder!!
Now the chance is one out of two.
Go! Guardian Grarl!
Resolute Assault!!
But why!?
Rafael, looks like fate has not made a decision.
How can this be? Is fate wavering?
There's no way...!
My turn has not ended yet!
Equipment Magic, Rod of Silence!
Rod of Silence, please guide your master towards you!
Come out! Guardian Kay'est!
Turn over!
Somehow we've gotten out of danger for the moment.
No, although it looks very unfavorable...Yugi is actually forcing his enemy into a desperate state.
My turn, draw!
Activate Magic Card, Angel's Charity!
I can draw three cards from my deck and then discard two cards from my hand!
This time I must draw that card.
Come out!
Rafael, I've drawn it.
It can't be!
From my hand, I activate The Eye of Timaeus!
The Eye of Timaeus will combine with Black Magician!
The Legendary Dragon, Timaeus...
Come forth! Amulet Dragon!!
I activate Amulet Dragon's Special Effect!
When it's Summoned, it can absorb a Magic Card from the Graveyard.
It receives an additional 300 Attack Points per card!
What?!
There were eight Magic Cards that I sent to the Graveyard.
Amulet Dragon's Attack Power will now increase to 5300 points!
Hell yeah! He can do this now!
Yugi!
Amulet Dragon, attack Guardian Eatos!
Magic Distortion!!
Eatos!!
Eatos...
Wh-What's going on...?
The Barrier is pulsing...
Rafael...
Because of your attack just now, Eatos is now sleeping in the Graveyard.
But her corpse will now rise as a new soul.
Eatos is immortal!
What?!
What is that?
Is it the Monster's spirit?
This is Eatos' Special Effect.
When Eatos is destroyed by a Monster in battle...
I can Special Summon Guardian Deathscythe in Defense Position from the deck!
Guardian Deathscythe...
Next...
Because of Guardian Deathscythe's Special Effect, it can equip the Equipment Magic, Great Sickle of Grim Reaper!
I activate the special effect of Great Sickle of Grim Reaper!
For every Monster in my Graveyard, it gains 500 Attack Points.
Don't tell you you intentionally put Eatos in the Cemetery?
Because Eatos is in the Cemetery, Deathscythe will become the savior.
Furthermore, when Deathscythe is on the field, I'll not be able to Summon or Special Summon any other Monsters.
Rafael, you...!
It's still too early for an ending speech.
Turn end.
My turn, draw!
I change Guardian Deathscythe into Attack Position.
At this moment, the Monsters on my field will all be sacrificed except for Deathscythe.
Impossible! You're sending your Monsters into the Graveyard?!
Stop it!
It's not like you to do that!
Because four Monsters were sent to the Graveyard, Deathscythe's Attack will increase by 2000 points!
Its Attack is... now higher than Amulet Dragon's!
I'm able to surpass the darkness in my heart.
Rafael...
Deathscythe, attack with all your fury!
Attack Amulet Dragon!!
Forbidden Requiem!!
You managed to dodge a fatal wound...
My turn is over!
Yugi, is there no other way anymore?
Yugi...
My turn, draw!
No problem, Yugi hasn't given up.
What are you going to do, Yugi?
I activate the Magic Card, Treasure from Heaven!
Both players draw until they have six cards in their hands.
I'll Special Summon Watapon onto the field.
Then I'll use this card to Tribute Summon Black Magician Girl in Defense Position!
I set one card, ending my turn.
This time I'll put an end to your struggling as I take your head!
My turn, draw!
From my hand, I activate the Magic Card, Obedience!
When a Monster with higher Attack Power attacks a Monster with a lower Attack Power,
the latter must receive the attack in Attack Position.
Deathscythe will attack Black Magician Girl!
This will be the last attack.
Then it shall be the the conclusion of both of our fates!
Forbidden Requiem!!
Reverse card open!
Magical Pigeon!
What!?
This card can only be used when Black Magician Girl is on the field.
For one turn, it can turn Black Magician Girl into two Pigeon Tokens in Defense Position.
I set two cards face-down and end my turn.
Why?
Why is fate always playing around with me?
Why is it always helping you?
When this battle ends, something will change.
This is what I believe.
Me... and you, I wonder how we'll change.
For the sake of seeing that change, I'll give it my all for this Duel!
That's all there is to it.
I'll change?
Is my destiny that strange?!
Partner...
If you're unable to recognize when you harm yourself...
...and if you aren't aware of the darkness in your opponent's heart...
It's impossible for you to understand the pain and sorrow of others.
For Haga-kun and even Mai-san...
No, even the three Musketeers of Doma...
You can't hear the cries of those suffering!
You're right, Partner.
Please lend me your strength.
My turn! Draw!
Partner, this card can save him!
Rafael, I can finally hear your anguished cries.
Cries?
That's right.
When Eatos was sent to the Graveyard, when you were sacrificing your Guardians...
Your heart was crying sadly, am I right?
What are you talking about all of a sudden?
It's what my partner taught me.
If you can't understand the darkness in your opponent's heart, you will never comprehend the pain and suffering of others!
I will shoulder the darkness in your heart alongside you!
What utter nonsense!
And I'll use this card to wipe away the cries echoing in your heart!
What are you trying to do?!
I'm going to activate this Magic Card from my hand, Underworld - Heaven Circle!
Underworld - Heaven Circle?
Rafael!
I'll let you see the Monsters you sent to your Graveyard!
What do you think you're doing, you impudent busybody?!
What's happening?
Yugi...!
I can't see the two of them anymore.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
In order to save Rafael from the darkness in his heart, Yugi has activated Underworld - Heaven Circle.
Inside the field engulfed in black aura, what Yugi saw was Rafael's sad memory.
The despair and sorrow of losing his family resulted in the creation of Guardian Deathscythe.
Can Yugi destroy Deathscythe and save Rafael's heart?
Next time!
"Destroy the Darkness of the Heart!"
Duel standby!