Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Inherit the Fated Duel"
The two gods
have the same Attack Points!
What?!
Osiris...! Obelisk...!
God against God...!
A battle of wits...!
Will they both perish?
This light...!
Are Osiris's and Obelisk's powers
reacting to each other...?!
Unreal...!
Don't tell me the
entire tower blew up...!
Yugi...!
What in the...?!
The Millennium Rod is...
...glowing once again!
The Millennium Puzzle...!
Wh-What...
...is going on here?!
It's Ancient...
...Egypt!
Impossible!
It's our two gods...!
Everything's been destroyed...
How... could this have happened...?
This fog's engulfed the town...!
What's this feeling...?
This throbbing...
It's coming from the royal palace...?
It looks like the High Priest of Darkness has
conquered Heaven and Earth
with his evil power...
Even your divine right, the Millennium Items,
were worthless against
the Power of Darkness!
In due time, this land will meet
a terrible fate of destruction!
That's the Millennium Puzzle!
Why have you
submitted to their will?
Don't misunderstand me.
It's not as if I'm being controlled by them or anything.
However, I have no intentions of
aiding you either.
The will of my Millennium Rod and
the power of my faithful servant
shall forever be your enemy!
The Millennium Rod!
So you've come here
to settle the score?
It is all the doing of destiny.
I'm sure you have realized by now.
I will defeat you
with my own two hands!
This is my one and only wish!
You miscreant...
I Wield the power of my servant,
whose roar shakes the Heavens!
Bear witness!
I am going to wipe your servant
from the face of this world!
Diaha!!
Arise! White Beast!
It's the Blue-Eyes!
I beckon the Black Magician sleeping
within the stones of Wedju!
The Black Magician!
This scene...
Is it part of my lost memories?!
It can't be...
But the Monster that
came out of that stone tablet is
without a doubt the Blue-Eyes...!
I see now!
It's the same image as the two Duelists
carved in the 3,000 year old slab!
What...?!
What in the hell is happening?!
The light's... starting to fade...
Yugi...!
Big brother!
The gods are gone...
The gods disappeared...
The Millennium Rod somehow
awakened their memories...
But what the hell did they see?!
That scene that
flashed through my mind...?!
What was it...?
It's absurd...!
The fight between the Pharaoh the Priest...
He really existed...!
The enemy I was fighting...
...was him...!
Yugi!!
The Pharaoh wielding
the Black Magician...
...and the Priest wielding
the White Beast...
They're exactly the same as us!
Part of that fight from 3,000 years ago
was recorded on that palette...!
That was a piece
of my lost memories!
My lost memories...
I'm sure of it!
Kaiba, you're a part of them!
Yugi! Don't tell me you saw
the same vision I did!
Kaiba, I finally understand!
This battle is a fated Duel we've been
fighting for the past 3,000 years!
A Duel of destiny that
has surpassed time itself!
Battle City...
is a test to become a True Duelist,
as well as a battle
to regain my memory!
With the gods gone,
this Duel's back to square one!
My Millennium Rod...
And Yugi's Millennium Puzzle...
Are their memories
sealed within them...?
If that's the case,
what the hell did they see?!
I'm certain now, Kaiba!
My battle with you will open the
first door to my memories!
I could care less about some bizarre trick
caused by the two gods colliding.
But whether that was reality or a mere illusion, it doesn't faze me in the slightest.
I will defeat you here and now!
And the only future I have is
to obtain the title "Duel King"!
We no longer need
the gods in this fight!
Let's go, Yugi!
Even though my god is gone, I haven't
declared the end of my turn yet.
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
In the end, the only thing
that can defeat you is my servant
that surpasses even God...
Blue-Eyes!
My turn! Draw!
This isn't it...!
This isn't the card I need...
There's one key card
I still haven't drawn yet...
Kaiba has but one
reverse card on the field...
But he still needs to be
wary of an attack...
What are you gonna do now,
Your Highness?
I'm going to Summon
Illusion Beast Gazelle on this turn!
And now I activate my reverse Trap!
Clone Reproduction!
Clone?!
This Trap clones the Monster you have on the field and places its copy on my field!
So, Yugi, what's your next move?
I'll place another card face-down!
Turn end!
What's wrong with you, Yugi?
Aren't you being a little too cautious?
But that prudence of yours will only
lead you to a future of destruction!
Next turn, I'm going to
sacrifice the clone of your Monster
to Summon a new servant.
Now that the gods are in the Graveyard,
the next Monster Kaiba will Summon...
You can't! Not the Blue-Eyes!
But it costs two sacrifices to
Summon an Eight-Star Monster...
Even if he has it in his hand, he won't be able to Summon it next turn...
Will I be able to draw my key card
before he does...?
My turn!
Draw!
Yugi... Let me tell you something...
The Blue-Eyes is already
resting in my hand!
You may think I'm not able
to Summon it this turn...
...but this card will change
all perception you had of that!
I activate the Magic Card
Cost Down from my hand!
Cost Down is a Magic Card that
lowers the Level of a Monster Card
by two stars for one turn.
I see!
His Eight-Star Blue-Eyes
will become a Six-Star...
He'll be able to Summon it
with just one sacrifice!
Take a good look, Yugi!
This is not an illusion!
It's the form of the ultimate Monster!
I offer the Clone Monster as a tribute!
Come forth, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
My brother's Blue-Eyes is here!
For him to Summon
the Blue-Eyes like that...
Heh! I can see the end of this match!
Yugi! The ancient illusions are over!
This is the real world and
your defeat along with it!
Blue-Eyes! Attack!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Gazelle is destroyed!
My turn ends there!
So bring it, Yugi!
But all your Monsters with
less than 3000 Attack Points
will go down in flames!
My turn!
If that vision was true...
...then the next card I draw
has already decided.
It all depends on this draw...
Will I be able to flip to the next
page of my lost memories?
Draw!
Kaiba, you saw it too.
The carving of a Duelist's battle
made 3,000 years ago!
Whether they were
a Pharaoh or a Priest...
It doesn't matter who they were!
What was carved there was
their spirit as Duelists!
And that spirit
has been passed onto us!
I'm going to prove to you that
this wasn't an illusion!
The Magic Card
Resurrection of the Dead!
Awaken!
The soul of the magician
sleeping in the Graveyard!
Magician...?
He couldn't have...!
Come out, Black Magician!
Damn you, Yugi...!
When Life Shaver forced him
to discard a card, he sent
Black Magician to the Graveyard.
And this scene...!
From before...!
A battle from my memories was recorded
on that ancient palette!
And if this Duel is a piece of
the puzzle of memories...
Kaiba!!
I must defeat you!!
In order to get back
my lost memories!
But neither the stone slab or the
vision shown to us revealed what
happens beyond this point...
What was the result of the battle?
But even if everything in this Duel has
been destined from the beginning...
Supposing that elaborate vision
we saw was in fact reality,
I decide what happens on
my road of battle myself!
It's my turn!
I set another reverse card!
Blue-Eyes has 3000 Attack Points...
And the Black Magician opposes
it with 2500 Attack Points...
The Black Magician can't beat it without any additional assistance in Attack Strength...
But now I have two
reverse cards on the field...
And one of them is
Spellbook of Black Magic...
Its effects will increase Black Magician's Attack Power by 500 points.
But that won't bring it higher
than the Blue-Eyes...
My only chance is to wait
until he attacks me!
Turn end!
Hmph! The Black Magician?
Looks like you
saw the same vision I did.
But let me tell you the truth
about that ridiculous "vision" we saw!
It was nothing more than subliminal images
our brains stored when we saw the carving
of the Priest and the Pharaoh!
A Pharaoh from 3,000 years ago?
Don't make me laugh, Yugi!
As far as I'm concerned,
you're nothing more than a naive bigot
who's trapped in his own fantasies!
You're just a prisoner bound
by a chain of the past!
What was that?
There is no light for those
who are shackled to the past!
If you turn your back on the future,
you tread down the road
of nostalgia and defeat!
My turn, draw!
I set one reverse card!
And I activate a
Magic Card from my hand!
Life-Shaving Card Treasure!
I'm able to draw until I hold five cards
in my hand, provided I discard my
entire hand five turns later!
A Hand Reinforcement card!
The reverse cards on his field...
One of them must be
a Magic Card to increase the
Black Magician's Attack Points.
And the other one...
A Trap Card activated
by Blue-Eyes' attack.
Hexagram Curse!
I've analyzed all of your strategies
through this Battle City Tournament
and long before it.
I know exactly
what you're going to do!
I can see through your deck
as if it were made of glass!
And this turn... I'm going
to Summon this Monster!
What?!
Show yourself, Lord of Dragons!
The Lord of Dragons...
As long as he has the Lord of Dragons
on the field, his Blue-Eyes is safe
from his opponent's Magic.
Next turn...
I'll crush you with one blow!
He's read my strategy
inside and out...!
What should I do...?
My turn!
Draw!
But I've planned even
farther than that, Yugi!
I'll Summon Magnet Warrior Beta!
In Defense Mode!
Are you going to attack
my Lord of Dragons with
the Black Magician, perhaps?
I attack Lord of Dragons
with Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
You fell for it!
Trap Card, activate!
Mechanical Magic Mirror!
Mechanical Magic Mirror is a card
that lets me activate a Magic Card
from my opponent's Graveyard!
Using that effect,
I'll activate this Magic Card
lying dormant in your Graveyard!
This card!!
Resurrection of the Dead!
And the Monster I choose to revive...
...is him!!
Obelisk!!
Gods can only be raised for one turn.
And he can't attack.
But despite that effect...
...he will act as my
impenetrable shield, acting as
the perfect defense for my servants!
What?!
Yugi, you can no longer stop
your Black Magic attack!
It can't be!
The attack is bounced back,
and is dealt to the player as damage!
We finally have a turn
in Life Point scores!
Kaiba-kun and Yugi saw a glimpse of their past in the clash between Obelisk and Osiris.
But Kaiba-kun denies everything he saw and declares that he will send Yugi to Hell along with his past!
And Kaiba finally gets all three of his Blue-Eyes on the field!
As he's pressed into a corner, Yugi sees an image of Jounouchi.
He's right, Yugi!
Don't forget your promise with Jounouchi!
Next time!
"The Promise Between Friends: The Red-Eyes Black Dragon"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other