Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Seriously!
Even if you're gonna make trouble for us, you should know when to draw the line!
It was finally time for Rebecca to have a fine Duel with Leon-kun,
but we were late to cheer her on because of Grandpa!
Even though Rebecca did her best,
Leon-kun, who was equally strong...
...was the one who won and got into the finals of the KC Grand Prix.
His opponent is the one who defeated Jounouchi-kun, Sieg Lloyd.
What kind of Duel will it be?
"Kaiba's Intrusion!
The Grand Prix Finals"
Climbing over the corpses of those who fallen before them,
the two strongest Duelists have been chosen, who now stand before us!
Let me introduce them!
The winner of the A Block, Sieg Lloyd!
The winner of the B Block, Leon Wilson!
Sorry to keep all of you waiting.
Right now, the first ever KC Grand Prix...
A tournament meant to determine the strongest Duelist in existence!
The Final Match will now begin!
That's...
What is that?
It's Kaiba!
Kaiba-kun!
Brother!
So you have finally made it...?
That's the end!
As the organizer of this competition,
I am now canceling this match!
What the hell's that Kaiba bastard saying?
What is going on?
It's canceled?
And Leon Wilson will be the winner by default,
as the winner of the first KC Grand Prix!
Eh... Me?
What the hell is going on, Mokuba?
I don't know either.
Could you please explain what is going on, Mr. Kaiba?
There's no need for me to explain.
You should know more than anyone else here.
Sieg Lloyd...
No...
Siegfried von Schroeder.
Schroeder...!
Grandpa, Schroeder is...
Yes... They are the number one entertainment industry in all of Europe.
And they are well known across the world...
Did he mean that when he said Schroeder?
Then they're a rival company of Kaiba Corporation?
Humph. To think that the leader of Schroeder Corporation would use a fake name...
...and join in a tournament held by my Kaiba Corporation.
And strange incidents kept happening one after another.
What the?!
I've seen through everything.
But I wanted a complete investigation of the reason behind it.
But Siegfried...
Your unknown background and you using a fake name are the undeniable truth.
Just this alone is enough reason to disqualify you from this tournament!
I certainly did not expect the leader of Kaiba Corporation to be so petty.
You are awfully wimpish.
What?
That the winner of the KC Grand Prix would be me, the leader of Schroeder Corp....
...seems to have given you quite the scare.
Mr. Kaiba...
Our conversation here is being broadcast live all over the world, right?
I am most certain Dueling fans all over the world would agree.
That Seto Kaiba is afraid of me, Siegfried...
And wants to kick me out of this competition.
I think you're mistaken.
Who said anything about kicking you out?
I'm going to prove to everyone that you aren't strong enough to reach my abilities.
Kaiba-kun against Sieg...!
This has taken an unexpected turn.
Oh? So you wish to be my opponent?
That was your motive from the start... Wasn't it, Siegfried?
Kaiba-kun's gonna Duel.
That's the way! There's no way my brother wouldn't take part in the Duels!
Isono.
Yes.
What's wrong? Perhaps you're the one who's afraid?
Hardly the case.
This is my honor, Mr. Kaiba.
The winner can decide if he wants to attack first or later.
I choose tails.
Then I shall choose heads.
I win.
It would appear that fate is still on my side.
Talking about fate just because you guessed a coin toss correctly?
Enough of the chit-chat. Which will it be?
I shall attack later.
Got it.
Brother, teach this guy a thorough lesson!
Yugi-san!
Leon-kun.
I didn't expect to fight with you in this manner.
But isn't it your dream to be able to Duel with Yugi, Leon-kun?
That's correct, but...
So it doesn't really matter.
No matter how you won, you're the one who was given the right to Duel Yugi, Leon-kun.
That's right!
I wanted to Duel with Yugi too, you know!
I'm... I'm sorry.
But listen...
Even if that Kaiba jerk is full of confidence as usual,
Sieg is no push-over Duelist.
You're right.
Kaiba...
Dueling fans around the world are watching this.
I plan to completely crush you so neither you nor Kaiba Corporation will stand up again.
Siegfried...
I won't let you have your way.
I want you to know very clearly that going up against me is a foolish thing to do.
Duel!!
My turn, draw!
I Summon X-Head Cannon in Attack Position.
I set two reverse cards.
Turn end.
It is my turn. I draw.
Kaiba.
The prologue to destiny does not always start quietly.
It will sometimes carry with it a storm upon opening the curtain on whim.
What disgusting words! I'm gonna throw up.
Get on with the Duel!
But of course.
My beautiful maiden warriors have begun laughing at you...
...as they wait to assault you.
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card, Walkuren Ritt.
I can Special Summon all the Valkyries in my hand.
What?!
Come forth!
Valkyrie Zwei!
Valkyrie Erste!
Valkyrie Dritte!
Activate the Special Effect of Valkyrie Zwei!
When Summoned, one Monster on the opponent's field is destroyed.
And in addition, using the Special Effect of Valkyrie Erstem,
by removing a Monster in my opponent's Cemetery from the game,
she can take on the Attack Power of that Monster for the duration of the battle!
There is more!
I activate Valkyrie Dritte's Special Effect!
She gains 100 Attack Points for every one of my opponent's Monsters destroyed.
He Summoned three Valkyries at once!
Kaiba-kun has no Wall Monsters on his field.
If he Direct Attacks him with all three at once...
Kaiba-kun will...
Brother!
It looks like we are already proceeding to the finale without the prologue.
Farewell, Kaiba!
My Valkyries...
First, Valkyrie Zwei, attack the player directly!
Reverse card, open!
Attack Nullification!
It negates the opponent's attack and ends the Battle Phase!
Good!
With that, the Valkyries Summoned this turn using Ride of the Valkyries
will return to the deck when this turn ends.
Humph... What a short prologue.
What are you doing?!
Ask those young girls to retreat already!
That is..!
Kaiba.
The prologue has ended long ago.
And we have already moved on ahead into the first chapter.
Valkyrie Zwei!
Attack the player directly!
What?!
What's going on?
Those Valkyries should have returned to the deck!
Why?!
Kaiba-kun!
He skipped a turn?!
Correct.
This is the effect of a Quick-Play Magic known as Mischief of the Time Goddess.
I can skip one turn and go directly into my next Battle Phase.
Brother!
Reverse card, open!
Mechanical Magic Mirror!
This card allows me to activate one Magic Card in the enemy's Graveyard!
The card I choose to activate is Mischief of the Time Goddess!
What?
Kaiba...!
So this time Sieg's turn was skipped and it's back to Kaiba's next Battle Phase.
I have no Monsters on the field.
And hence I cannot attack during the Battle Phase.
But I can still Summon new Monsters in the Main Phase Two.
I Summon Z-Metal Caterpillar in Defense Position.
Next, I Special Summon Clone Dragon from my hand in Defense Position.
This card can only be Special Summoned when a Monster is Summoned successfully.
And it will take on the stats of that Monster and become a clone copy!
Turn end.
Amazing.
It's just beginning and it's already such an intense fight.
But it feels like Kaiba is on the losing end...
On the other hand, there are still three Valkyries in his field...
You can continue struggling, Kaiba.
Because I have skipped the first turn's End Phase...
The Valkyries are not returned to the deck and remain on the field.
Looks like the Death God is still hanging around you.
What a load of crap.
Draw a card already!
My turn, draw!
From my hand, I activate Valkyrie's Embrace!
And I change Valkyrie Dritte to be in Defense Position.
What?
By switching a Valkyrie into Defense Position,
it allows me to remove the opponent's Monster from the game.
With one additional Monster removed from play...
Valkyrie Dritte gains another 100 Attack Points.
Bury that fake!
Valkyrie Erste, destroy Clone Dragon!
Next, Valkyrie Zwei, attack the player directly!
Brother!
Kaiba-kun...
That's Sieg's true strength.
No, that's just a warm-up.
My turn, draw!
Oh? You still look so calm.
Or perhaps you are only pretending?
I don't have the time to bother with your useless attacks.
From my hand, I Summon Pitch-Dark Dragon in Defense Position!
I set one card and end my turn.
It is my turn. Draw.
I switch Valkyrie Dritte from Defense back to Attack Position.
Next, I use Valkyrie Zwei to attack Pitch-Dark Dragon!
Kaiba's Monster was destroyed again.
Will he be okay?!
No... Since it's Kaiba-kun we're talking about, he must be planning something.
Reverse card, open!
Flat Level 4!
This card is activated when a Monster gets destroyed.
Both players can Special Summon a Four-Star Monster from their deck.
I Special Summon Y-Dragon Head in Defense Position.
Then I'll Special Summon Valkyrie Dritte in Attack Position.
Two Monsters have been removed from play...
As such, its Attack goes up by 200 points!
You should feel thankful that I refrained from offing you so soon, Kaiba.
Turn end.
My turn, draw.
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
I draw two cards from my deck.
Then from my hand, I activate Dimension Fusion.
By using 2000 Life Points...
I Special Summon back all the Monsters that were removed from play onto the field.
What? Don't tell me...
Right! He'll fuse XYZ together for a combo!
But to use 2000 points for a cost like that...
Isn't that a little too much?
I activate the Continuous Magic from my hand, Soul Absorption!
With this card's effect...
For every card that is removed from the game, I will gain 500 Life Points.
Next, I'll remove X-Head Cannon, Y-Dragon Head and Z-Metal Caterpillar
from the game by fusing them as one Monster!
I Union Summon XYZ-Dragon Cannon!
That's a good move.
By using the Summoning Requirements for XYZ-Dragon Cannon,
he was able to replenish the Life Points he used as a cost for Dimension Fusion.
Truly a strategy only the former reigning champion in Duel Monsters, Kaiba-kun, would think of!
Here I come, you phony Duelist!
XYZ-Dragon Cannon, attack Valkyrie Dritte!
Hyper Destruction!!
Good job, Brother!
Amazing!
He brought them back to level playing ground with just one attack!
As expected of Kaiba!
As expected... of Kaiba...
As expected of Seto Kaiba!
This is sure to stir up a revolution in the gaming industry!
He is truly a genius.
Just one step...
I was only one step too late...?
Kaiba...
Sieg's expression has changed.
It's my turn... I draw.
From my hand, I activate Nibelung's Treasure.
That card is..!
Jounouchi, that's the card he used against you in the previous match!
Yeah, that annoying ring...
Nibelung's Treasure can be equipped onto one of the opponent's Monsters on the field.
I then draw another five cards.
Due to the effect of Nibelung's Ring...
...the player cannot control the Monster that is equipped with the ring.
And that's not all...
In the next turn, Kaiba will be forced to draw two cards.
If there's a Monster Card, he'll be forced to discard that card to the Graveyard.
In addition, I sacrifice Valkyrie Dritte to Summon Fortune Chariot.
What is that?!
In each turn, Fortune Chariot can be equipped to one Valkyrie.
And because of Fortune Chariot's effects, the equipped Monster's Attack is halved...
And it can Direct Attack the player.
How can that be?
I use Valkyrie Zwei to attack the player directly!
Brother!
Kaiba-kun!
That is not all.
From my hand, I also activate the Quick-Play Magic, Cyclone!
Destroy Soul Absorption.
I set one card and end my turn.
As Soul Absorption is destroyed, you cannot regain Life anymore.
Also...
As long as Fortune Chariot remains on the field...
I can continue to execute Direct Attacks on the player.
Kaiba...
The curse of the Valkyries has only yet begun.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
We didn't expect Sieg to be one of Kaiba-kun's rivals from another company!
Even though he has been disqualified from the competition...
Kaiba-kun went to challenge him.
Sieg's Goddess Deck is no joke!
Even Kaiba-kun is feeling the impact of the Valkyries' attacks...
...and is facing unprecedented danger.
And Sieg has Summoned the Three Goddess Combo that he used to make Jounouchi suffer!
Next time!
"The Valkyries VS Blue-Eyes White Dragon"
Duel standby!