Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Amelda was foolish enough to sneak aboard my private plane and demand a rematch.
If you plan to stand in my way no matter what...
...then I'll have to defeat you in order to move on!
Very well.
I accept this Duel.
But that guy is trying to do something...
By showing me illusions in order to affect my emotions.
That's useless, Amelda.
Do you think that such low-class tricks will work on me?
"Sky Devil Fortress Ziggurat"
Anyone, please answer, quick!
Yes, this is Isono.
Isono!
I don't have time to explain!
The plane's gonna crash!
Eh?!
Quick, tell me how I can operate this!
Pl-Please hold on a sec.
Hey!
Kaiba.
Let me show you my trump card.
I activate the Magic Card, Junk Dealer!
This card can Special Summon at most two Machine-Type or Warrior-Type Monsters from the Graveyard
in Attack Position with half of their Attack Points.
Revive!
Science Special Soldier!
Machine Soldier of Demon World!
In addition, I Summon Cypher Scouter from my hand cards!
Due to the The Barrier of Orichalcos's effect,
their Attack Points go up!
The control panel to the left of the control stick...
Balance the plane...
I did it!
Pull the lever at one go!
Get the jet ready!
We must save Seto-sama and Mokuba-sama!
I activate a Trap Card! Soldier Revolt!
This card can only be activated when Science Special Soldier, Cypher Scouter and Machine Soldier of Demon World are on the field.
I'll have to forgot my Battle Phase in this turn.
But I can make my opponent send
every card in his hand and on his side of the field to the Graveyard.
Next, from my hand, I activate the Magic Card Sky Devil Combined Body!
By sacrificing my three Monsters...
I Summon Sky Devil Fortress Ziggurat to the field!
What... is that?
Please!
Change it to auto-pilot mode.
Good!
Big Brother, I did it!
Seto?
You bastard...
That Monster is...
It's the most fitting Monster to give you a fatal blow.
This Monster is not affected by the effects of any Magic Card or Trap Card the opponent has.
In addition, during my End Phase...
...one "Toy Robot Token" will be Special Summoned to the field.
The opposing player cannot attack this token.
No way...
That Monster is...
This is my trump card.
Kaiba.
I'm gonna use this Monster to acquire my revenge on you.
Nonsense!
Such "sentimental acts" have no effect on me!
My turn, draw!
Stop now, both of you!
Mokuba, if I don't defeat him, our dream won't come true.
Our dream?
Kaiba Land...?
No matter who it may be, anyone who obstructs me from realizing our dream...
I'll destroy that person without mercy!
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
Looks like you're being hated by the cards you trust so much.
In the next turn, once Ziggurat Direct Attacks you, you'll lose!
Don't make me laugh.
What about Kaiba Land?
A person like you raised by Gozaburo can't possibly bring happiness to others.
You're wrong!
My brother never acknowledged anything Gozaburo did!
Kaiba Land is a dream that we had even before meeting him!
Say no more, Mokuba.
He won't be able to understand.
You're right about that.
Just like how you won't understand the hell that my younger brother and I saw.
But such small things are not important now.
I'll end it all!
I want to use your soul to put an end to all of this!
My turn! Draw!
Sky Devil Fortress Ziggurat, Direct Attack the player!
Disappear, Kaiba!
Seto!!
I open my Trap Card!
Traps are useless in front of Ziggurat!
Mechanical Magic Mirror!
This card allows me to activate a Magic Card in my opponent's Graveyard!
What...?
And the card I want to activate from yours is Junk Dealer!
Using Junk Dealer's effect, I can revive Judge Man from the Graveyard with half his Attack Points!
Damn, what a troublesome guy.
Turn end!
The rescue choppers!
Seto-sama!
Mokuba-sama!
Isono!!
KAIBA!!
Quick, link up!
We must save Seto-sama and Mokuba-sama!
Seto-sama!!
Mokuba-sama!!
Seto!
Kaiba.
It's about time you took off that mask you hide behind!
You treasure those accursed choppers of yours...
...and you still dare speak of "Kaiba Land"?
Despite all the nice words you utter,
you're just the same as Gozaburo in the end!
That's right.
You're no different than those murderers.
Someone like you will never understand how persecuted people like us feel!
My turn.
Brother...
I activate a Magic Card from my hand...
Cross Sacrifice!
We can each take the opponent's Monsters as sacrifices.
Kaiba...!
You bastard...!
We're in the middle of a match here...
You can repeat that nonsense again after this.
Stop your fruitless struggle.
You can't use Ziggurat as a sacrifice!
Just those puppet Monsters will be enough.
Come out! Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
I end my turn.
What use is there in Summoning your Blue-Eyes now?
I'll end this...
If I draw a Monster Card on my next turn, it'll all be over!
That's if you do.
Draw!
You're a really lucky bastard.
I set a reverse card and end my turn.
My big brother has Blue-Eyes on the field...
But he can only direct his attacks towards that token.
My turn! Draw!
I use Blue-Eyes White Dragon to attack the puppet Monster!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
I set a card face-down and end my turn.
My turn!
This is it... With this, I can put an end to our struggle!
Miruko, watch carefully.
I activate the Quick-Play Magic,
Toy Robot Box!
By discarding one card in my hand...
...I can Special Summon another three Toy Robot Tokens.
Then, by offering the three tokens...
I can Summon Magic Canceller!
As long as this card is on the field, Magic Cards cannot be activated!
There's nothing you can do now, Kaiba!
First I'll use Ziggurat to attack Blue-Eyes so that they'll both be destroyed.
And then I'll Direct Attack you and you'll lose!
Rejoice!
Your soul will be used for the birth of a new world!
You plan to destroy all human beings?
I do!
Is that so?
In other words, just as your little brother and your parents were murdered...
...you're planning to do the exact same thing to all the parents and brothers on this world?
Th-That's not it.
This is a reset.
I need to make everything return to zero before starting over again!
To create a peaceful world without wars!
"Reset", you call it?
Would you do that even if your little brother was alive?
What?
Even so, would you still plan to reset the world?
S-Stop your nonsense!
You killed Miruko and you still dare say such things?!
You're wrong.
You couldn't save him. Your little brother!
What... a-are you saying?
You still don't understand?
You couldn't manage to save your younger brother.
You're the loser
based on this point alone.
A guy who wants to reset the world?
That's nothing but the howls of a loser dog!
Kaiba...
You're the only one...
You're the only one I'll never forgive!
Go, Ziggurat!
Seto!
Amelda... If that had been
me instead of you...
I would not have let my little brother die!!
No matter what it took!!
Trap Card, activate! Tyrant Wing!
What...?
This card adds 400 Attack Points to the equipped Monster!
In addition, in my next Battle Phase, I can attack twice!
That's absurd...!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon attacks!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
You don't have any more Monsters that can defeat me.
And what of it...?
In any case, this plane can only last for a few more minutes!
If we continue like this...
...both of us can go to Hell together!
Are you planning to avoid declaring "end" in order to buy yourself time?
You're the one who said you wanted to put an end to this!
This is the end between you and me.
You lowly bastard...
From the start, you came here looking for a coffin, didn't you?
Stop this, Amelda!
Even if you do this, your younger brother will just be sad!
You're a loser dog right down to the bone.
You said that you would be able to save your brother...
Can you really save him? Your little brother?
I can.
Big Brother...
Don't be foolish!
I still have three Monsters on my field!
Before this plane crashes, how are you going to defeat me, win the Duel and save Mokuba?
Just continue the Duel, Amelda!
I won't let Mokuba die!
In order to ensure that, I'll end this Duel in the next turn!
Can you do it?
Then show me.
Turn end.
Amelda! Witness the power of a True Duelist and the splendor of the Chosen Ones!
I'll draw...
I'll surely draw that card!
Seto...
My turn! Draw!!
I activate the The Fang of Critias from my hand!
And fuse its power with the Trap Card, Tyrant Wing!
To Special Summon Tyrant Burst Dragon!
Tyrant Burst Dragon can attack all the Monsters on the opponent's field in one turn and deal their damage.
Then, I'll combine it with Blue-Eyes!
Go!
Tyrant Burst Stream of Destruction!!
You're not bad, Kaiba.
Amelda!
Miruko...
Amelda!!
Amelda...
Mokuba! Stay here!
Seto!
Amelda...
I'll show you that I can do what I've promised.
I won't let Mokuba die!
What?
Wh-What's wrong?
That's...!
Jounouchi!
Honda, too!
Yugi!
Anzu!
That mark...
It's Kaiba's jet?
I wonder if the passengers are okay...
Kaiba!
Yugi.
You guys!
He's from Doma...
You won?
Of course.
That aside, why are all of you here?
The three dragons led us here.
Kaiba...
It looks like we're fated to fight together.
I don't believe in fate.
But it's true that you groupies might be useful in some ways.
Seto-sama!
Mokuba-sama, you're safe too!
Isono!
Seto-sama!
I'm afraid I have bad news!
The buy-out of Kaiba Corporation's stocks has ended.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Kaiba-kun has defeated one of the Three Swordsman of Doma, Amelda.
But soon after, Kaiba Corporation has fallen into Doma's palms.
And the Florida Museum is also raided.
In order to properly analyze the undersea relics, Kaiba-kun and Yugi rush to access Kaiba Corporation's super computers.
Be careful! It's already under Doma's control!
Next time!
"Dartz's Stealthy Shadow"
Duel standby!