Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
We launched our plan to learn information about Doma, boarding a train to do so.
But Doma already got to us first!
Me and Yugi have been separated from each other after the train split up....
And Ryuzaki and Haga, both now working for Doma, have forced us into a Duel!
You guys...!
Do you have any idea what you're doing to yourself?!
"Powered Up Decks!
Haga and Ryuzaki"
My turn!
Draw!
It's the first turn of Parasite Caterpillar's Effect!
What?!
If Poison Butterfly is born...
I'll lose 500 of my Life Points each turn...
The Magic Card Fusion
From my hand, I fuse together Dark Knight Gaia
and Curse of Dragon!
I Summon Dragon Knight Gaia!
Attack Leghul!
That's useless!
Reverse Trap!
DNA Surgery, activate!
What?!
As long as this card remains on the field,
all Monsters on the field will become the Type I declare!
Of course, I choose...
Insects!
And at that very moment, the Continuous Magic Card Insecticide Barrier...
...will seal away Dragon Knight Gaia's attack!
Insecticide Barrier is a method to stall time for Poison Butterfly's birth...
So he was aiming to seal away my attacks with the DNA Surgery Combo?
Stay calm, Yugi!
Don't rush things!
I know that!
Yugi...
Turn over.
Don't you lose, Jounouchi!
If you lose, your soul'll be taken!
I know that!
I totally feel it!
The power a' Orichalcos is consumin' me from head to toe!
My turn!
I draw!
Here I go.
I activate the Magic Card Fusion!
I fuse Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus with Chitoptera!
And I Summon Hell Horned Saurus!
I also Summon Giant Rex!
And with the power a' Orichalcos Barrier,
they become Dark Monsters!
Well, guess that's all ya had!
I'll take ya ta' pieces with my new-found power deck!
Go!
Hell Horned Saurus!
Go an' Direct Attack Jounouchi!
What!?
A Monster that Direct Attacks right off the bat?!
Right!
This guy's got the Special Ability to Direct Attack the opponent the moment it's Summoned!
Jounouchi!
What the hell are you doing, Jounouchi?!
Shut it! I know already!
And there's still more!
Giant Rex, go an' attack Panther Warrior!
This is bad!
Jounouchi lost all his Monsters!
Too bad for ya!
This ends it!
Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus, Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!
Quick-Play Magic, Scapegoat!
Your lucky streak never ends.
Seems this match'll continue!
Don't make me nervous like that, man!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Cell Division!
Leghul Cell Division!
What in the world?!
This card lets me select a Level Three Insect-Type Monster and create a Cell Division Token of it!
Even by throwing out another worthless 800 Attack Monster,
it's not much of a threat!
I'm surprised!
Those aren't the words
of the Duel King I know!
Do you really think I played this for nothing?
It seems you haven't recovered from your loss to Rafael yet.
Well, maybe it's pointless.
It was, after all, because of your own self-inflicted wound that you lost your precious "partner" of yours!
Hey, that's enough of your lowly tricks!
So sorry!
I was just rattling on to myself a bit.
Haga! You bastard!
Aren't you supposed to be the former Regional Champion?
Doesn't a champion like you have any pride?!
Don't get so full of yourself just because you're cute.
People will start to hate you if you act all big like that.
Now then...
I sacrifice Pheromone Wasp and Cell Division Token...
To Summon Insect Queen!
My queen has finally been reborn!
And her Attack Power goes up thanks to the power of Orichalcos!
I then activate Insect Queen's Continuous Effect!
She gains 200 Attack Points for every Insect Monster on the field!
That refers to my Insect Queen and Leghul...
Totaling four with your Dragon Knight Gaia and Retrained Elf Swordsman!
So she goes all the way up to 3500 points!
3500 Attack Points?!
Now, here I go, Yugi!
I'll start off by Direct Attacking with Leghul!
Leghul can bypass all other Monsters and attack the player directly!
Not yet!
Now it's my queen's turn to attack!
I sacrifice Leghul so Insect Queen can attack!
Now it's your feeding time, my queen!
Queen's Hell Breath!!
Dragon Knight Gaia is beaten!
When Insect Queen destroys an opponent's Monster in battle,
she leaves behind an Insect Monster Token in Defense Mode!
Turn end.
Jounouchi! This time I'm gonna beat ya!
For sure!
There's no way the great Jounouchi's gonna lose to some twerp who relies on the power of Doma!
Quit shittin'!
No matter who the bastard is,
long as I beat ya, no one can stop me!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Rocket Warrior in Defense Mode!
I also place two reverse cards!
Ryuzaki! You jerk!
Wh-What the hell ya want?
Do you really want power that much?
Is power the only thing that matters to you in a Duel?
Jounouchi! You're always babblin' on about this goody-two-shoes nonsense!
That's what I hate the most about ya!
I'm always serious when it comes ta' Duelin'!
Winning and losing's the only thing that matters!
A guy who loses is nuttin' but scum! Not worth a cent!
All that matters is winnin' the match at all costs!
"Always serious when it comes to Dueling..."
Dueling is always a serious matter!
It's about putting yourself on the line.
I have been fighting like that all this time...
This isn't just a game!
Shit...! Every single one of them...!
They all say the same thing...!
Turn over!
My turn! Draw!
Hell Horned Saurus, attack Rocket Warrior!
Reverse Trap open!
Magic-Arm Shield!
This redirects the strike to your Monster instead!
I ain't gonna let ya!
Counter Trap, open!
Jurassic Heart, activate!
What!?
This makes all effects used on Dinosaurs useless!
Keep it comin'!
Giant Rex!
Attack Scapegoat!
Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus, attack Scapegoat!
I then place 1 Reverse Card...
End my turn.
Shit!
This is bad!
Oi, Jounouchi!
My turn...
Red-Eyes...
I have little to no Life remaining...
I'm counting on you, Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
I sacrifice 1 Scapegoat!
I activate the Magic Card Star Blaster!
If I hold a Monster in my hand whose Level equals
the Level of the sacrificed Monster plus the number I roll on the die,
I can then Special Summon that Monster!
Please make it...!
Alright!
The die rolled a 6!
The Level of the Scapegoat I sacrificed is 1!
6 plus 1 equals 7!
Yer damned luck keeps on surprisin' me...!
I Special Summon a Seven-Star Monster!
And his name is...!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Wh-What'd ya say?
Red-Eyes Black Dragon...!
Then, I open my Reverse Trap!
I activate Metal Conversion - Magic Reflection Armor!
This increases the Attack and Defense of the equipped Monster by 300 points!
And when it attacks the opponent, its Attack Points increase by half of theirs!
Here I come, Ryuzaki!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Attack Hell Horned Saurus!
Hell Horned Saurus has 2500 Attack Points!
So 1250 of that total is added to Red-Eyes's Attack Points!
Hell Horned Saurus is beaten!
Alright!
I also set 1 Reverse Card.
Turn over!
Now it's your turn, Yugi.
How about you stop hiding behind that mask and show us your true face.
What?!
What do you mean by "true self"?!
Huh?
Seems I said too much again!
Please don't let it bother you!
If you've got something to say, then say it, Haga!
You mean it?
Then stop playing the hero of justice over there!
Because you aren't even close to one!
Knock it off!
Someone like you who succumbed to Orichalcos Barrier just as I...
Aren't we the same?!
You know, aren't you carrying the same mindset as I am?!
Just because you couldn't bare to lose,
you lost your precious partner!
You really mean to call yourself a "True Duelist"?!
You're the complete opposite of that!
Didn't I tell you to knock it off!
No matter what you say to me,
whether it be some disgusting plan to throw me off,
there's no way I'll fall for it!
Oh, oh, oh, oh? Funny you say such a thing...
Perhaps I'm just imagining your hand shaking over there?
Yugi!
I'll beat you today for sure!
I've been waiting ages for this day!
Red-Eyes represents the friendship between me and Yugi!
It's a Monster of friendship!
How the hell's that a Monster a' friendship...?
Wasn't that Red-Eyes mine before?!
Ya steal it away from me and ya act so big?!
Steal?!
Don't make up fake stories!
I won it fair-and-square in that Duel!
Right... That Duel back in Duelist Kingdom...
Ever since then...
Ever since that day, my life's changed so much...
Since the day me and Haga became Regional Champions...
The two of us became super famous in the Duelist world!
Oi, look!
It's the Regional Champion, Insector Haga and...!
The runner-up, Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Amazing!
They're the real deals!
Everyone was watching us wherever we went!
And it was the best feeling!
It almost felt like we were kings or something!
Oh my, weren't you a real king or something?
Haga-san!
Please do your best!
You're our hero!
We'll be rooting for you!
Um...!
Please give me your autographs!
Haga-san! Ryuzaki-san!
Autograph?
Fine, I'll do it!
Here you go, Ryuzaki.
Right.
Thank you so much!
Hold it.
Don't tell me you thought it'd be free.
Give me one of your rare cards.
We were on top a' everyone!
But that didn't last very long...
Jounouchi! It's all because of you!
Huh? Because of me?
The fact that I lost to such a newbie like you in that national tournament made unrealistic gossip!
There's no mistake...
Red-Eyes ain't the only thing I lost in that match...!
Can you believe those two?
They lost right away in Duelist Kingdom, and to some newbies, too!
And one of 'em even had his rare card taken! How pathetic!
Yeah, yeah!
What the hell?
Guess they aren't anything great to have lost in the first round of the tournament!
Everyone acted the same!
As soon as we failed, they turned their backs on us!
Dammit!
Every single one of them made fun of us!
Dammit! DAMMIT!
It pisses me off!
Haga and Ryuzaki, right?
Who the hell're ya?
Is this your card?
Yup!
Thanks, big brother!
Eh?
Their autograph?
I threw it out!
I'd look uncool if my friends caught that!
What a disgrace....!
And from that day on, my life was the shits!
I remember it clearly to this day!
And it's all 'cuz a' you!
And what of it?
I asked what of it?
Just because you lost to me?
Everyone looks down on you just because you lost to me?!
Don't freakin' insult me!
What was that?!
Ryuzaki.
There can only be one winner in a Duel.
The other person loses completely.
Isn't that what makes everyone try their hardest?
Don't go around acting like you're some hero's victim!
Shut yer trap!
I'm sayin' all 'cuz of you, my life was ruined!
Then fight me fair-and-square!
If you lose, shouldn't you just try and try again?!
I'll take you on no matter how many times it takes!
It's not like I became strong over night.
No, even now it's the same.
I lost over and over again...
But I became stronger because of those loses!
That's what brought me up to my current level!
I'm different from a Duelist like you,
who gets stronger by joining Doma and taking people's souls!
Yer just like Mai Kujaku said...
What?!
It's that goody-goody attitude a' yers that pisses us off!
We all tried that strategy a' yers and thought we could get better!
Haga and Mai Kujaku, too!
But we just couldn't make it.
Ya get it, Jounouchi?
Just how much we suffer?
A damn-lucky bastard like you couldn't possibly understand what the two of us and Mai Kujaku go through!
Don't you dare compare yourselves to Mai!
No use sayin' a thing more to ya!
My turn!
Draw!
I sacrifice Fleet-Footed Gilasaurus and Giant Rex!
I Summon Tyrant Dragon!
And its Attack goes up by 500 points cuz a' da Orichalcos Seal!
Jounouchi!
I'm gonna beat ya no matter what!
Right! Bring it on!
You've hated me way too much, Haga!
That doesn't matter in the least bit!
In any event, you're gonna lose to me today.
My turn!
Draw!
Just 2 turns left until Parasite Caterpillar's Effect activates!
I'll send you to where your partner is very soon.
To where your poor partner suffers within the darkness of his heart!
Partner...!
I Summon Kuriboh in Defense Mode!
The Effect of DNA Surgery now activates!
I'll save Partner with my own two hands!
I set 1 Reverse Card!
Turn over!
Don't lose, Yugi...!
If you were to disappear, too...!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Hating Yugi and Jounouchi,
the two begged for Doma's assistance.
What's going on with Ryuzaki and Haga?!
It seems their decks have been powered up by Doma,
and the Orichalcos Seal powers them up even greater...
Yugi and Jounouchi are in over their heads!
It seems they must count on the Legendary Dragon cards!
If they have those cards...
Eh?
Yugi, what's wrong?
Next time!
"Timaeus Can't Be Activated"
Duel standby!