Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
We have finally arrived at the location of the Final, Alcatraz.
So we're going to settle Battle City on this Duel Tower built atop a pile of scrap?
Jounouchi-kun...
Kaiba...
Malik...
...and myself as well.
The four finalists have gathered and are now fighting against one another in a Battle Royale!
How should I fight in this battle meant to decide our opponents in the Semi-Finals?
"Battle Royale!"
Damn you, Yugi!
You're backing Jounouchi up?!
I owe you one, Yugi.
For me to play Jounouchi-kun in the Semi-Finals,
I have to make sure Kaiba and Malik's Life Points hit zero!
Kaiba, in order to ensure that happens, I won't let you attack Jounouchi-kun's Life Points any more!
Yugi, my life has been dictated by one purpose... and that purpose is to defeat you!
And to win this battle is my fate!
And above all, I must use the Obelisk I hold...
...and use it to win the Osiris you possess...
I need two so I stand a chance against the God Card he owns, the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Yugi, in order for me to dominate Battle City...
...as well as to earn the title of "Duel King"...
...I will face you in the Semi-Finals, even if I have to drag you there myself!
Thanks a lot, Yugi...
He wants to face me in the Semi-Finals so he can keep our promise.
I know how he feels.
Yugi, I really wanna fight against you, too!
But...
If I don't beat that guy, Mai may never wake up.
Mai's been waiting a long time now for me to save her!
Hmm, I see now.
Huh?
A scrub like you needs Yugi's protection.
What was that?!
I suppose a deadbeat like yourself can't manage to be a Duelist on his own.
You bastard! I dare you to say that again!
It's fine if you two friendship-obsessing dweebs want to keep your promise to Duel.
But just think about it, Jounouchi...
Why would Yugi help somebody like you?
I'll tell you why...
Because the Semi-Finals is your only chance to fight!
What!?
Jounouchi, regardless of who you face in the Semi-Finals, your chances of getting into the Final are 0%!
On top of your general lack of skill...
...the fact remains that the three of us have God Cards!
Yugi knows that the Semi-Finals will be your only chance to face him in battle.
And Yugi also knows that he'll be able to easily wipe the floor with you as a warm-up for the real challenge!
What did you say?!
I can't believe you would try such underhanded tactics right in the middle of the Battle City Finals!
You really insult me...
Kaiba! I won't let you insult him any further!
Insult him?
If you want to prove my words wrong,
shouldn't you leave your friendship nonsense out the window and settle things with me fair and square in the proper battlefield?!
Kaiba!!
Knock it off, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
I'm grateful that you saved me back there.
But this is my fight and my fight alone!
Don't be rattled by Kaiba's crap.
I'll see you in the Final, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun...
Thank you, Kaiba!
Your words cast my doubt away!
Just the howling of a loser dog...
As for you, Yugi...
You'll be fighting me in the Semi-Finals!
Kaiba...!
Stay strong, Mai-san!
Hey! That's dangerous, you two!
W-We're so sorry!
I'm sorry, but we're in a hurry here!
Let's get moving, Shizuka-chan.
Jounouchi-kun's waiting for us.
Jounouchi?
Hang on!
Do you guys know Jounouchi?
This girl is Jounouchi-kun's little sister.
We're being chased by some weird people called "Ghouls".
Ghouls...?
Get in!
I have decided that the first thing I want to see when my eyes are healed
is the sight of my big brother fighting his hardest!
I never knew Jounouchi
had such a cute sister.
I'm sure he'll be just fine.
He really is a good man.
He's kind... and courageous...
Even back in Duelist Kingdom, he fought for you as if his very life was at risk.
That's why I'm certain the brother you see will be one who will never betray you.
Mai-san!
Well, I may have over-exaggerated a bit there...
My brother's fighting his hardest right now, believing that you're going to wake up.
So open your eyes!
And cheer my brother on...
Mai-san!
The Tournament Final has finally begun.
That's right. Last night...
You're...?
My sister...
Big sister!
Rishid...!
Malik!
Save Rishid from that man!
I followed Malik's pleading and moved Rishid to another room.
But I haven't heard
Malik's voice since then!
Has Malik's soul disappeared altogether?
Or has he been completely trapped by his dark half's Power of Darkness?
Rishid...
This tragedy started
when you collapsed...
And the very day after...
Malik disappeared along with Rishid.
And they took the Millennium Rod with them.
After that tragedy, my tribe's mission failed miserably.
It faded away into the World of the Dead.
Oh, Millennium Tauk...!
Are you trying to tell me that this is only the beginning of the tragedy?!
Soon after, Malik stole the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra and Osiris the Heaven Dragon cards from the Valley of the Kings.
You will not find the Obelisk the War God card here!
It's been some time, big sister.
This can't just be coincidence.
For us to meet here this way, I mean.
Malik! Ghouls! Turn yourselves in!
Give it up, sister.
I take it you're now the official in charge of this place?
Well, it does make sense that a member of the Tomb Guardians would want to protect the palette depicting the God Cards.
Malik! Return the Ra and Osiris cards this instant!
They belong to me.
Just as this Millennium Rod does.
No! They belong to the nameless Pharaoh!
They must be returned
to their rightful owner!
Sister!
Have you forgotten?!
Our tragedy... no, the tragedy of the Tomb Guardians...!
All of it happened because of the nameless Pharaoh!
I'm going to find him no matter what it takes, and take revenge on him!
Stop this at once, Malik!
Your fate has already been decided!
You're only going to cause another tragedy to occur!
Quiet!
The scars carved into my back...!
The scars Rishid implanted in his face...!
Are you trying to tell me that our suffering was not caused by the nameless Pharaoh?!
I will never accept that!
Malik...!
Big sister... Using the Millennium Rod, I have organized the Ghouls.
Using this power, I will be able to kill the nameless Pharaoh!
Once I become the Pharaoh, I will change the fate of the Tomb Guardians forever!
And when that moment comes, my sister...
I will come back to pick you up.
And the three of us shall live together like we used to!
Malik, you will not get away from here!
Rishid...!
Big sister, I will get my hands on the remaining Obelisk card.
Rishid...
You're the only one who can stop the other Malik from awakening.
In order to prevent it, you have chosen to walk the same path as Malik, it seems.
Rishid... Now that you have fallen once more, all that's left of Malik's soul is his evil.
Thinking back on it now, everything has been chosen by fate.
A young boy named Yugi solving the Millennium Puzzle...
Pegasus discovering the location of the palette...
...and creating Duel Monsters as a result.
Seto Kaiba obtaining the God Card...
Oh, nameless Pharaoh...
Ours... as well as Malik's future...
They all ride on your shoulders!
Hey! Come on, now!
Let's continue the Duel already!
Whether it be your sealed memory or the Tomb Guardians...
You piss me off in
more ways than I can count!
So my target in the Semi-Finals...
It's you, Yugi!
My turn! Draw!
But first I'll sweep away all of these other yapping fools!
I set a reverse card!
And then I Summon Lord Poison!
Attack Mode!
Then, Newdoria goes into Attack Position!
Brace yourself, Kaiba...!
In order to reserve my fight with Yugi, I have to eliminate you!
Newdoria attacks Kaiba's Blood Vorse!
What?! Attacking me with a Monster that has lower Attack Power?!
How amusing!
Does Malik's Monster have some kind of Special Ability?
Counter him!
Blood Vorse!
Newdoria dies!
His Special Ability activates!
The moment he is placed in the Graveyard,
his curse destroys one Monster on the field!
And I choose...
Blood Vorse!!
Yes! Now Kaiba's field is wide open! The bastard!
I take 700 points of damage this turn because of that attack.
But I will now activate this Magic Card from my hand!
Spell of Pain!
It's a card that transfers damage you receive to one of the other players!
I wonder who will
take this effect... Let's see...
I shall activate this effect on Jounouchi!
What?!
As a result, your gondola rises 700 units thanks to the points you lost!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Shit...! I'm closest to the top!
Calm down! You only lost 700 Life Points!
You'll be fine! There's still a chance to turn things around!
Easy for you to say...
I got no Monsters on the field...
I'm totally at a disadvantage!
Just as planned, Kaiba's Monster was destroyed and the damage was sent to someone else.
And on my next turn, I'll sacrifice this Monster to Summon a better Monster.
Turn end!
My turn!
Right now, Kaiba doesn't have any Monsters on the field!
I'll take him out with one blow!
I sacrifice Big Shield Gardna!
To Summon the Archfiend of Gilfer Demon!
Here I go, Kaiba!
Bring it on, Yugi!
Gilfer Flame!!
Big brother!
That was naive, Yugi!
I read right through that strategy!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Attack Guidance Armor!
This card redirects any attack sent my way to the Monster attached to this armor!
A card that switches the attack target...?
I could make your Gilfer Demon attack himself, Yugi...
Now then... Who do I pick...?
Oh wait, I don't even have a Monster in play...
Lucky!
I place the Guidance Armor on...
...your Monster!
Malik!!
You're going to take Gilfer Demon's attack!
Can't be helped, I guess.
Trap Card, activate!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
Mirror Force?!
So now your Gilfer Demon's attack will be negated, Yugi, and all of your Monsters will be destroyed!
We'll see about that.
Counter Trap, activate!
Seven Tools of the Bandit!
This card negates the activation of your Mirror Force and destroys it.
What did you say!?
This is really heating up...
Malik! You just lost some of your Life in the attack just now!
Therefore, your gondola will rise!
Malik's Life Points are the same as mine...
Hold it. I hope you don't think you can simply forget about this, Yugi.
The cost of using that Seven Tools of the Bandit you just played is 1000 of your Life Points.
So you'll be rising along with me!
I'm well aware.
What?!
Yugi's the closest to the top.
I get it! The point in this Battle Royale isn't to win!
You can still choose the opponent you want even if you lose.
Damn you to hell, Yugi...!
Are you still trying to fight with that deadbeat in the Semi-Finals?!
My turn!
I don't have a Monster Card in my hand!
Please be one!
Draw!
Yes!
I Summon Iron Knight Gearfried!
Attack Position!
He finally got a Monster out.
Go for it, Jounouchi!
All right, who should I attack...?
Kaiba and Malik both used their face-down cards on Yugi's turn just now...
And they don't have any Monsters to protect them!
They're wide open!
Which one should I attack though?
Although...!
It's an easy pick!
Here goes, Kaiba!
I'm going to Direct Attack you!
Kaiba has no way to defend himself!
Take this, Kaiba!!
Big brother!
Hell yeah!
Damn you...! How dare a lowly scrub like you wound me...!
Hey, Kaiba! I'm gonna send you to the top just like you wanted!
As a loser, anyway!
Now Malik and Jounouchi-kun are closest together in the gondolas...
Jounouchi-kun went after Kaiba instead of attacking Malik...
Could that mean...?!
Does that mean he wants to fight Malik himself?!
Mai's life could end at any time...!
I have to beat Malik in the Semi-Finals!
I'll also place a card face-down!
My turn is over!
My turn! Draw!
It's true that if I attack Yugi and find a way to off myself in the process...
I would be guaranteed to fight Yugi in the Semi-Finals.
But for me to lose before the Semi-Finals...
I set three reverse cards!
I then Summon Blade Knight in Attack Mode!
Knocking that deadbeat out can wait!
I'll be attacking you, Malik!
Blade Knight!
Direct Attack Malik!
Blade Attack!!
Damn...! Now it's gotten harder for me to fight Malik in the first round!
Now Malik is closer to the top...
I really wonder who will end up fighting who.
There's no room for failure on my road of battle...!
All I need to do is dispose of Malik and the deadbeat...
...and defeat Yugi in the Semi-Finals.
Don't you also want to show them all, Yugi?!
Our battle of the gods!!
As the four continue to face off in the Battle Royale,
the Duel is getting so complex that we can't tell the ending!
Jounouchi finds himself in trouble when he gets attacked by both Kaiba and Mallik at the same time.
Just as Yugi is about to attack, Jounouchi suddenly asks him a question.
"What does it mean to be a True Duelist"...?!
What in the world are you thinking?!
Next time!
"The Respective Opponents"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise