Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Unknown Challenger:
The Giant Mobile Fortress Submerges!"
The Dark Games that occurred last night...
Did Bakura-kun really lose like Malik said...?
So you came here, Yugi?
Where did you send Bakura?!
Who knows?!
Nobody knows where those who lose a Dark Game are sent!
So how should I know?
And the man who acted as Malik's shadow...
And Mai-san also got hurt because of Malik!
I don't know what happened between him and my other self relating to his lost memories...
But I just can't forgive Malik!
That hurt!
Wh-What happened? An earthquake?
Oh, I forgot that I'm on an aircraft.
No way that's possible.
Shizuka-chan~
What are you two dreaming about huddled together like that?!
Get up!
The hell was that for...?
Morning already?
Get up! Something's wrong with the ship!
Huh?
Anzu-san! When did she...?
What?! What!?
What are you doing? Steady the ship already!
What's going on?!
Brother!
The Battle Ship went off the route of our destination.
What did you say?!
Hurry and turn us back!
Right...! It's just... The auto-driving system changed route by itself!
What the hell are you talking about? Then manually override it!
Kaiba-kun!
What's with the shaking?
Is this ship okay?
I feel you... I feel you!
Some kind of evil intent...
I feel like something really entertaining is about to happen!
What the hell are you doing?!
I can't change it to Manual Mode!
I've lost control!
What?!
Alcatraz's computer also refused access!
There's no signal from the tower.
That's impossible!
What's that island?!
That's the destination of our final battles, Alcatraz.
So that's the location of the Finals?
That's right.
That pitiful wreckage is a symbol of the founder of Kaiba Corporation, Gozaburo Kaiba.
Our foster father, Gozaburo Kaiba,
attempted to conquer the world using the great military industry he founded.
These ruins are a symbol of his dream.
After he died, my big brother changed Kaiba Corporation into a gaming industry.
He destroyed the former military facilities,
and he then built the Duel Tower in their place.
That's enough, Mokuba!
I built the Duel Tower deliberately in the ruins of Alcatraz.
It's a symbol of my determination.
The moment I receive the title of Duel King at the top,
I'll gain true victory for the first time in my life!
And I'll finally be freed of his abominable curse!
Kaiba-kun seems to hate his father....
I wonder what happened between them?
I figured out the cause!
A hacker invaded our computer and gained access to the ship!
He is controlling the system, and it
seems he wants to steer the ship!
Then do something about it!
We must land on Alcatraz on schedule!
Who the hell did this?
What the heck's going on here?!
You trying to kill us?!
Do something, Kaiba!
Is there really no way to override the control?
It's not working!
We're completely under the hacker's control!
How's this possible?
Is it Gozaburo's ghost?
He doesn't want us landing on the island?
What...?
Who the hell are you?!
Are you telling me it was this child...?
I've been waiting for you, Seto...
And I welcome you Duelists as well.
What?!
A child?
He addressed Kaiba-kun so formerly...
And that kid looks kind of like him...!
He looks exactly like my brother used to...
Answer me! I asked you who you were!
My name is Noah.
Let's see...
If I had to put it in simple terms, Seto, I'd say I am a person far greater than you.
Now shall we get to the point?
Little punk... You sure like to hear yourself talk!
Now then, I would like to invite you to be my guests in my home.
Noah... What in the world are you planning?
That's...!
Wh-What is...
...that?
Wh-What the hell?
You're kidding me!
I-It's so big!
It's monstrous.
I'm not really sure what's going on, but things are getting quite amusing.
You have to do something!
I'm trying! We've lost complete control of the ship!
We're in their command now!
Damn!
What the hell's going on here?!
Big Brother!
Don't worry, I-I'll protect you.
Damn you...!
Could this Noah brat be capable of doing all this?
No...
Can I ask you to get off the ship, Seto?
Of course, the other Duelists, too.
And if I were to... refuse?
I'm afraid you all have become my prisoners.
You don't have a choice.
O-Oi!
Is he serious?!
Kaiba-kun!
He's after me. This has nothing to do with you guys.
But...
Mokuba, you stay here.
Brother!
Noah, what are your intentions?
Just tell me.
I believe I told you before that I was inviting all the Duelists.
I think that we should do what he wants for the time being.
Kaiba, this isn't only your problem anymore.
It doesn't look like he's going to let us go that easily.
-Seto-sama!
I don't need anyone else but them.
You two will remain on the ship.
What's the deal?
I guess he's mistaken us for Duelists...
Shizuka, you should stay on the ship.
But I can't let you risk your life alone.
Shizuka!
The atmosphere here is filled with chaos and destruction.
I'll just stay back and observe for a while...
What are you going to do with us?
To be honest, there are some people here who have been eagerly waiting to see you.
They're just a bit up ahead.
They'll explain everything to you.
What's up with this room?
It's so dark we can't see anything.
If there's someone here, come out already!
What's that?
Seto Kaiba and your little friends...
It's been quite some time.
It can't be! You guys...!
The Big Five!
Huh? The Big 5?!
You guys know them?!
They betrayed Kaiba-kun. They were the group that controlled Kaiba Corporation.
They used cheap tricks to try and take over my big brother's company!
But didn't they lose in the game they set up themselves?
And weren't they unable to return to our world?
President...
Why don't you play a little game with us, gambling on your firing us.
In the end, you aren't qualified to be our president!
Disappear along with the Blue-Eyes!
Big Brother!!
Unforgivable...
You'll pay, Big Five!
Go!
Master of Dragon Knight!!
Galaxy Crusher!!
This is impossible!!
Upon returning to the real world, they never regained consciousness...
We wandered the Virtual World for ages after that...
In a world where you eventually lose all sense of who you are.
The only thing driving us is the anger and need for revenge against you!
You're not the only one who we hate, Seto Kaiba.
The other people who also got in the way of our plans and caused our suffering...
Yugi Mutou and his pack of buddies are just as guilty for shaming us!
That grudge isn't even justified!
Just as persistent as you always were, I see...
How'd you fools come back, anyway?
While we roamed the world of cyberspace,
someone who understood our feelings gave us a hand.
I presume you mean that little brat we met earlier called Noah?
Noah-sama gave us but one condition to follow.
If we still want to control Kaiba Corporation as the Big Five,
we have to Duel you all and beat you fairly.
So you want to Duel us?
Though we want to kill you all as soon as possible, we can't disobey Noah-sama.
If you want to get out of here safe and sound, the only way is to Duel with us.
If we're gonna Duel, there's no way I'm gonna lose to you guys!
Now then, we invite you to be our guests in the Duel World.
This is...
Why are we in a jungle?
Virtual Space, eh?
Big Brother!
Don't worry. No matter how scary it looks, it's all just an illusion.
But it's not just the colors and shapes... Even the smells seem real.
They can even imitate pulses in the air.
Big Brother!
I-I told you... It's an illusion!
Kaiba-kun!
Big Brother!
Threatening me with such childish holograms that can't even project the sense of touch?
At any rate, this is nothing more than a poor monkey-level copy of the Solid Vision I created.
It's true.
Are you guys kidding here, or what?
What's up with that guy?
Our Duels are based on the Deck Master System.
Deck Master System?
I'll present a simulated system Duel so you can understand.
Total Defense Shogun will act as his own Deck Master.
And we'll set Blue-Eyes White Dragon as
Seto Kaiba's Deck Master!
Blue-Eyes is the Deck Master?
What kind of rule is this?
It's my turn! I'll Summon Lord of Dragons!
And I'll activate the Magic Card,
Dragon-Calling Flute!
Then I'll use its Special Effect to Summon two other Dragon-Types to the field from my hand.
And finally, I'll Summon my Deck Master to the field!
Hey, he Summoned three
Blue-Eyes at once!
I see! So the Deck Master can be placed on the field as a separate Summon from a Normal Summon?
Next, a Fusion Summon!
I Summon Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!
And thanks to its Deck Master Ability,
the Ultimate Dragon can attack on the same turn it was Fusion Summoned.
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!
Direct Attack Total Defense Shogun!
But because Total Defense Shogun is a Deck Master himself,
he can pay the cost of 1000 Life Points to activate his Deck Master Ability.
Total Defense Barrier!!
Due to the Effect of Total Defense Barrier, the attacking Monster is destroyed!
When the Deck Master is destroyed,
regardless of how many Life Points the player has, he loses.
Any Monster chosen to be the Deck Master has an additional Special Ability to its usual ones.
The Monster you choose to be your Deck Master becomes one of the main points to your strategy.
Screwing with us like this...!
Since you said we'd be Dueling fairly,
why did you make up such ridiculous rules?!
Big Five, I won't go easy on you guys!
What do you think?
Will you accept the Duel with us?
You don't have any other way out of here if you don't accept.
Damn it all...! You're not giving us a choice at all!
Okay, I'll take your challenge!
Big Brother!
Don't worry, Shizuka.
Betting my pride as a Duelist on the line, I swear to win this!
And... I'll be sure to protect you as well.
Okay! Good luck, Big Brother!
We have no choice but to accept the Duel now.
Count me in! I'll give you a hand!
Me too.
Alright! Let's get em, guys!
Just a minute. But what'll happen to us if we lose?
You bring up an excellent point.
It's only natural that the victorious party is to be presented with compensation from the losing party.
As per the risk of your losing to us,
our minds wandering this Cyber World will enter your bodies and take control of them.
You scumbags...!
That means you'll be exchanged with us.
You'll wander the Cyber World for all eternity!
No way!
Shit! That's low!
This is our revenge against you all!
"Preview"
The Big Five, who didn't learn their lesson, show up before us
and they want to have a Duel with us.
If you're told, "You can't go back
if you don't accept",
You have no choice but accept it.
In a different Virtual Space, separate from before,
the first coming before Yugi is The Deepsea Warrior.
I got it!
This Deck Master System is to allow the Big Five to take the forms of Monsters!
Next time!
"Deck Master - Deepsea Warrior"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise