Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Mai Kujaku, who became a subordinate of Doma, came to get Jounouchi-kun's soul.
But because of the appearance of the Claw of Hermos,
Mai disappeared before us.
The message left by Pegasus revealed the truth about Doma.
With such a mighty enemy ahead of us,
Jounouchi-kun and Kaiba, who were chosen by the Legendary Dragons...
The three of us have to join forces no matter what!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Target is the Nameless Pharaoh"
Impossible! There's no way this can happen in reality!
I feel it! There's a strong power coming from the card!
The three cards are resonating towards one another.
It seems like it became our destiny to defeat Doma ever since we got these cards.
Destiny? Nonsense!
I decide the path I follow on my road of life!
Don't speak words like "destiny" or "fate" in front of me!
You're still saying that now, Kaiba?!
These aren't opponents you can beat by yourself!
We need your strength!
I refuse!
I won't take orders from you!
Kaiba!
I'll settle things with Doma by myself.
The rest of you can continue playing your make-believe occult games.
Let's go, Mokuba
Kaiba!
B-Brother...!
We don't need to rely on someone like him.
With a card like Claw of Hermos, we aren't gonna be beaten by the likes of Doma!
You're becoming more like yourself now, Jounouchi!
Of course!
If we keep being so pessimistic, nothing will get resolved!
Damn!
Where are they?!
Why're they the only ones gettin' such strong cards? It's so unfair!
We just need to keep searching...! They must be somewhere...
What are you guys doing?
My glasses... My glasses...
They're right there, aren't they?
But what should we do now?
Pegasus is missing and we have no further clues.
It's obvious that we need to go after those Doma bastards and get Mai back!
Even if you say that, we have no idea where to start.
How do we find them?
Well, I guess...
Exactly...
For the time being, why don't you guys come over to my apartment?
It's small, though.
Oh yes, Professor Hopkins..
If it's Professor Hopkins, he may have some clues on this!
That's true!
The professor returned to America to unveil the mysteries of those relics found underwater.
Yes.
Doma and the relics...
I feel that the both of them must be related to one another in some ways.
OK!
Since we've already decided, all we need is to find a way to get there!
HEY!! Let us get on, too!
Drat, he left...
We've got transportation!
Let's use my car to get there.
But look at how many people we have here...
Erm...
Are we also...?
Come to think of it, what are two here for anyway?
So this is our fate in the end?
Even though Yugi an' his gang somehow obtained super strong cards...
...the two of us got nothin'!
The show is just starting!
Everyone knows that Professor Hopkins is an avid card mania collector!
He must have many of those collector's must-have cards!
There's still room for our skills ta' improve, long as we get hold a' rare cards!
Having said that, Mai Kujaku has gotten really strong!
Hey, pass it over. Let me look at it for a bit!
You're so noisy...!
I am the navigator now, so don't interrupt!
Wouldn't it be faster if we took this road instead?
What good will going to Alaska do us?!
Do you have any sense of direction?
Well... Uh...
Huh? Where are we again? Somewhere around here...?
Mai...
With my own will, I've chosen to fight with you!
What did you say?!
That can't be true!
The things you guys obtained in Battle City...!
I want that too!
I want to catch up to you guys!
I want to beat you all, no matter what!
This is the only way!
Dammit...!
I can't convince her with my words now...
But...
You're mistaken, Mai!
This isn't the way we aim to become True Duelists!
The other me...
Partner.
You must not be hasty.
I know.
But Mai has been
bought over by our enemies...
And even Pegasus's soul has been taken away.
I've lost too many things.
You're right...
We couldn't get Kaiba-kun to cooperate with us either...
Looks like it will be a tough fight ahead...
Why did you stop me!?
If I continued with the fight, I would have defeated Jounouchi!
If only you hadn't interfered!!
Varon!
Shard of the Orichalcos!
Release your power!
Give it a rest.
Who do you suppose is the reason Varon's in this state right now?
That doesn't have anything to do with me!
This is the retribution from interrupting my Duel!
Interrupt?
You already lost.
Don't say anymore, Rafael...!
Stop screwing with me!
I won't let you off easily if you continue spouting rubbish!
Up 'till now, how have you been perceiving that man?
Huh?
The Legendary Dragon card that appeared in his deck suddenly...
That is something only the Chosen True Duelists can obtain.
Do not think lightly of him.
Hmph! Jounouchi is a True Duelist?!
Whatever!
I'll show you who the real True Duelist around here is!
Hey! My bike!
Jounouchi, I won't let this matter rest.
I'll make up for Mai...!
I'll defeat Jounouchi!...!
Don't be so anxious.
Before that, we have to deal with Yugi.
We have to Duel with him all of a sudden now?
It is true that he has received the Legendary Dragon card.
But the situation is still in our favor.
As long as we defeat the nameless Pharaoh,
the rest of them will be easy pickings.
How are you going to lure Yugi out?
I know where they are going.
I have already made preparations.
Doma...
Down, boy! Down!
I think I bought a little too much food.
I know it's rather heavy, but please keep going a bit longer, Billy!
Visitors..?
Grandpa!!
Billy!!
Grandpa!
How could this happen...?
Grandpa!!
How terrible...
Professor Hopkins! Rebeca!
Yugi!
Rebecca...!
Yugi...
Grandpa, he...
Grandpa, he...!
What happened, Rebecca?
Yugi...
Who could have done such a thing?
It's got to be Doma! They're the only ones capable of this!
But why would they want to capture Professor Hopkins?
So there was a relation with those cipher texts after all!
Yeah, that's what I'm thinking.
Rebecca, that fragment...
It's the crystal-like fragment I left with the professor.
Ah, right... It's all right. Here it is.
Grandpa told me to hold on to this carefully.
So in the end we don't even know what this thing is and we don't have any clues...
What should we do now?
What should we do?
This is a crime if I've ever seen one!
We have to contact the police!
We can't!
If you do that, my grandpa...
Rebecca...
Anyway, let's not jump to conclusions.
Lets observe what the enemy does first.
Damn!
So in the end we can only wait?
Can't be helped.
Anyway, shouldn't we eat something first?
We haven't eaten all day.
True.
Rebecca, can I borrow your kitchen?
Then I'll help you out.
Otogi, you know how to cook?
Don't worry, I'm sure Professor Hopkins will return to us safely.
Let me handle this.
Yeah...
Honda, please set the table!
We don't have enough plates!
Hey Jounouchi, what are you doing?
You jerk!
Where'd Haga and Ryuzaki run off to?
Now that you mention it, Yugi and Rebeca aren't here either.
Where is it?
Why are you resting?
Continue searching!
How can there be any cards here?
Even if there was, they'd 'ov been burnt anyway!
You're right...
I feel like eating takoyaki...
[Fried/baked octopus dumplings]
I don't wanna eat spaghetti...
I wanna eat sushi...!
What did you want to tell me?
Yugi, please save my grandpa!
I know that. I promise I'll rescue the professor.
It's not that.
This is...
I didn't know know to say this, so I kept quiet about it before...
Nameless Pharaoh, I'll wait for you at Death Valley.
You must come alone. The Three Musketeers of Doma - Rafael.
Rebecca, where is this "Death Valley"?
It's about an hour or so if you travel in this direction by car.
I'm sorry, Rebecca.
I've gotten the both of you involved in our battle.
But I can't let you go alone, Yugi.
It's all right.
I will rescue Professor Hopkins!
But I want you to keep this a secret from the others.
Yugi...
Are you awake?
Professor Hopkins.
W-Who are you?
I am one of The Three Musketeers of Doma, Rafael.
Doma?
Are you referring to the "Doma" in the cipher texts?
So those relics found underwater have something to do with you guys?
And with Yugi-kun, or rather, the nameless Pharaoh, right?
Professor, I advise you not to involve yourself any further with us.
We've already turned your research lab into ashes
Even so, you can never stop us from researching the relics!
Even if I am not present, as long as those relics still exist in this world...
That is impossible.
What do you mean by that?
Who knows...
But you should feel relieved.
Because you are now free to go.
I have now finished my prior preparations.
Doma...
I'll never forgive all of you.
Yugi...?
Please don't worry about me.
I'm headed out.
Yugi...
Rafael...
Wait for me!
I will defeat you, no matter what it takes!
O-Ow! Ouch!!
Huh? Yugi?
You idiot!
Why didn't you say anything?!
She couldn't help it, Jounouchi!
You should spare some thought for Rebecca!
We should have informed the police about it after all, huh?
Dammit!
Jounouchi!
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
Professor Hopkins!
Grandpa!
Professor!
Rebecca, where is Yugi-kun?
Other Me!
Partner!
They didn't think this through all the way.
So you noticed as well, Partner?
Of course I did.
The two of us can never be "alone".
Indeed!
Anzu, leave Yugi to us.
Please take care of the professor and Rebecca.
Alright, I understand.
I will leave Yugi in your hands.
You can count on us!
By the way, where the heck did Haga and Ryuzaki go, anyway?
No matter what, I must witness the match between Doma and Yugi!
I want to learn the secret to why Mai became even stronger than before!
I know!
That's why we're takin' this ta' get there 'fore he does!
Cripes! He's gonna surpass us!!
Dammit!
Yugi...
We'll be there soon, Yugi!
Nameless Pharaoh, we will defeat you!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Because of Doma's despicable methods,
Yugi was made to proceed to Death Valley alone.
I beg you! Please be careful!
Professor Hopkins came back safe and sound!
But we have no idea what kind of traps we will be facing in the future!
That guy named Rafael...
His cool and composed nature brings forth a certain danger!
What kind of deck will he be choosing to Duel with?
Next time!
"Yugi vs Rafael - The Impregnable Guardian Deck"
Duel standby!