Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
After having his heart infected by evil, the High Priest of Darkness, Akhenaden,
planned to destroy the world so his son, Seto, could reign as Pharaoh...
...taking Kisara's life to do so.
But Kisara was reborn as the White Dragon and she protected Seto.
She was able to take Seto's heart away from the darkness.
But the sand in the Hourglass of Isolated Desperation has run out...
...meaning Zorc's resurrection has begun!
"Revival of the Great Wicked God Zorc"
You'll find the deck in your Disk contains exactly 40 cards that you imagined.
However, we both won't know which card we'll get until we draw...
A deck we formed from our imaginations?
I'm pretty sure you're prepared for what lies ahead.
This Duel is a Dark Game.
The second our Life Points reach zero, our lives will fade away.
Stop this, Yugi!
This Duel is far too dangerous!
Just hold on, Bakura!
What'd you do with Honda?!
Honda?
Back then, I sent a parasite into his body...
...and I used him to spy on you guys this entire time.
So it happened back there...
That's a really low trick you pulled!
Give Honda back!
If you want him back, you'll have to defeat me in this Duel.
Honda-kun...
Let's go!
Yugi!
Duel!!
This way!
Hurry!
Kalim!
Isis, we must go!
Thank you, Mana!
Serves you all right!
Bakura!
You've got nowhere left to run, fools!
That's...!
The Stone Tablet of the Underworld...
Your lives end right here.
Arise! Great Wicked God Zorc!
That is...!
Wh-What?!
That's... The Great Wicked God Zorc!
He ended up reviving...
At this very moment,
I hereby control the character known as "Great Wicked God Zorc"!
Your puny priests are no longer a match for me!
Now, turn this city upside down!
Burn all the humans to the bone!
If Zorc's Power of Darkness is resurrected once again,
this world will be annihilated!
I have been brought back from a long slumber in order to bring this world to naught!
None of you can dare to raise even a finger to me!
Both the living and the dead...
You shall all be swallowed
in the fires of Hell!
Zorc Inferno!!
Sir Hasan!
Let me... handle this...
All of you, get going!
But...!
You must return to the royal palace in order to protect the city!
Now! Make haste!
Yes!
How foolish are you to even think of opposing me?
You are the equivalent of nothing in the face of my power!
M-My Pharaoh...
Seems Zorc's already made his appearance above ground.
What did you say?!
But since this entire tomb is currently being protected by a massive barrier,
Zorc's assault won't affect us.
It means we can enjoy this Duel to our hearts content.
Yugi!
You can do it! Don't you lose!
Now that the Great Wicked God Zorc has resurrected,
we only have one shred of hope left.
My turn!
Draw!
I've got to tell my other self his name now that we've finally found it...
...so he can seal Zorc away once again.
I can't afford to lose here.
I play one reverse card...
...and I end my turn by Summoning a Monster in Face-Down Defense Mode.
Hmph. Aren't you the passive one?
It's my turn!
I draw!
You can't beat me playing like that!
I Summon the Knight of Death -
Deathcalibur Knight!
Attack his Face-Down Defense Monster!
I activate Marshmallon's Reverse Effect!
The player attacking it receives 1000 points of damage!
Also, Marshmallon can't
be destroyed in battle!
You used a really annoying card...
I place one reverse card and end my turn!
Zorc is headed for the city!
What?!
We must hurry!
No matter what it takes, we must not let him into the city!
So Zorc's already...
Hmph. So that's the so-called "Great Wicked God" you've been going on about...
Kisara...
Please lend me your power...
Pharaoh!
I know!
Kaiba, what do you plan to do?
I already told you.
I have no intention of
taking orders from you.
Then do as you please.
How mysterious...
You give off the
same feeling as Lord Seto.
But I have a feeling that
we will meet again.
Shimon!
Shada!
The Pharaoh has returned!
Pharaoh!
Are you feeling okay, my Pharaoh?
Seto!
I am glad to see you're safe!
I apologize for making you all worry.
What about Lord Akhenaden...?
Akhenaden has been destroyed.
I don't...!
Seto will be all right now.
Pharaoh...
Zorc is headed this way!
Have you prepared?
Pharaoh!
Pharaoh, you have little Ba remaining.
Please let me handle this.
Please focus on recovering and let me give the orders.
I'll leave this to you, Seto.
Yes, my lord!
Here he comes!
Are all of you prepared?!
We will not allow him to take even one step into our city!
Protect it with your very lives!
- YEAH!!
- For the Pharaoh!
This is different from anything I've ever imagined before...
It's a new deck I created.
Wait for me, Other Me.
I'll definitely defeat Bakura-kun using this deck.
And I'll get your real name to you!
My turn!
Draw!
I set one reverse card!
Then I Summon Silent Swordsman LV. 0 in Attack Mode!
Marshmallon and Silent Swordsman...
They're all Monsters I've never seen.
The deck is different from the one he usually uses.
He's probably using Marshmallon as a way to earn himself a chance...
And he also Summoned that weakling Monster...
What is he thinking...?
Reverse card, open!
Marshmallon Glasses!
The Monster wearing the Marshmallon Glasses can only target Marshmallon when attacking.
Tch... He used something really irritating...
I'll end my turn there!
A trick of that level won't work against me!
It's my turn!
Draw!
The vessel without the king is nothing but a dried up stream!
Magic Card!
Dead Spirit's Defense Seal!
It switches Marshmallon into Attack Mode!
Take this!
Deathcalibur Knight attacks Marshmallon!
I'll then set one card in reverse and end my turn!
Fire!
He's a monster...!
Do not falter!
Fire! Fire!!
Miserable worms...
Stop this, Bakura!
What are you babbling about this late into the game?
What?!
What is...?
Seems what's happening in the world of the Dark Games
has started to link to the real world.
What do you mean?
That's the "Ultimate Dark Game" for you!
Things are starting to get even out of my control...
But it's a favorable change.
I'm about to uncover the Eighth Key, your real name.
Then I intended to resurrect Zorc in the real world.
But this just makes things easier for me.
Now the world of memories is no different from the real world!
Everyone will perish within the darkness!
I have to seal Zorc... No matter what it takes!
If this continues...!
Seto! We should retreat for now and refortify our shield!
Damn it...
Everyone, fall back!
Save me, Mama~!
I don't wanna die yet~!
Nice...
Rampage more...!
More! More! Create more destruction!
Damn you, Bakura!
My turn!
Draw!
This moment, Silent Swordsman rises to Level One!
Silent Swordsman...?
One of those Monsters that raises its level every turn...?
It's got 1500 Attack Points...
It still can't beat the 1900 Attack Power Deathcalibur Knight...
If so...
It's my Battle Phase!
Hold it!
The moment you enter into your Battle Phase...
...I can activate this!
The Trap Card...
Earthbound Spirit's Invitation!
Earthbound Spirit's Invitation forces the Silent Swordsman
to attack the Monster of my choice.
I then activate my second Trap Card!
I use a Special Summon to call upon the Trap Monster, Death Spirit Zoma!
In Defense Mode!
Silent Swordsman attacks the Death Spirit!
Hey... Why'd he purposely have him attack his Defense Position Monster?
If he had it attack his Deathcalibur Knight, Silent Swordsman would have been destroyed.
How naive.
Now that the Death Spirit's been killed,
Zoma changes into ectoplasm!
And when Zoma is destroyed,
its Special Ability inflicts damage onto the opposing player
equal to double the total Attack Power of the Monster that attacked it.
In other words, double the Attack Power of Silent Swordsman...
It means that, Yugi, you'll be taking 3000 points of damage!
Yugi's only got 2400 of his Life left!
Shit! Bakura's about to win this match in one turn!
That was the true objective I was aiming for with my Trap Combo.
Die!!
Yugi!
I've been waiting for this moment!
How did he...?! The ectoplasm...!
I activated my Magic Card... Turn Jump!
Turn Jump...?!
It means I skipped this turn's Battle Phase
and Death Spirit Zoma's
Effect was negated!
But still...
That's not all!
What!?
At this moment, the Silent Swordsman... advanced to Level Four!
3000 Attack Points!?
Here we go! Silent Swordsman attacks!
Silent Sword level Four!!
Deathcalibur Knight was blasted to pieces!
He's strong...!
Yugi...!
Finally... Marshmallon, Direct Attack the player!
Turn end!
That's awesome, Yugi!
When you think about it...
The other Yugi was always the one fighting the other Duelists we've encountered.
But now, Yugi's fighting himself to save the other Yugi.
With his own deck.
You can do this, Yugi!
For a mere vessel, he's sure giving me quite the entertainment...
If we do not defeat the Great Wicked God Zorc,
this world will be swallowed by the blackest shadows,
and we will never be freed from this curse of darkness.
We High Priests will mobilize all the Ka we possess!
Spiria!
Two-Headed Jackal Warrior!
Summon!
Duos!
How long will it take for you ants to learn the foolishness of opposing me?
Aura Force!!
Please lend me your power, Master!
Magic Blast!!
What desperate little fleas.
Perish, lowly worms!!
Curse you!
What destructive force...!
Hey, hey... Such a one-sided game is hardly fun at all.
Honestly, I thought you'd at least entertain me for a bit longer than this...
Boy, were my expectations wrong.
Bakura...! You bastard...!
Guess it's about time we set the game, eh?
Pharaoh!
The end.
Shada...!
My Pharaoh...
Pull yourself together!
I am... glad... you are unharmed...
Shada...
Shada!!
Looks like your life was extended because of your little servant.
You monster...!
Of course, it just means that guy won't stick around to see you suffer.
Give up, Yugi.
Nothing you try now will make a difference.
This Dark Game, Yugi...
...leaves you with a zero percent chance of victory.
Shada...
Does this mean that I have...
...nothing left to fight with?!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The Great Wicked God Zorc has finally been resurrected.
His power is ridiculously enormous!
Good luck, Yugi!
You have to hurry up and beat Bakura in this Duel so you can find the Pharaoh's name...
...or this world will be destroyed by Zorc!
Elsewhere, the Pharaoh and his priests are cornered by Zorc.
They try to reclaim the Millennium Items!
Next time!
"The Legendary Protector God:
Exodia Revives!"
Duel standby!