A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"The Girl From America"
Bakura!
Everybody!
You're awake, Mokuba?
Thank goodness.
Oi~!
Yugi!
What were you doing?
I'm sorry, I had some things to do.
Mokuba-kun, the seal has been removed.
Where's my big brother?
Where is my big brother at?
Mokuba...
Croquet-san.
Master Pegasus has been sent away to a hospital.
Bakura-kun can't be...
But the Millennium Ring was thrown away...
I don't think so.
Take this.
This is...?
A card called the Bonds of Friendship.
Master Pegasus told me to give this to Yugi Mutou.
You guys did well in your duels.
This is the prize money.
Jounouchi-kun.
That's great, Jounouchi.
Now Shizuka-chan can be...
Shizuka, wait for me... I'll surely...
Jounouchi-kun...
Then please excuse me.
Yugi. The seal on Mokuba-kun was broken. Could it be....
Grandpa must be.....
Yu-gi...
Big brother!
Where's Kaiba-kun?
Big brother.....
Mokuba.
Geez. You have to take care of each other, you idiots.
Brother, I protected our Kaiba Corporation.
I know.
I'm sure they haven't discovered that this is the key card.
Mokuba, that was really cool.
You protected Kaiba Corporation.
Yugi, you saved Mokuba.
I owe you one.
It's nothing.
But Yugi, don't you forget that our duel is not over yet.
I know.
I'm looking forward to dueling you again.
Good job.
Thanks!
It was thanks to you!
We did it together.
No, not just us.
It's everyone's victory.
Come to think of it, how are we going to get off this island?
Ah... hold on a minute, Kaiba!
Don't leave us here!
I finally got the Millennium Eye.
Grandpa.
Grandpa!!
Yugi!
Welcome back, Grandpa.
I see! Good job, Yugi.
No. Everyone helped out.
Yeah, everyone. Especially me.
Alright. Let's all celebrate tonight.
Lucky.
Alright!
Grandpa, the doctor said you need rest.
What are ya talkin' about?! As you can see, I'm perfectly healthy!
Grandpa?!
Are you sure you're alright gramps?
Who's that? Someone we know?
You Suguroku Mutou?
I am. And you are?
My name is Rebecca.
I arrived here this morning from America.
My goodness! You guys are so slow.
What's the meaning of keeping a lady waiting?!
Lady?
What's that? Aren't I a lady?
Oi oi, why are you coming all the way to Japan by yourself?
What are you here for?
Goddamn! I don't speak to impolite people like this guy. Right, Teddy-chan?
What'd ya say? You punk.
Rebecca, what did you want to talk to me about?
Give it back!
What?
Give back the Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Hurry up and give it back! It's mine.
That card's...
Blue-Eyes White Dragon was an American super rare card.
It's only right that I, America's number one strongest, should have it. Right, Teddy-chan?
America's number one strongest?
That's right. Because I'm the U.S. Champion!
U.S. Champion?
Yes.
Come on...
Is this some kind of joke?
There's no mistake. I saw her on a magazine once.
Winning the American Championship at the age of 12.
A genius duelist who had stirred up quite a commotion.
Oi oi... This damn cocky girl is the U.S. Champion? Stop kidding me.
What! Are you insulting me, the U.S. Champion?!
Shut it! I won second place at the Duelist Kingdom.
Right, right. Now risen from number 8 to number 2.
You punk! Who's side are you on anyway?
I know all that. The number one at Duelist Kingdom is Yugi Mutou.
And second place is Katsuya Jounouchi.
Anyone who's not first place ain't important. Right, Teddy-chan?
You jerk! Don't you look down on me!
Rebecca, the Blue-Eyes White Dragon is an important card to me.
Of course it is! You stole it from America.
Stole? Rebecca, there must be some misunderstanding.
Umm, Grandpa wouldn't...
But I was told by Bandit Keith that someone stole the Blue-Eyes.
That idiot. Why'd he say something like that?
Anyway, Blue-Eyes belongs to me, the U.S. Champion!
Give it back!
Rebecca, that card...
What? I get it. You don't want to return it, is that right?
Wait a second! It's not I don't want to return it...
How should I explain it? Um...
Then let's fight for it!
With a duel! A duel!
Suguroku Mutou, if I win you have to return the Blue-Eyes.
Is that clear?
Come on! Would you give it a rest already?!
Okay. Let's head to the duel ring! Hurry up!
Alright!
I beg you, Mokuba-kun!
There's no helping it. The duel rings are booked for 3 months.
There won't be a second time.
Thanks!
Now! Hurry and take me there. Let's go. Hurry up!
This is the duel ring?
Let's get started, Suguroku Mutou.
Grandpa...
It's okay, Yugi.
But...
Hold it! How long are you going to keep me, the U.S. Champion, waiting?
Rebecca, I'll be your opponent.
Yugi!
Grandpa just got out of the hospital. He's not well enough to duel.
OK! Fine.
It's not too bad having the Duelist Kingdom first place Yugi Mutou as my opponent.
It's impossible to defeat me, a genius duelist, anyway.
Right, Teddy-chan~?
What the hell? How stuck up can you be?
Grandpa, stay here and watch.
I'm sorry, Yugi. I'm counting on you.
Duel!
Hey now, are you sure about this?
What?
You know, it's gonna be so easy. I'm the U.S. Champion after all. A genius!
Right, Teddy-chan?
Yes! Rebecca. A prodigy! Genius!
What does this little girl want?
Why does she want Blue-Eyes so bad?
Witch of the Black Forest, Attack Mode!
Now! Come out, my cute monster!
Witch of the Black Forest...
Bandit Keith, and Pegasus J. Crawford...
I know something about American-styled duels.
How slow, Teddy-chan! What's taking him so long?
Here I go. Elf Swordsman, Summon. Attack!
Witch of the Black Forest is defeated.
NOOO~!
My Witch of the Black Forest was sent to the Graveyard~.
What now~?
What, what?
Oh yeah!
When Witch of the Black Forest is sent to the Graveyard,
A monster with 1500 Attack or less can be added to my hand.
And then the deck is reshuffled.
Thank you, Teddy-chan! Good boy!
Rebecca, it's your turn.
I'm thinking. Don't talk to me!
What now?
Is she really the U.S. Champion?
Okay, this one! Yeah, I'll play you.
Critter, Attack Mode.
Critter, how cute!
Rebecca, I'm going to attack.
Battle!
He defeated my Critter again and sent it to the Grave! Goddamn!
You weren't going to win anyway!
Teddy-chan, that boy's taking advantage of me.
I am not!
What, I can't give up yet?
Due to Critter's effect, I get to take a monster from the deck?
I know!
That girl's really weird.
Is this really a genius over there?
That damn brat!  I don't believe she's the champion!
I've seen that dueling style somewhere before...
It's my turn now. Here goes!
The atmosphere just changed.
Magic Card, Welcome For the Dead.
It can destroy a monster by sacrificing a card in my hand.
Destroyed Elf Swordsman!
Then I'll put this card in standby Defense Mode.
It's gonna get more interesting from here on out.
I will get back the Blue-Eyes White Dragon.
What's going on all of a sudden?
Isn't she different than a second ago?
She's only 12, but she's still the U.S. Champion!
Be careful, Yugi!
It's like she's a totally different person.
If I don't pay attention, I'll be in trouble.
My turn. Demon's Summon, attack!
You fell for it! This is Millennium Shield!
What did you say?
Battle!
That's steel defense!
All right, Teddy-chan~!
T-Too strong...
She's not an ordinary person.
Millennium Shield, not bad, wouldn't you say?
Yeah, that's steel defense, huh?
Now then, let's continue.
Yeah, Professor Hopkins.
Suguroku, why don't you call me Arthur from now on?
It's just like that duel.
Excuse me for scaring you like that.
I'm a genius, so it's only natural.
Okay, Teddy-chan. It's gonna get even better.
Magic Card, Ring of Magnetism.
Ring of Magnetism?
This card can lower your Defense Points...
Teddy-chan, it looks like he's completely clueless!
What an idiot!
I'll pass this turn.
Really? Are you
gonna observe?
Then I'll go.
Cannon Soldier, Attack Mode.
This is not good!
Cannon Soldier sacrifices a monster to attack the player.
It's alright, gramps. Demon can block that weak attack.
Demon's Summon, attack Cannon Soldier!
Not a chance. Ring of Magnetism, activate!
Ring of Magnetism can absorb an attack from the enemy monster.
Well? Now you can only attack Millennium Shield!
It's not that easy to defeat a 2500 Defense monster.
Demon's Summon and Millennium Shield have the same Attack Points and Defense Points.
But that doesn't mean it will be destroyed if it's in Defense Mode.
Teddy-chan, it's fun, huh?
Okay, it's my turn this time.
Ha, I was waiting for this one.
But it's not time to use it yet.
I Summon Witch of the Black Forest in Attack Mode!
Then I sacrifice Witch of the Black Forest!
Cannon Soldier, attack the player!
And use Witch of the Black Forest's effect to get a card from the deck.
Does that brat really have what it takes to be the U.S. number one?
This is just like him.
You'll know the pain in your heart from losing the Blue-Eyes.
What's going on?
I get it!
Rebecca, you are...
You finally found out. Yes, my name is Rebecca Hopkins.
I'm Arthur Hopkins's granddaughter,
the man you stole his cherished Blue-Eyes White Dragon from!
What?
You're Grandpa's best friend's granddaughter?
That's right. Now! I'm going to avenge my grandpa!
Prepare yourself!
That punk turns out to be Grandpa's best friend's granddaughter?
Yugi will clear his grandfather's name in this duel.
But, as we'd expect from the Whole Champion.
Rebecca is turning the match around with hard tactics, and making Yugi sweat.
Huh? This duel is the same as the one you played before, sir?
Then the ending...
On the next episode ''Deadly Shadow Ghoul''
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship