A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"The Mysterious Transfer Student, Ryuji Otogi"
Grandpa, I'm off!
Right...
Grandpa?
Good morning, Yugi!
A-Anzu, good morning!
Good morning, sir!
Hey...
Yugi, what's wrong with him?
Your grandfather doesn't seem too well.
Just between you and me...
Grandpa's not in a very good mood these days.
Uh... why?
I thought you'd never ask!
I, Sugoroku Mutou, at age 72,
am facing the biggest crisis of my life!
My store is in danger of going out of business!
Look over there!
A new game shop?
Mhm.
They've gathered the best games from around the world.
They've got good deals on almost everything,
and they're rumored to be selling the latest, most popular games!
The latest games, huh?!
I feel bad for grandpa, but it's got my interest!
What'd you say!?
Anzu, let's go check it out!
Wait up!
Here!
Th-Thanks.
"The Revolutionary New Game: D.D.M.
On Sale Tomorrow!!"
I wonder what kind of game this "D.D.M." is...
C'mon!
We're gonna be late for school!
That's Yugi Mutou...?
Otogi-chan.
The rumored one?
Yeah!
He's supposedly a revolutionist when it comes to Duel Monsters!
He beat the Pegasus in Duelist Kingdom and won the championship!
-Although I doubt the Duel Monsters champ would be beaten that easily.
- God, Yugi! I saw that look in your eyes again!
I do doubt he's a match when it comes to D.D.M.!
No problem.
Just you watch.
Starting today, I'll steal something important from him.
And I'll surely force him into the D.D.M. arena.
Sounds good!
Hey, you sure you're only aiming to promote D.D.M.'s appeal here?
Please mind to your own business.
I'll beat Yugi,
and once D.D.M.'s name roars across the world, you'll get your cut.
Ooh, scary!
Calm down, Otogi-chan!
Yugi Mutou...
I'll beat you, no matter what!
I've prepared a ton of games to steal your gaming title from you!
A new game shop?
Grandpa's not doing so well.
It feels like it's gonna become a really tough rival!
Seems they've made some new game called D.D.M.
"Dungeon Dice Monsters", right?
Why... do you know that name?
There was a flyer for it in today's paper.
Eh? Jounouchi, you read the newspaper?!
I read them while delivering them at my part-time job!
But aren't part-time jobs prohibited here?
I don't wanna here that from you!
I have special permission to work for my tuition!
After all, I spent all the cash prize Yugi won for me on Shizuka's operation.
So Shizuka-chan's operation date's been decided?
Yeah.
The doctor took a look,
and said her eyes can be fully restored after the operation.
That's really great, Jounouchi-kun!
Yeah!
Ah~! Cool~!
What the?
Awesome~
Can you show us one more time?!
Sure.
But this time I'll do it with six dice.
Here goes.
Wow~! That's so cool~!
Who's this guy?
Hey, is he from your guys' class?
Huh?
Oh yeah, he's a new transfer student named Ryuji Otogi.
Okay, that answers your question.
I don't like it!
I can't stand guys like him who use cheap tricks to pick up girls!
You're just jealous of whoever's more popular than you!
I'm the type of guy who keeps a well-sharpened katana in its sheath!
I don't need to show off my talents to others!
You actually have talents?
What the hell were you watching
when we went to Duelist Kingdom?
An amateur who won by pure luck, right?!
What was that?!
Knock if off, you two!
My talents were awakened on that island!
My talents as a Duelist!
You say you're good at Duel Monsters, huh?
It was a little while back, but did you hear?
This guy named Keith Howard was the U.S. champion and stuff,
and he was one hell of a strong man!
Well, he sure put up a good fight,
but he couldn't stand up to me!
He's totally bragging...
He's just drawn every katana he's got...
I hope ya get it now!
I'm-
Are you the Duelist Kingdom champion, Yugi Mutou-kun, by any chance?
Y-Yup.
I heard the rumors about your victory.
Have you heard any rumors about the young talent, Katsuya Jounouchi?
I'm terribly sorry.
So, would you like to play a game with me
so you can show me what this "young talent" thing is all about?
A game?
Right.
We'll use this die and this cup...
I wonder what kind of game this is...
-Yeah!
-You can do it!
If I beat this Otogi bastard, I'll get all his fans!
Okay, I accept!
In that case, watch closely.
Now, do you think I can move the die
into my right hand without touching the cup?
Ain't it obvious that's impossible?
Unless you have some kind of telepathic abilities,
there's no way you can get to the die.
As I was talking, the die should have vanished from the cup.
What?!
You think I'm lying?
Then why don't you see for yourself?
It can't be!
It's a trap, Jounouchi-kun!
Isn't the die right here?
I just moved the die to my right hand.
And I didn't touch the cup.
I win.
Are you freakin' kidding?!
You're the one who lost, by winning using such a low method!
Let's have a Duel Monsters match fair-and-square!
Very well.
However...
There's a condition I'd like to set before we start the game.
A condition?
Sure!
I'll take whatever you throw at me!
I don't even have my own deck.
-What?! That's not fair!
-That's not fair!
I-I get it.
So what do you wanna do about it?
Before we Duel,
we open new packs,
and build our decks from them.
How about it?
It's a reasonable condition, right?
That's way too reckless!
If they aren't the normal cards you're used to,
you're bound to lose!
Besides, there's a ton of cards Jounouchi-kun doesn't even know about.
Don't worry about it, Yugi.
Are you doubting my skills after taking Pegasus' tournament head on?
I didn't mean it like that, but...
I accept your condition.
Jounouchi-kun!
That's right.
We've got to make this better than that last game we had.
If you lose, how'd you like to become my dog for a week?
Sure.
Interesting!
So, if I win, I'll be taking that little cheering section over there as my fans!
-What?! That's terrible!
-You're the worst!
Be quiet!
Don't you dare belittle a match between men!
Idiot...
He's hopeless...
Jounouchi-kun, you should just forget it.
Yugi!
Do you really think I'd lose to this cheating bastard?
Don't think I'm the same guy who won the Best 8 in the City District League!
I know that, but...
Then keep your mouth shut and watch!
Good.
The match will be held after school today.
We'll hold it at the Duel Ring in my newly opened game shop.
Got it?
Yeah!
I'd like you guys to watch your friend's "cool battle" as well.
Otogi-kun, huh...?
Just what could he be thinking?
Alright, I'm really pumped now!
I'll pay him back good!
Will Jounouchi really be alright?
Ya think anyone can stop that idiot from bragging so much?
Alrighty!
His head's starting to swell.
Well now, welcome~!
You must be Otogi-chan's special opponent.
Please come this way.
Hey. So you're here?
This way to the Duel Ring.
Please step inside.
Now.
Choose any packs you like.
Use the new cards to make your deck.
Right.
I got you.
Oh yeah!
I'm lucky as hell to get these good cards!
Well, Jounouchi-kun?
Don't worry!
Victory's mine!
Hey! Hey! Otogi!
Let's go! Let's go! Otogi!
Wh-What the?
Go, go! Otogi!
It's the same Ring Kaiba Land has.
I rented it.
It was quite easy.
Why are there cameras?
Isn't it more fun to Duel when everyone can watch us?
This Duel is being broadcast across the world over the Internet.
The world will bear witness as the once-proud Duelist Kingdom runner up loses.
You're naive.
Nice face you're making, Otogi!
I'll win!
And...!
I'll turn the "Otogi Girls" into the "Jounouchi Girls"!
No way!
You're the worst!
It's alright.
I shall protect you gals.
He's cool~! He's stunning~!
Oh, shut it!
Dammit!
We're all set here!
Let's start the Duel!
I'll take you out!
Duel!!
Well, it's my turn.
Oni Tank T-34!
Attack Position!
And my turn's over.
Show me your superb talent as a Duelist...
Jounouchi-kun.
I don't need you to tell me that!
What?!
I got a card with an awesome Effect!
A Monster it destroys becomes an Equipment Card, eh?
Okay!
I play Sword Hunter in Attack Position!
Battle!
Hunter Lance!
Good one!
Oni Tank is beaten!
Oni Tank will become an Equipment Card on Sword Hunter!
And his Attack Power goes up by 200 points!
No~! No~! Otogi-kun~!
That Jounouchi's not doing too bad.
Right, Yugi?
Right...
How's that, Otogi?
You ain't a match for me!
As I would expect from you, Jounouchi-kun.
It's way too late to realize that now!
Here. It's your turn now.
Dark Bat in Defense Position.
I'll then place another set card.
Hey there!
You're not gonna get out of this by playing on the defensive side!
Charging Swordhorn Beast!
You're up!
Thank goodness I placed it in Defense Mode.
Even if it was in Defense Mode,
the Charging Swordhorn Beast smashes right through their guard,
and the player receives the difference as damage!
You sure are something else, Jounouchi-kun.
But my Monster won't be going to the Graveyard alone.
Sorry.
What?!
"Murder-Suicide"
Jounouchi was way too naive there!
Don't let your guard down, Jounouchi!
I did that on purpose to make the game more interesting!
And you fell for it hook, line and sinker!
It may seem that way...
...but Otogi-kun's the one controlling this game.
Be careful, Jounouchi-kun.
That was a pretty cheap trick back there!
But it's still way to early to get cocky!
Now then, it's about time I play a tough Monster,
and make my counterattack.
I set 1 card face-down.
And then...
I Summon Spike Head!
Battle!
Try harder, Jounouchi!
This isn't like the tortoise and the hair!
This isn't the time to be resting!
You jerk! If you lose, you're gonna become Otogi's dog!
Don't you get that?!
Oh snap, I forgot about that!
It's time I get serious!
Oh, wow!
The card stands no chance if I play this Monster!
Go!!
Yes!
Otogi, your Life's practically drizzled away!
Otogi-kun~!
No~!
These guys go into Defense Mode the turn after you use them...
But now Otogi's Life is down to 50!
My victory's set!
You better get ready, Jounouchi Girls!
No~ No~! Otogi-kun~!
You can do it~!
I don't agree with the Jounouchi Girls part,
but go for it, Jounouchi!
Alright! You're one step away!
Why...?
He has such little Life remaining, yet Otogi-kun looks so calm...
Is he still planning something...?
Jounouchi-kun!
Don't let your guard down!
-You have to focus!
-This match is mine!
Hey~! Hey~! Jounouchi~!
It's no use!
It's my turn.
I Summon Super Dimension Fighter Vic Viper in Attack Position!
Not good enough.
It's still too weak.
I play the Magic Card, Limiter Removal!
The Vic Viper powers up!
It's got 2400 Attack Points?!
My Goblins are screwed!
They'll be beaten in one shot!
Furthermore...
I activate the Equipment Magic, Meteor Strike!
What'd you say?!
So... what Effect does that card have?
I can't believe you're the runner up of the championship
and still don't know these things.
Think of it as a Magic version of the Charging Swordhorn Beast you used earlier.
So I see.
So, then...!
When it attacks a Monster in Defense Mode,
the Attack Points of the Monster equipped with this card
are greater than the Defense Points of the Monster it attacks,
the difference in points comes directly out of the opponent's Life Points!
Say what?!
Viv Viper Attack!
You did it, you did it~!
This ain't good.
Jounouchi got way too overconfident!
Thank goodness!
Here.
I expect you to keep your promise, Jounouchi-kun.
You'll be my dog for the next week!
Have I grown rusty since the Duelist Kingdom?
I tried harder than my own skill limit,
and I grew better, to achieve my goal.
Have I gotten in over my head now?
That's enough, isn't it?!
Just leave this be as is!
Yugi, just stay quiet.
This is my problem.
Oww~!
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
Who said you could talk?!
You're my dog!
You only talk if I say you can do so!
-That's just...!
Okay...
As I promised.
That hurt...
You don't say "That hurt", you say "woof"!
Now...
Won't you bark out a "woof" for me?
Do it.
Hmmm, that sure fits you.
"W-Woof!"
Very good!
Jounouchi...
Otogi!
You've got some guts messing with my friend right in front of me!
You're facing me, now!
If I win, you'll let Jounouchi go!
Very well.
But I'd like to change the game this time.
We'll be facing each other with Dungeon Dice Monsters, D.D.M.!
What?!
If you lose to me, I'll be taking your "King of Duelists" title for myself!
And you'll swear to never play Duel Monsters again!
That's going too far!
Forget it, Yugi!
Jounouchi brought this on himself!
Right, don't do it, Yugi!
Listen up!
You better remember this!
You can't break our friendship with a game!
I'll take you up on your D.D.M. match!
"Preview"
Don't be reckless, Yugi!
I can't believe you accepted to play Otogi-kun in D.D.M.!
And you even promised to never play Duel Monsters again if you lose!
Yugi doesn't even know how the play the game,
and Otogi-kun knows all the rules,
but why did he go through all this trouble to lure Yugi here?
He seems to be hiding something.
Next time!
"Showdown! Dungeon Dice Monsters!"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship