Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
What on Earth is this?
The Barrier of Orichalcos...
The ones imprisoned within this boundary
can't escape until someone wins the Duel!
And the one to lose...
His soul will be sealed within the barrier!
What did you say?!
Don't screw around!
Big brother!
Mokuba!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Wake Up! Critias"
Big brother!
Big brother!!
Big brother!!!
That's a considerably elaborate trick you've pulled off.
Seto Kaiba...
Do you have any idea of just how long I've been waiting for this day to arrive?
You said you were Amelda, correct?
The appearance of Duel Monsters as well as buying out all the stocks of Kaiba Corporation...
That was all your doing?
Who knows?
Then what's the point of this little farce?!
I thought I told you.
This is for the sole purpose of retrieving your soul.
Put an end to the stupid jokes already!
"Jokes," was it?
It doesn't matter.
You can't walk away from this Orichalcos Barrier.
I'll take your soul as atonement for the sins you and Kaiba Corporation have committed!
Sins? What the hell are you going on about?
What's wrong with you, Yugi?
I'm a bit worried about Pegasus.
Worried?
Pegasus told us in the video letter, right?
That he was being followed by someone.
Yeah...
If that's really true,
there's a chance Pegasus is in danger.
Danger?
I Summon Balrog in Attack Mode!
Its Attack Points went up!
Why?
The Barrier of Orichalcos increases the Attack
of all Monsters on my field by 500 points!
What?
Also, whenever you have a Fire-Attribute Monster with Balrog on the field,
its Attack goes up by 500 points.
And...
Balrog himself is of the Fire element!
2000 Attack Points?
Balrog! Attack God of Destruction - Vasago!
Any Monster destroyed by Balrog, at the end of the Battle Phase,
will be Special Summoned on my field in Attack Mode.
And will become a Fire-Attribute Monster.
But they will lose their Special Effects.
And with the increase in Fire-Attribute Monsters,
Balrog's Attack Points will further increase!
Shit!
Whenever Brother's Monsters are destroyed,
the opponent's Monsters will increase in number!
I set a reverse card. Turn over.
This strategy using Balrog is no joke...
So he wasn't just talking big?
But...
As long as I can destroy Balrog,
the Monsters he Special Summoned will also disappear.
I'll make him an offering for the Virus Combo next turn!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Pitch-Dark Dragon in Defense Mode!
Also, I set a reverse card!
Deck Destruction Virus of Death, is it?
I know exactly what you're thinking right now.
Because I've analyzed
all the information I could find on you.
I see... You must be well-prepared.
I guess those ignorant
to the ways of the world
must put in extra effort when recklessly challenging those stronger than them.
You're the one who doesn't know the ways of the world!
What?
Look at this.
Humph! And what exactly is that piece of garbage supposed to prove?
I'm sure it looks like
a piece of garbage to you!
So if it's not garbage, then what is it?
This is a...
...memento of my little brother!!
My little brother was...
...killed by your company!
My country used to be beautiful...
Even now, I recall the beautiful streets of my country...
But before I knew it, I was staring straight into the pits of Hell...
Look out!
You're still holding onto that thing?
But you gave it to me as a present for my birthday, Brother!
This is my treasure!
You little...
Once this war ends,
I'll buy you as many toys as you want.
Really?
Can we hurry up and... end this war then...?
It's going to be over soon.
And we can play soccer together!
Yeah!
Now! Let's move!
You alright, boys?
Wow! Cool!
Amazing!
This is a brand new tank!
The newest combat tanks created by Kaiba Corporation!
Its functions excel
those of the enemy's.
Kaiba Corporation has
agreed to work with us!
We can have as many weapons
as possible!
We will win! We'll win this!
And we can end this war then!
Yeah!
Wait for me!
Hurry!
Mama...
Brother, you're crying.
Not true!
The one crying is your stomach.
I'll get you some food.
Brother!
Come on, Miruko!
Get on!
It's safe in here!
Okay!
Mama's pendant!
Hang on!
Miruko!
Miruko...
MIRUKO!
MIRUKO!!!
Do you know who that man is?
Gozaburo Kaiba.
He's the president of Kaiba Corporation.
Kaiba... Corporation?
Yes. He is the true murderer of your little brother.
This man gave new weapons to both sides in order to test their combat strength.
No way...!
Do you want to take revenge on that man?
My heart died that day.
This is my revenge!
My brother...
This isn't my brother's fault!
Mokuba...
It was Gozaburo who sold the weapons!
And my big brother hated him for that!
So he bought out Kaiba Corporation's stocks!
He wanted to use the wealth and power he obtained to create a better future!
And that was my brother's... and Kaiba Corporation's redemption!
Redemption, you say?
That's right! For all the kids around the world,
Big brother built Kaiba Land!
Don't make me laugh!
Is that going to bring back my little brother? My parents?
W-Well...
Enough, Mokuba.
But, Big brother...!
Kaiba Corporation destroyed peace in order to obtain its wealth.
The Duel Disk you created...
As well as the enormous investment you placed in order to conduct this plan of yours.
No...!
Even the food you've been eating throughout your entire lives...!
The clothes on your backs, even!
All of it was bought using the money from Kaiba Corporation!
Money obtained by taking others' lives!
I'll make you pay for your sins, with your soul!
Revenge, huh?
I have indeed taken over Kaiba Corporation's, as well as Gozaburo's crimes.
I have no intentions of denying this.
But even if you're gonna
Duel me because of it,
you have your own way of seeing the truth, and you can continue Dueling that way!
All I can do is Duel my way to show you who's right!
In that case, I'll be the right one! You can't defeat me!
I activate the Trap Card, Proclamation of the Royal Palace!
As long as this card remains active,
all Trap Cards on the field will be negated!
Trap Cards will be negated?!
That Deck Destruction Virus of Death you worked so hard to bring out is now useless.
Turn over.
My turn!
Balrog, attack Pitch-Dark Dragon!
Now your only defending Monster is gone!
Then I use God of Destruction -
Vasago to Direct Attack you!
Brother's Life Points...!
And the destroyed Pitch-Dark Dragon becomes my Monster.
I don't have any Monsters in my hand that doesn't require a sacrifice.
Everything depends on the card I draw next turn!
My turn!
It's here...
I'll create my future with my own two hands!
Magic Card activate! Life-Shaving Card Treasure!
Now I have five cards in my hand!
Look! This is the power that will determine my future!
I activate the Ritual Magic, Descent of White Dragon!
I sacrifice Monsters worth Level Four or higher in order to let Knight of White Dragon descend!
What?
I sacrifice Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Ritual Summon! Knight of White Dragon!
Also, I Special Summon Blue-Eyes from the Graveyard using Resurrection of the Dead!
Knight of White Dragon, attack Pitch-Dark Dragon!
Now that I've removed a Fire-Attribute Monster, Balrog's Effect causes it to lose Attack Points!
I use Blue-Eyes to attack Balrog!
And if you sacrifice Knight of White Dragon,
I am able to Special Summon another Blue-Eyes White Dragon from my deck!
I believe you said it was impossible for me to win.
I return those words to you in earnest!
My turn.
That was an admirable attack, Seto Kaiba.
But a flame radiates for only a brief moment before it goes out.
Still bragging, even after all this?
Magic Card, activate! Pot of Greed!
I draw two cards from my deck!
And then I activate the Magic Card, Aetonix Flame!
Impossible...!
Both Blue-Eyes were taken out at the same time!
Aetonix Flame destroys all non-Fiend-Type and non-Fire-Attribute Monsters on the field.
I can then Special Summon a Fiend-Type Monster or a Fire-Attribute Monster to the field from my Graveyard.
Also, I activate the Magic Card, Fire Whip!
Fire Whip Special Summons all Monsters destroyed on this turn
to my side of the field as Fire-Attribute Monsters.
My Blue-Eyes have...!
You have the honor of your trusted Blue-Eyes delivering you the final blow.
For you, there can't be anything better than this.
And due to the two Blue-Eyes becoming Fire-Attribute Monsters,
Balrog becomes more powerful as per his Effect.
Due to the effect of Aetonix Flame,
I can't go into battle this turn.
I suppose I just spared your life a bit longer.
I set a reverse card and end my turn.
Now draw a card, Seto Kaiba.
This will be the last draw of your life!
Now that I've lost my God Card,
I have no card to turn the tables...
Absurd...! Is it all going to end in a place like this...?
Such a  thing...!
I will not accept such a thing!
What is this place?
What is this statue?
Am I supposed to pull it out?
Why?
I know your name.
Your name is Critias!
This...
What?
Was I hallucinating?
What is this card?
Impossible...
Why is there a card I don't recognize in my deck?
Still...
I know the power this card holds!
I'll bet on this card to turn the tables!
Go! The Fang of Critias!
What did you say?! That card is...!
Due to its Special Ability,
I can Summon a Fusion Monster merged with a Trap Card!
Impossible!
A Fusion Monster merged with a Trap Card, you said?!
I have just transcended common sense!
Come forth! Death Virus Dragon!!
"Death Virus Dragon?" For real?
Death Virus Dragon destroys all Monsters on the field
with 1500 Attack Points or more!
Take this! Death Virus Dragon, Direct Attack!!
I win, Amelda!
Reverse card, activate! Quick-Play Magic, Contagion of Madness!
What?!
Contagion of Madness!
It deals damage to the opponent player's Life Points equal to half of the attacked Monster's Attack Points!
Big brother!
A draw?
You better remember this!
I shall have my revenge on you!
What's up? Out of gas?
O-Oi!
What's with him?
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
While Kaiba-kun was busy fighting against Amelda of Doma,
the limousine was taking us to see Pegasus at Industrial Illusions.
But now the car has stopped
at an old gas station,
and the driver went out
and never came back.
I have a bad hunch.
What?
There's a group of motorcyclists
coming this way!
Next time!
"The Unexpected Enemy"
Duel standby!