The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Lost Exodia
Pegasus has the power to read his opponent's minds.
Can I really beat an opponent who can read my entire hand and strategies?
But I have to try it.
Because of me, Grandpa...
I won't run away!
I'll go to the Kingdom.
To get back the person important to me.
Just you wait, Pegasus!
Big brother Katsuya!
Long time no see!
Have you been doing well?
Shizuka!
I made this video so you won't forget my face, big brother.
Big brother!
SHIZUKA!
Sadly, I won't be able to see your face anymore.
To be honest, I didn't really want to talk through a video.
But face-to-face...
I wanted to see your face one last time!
"Last time"...?!
Shizuka...!
Well then, bye bye, big brother.
Dammit...!
Huh?
What's this?
This is...
An invitation for entering the Kingdom...!
You go by boat?
So that means the battlefield for this tournament is on an island, right?
Yeah...
It says at 10:30 P.M. I should board from Domino Pier.
An invitation to the Kingdom...
Yugi, is your grandfather there?
I don't know...
But I have no choice but to go to that island!
But this sure was surprising.
I can't believe your grandfather was taken just like that while we were out cold.
That man, Pegasus...
He's really something.
Shit, we can't get aboard the ship without an invitation card...
We have to find a way to go there with you!
That's right.
It would be great if we could all go.
Oi, Yugi...
Look at this "Glory of the King's Hand" card...
A huge cash-prize.
Cash prize?
It means the winner will receive a huge cash prize.
Hey, let me see that!
It's true.
Jounouchi-kun...?
A huge cash prize...
Jounouchi-kun!
What's wrong?
Look, you can see the sunset crystal clear from here.
Yugi, your grandfather taught me the heart of the cards.
I'm thankful for that.
Jounouchi-kun...
You have to win!
And get gramps back here safely!
I'm really glad to have met someone like you.
Why did you say such a random thing?
That day, I was ready to finish the Millennium Puzzle given to me by Grandpa.
This is my treasure.
I heard that this puzzle was found in Egypt.
I haven't completed it yet,
So I really don't know what it looks like.
In other words, It's something that can be seen, but is not seen.
I wished a lot on the puzzle.
I wanted friends.
I had a feeling that the Millennium Puzzle would grant this wish.
Then, I met you and Honda-kun.
I don't think you can call that a "meeting".
Back then, I always got pissed off whenever I looked at you.
So you're saying this is your treasure?
But then a senior who was pretending to be my bodyguard,
Ushio-senpai, showed his true objection was my money.
Ow...
Dammit...
By the way, Yugi,
you still owe me some money!
My bodyguard fee... ¥200,000!
N-No way!
It's a good chance to pay them back.
You should beat these guys up too.
Stop!
There's no way I'll do that to my friends!
What a strange guy you are...
Then how about you as well?
That time, I told my wishes to the Puzzle...
I really wanted to get some friends.
Then you got the final piece of the Puzzle for me.
I decided to learn from you, and now have my own treasure.
Really? Show me!
Unfortunately, my treasure is something that you can see...
but can't see at the same time.
It's friendship.
Me and you know what the treasure is...
But you can't see friendship, right?
Did I really say something that corny?
It would be best if we could all go together...
Don't get so down.
Our hearts will always be with you, Yugi.
You're right!
That's right. Just put your heart into it.
I'll do my best.
Chosen Duelists!
Welcome to the event held by Industrial Illusions!
I have investigated every single one of your Duel Monsters records.
You are all excellent Duelists.
So, you each have an equal chance of winning this tournament.
Now, all your heads...
Are surrounded by a bright halo.
Now, all my fellow Duelists!
Let's go across the ocean, to get your greatest honor in the Kingdom.
Please show your Star Chips when boarding.
Please enter.
Good.
Where's your Star Chips?
Hey, chill out!
Let me go on!
No way!
Hey, take this kid out of here. Go that way.
Hands off! I know the Yugi Mutou who beat Kaiba!
Jounouchi-kun!
Don't be crazy! I'll throw you off!
That's interesting! If you think you can beat me, I'll take you on!
Wait!
Yo, Yugi.
Who are you?
Jounouchi-kun... Why are you...
In the end, I was worried about you going by yourself.
This way.
Let's go.
Okay.
Please let my friend aboard the ship.
There's no exception!
Only those with a Star Chip can board the ship.
Jounouchi-kun has a Star Chip.
What?
See?
This is...
This card says anyone with a Star is a Duelist eligible to play.
That's right.
But the other Duelists all have 2 Stars.
If you do that...!
It's fine. Even by being at a disadvantage...
I would choose to be with Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi...
What should we do?
Hello, it's me. The thing is...
This way!
Hey, don't get so close to me!
Oh please...
It's great that you came along.
That crappy Pegasus stole something you love.
Yugi, I'll never forget your kindness.
Don't worry.
I'm so excited!
Unbelievable!
Are you that boy, Yugi?
Alright! What a nice woman!
It's really unexpected that a shrimp like you beat Kaiba.
You're famous, you know.
Really? Thanks!
Miss, I'm a friend of the famous Duelist Yugi!
I'm a great Duelist, ya know!
In a Duel, even if the opponent is a shrimp, I won't go easy on them.
I'll beat you down.
Duel me~
I am Mai Kujaku.
See you around, kid.
What the hell was that?
Those two sex maniacs worry me!
Those two piss me off!
You're too loud!
That's how men are.
What, are you kidding?
They let us on a giant ship...
But there's only one big shared room?!
You again?
Aren't there any single rooms?
Why are ya talkin' so loud in da lounge?
Huh? Yugi-kun?
Aren't you Yugi-kun?
You guys're...
Insector Haga and Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
Yeah, only champions like us get da single rooms.
Haga-kun! Congratulations to you for winning the championship!
It was nothing.
What? I was holdin' back 'gainst this loser.
We're gonna be the winners in this tournament!
Right, Yugi?
Actually, even though I was the champion last week...
I don't feel very successful.
I won't until I beat champions like you or Kaiba-kun.
I think we will Duel at the Kingdom, Yugi-kun.
I'm looking forward to it.
The same here, so please do.
What? Ain't he jus' a kid?
That's right. Do you know the new rules of the Duels?
New rules?
I'm not sure...
But I heard you should think of new strategies aside from your normal ones.
Anyway, for me, it don't really matter if der's rules 'er not.
Just beat da crap outta each otha'. Dat's da only rule fer me.
You're right, you're really good. I like you.
Appreciated.
I'm gonna rest in my single room now.
I don't like him... The bastard pisses me off...!
This room isn't any worse than that.
What?
Look around, they're beginning to practice.
People can trade cards from their card collections...
To improve their Decks.
At the same time, they get the advantage of learning about their opponents before the tournament.
As expected of Insector Haga.
He's really smart.
Hey, I'm Jounouchi!
Can I see those cards? They look strong!
I have this one too!
Jounouchi-kun...
These people can't be trusted with cards.
I have to go in.
Hey, are you kidding me?!
You want a lady like me to stay in a room without even a shower?
But... those are the rules.
Ask the person responsible to get in here!
Actin' like dis is gonna get yer ass thrown off da ship.
Who're you?
Do ya wanna sleep in my room?
Wow, I'm happy! Really?
Fer real!?
It's no good.
Oi, get down!
But I can't stand it anymore...
Where's the bathroom?
Just do it here!
Idiot! I'm not a man!
Bakura-kun?
Was that Bakura-kun just now?
There's no way that's Bakura?
It's cold~!
What'd ya think?
This's da "Special Guest" room.
It's very nice!
Ryuzaki-san, you must be so good at cards!
I guess.
I love to challenge strong men.
Who d'ya think yer talkin' ta here?
It's impossible for ya ta beat me.
What? Do you wanna have a Duel with me right now?
What'd ya say?
If you win, I'll do anything you want.
I got some new cards from trading.
Show me! Show me!
Salamandra...
Chain-Equipped Boomerang...
Kunai With Chain
Baby Dragon and...
Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand...
With these Magic Cards, you'll get a way more powerful strategy.
Really?
Alright!
I will definitely win!
But this tournament is not as easy as you think.
Right, use this one too.
Time Wizard
I think it'll give you a hand when you're in trouble.
Really? Thanks a lot.
Hey, Yugi-kun...
Haga-kun?
First, shuffle the cards.
Alright, let's start.
I'm so lucky tonight...
Alright, done.
I will guess those cards with my eyes shut.
What? Dat's impossible.
The first card is Shadow of Temptation.
What?
That's just a coincidence.
The second card is Harpie Lady.
Next is Kaleidoscope.
The fourth is Cyber Bondage.
U-Unreal...
This is my card trick.
At any given time, I know the next card I will draw.
Alright, let's play the game.
If you lose, you must leave the room.
Ya really want that?
The wind feels good.
Did you trade cards with anyone?
No, I'm using my own cards.
I thought so.
In your Deck, you have the one card that beat Kaiba-kun.
Exodia, was it called?
As expected of you.
Can I have a look at that legendary card?
Since it's been found out,
there's no point in hiding it.
Darn, you know my strategy.
Here.
Oh? So this is Exodia the Sealed One?
Exodia the Forbidden One
Yugi-kun, I've been thinking of a way to beat this card for a long time now...
But I couldn't come up with anything...
But I finally found a way...
It'll be over for sure if I do this!
What!?
Now I have no more opponents!
Bastard!
My cards!
The treasured cards my grandpa gave me!
Damn!
Jounouchi-kun!
No! It's too dangerous!
Wait for me, Yugi!
I'll find it.
Get aboard quickly, now!
I will find it...
I got the first one.
Living is more important than those cards!
There are some things in this world that need to be protected.
Some things that can't be replaced!
Some things just cannot be lost!
I found the second one!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi, just three more to go...
Just three left...
Yugi!
Are you alright?!
Get on!
Hurry it up!
Anzu!
Honda-kun!
Go away, freak!
Ya weaklin'.
Thanks for your help, but why did you come on the ship?
We were worried.
We didn't want to leave you alone.
Everyone, thanks!
Sorry, Yugi.
I only found two cards for you...
That's okay, Jounouchi-kun.
What do you mean by "okay"?
I'm always like this...
I can't help anyone!
Even my own little sister, Shizuka...
Your little sister?
You have a little sister, Jounouchi?
My parents got divorced when I was young.
She's very far away now, living with my mom.
When my sister was born, she had bad eyes.
Someday, she will go blind.
Blind?
Last week, she sent me a video tape.
I wanted to see your face one last time!
I guess her doctor warned her that the time she'd been dreading is coming near.
This problem's not easy to heal.
There's some experienced doctors with good needed equipment in Germany.
I want her to see one of the doctors, but I don't have enough money.
So I have to win this tournament.
If I'm the winner, I'll get the cash prize.
Then I have a chance of saving Shizuka!
Jounouchi-kun, we will make it.
Me for my grandpa, and you for your sister.
Yeah, be confident.
Look, land!
That's the Duelist Kingdom.
Insector Haga, I will beat you in this Kingdom!
Finally, we arrived at Pegasus's Duelist Kingdom.
During these two days, only those who collect 10 Star Chips can enter the Finals.
Now, Yugi, first go beat the shameless Insector Haga!
Invited to the forest, a Duel Ring suddenly appears.
What's going on?
Why is Haga laughing?
I bet he has a trick up his sleeve again.
Next time!
The Insector Combo
Duel Standby.
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship