Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
The one behind Doma has finally come to light. The true identity of Dartz.
He is the one that controls this massive organization that can manipulate the world's economics and politics.
The President of the Paradias company...
But I'm certain of what I saw in the Stone Wilderness.
This guy has battled with the Duel Monsters a long time ago.
The one that destroyed Altantis... is it Dartz?
"Duel! Jounouchi VS Varon"
Wait up, Jounouchi!
It's dangerous over there!
Jounouchi!
What the heck?!
This is bad!
Run!!
Watch where you're goin', dammit!
W-Wait!
It's dangerous over there...
Monster?!
Ah! Save me!!
It's coming!
Damn!
If that's the case...
Jounouchi!?
Th-The hell?
Y-You're...!
Follow me, Jounouchi.
Wait for me!
Hey!
Damn...
I'll borrow this.
Wait up, Jounouchi!
That idiot... He could be walking right into a trap.
Stop right there!
You bastard!
Damn!
Shit!
I won't let you escape!
DAMN!!
Damn you!
How was that?
Don't go gettin' cocky just by doing that.
Say wha?
C'mon!
Hey!
Seto!
Yugi!
Seto...
I'm so glad you're safe!
Of course I am.
We've gotten hold of the enemy's true form.
Lets go, Mokuba.
Lets send Doma off.
You better hurry up.
Jounouchi has already gone to the Paradias company alone!
What?! Jounouchi-kun did what?!
That damn deadbeat is too impulsive.
This is bad! Jounouchi and Honda...
Anzu!
The monsters that attacked Yugi are all over the place!
What?
Lets go.
If we use the car, we can catch up to them.
It appears to have already begun.
Grandpa...?
Professor Hopkins...
The news mentioned that more people are losing their memory, or rather, losing their souls.
Don't tell me...
So that text recorded on the ruins is really going to happen?
Yes...
Doma's influence has even reached the cops.
Looks like we can only rely on ourselves.
Lets go.
We are going to stop Doma's ambitions and save everyone.
Wait for me, Partner.
The time has come.
Jounouchi! Where are you!?
Jounouchi?
Honda, where is Jounouchi?
Mai!
Jounouchi isn't with you?!
What are you talking about?
That guy named Varon brought Jounouchi somewhere!
I should be the one asking you where Jounouchi is!
Varon did what?!
This is all your fault!
If something happens to Jounouchi, I won't forgive you!
Hey, you! Wait!
This place should be okay.
No one can interrupt us here.
Varon!
Where is Mai?
Why are you asking me that?
Mai is not your comrade anymore.
You're wrong!
Mai...! I will definitely get Mai back!
You're pretty clueless, ain't ya?
What?
What Mai is thinking...
Do you know her pain and why she wants to defeat you?
And I doubt you'd be able to understand her feelings.
I am the only one that can understand her!
There's no way that's true!
Mai is my...
She's our friend!
We've battled together with her all this time, much more than she has with you...
But why...
With my own will, I've chosen to fight with you!
What did you say?!
That can't be true!
You wouldn't understand...
You, who only knows how to move forward...
Listen up, Jounouchi.
This is not a battle for Doma.
I want to defeat you for Mai!
Wha-? What do you mean?
As long as you are here, Mai's suffering will never disappear.
And even if Mai wants to defeat you herself and she won... nothing will change.
By doing that, she will only be hurt more.
What this guy's really thinking right now...
You are such an eyesore!
It's the same for both me and Mai!
I will defeat you here!
If you want to battle no matter what... I'll accept your challenge!
Duel!!
I'll attack first. Draw!
I Summon Wyvern Swordsman in Attack Position!
Turn end!
Varon...
What kind of tactics will that guy use?
My turn! Draw!
My battle tactic is only "attack".
I shall let you witness the power of my invincible Armor Deck!
Armor Deck?
I Summon Psychic Armor Head in Attack Position!
He Summoned a Monster with zero ATK in Attack Mode?
You're right! Psychic Armor Head has no Atack Power!
But this is just the stepping stone for my Armor's invincible Attack Power!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand...
Armored Gravitation!
Armored Gravitation?
I Summon Trap Buster in Attack Position!
I Summon Big Bang Blow in Attack Position!
I Summon Over Boost in Attack Mode!
I Summon Active Guard in Attack Mode!
Let's go!
Armored Gravitation!!
What?
The Magic Card, Armored Gravitation's effect is that it can Special Summon Level Four or lower "Armor Monsters"!
I'm gonna let you see it, Jounouchi! The power of Armor Monsters!
Has it started?
It doesn't matter if Varon or Jounouchi loses, for the loser's soul will be under my control.
For the sake of reviving my God, please fire up your souls and burn them out!
As long as we follow this path straight, we can get to Paradias HQ.
We're finally gonna raid their main base, eh Brother?
It's too quiet.
Based on their actions in the past, it's impossible for them to not interfere and let us close in on them so easily.
Where the heck'd that Jounouchi run off to? Seriously...
It came out again!!
What the heck happened?
Otogi-kun, that's dangerous, ya know!
H-Honda-kun!
Eh?
Dammit!
Come get me if ya want!
Elf Swordsman!
Honda-kun!
Guys!
Yugi, what's going on here?
What the hell are those things?!
It looks like spirits from 10,000 years ago in Atlantis have revived.
Spirits from Altantis?
Where's Jounouchi? Wasn't he with you?
Yeah, but that guy named Varon from the Three Musketeers of Doma told him to follow him somewhere.
What did you say?!
This is bad... That guy...
Right! Jounouchi-kun's in danger!
Huh? What do you mean?
His deck comprises of Monsters that we've never seen before, a fearsome deck.
Everyone! Lets search for Jounouchi-kun!
Now's not the time to be worrying about the deadbeat.
Kaiba!
Look around you.
Eh?
Big Brother...
We're surrounded.
He Summoned five Monsters so quickly...
But he equipped them to himself... what is he trying to do?
Armor Monsters can be used as both a defensive shield and an offensive weapon.
Well whatever they are, they've all got zero Attack Points!
How do you plan on attacking me with that?
Allow me to show you how...
...using the Armor Monsters's true strength!
Opposing player's Life Points: 4000.
One enemy Monster. Wyvern Warrior. 1500 Attack Power.
Reverse card scan:
Zero reverse cards in play.
Using Big Bang Blow and Active Guard's combo, there is 99% chance of defeating opponent's Monster.
Here I come, Jounouchi!
I use Big Bang Blow
to attack Wyvern Warrior!
He's attacking me
with a zero-Attack Monster?!
What's his problem?!
I use Wyvern Warrior to counter-attack!
Against Big Bang Blow, no matter who the enemy is, they will all be destroyed!
It's the same against the enemy or myself!
What?
I activate Big Bang Blow's Special Effect!
Activating Active Guard's Special Effect.
Absorbing damage.
What exactly happened?
Why did my Life Points...?
When Big Bang Blow is destroyed in battle, all Monsters on the field will be destroyed.
And the destroyed Monster's combined ATK will be inflicted on the players.
What?!
But nothing happened to you...!
That's because I've got this.
This Active Guard holds an Effect that makes all battle damage received on my end reduced to zero.
What did you say?
Combo clear.
All armors will be destroyed.
Even if all my Monsters disappear, I will not be damaged at all.
So what do you think, Jounouchi?
This is the power of my Armor Deck!
So bring it on, Jounouchi!
It's your turn.
What?
He didn't play any Wall Monsters or set any reverse cards and he's ending his turn?
You jerk...
You're only Summoning your Monsters so you can attack?
There's only "attack" in my Dueling!
There's no need for unneccessary moves.
That's how I've survived up until now while I was a kid...
That's right...
Just like the city we're in now...
Cease this as once, Varon!
If you don't amend your ways, I won't let you off easy!
Varon.
Why do you always get into fights?
Okay, it's all done now.
Hey there!
You still here, heh?
Our boss already bought 'dis place.
So go an' scram!
Please wait! There are still many kids here!
Like I give a shit?
Be gone by 'da end a' the day! Capiche?
Varon!
What a huge blaze.
This can't...
For an old, rundown church, it's burnin' stunningly!
Now we ain't gotta waste time demolishin' 'da thing.
Come out.
I see...
You've got nice spirit in your eyes.
How is it living here?
If this goes on, you will be staying here for quite some time.
Yes, you will be here for a long time.
But what if I were to tell you there was a way you could get out of here instantly?
I'm giving you a chance.
I want you to use this to fight...
Only one person who manages to survive will achieve his freedom!
But if you lose, then it's all over.
I'm sure you know what that means.
What will you do? You are the one that is choosing.
I have acknowledged your strength.
And who might you be?
As promised before, you are free.
But do you want to battle with much stronger people?
Sounds interesting.
Let me try.
I wanna battle much stronger guys!
Then I shall take you in as a member of Doma.
But let me say just one thing.
I may end up beating even you.
The things that were important to me disappeared a long time ago.
I'm different from Rafael, Amelda, and even you and your pals.
I'm no longer shouldering any burdens!
I only battle to win!
To keep winning!
That's all that matters to me!
It's not that I don't understand...
The me in the past may have agreed to what you said.
During those times, I was also fighting everyday.
Victory was everything.
But now I know that doesn't mean that you are truely strong.
After meeting Yugi and Dueling with many others...
It's not like every one of 'em was a joyride, but I've learned many things from them.
Dueling isn't a tool for us to measure our strength!
I will not lose to a guy like you!
Interesting.
Try and see if you can defeat me!!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
With his strong feelings towards Mai-san,
Varon regards Jounouchi as his enemy and wants to defeat him.
Jounouchi, too, accepts his challenge.
With that, their Duel begins.
Due to the effect of The Barrier of Orichalcos,
Varon's Armor Deck showcases its amazing power.
Faced with Varon's overwhelming fighting ability,
even Jounouchi is injured.
This isn't a normal Duel; This is a fight!
Next time!
"Full Armor Gravitation"
Duel standby!