Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In my Lost Memory World...
Back in Egypt three thousand years ago...
The battle between Bakura and me has started.
Stealing and killing... and showing no respect for the dead...
Bakura, I cannot forgive you!
But Bakura got away and his whereabouts was unknown.
Mahado brought a group of guards with him and headed to the tomb, but...
"Battle to the Death!
Mahado VS Bakura"
Good, the entrance is sealed!
Now the thief can't get out!
Raise the stone tablet!
If a Ka should appear on this tablet, we have been ordered to seal this tomb forever!
Lord Mahado is prepared to give up his life for the country.
In order to allow him to fight in peace, we must prevent all possible interferences!
Even at the risk of our lives!
I've been waiting for you, Bakura!
Really now? I'm happy to hear that!
Are you dying to give that Millennium Ring to me that badly?
I won't hand the Millennium Ring over to you.
And you will not walk out of here alive!
Those are pretty bold words coming from such a lowly spellcaster as yourself!
I will say it once more.
You will not leave!
I will unleash the entirety of my magical energies, my Heka, for this battle!
This guy...
For generations, magicians have trained their magical powers in this training ground.
Bakura! Today, this place will become your grave!
I wonder...
Come out, Diabound!
The appearance of his Ka.. his Diabound has changed!
Each time my hatred grows,
Diabound evolves!
Then I'll release all of my repressed Heka!
I summon forth Magus of Illusion!
Looks like your Ka has become more powerful than before.
But you're no match for my Diabound.
Then let me put that to the test, Bakura!
Diaha!!
Let's go!
Diabound, attack!
Thousand Poison Fangs Strike!!
In just a flash, he...?!
Attack, Magus of Illusion!
Magic Blast!!
And now I give my Heka
to Magus of Illusion!
Thousand Magic Blasts!!
This guy... is no ordinary magician!
Bakura... Even if it costs me all the Heka I have within me...
I will defeat you!
For the Pharaoh!
What's up with this feeling of uneasiness?
That's... Mahado's Shrine of Wedju...
There's no wind but the light is flickering...
Mahado...
Your Ba should be reduced as well...!
Enough!
That was just right for a warm up...
Diabound's finally gotten heated up...
Hmph! Then I shall give you more "warmth"!
So much so that your very mind and soul will burn in the process!
Magus of Illusion!
Diabound, counterattack!
The Wall Concealed Ka!
Shadow Ghoul!
He had a new Ka hidden?
That is the Special Power of Shadow Ghoul, Wall Concealment!
Go, Magus of Illusion!
Magic Blast!!
Shadow Ghoul! Consecutive Attack!
Diabound!
Tear the enemy to shreds! Shadow Ghoul!
What?!
Did you really think that the same trick would work twice?
Shadow Ghoul!
Magus of Illusion...!
Magic Blast!!
Did I get it?
No...
Diabound disappeared?
Diabound, kill the Magus of Illusion!
You fiend... Why are you able to use Shadow Ghoul's Wall Concealment?
Heh! Oh yeah, I never mentioned this earlier, did I?
Diabound's Special Power...
It steals the Special Powers of the Ka it defeats!
What?!
Well, what do you think?
Don't you think it's a special ability fitting for a thief?
Please! Let me get inside!
No means no!
Lord Mahado specifically ordered us that no one is to enter before he returns!
What's your problem!?
Let her in.
Prince...
Pharaoh!
Yes, we abide by Pharaoh's wishes.
What's wrong, Mana?
Why have you come to Mahado's Shrine of Wedju?
Just now, I saw Master in great pain within my dreams.
I may be overreacting, but I got so worried I couldn't sleep.
I thought that if I came here, I might be able to sense what Master's feeling.
You saw Mahado in pain?
The tablet is...!
Don't tell me...
Mahado summoned his Ka?
Prince!
Magus of Illusion!
You're too late!
Spiral Wave!!
Master!
Mahado...!
Damn!
What's wrong, Jounouchi?
Look at this!
I've been marking the doors with a magic marker so we know which paths we've tried!
Marking your territory, eh?
That's just something Jounouchi'd do!
In another sense, you're just tagging someone's soul...
We already went this way...
Which means, we're going in circles around the same path!
Yeah...
Yugi! Can't you hear us?!
We're calling you here!
Jounouchi-kun...
Yugi, tell me!
Which one is the right door?!
Hey, stop that, Jounouchi...
Can it, Anzu!
You mean you don't care what happens to Yugi if we can't get out of here?
Nobody said that!
Yugi?
What's wrong, Yugi?
I don't know why...
But my heart hurts when I go near this door...
Yugi?!
Are you here?
Bakura-kun...!
W-What's up with him?!
Everyone, are you okay?!
Yeah...
Yes...
It hurts...
That monster...
It vanished along with the room!
That is the true enemy the Pharaoh will have to fight against.
My other self's true enemy...?
Magician scum!
That's about all you can do!
The likes of yourself never had a chance of winning against someone as great as me!
You hardly rank in that level!
Now then... Guess I should finish it.
Y-You bastard!
That trap is a real trap.
It has always been there.
I was simply casting a spell so you couldn't see it!
Using such cheap tricks...!
Bakura! I'll resort to any means necessary if it means defeating you!
What...?!
That sure was close!
Now you've done it!
How ironic!
You're going to perish by the very trap you set yourself!
That's what I was after!
Diabound! Smash that magician and his Ka until nothing remains!
Spiral Wave!!
Pharaoh!
Master!
Mahado... Don't be reckless!
Prince, look there!
That's...!
Could... Mahado be there?
He's not in the Valley of the Kings?
That's... the training hall for spellcasters!
Hold on tight, Mana!
Where's Mahado?
He's inside the training hall... with Bakura!
What?!
Master!
Mana, inform everyone at the royal palace!
Y-Yes!
Are these things immortal?
Mana, get down!
Y-Yes!
Come! I'll take you!
Looks like this match is mine, Mahado.
I'll be taking your Millennium Ring now!
Great Pharaoh...
I really wanted to see the new world you've wanted to create.
But if I can assist in fulfilling that wish...
Then I'm very willing to sacrifice my life.
Damn that Mahado!
I've warned him so many times!
Mahado...
This guy... still wants to fight?
It's not over yet...
I may not have much Heka remaining...
But I still have some!
I'll show you... the forbidden ritual!
The forbidden ritual?
I will give my life as sacrifice...
...to fuse my spirit and my soul,
my Ba and Ka!
Come again?!
Pharaoh...
Mahado!
Please don't let this bother you-
Hold still.
Prince, please stop!
One who will become the Pharaoh doing such a thing...
Just what is the difference between me and you?
My Pharaoh...
My soul...
...is your eternal servant!!
Mahado!
Mahado...
Mahado!!
So he killed himself in the end, eh?
Impossible...!
Why's his Ka still here...?!
What?! Did he really fuse his Ba and Ka together?!
Bakura...
For the peace of the people, and for the new ideal world that the Pharaoh hopes for...
I'll get rid of you!
What nonsense!
Diabound, finish off this half-dead fool!
Magic Blast!!
Spiral Wave!!
What...?
Mahado!
Master!
Master!!
Mana!
Master!
This can't be...
Mahado... How can this be...?
What... is this feeling?
What's wrong, Yugi?
The Soul Labyrinth is... trembling...
Pharaoh!
This is...!
Mahado... sacrificed himself?
Pharaoh... My soul is
your eternal servant.
Mahado...
My other self's heart is trembling...
That's right, this maze is his heart, one and the same.
His heart is being swallowed by loneliness.
You are the only ones who can hear his loneliness and his sad cries.
I get it!
Then it's no use in us continuing to check all the doors!
Because it's the other me who's knocking at the door!
So we must concentrate and listen to him!
So that's it then?
If that's the case, we must listen carefully for the cries of the other Yugi!
Yes!
Everyone...
Other... Me...
Did you guys see that?
Yeah!
Let's try again!
Right!
I want to see you...
I really want to see you!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Mahado sacrificed himself in order to carry out the forbidden ritual...
And Bakura disappeared
from sight once again.
But is this really the end of the duel with and Bakura?
Meanwhile, we found the True Door...
And managed to come into Yugi's Lost Memory World.
But why is it that nobody here notices us?
Next time!
"The Blue-Eyed Kisara"
Please look forward to it!