Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
You're kidding me!
I-It's so big!
It's monstrous.
I've been waiting for you, Seto...
And I welcome you Duelists as well.
What do you think?
Will you accept the Duel with us?
Just a minute. But what'll happen to us if we lose?
You bring up an excellent point.
That means you'll be exchanged with us.
You'll wander the Cyber World for all eternity!
No way!
Shit! That's low!
This is our revenge against you all!
"Deck Master - Deepsea Warrior"
If you can beat us,
we'll let you leave this Virtual Space.
But if you to refuse our challenge,
unfortunately for you people, we will not permit you to return.
Only scumbags would think of such a low plan...
Bring it on, then!
I'll be your first opponent!
Big Brother!
We take what your friend there just said as an agreement to Duel against us.
Eh?
Anzu!
-Shizuka-chan!
Big Brother!
Kaiba-kun!
Big Five! Where'd you send everyone?!
Big Brother!
Damn you, Big Five! How dare you make a fool of me?!
What the...?
Where am I?
Where's my brother and everyone else?
Why am I here alone?
Otogi! Hey, are you okay?
Where am I? Where's Shizuka-chan?
Big Brother?!
Are you hurt?
No, Big Brother.
Seto, you're my very important guest.
Enjoy this world for the time being!
Hey! Shizuka-chan!
Now then, the first matchup will be between Yugi Mutou
and the first member of the Big Five, the Deepsea Warrior.
Is this also Virtual Reality?
They want us to Duel here?
I shall be the first opponent you face.
A Monster!
As a loyal subordinate of Kaiba Corporation,
I have taken over, raided and merged countless companies.
Using my great skill and abilities while imagining it,
I have taken on the form of the Deepsea Warrior, as you see before you.
In other words, I myself am the Deck Master.
So that's why you made the Deck Master System!
Yes, I lost my body because of you people.
It's just a pseudo form made to get my revenge.
I forgot to tell you a little something.
If you underestimate this world just because it's virtual, you're in for some pain.
What do you mean?
You'll understand soon.
Well then, it's about time I make do on my grudge.
I've grown fed up
with lingering in this Cyber World.
I want to get myself a body as soon as possible.
Enjoy the youth and energy of that young body while you still can!
Oh, and my colleagues will greet your friends in due time.
This is bad, Partner!
They're going to go after Anzu and Shizuka-chan.
Right!
Even if we have no reason to Duel with him...
...we have to beat him fast and go find Anzu and the others.
Yeah, it seems there's no other choice but to accept this Duel.
Even though I have no intentions of getting involved with your so-called "revenge",
I suppose we should get this started.
Now bring it on!
You're the Type-B Yugi, correct?
What did you say?
Yugi Mutou... Our references told us that you have two alternating thinking patterns.
Like a Duelist with two thinking minds.
It's essential to do your research before issuing a challenge.
They say, "If you take interest in your enemy, you cross the white line of victory and reign supreme".
So, shall we begin?
You won't be able to use your deck in this world.
To begin, you will have to make a new deck.
What?
This is the card data owned by Kaiba Corporation.
Simply touch the cards you desire with your finger.
The Big Five... How exactly are they related to this kid called Noah?
I'm all set.
I've finished my deck.
Then choose one of them as your Deck Master.
He told me to choose one...
...but I have no idea what abilities each individual card possesses.
Gazelle and Berfomet...
I don't think they'd be a good choice for the Master...
Then should I try for the Black Magician?
Yeah, I'll go with the Black Magician!
Kuriboh?!
Oh, you chose Kuriboh?
No! Kuriboh just came out on his own...!
I'm sorry, but once your Deck Master appears,
you cannot change it.
What?
You said "Count on me"?
Alright. I'll believe you then.
My Deck Master is Kuriboh!
As you see, my Deck Master is the Deepsea Warrior.
Now then, preparation time has ended.
I'll let you experience the Duel of an adult.
Let's start the Duel!
It'll be my turn first. Draw!
I Summon a Monster in Defense Position!
The first step is okay like this.
It's only the first step of my formation strategy.
It's also a fine trap.
Turn end!
I figured he'd have something special.
But he did nothing except place a Monster in Defense, which is your common move.
But he must have a special plan.
According to my research,
in this situation,
Type B Yugi will disregard all other options and choose to attack head-on.
He lives by the motion, "One must take action at all costs."
I can't let him set his formation the way he's planning to!
I'll destroy that Defense Monster!
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Retrained Elf Swordsman!
And set a reverse card!
And then I battle!
Retrained Elf Swordsman attacks your Defense Monster!
Good.
Everything is exactly as we learned of of you.
Children truly are simple-minded.
At this moment, I activate its Reverse Effect!
The opposing player must discard one card from their hand.
What?
And if Ashingrai is beaten in battle
and you still have an Ashingrai in your deck,
you can Special Summon another
from your deck in Reverse Defense Mode.
And then shuffle the deck.
How do you feel about this, Yugi Mutou?
The Ashingrai you went to the trouble of beating is back once more.
Have you begun to read my strategy?
Turn end.
Ah, they're beautiful!
The wind feels so good...
That's cold!
It's true this scenery is beautiful...
...but this is all only an illusion, isn't it?
But... this water is so cold.
Big Brother...
Where on Earth am I?
That aside, I can't believe those Big Five jerks actually came back...
God, if anything, at least they've got tenacity down-pact.
Hey, Big Five!
If we're gonna Duel, get yer asses out here and face me already!
I don't got all day, ya know!
You're off hiding somewhere and watchin' me, ain't ya?
Stop stalling for time!
Gonna ignore me, are ya?
I have to hurry up and beat Malik so I can rescue Mai from that weird trick he used on her!
Found you!
I don't have the time to be wasting waiting for you punks to decide to Duel me!
If we're gonna do it, let's do it!
Come on out already!
Shizuka-chan!
Shizuka-chan, where are you?
Damn, we're still getting lost in this maze despite it being virtual!
It looks the same no matter how far we run.
Even so...
What's wrong, Otogi?
Isn't this virtual room a little too big?
What do you mean?
More importantly, we'd better find Shizuka-chan soon. Let's go!
Wai- Hey!
Brother, they made this Virtual Space so vivid.
Indeed this Virtual Space does look quite real.
But it's just a copy of my Solid Vision in the end.
I wonder who that Noah guy is.
First that huge mobile floating fortress,
and now the virtual system.
They aren't things a little brat can come up with on his own.
And I highly doubt those Big Five scumbags had the strength to pull this off.
We just have to assume that there is somebody more powerful backing them up
with the intentions of
destroying Kaiba Corporation.
Brother, can we escape from here?
Don't worry. I know the basics of this system.
There must be an emergency exit programmed in here somewhere.
It'll probably look like a window or a door, to given an example.
Mmm-hmm!
My turn.
Draw!
Ipiria, huh?
Any player who successfully Summons Ipiria can draw one card from his deck.
Nice process, don't you think?
In the past, during the Renaissance, an Italian political thinker once said the following:
"There are three conditions for victory."
What's with this guy?
The first being, "Seize the chance."
I Summon Ipiria!
Because I successfully Summoned this card, I am permitted to draw a card.
I then switch the Ashingrai I have in Reverse Defense Mode into Attack Mode!
Continuing with the the conditions for victory, the second is...
"Maintain your expenses."
After this change of formation, I activate its Reverse Effect!
The opponent player has to throw
one card from his hand into the Graveyard.
Again?
Though this Ashingrai doesn't have very strong Attack Power,
it can still perform quite a few tricks that can be used in many different ways.
Both Ashingrai and Ipiria have 500 Attack Points...
Is he tempting me to attack?
We can't make it out.
We can't save Shizuka-chan
if we keep running like this.
That's right! There's no exit here because it's a virtual world.
So?
That means if there's no exit from the beginning, there won't be one at all!
The hell? That means we'll be running around here forever.
I think so...
Why are you depressed?
It's really a simple matter then.
If there's not an exit, we make one!
We just gotta smash through these walls.
That's right! This wall's nothing but special screening designed to intimidate us.
These are really just the walls of that mobile fortress.
If we can break through here, we can go out from the back stage.
But... how?
That ax isn't virtual?
Why was he able to grab it?
Here goes!
Is this Virtual Space, too?
Anyway, I have to search for the others.
What?
They've got me surrounded...
Help! Yugi!
Big Brother, look!
I have no doubts.
That's the program used as an exit.
Big Brother...
That's...
That's the orphanage where my big brother and I stayed...!
What bad taste...!
What possible reason could Noah have to program this in the Virtual World?!
Is he tempting me?
Or just trying to bluff me?
Shit... I'm falling into his pace...
I'm starting to think too much!
Kuriboh...
No matter what his goal is,
I can't just stand here and do nothing.
The others are in danger and waiting for me
while I'm just standing here.
My turn! Draw!
The Fusion card?
OK, let's decide this battle!
I'll fuse Berfomet and Illusion Beast Gazelle!
Fusion Summon!
Winged Illusion Beast Chimera!
And I activate the Magic Card, Quick Attack!
I use Winged Illusion Beast Chimera to attack Ipiria!
The third step of the conditions for victory states...
"Tempt your enemies to follow the path of self-destruction."
You fell for it! I activate my Deck Master Ability!
Your Deck Master Ability...?
My Special Ability is called Reflector Hole!
I use two Monsters as sacrifices,
and make the opponent's attack
bounce back directly to the player!
What!?
How was it?! That was my Deck Master Ability!
I understand now that this is no ordinary Duel.
In pain, are you?
The wounds you get in this Virtual Space
will be taken by your brain as real ones.
And add the burden to your heart.
It's almost time for your friends to Duel in the other Spaces.
You aside, I wonder if your other weaker friends can take such suffering...?
Aren't you worried about them?
This Duel can't last much longer!
Right! We should beat him as soon as possible and get to where the others are!
"Preview"
No matter how many are beaten,
Monsters still show up one by one.
The Revival Combo of Deepsea Warrior
starts to get Yugi frustrated.
At this moment, Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun, who were relayed
to another Virtual Space
meet their past selves.
Shizuka-chan and the others are
attacked by Monsters.
And I am caught by Cyclops.
Hurry up and rescue us, Yugi!
Next time!
"The Terrifying Revival Combo"
Duel Standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise