Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Ectoplasmer, attack!
"Magician's Disciple:
Black Magician Girl"
Black Magician, I won't let you sacrifice your soul for me in vain!
I sacrificed my Black Magician in order to finish off Yugi, but...!
It was all in vain...?!
Wait just a little longer...
Well, he's lost his Black Magician as well.
In my deck I still have two more Black Magicians waiting to kill you.
Continue the duel!
My End Phase!
Reverse card set!
Turn over!
Yugi, I know. You don't have another Black Magician in your deck, right?
The true title of the Black Magician user goes to me after all.
We'll see about that, Pandora.
If you truly are the true Black Magician user, you should have heard it.
The mourn of the card's soul who was betrayed by his master!
I don't hear anything like that.
The only sound filling my ears...
Is the buzz of the circular saw about to cut you up!
Yugi, you only have 700 points of your Life left.
At the moment it hits 0, the cutter will slice into you!
And I will conduct the perfect ending to the greatest escape show!
The cards decide how the fight ends!
Here I go! My turn!
Right now, Pandora has no monsters on the field.
This may be my chance!
I Summon Gazelle the King of Mythical Beasts!
You fell right into my trap, didn't you?!
Trap Card! Demon's Scale!
What?!
This Trap Card is activated when the opponent Summons a monster.
Judging by the number of monsters I have on the field, it will make your field equal to that!
Damn it...! The number of monsters he has on the field is 0! That means...!
That is correct!
Demon's Scale!
My monsters are...!
Now the number on both our fields is 0!
It's a shame, since you just Summoned a new monster.
My turn!
With this card, my victory is guaranteed!
Both of our fields have no monsters...
That means he shouldn't be able to sacrifice lower level monsters
to Summon a more powerful one...
Yugi, it seems you think you've read through my strategy.
On the contrary, I have a card that will let me Summon a high level monster in an instant!
A card that will let me call the best magician, Black Magician!
An Instant Summon card...?
I'm going! This is the key card to victory!
Black Magic Curtain!
This turn, the player will pay half his Life Points as a cost
to Summon the black magician from their deck!
Come forth! Black Magician!
Yugi, how do you like my perfect Magician Deck?
Summon speed, quick acting, and magic combination.
Including everything, it surpasses your deck.
I'm the only one worthy of being called the true Black Magician user, don't you think?
Right now, you have no monster guarding you.
This turn, If I were to attack you with Black Magician,
it's certain that your Life would diminish and that I would win.
The only thing guarding you is that set card on your field.
Most likely, it is a Trap Card that activates when an attack is launched,
and it wipes out the attacking monster.
What an eyesore.
Why don't I seal that set card?
Seal my set card?!
Magic Card, Magic-Sealing Arrows!
Now all of your remaining hope has been sealed!
You lose!
Black Magician, attack the player directly!
I win!
What?!
Black Magic Curtain is... on Yugi's field?!
Yes. The Magic Card you played, Black Magic Curtain, is a card that affects the entire field.
In other words, I am also allowed to use that magic.
I will also Summon a Magician Card!
Impossible...! You shouldn't have another Black Magician in your deck...!
Ah, I have only one Black Magician in my deck.
T-T-Then what are you...?
In the world of Duel Monsters,
there is but one female magician that is called the "Magician's Disciple".
Impossible...! There is a Magician Card that I, the Magicians user, don't know about?!
I'll show you!
Black Magician Girl!
B-Black Magician Girl...?!
But Black Magician Girl's Attack is only 2000!
It can do nothing against Black Magician's attack!
Black Magician, attack Black Magician Girl!
Black Magic!!
Black Burning!!
This time, I win!
Is that so?
Impossible...! My Black Magician is disappearing...!
W-Why...?
It's Attack should be 500 higher...!
I'll tell you. Black Magician Girl, for each Black Magician sleeping in the Graveyard,
increases her Attack by 300 points for each.
The soul of a fallen ally makes her stronger!
B-But...!
There's only one Black Magician in Yugi's Graveyard...
Even with an increase of 300 points, her Attack should still only be 2300!
My Black Magician should still have won!
Look closer. If you are truly a Black Magician user, the truth should spread out before you.
T-There's one more...!
N-No way...! My Black Magician's soul... is there as well!?
Black Magician Girl inherits the souls of all Black Magicians sleeping in our Graveyards!
Betrayed by you, your Black Magician's soul has chosen to fight against you instead!
It's my turn!
Prepare yourself, Pandora!
Black Magician Girl, direct attack player Pandora!
Black Burning!!
Because you betrayed your cards, you've lost, Pandora!
Oi guys, What happened?
Honda, Yugi's gone missing!
What?!
Most likely, he's been captured by the Ghouls!
Big brother lead us to this building.
If you know the location, then it's a different story.
Let's break in!
For a duelist, to not cherish the bond between your cards,
you're only walking down the path of failure.
You lost because you disrespected your Black Magician!
I-Impossible! A duelist who respects their cards...!
A card should only follow the instructions of the master controlling it!
A duelist like you who threw away the bonds between your cards
in order to obtain victory...
You've already lost the duelist's soul!
Pandora, all that awaits you is your last act of cruelty!
You've got to be kidding me...!
When my counter hits 0, the cutter will be triggered,
and it's moving to saw through my legs!
GET AWAY~!
The key and Puzzle Card...!
In here...?
What is it... that sound...?
It's all over!
Just kidding!
Don't dare underestimate a conjurer!
I thought over this possible outcome, and prepared a spare key in my sleeve!
As long as I have this, I can still escape from here!
W-What's wrong?
Am I scared? So scared I can't move?
Pandora!
Malik-sama!
You lost the duel. You have to pay the price.
Save me! Please let me off the hook, Malik-sama!
H-Huh...? The key's gone...!
I WAS JUST HOLDING THE KEY A MOMENT AGO...!
I just altered your memory.
Your memory of that key just faded away right now.
To you, the key may as well not exist.
Oi, Yugi!
Are you in there?!
Answer us if you're in there!
LOOK OUT!
It's definitely wrong to throw your life away for a game!
Catherine... Catherine...
CATHERINE~!
Catherine...!
Please don't leave my side again...!
Oh, Catherine!
I'm so sorry I didn't accept your feelings then and drove you away...!
I don't care about my fame anymore...!
Let's both return to France together and start over...!
Just what's going on here?
Pandora-san.
Why'd you go and do that?
You're the vessel for the other Yugi, am I right?
His personality changed suddenly...! You are...!
I see. You weren't conscious when we met earlier today.
My name is Malik.
Malik?!
I can control people from any location. I can even alter their memory.
If I ease off enough, their voices can still be heard.
I controlled Keith using this same method.
Back then...!
Yes. In order to prove the existence of your other self.
To see if you were really the one chosen to solve the Millennium Puzzle,
and to see if the man inside you was who I thought he was.
And when you completed the Millennium Puzzle again,
you confirmed the existence of that man.
Why do you wanna kill us?! Answer me!
It doesn't concern you...
But I have business with the soul you contain!
Revenge...
I am the heir of the clan of Tomb Guardians who lived in darkness for 3,000 years.
And I will avenge them!
Revenge...? Clan of Tomb Keepers?
On the edge of Necropolis in Egypt...
We Tomb Guardians have lived apart from the world,
hiding in the shadows, passing the task from mother to daughter and father to son.
My clan must avoid all contact with the outside world,
living only to protect the Millennium Items we were handed...
And...
We must die for this fate.
We must return the Pharaoh's memory to his soul.
Memory...? Does that mean the Pharaoh's memory stone tablet
and the 7 items are related?
Yes. I hold one of the seven secrets as well.
I must guard it, even if it means my life, until I present it to the Pharaoh's soul.
That's what I was taught as a child.
The problem is finding the Pharaoh's soul.
The only clue is written in the original Ancient Egyptian hieroglyphic text
of the Pert Em Heru, the Book of the Dead.
It says of the Pharaoh "You will know him by the three God Cards he wields."
In other words, the one who collects the three God Cards will be crowned the title "Pharaoh"
and regain the Millennium Items and his lost memories!
The three God Cards...?
Lost memory?!
For countless generations, my clan has protected
the Millennium Items at the cost of suffering and pain...
Including my father!
I will put an end to the curse laid upon us...
And to do that, I will take revenge on the Pharaoh's soul and kill him a second time!
And if the prophecy says that the Pharaoh will wield the three God Cards...
...then I will obtain the cards and become the new Pharaoh!
New Pharaoh...?
I formed the Ghouls for the sole purpose of locating those God Cards.
And I have already obtained two of the cards.
The third resides in this town.
In this Battle City!
I finally understand what it is the other me is looking for in this town.
That's his lost memory.
I shall obtain the three God Cards!
And Yugi, once I kill you...
...I will be freed from my family's cursed fate, and the world will be mine!
If we don't locate the God Cards and the other me's lost memory, I can stay with him forever.
However...
The other me knew this well in his heart.
For his precious memory, he saw our future.
But the other me doesn't know his memories, so he can only stay where he is...
Even so, he continues to search.
If that's the case, there's no point being sad about it.
Even if, when he obtains that memory, we are to be separated...
I'll gladly help him search!
Malik! I won't let you take away the other me's life!
We'll fight!
You're merely a vessel.
When the time comes, you can die alongside him.
Within this city, another Rare Hunter wielding a God Card is lurking.
A man who holds Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...?!
He will appear before you sooner than you think.
So remember... beware the Silent Doll.
Silent Doll...?
We'll meet again, Yugi.
We'll fight in order to get back his lost memory!
Are you alright, Yugi?!
Yugi!
Everyone!
Thank goodness!
I was so worried!
Just you wait...
Alongside your impertinent vessel, I will bury your soul in darkness.
How will you get the God Card?
Use a God Card against a God Card.
I, holding the Ra card, will enter Domino City shortly.
So you're going against Kaiba personally, Lord Malik?
Eventually, it will come to that.
But I'm focusing on Yugi for the time being.
Let the Silent Doll out of his stall and set him loose.
Yes.
No doubt he's going to make things really fun.
Fun...?
Lord Malik rarely uses that word unless he's thinking terrible thoughts.
Gathering together the three God Cards is supposed to be the Ghoul's primary objective.
But Lord Malik is focusing on Yugi.
The Ra card...
Yugi, with these hands, I will surely...
Swearing by the scars on my back, I will defeat you and get my revenge!
Dear sister, I can't forgive him.
The man who killed our clan and our father! Yugi!
Someone wants Jounouchi's autograph.
Hey, isn't he just stealing your Duel Disk?!
He manages to get it back, although...
It seems his rare card was stolen by Insector Haga!
Filled with anger, Jounouchi challenges Haga to a duel, however...
Wait a minute!
Do you have a card like that?
Next time!
Trap of Revenge
Reckless! Parasite
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...