Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In my Lost Memory World, the Ultimate Dark Game between Bakura and me has started.
With the increased power he has obtained
after defeating Mahado to get the Millennium Ring,
Bakura infiltrates the royal palace once again.
Who are you after this time?
And who is that blue-eyed woman Seto has rescued?
"The Secret of the Creation of the Millennium Items"
Now that I have absorbed the evil memories of the Millennium Ring,
my powers are unbeatable.
You really killed Mahado...
To think that you would be concerned about the death of a comrade
when you committed that
massacre in Kul Elna.
What? Why do you know about that?!
Because I'm the one and only survivor of that very same Kul Elna!
But well, that's not important.
Because this is a Dark Game, you see.
That has nothing to do with me now.
Wh-What are you talking about?
I want you to become my pawn, just as you did 3,000 years ago!
Using this, I can send these evil memories into your Millennium Eye.
You must fulfill your end of the bargain - a promise that spans 3,000 years of time!
What's that?
What's this feeling of uneasiness coming from the Millennium Puzzle?
Pharaoh!
What's wrong?
A village along the river got attacked by unknown people and is now destroyed!
What!?
That is...!
What is that?!
That sound was...
That person... is Bakura!
Bakura has appeared!
He should still be within the royal palace! Go find him!
Send troops out to surround the palace!
Don't let him escape!
Yes, sir!
What in the world is happening?!
Lord Akhenaden, please get a hold on yourself!
Lord Akhenaden!
Se-Seto...
He's only lost consciousness.
Looks like he was after the Millennium Eye.
That cursed Bakura!
Shada, I'll leave Lord Akhenaden to you.
Kalim, we must go after Bakura!
Yes!
Wait up!
Don't let him get away!
Don't let him pass!
Stop! Stop!
Anyone who dares come near me will become food for my Diabound!
So His Highness came to fight me personally, did he?
Bakura, I won't let you get away!
I summon forth a God!
Come forth!
Osiris the Sky Dragon!!
Finally here, huh? The second god, Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
That's good, King!
Let's open the second act of our battle!
Come chase me into the depths of Hell!
Bakura! I won't let you shed any more innocent blood!
Bakura is coming!
Don't let him escape!
Strength our defense!
The other me!
Yugi!
He may be dressed weirdly, but there's no mistake.
That guy's Yugi!
Isn't Bakura the one running in front of him?
Yugi...
Everyone, let's follow them!
Okay!
I know everything there is to know.
The things you did in the village of Kul Elna...
Or how you've abandoned your son, Seto, to accomplish them.
That's right... That happened fifteen years ago...
Pharaoh Akhenamkhanen, I hereby report the situation to you.
The foreign armies have
crossed into our land!
We have no forces left to fight back!
How long can our
remaining troops hold up for?
If I had to guess, I'd say seven days, more or less.
Is this the end?
King Akhenamkhanen, you mustn't give up.
This battle isn't just about our country.
It concerns the future of the whole land!
Our enemy is, without a doubt,
after the ancient scriptures our land holds - the Millennium Tome.
The Millennium Tome...
It's been said that whomever deciphers the ancient spells can obtain godly powers...
Powers that would make all other armies bow before us.
If that spellbook gets into the enemy's hands, the whole land would...
But we have yet to decipher the ancient texts in the tome.
No my king, a portion of it has already been deciphered.
What?!
Are you speaking the truth, Akhenaden?
Yes.
A form of "Dark Alchemy" is described inside.
It tells us a method to create seven mystical treasures using magic.
If we succeed, we would be able to drive away out enemies from our Egypt...
And regain peace for all.
Using seven mystical treasures to regain peace?
Seven days are needed to create these mystical treasures.
But I, the philosopher Akhenaden,
have already made the preparations for this Dark Alchemy.
Dark Alchemy...
We have no other choice.
For the future of our kingdom and peace for our land,
proceed with the creation of those seven items.
I'll leave this to you,
Akhenaden... my brother!
Sir!
I'm sorry.
In order to save the country, I must seal my actions forever.
As such, I must abandon my past as "the King's younger brother".
Both you and Seto must abandon your past as well.
Forget about me and go live in a faraway town.
Dear...
Tell Seto that his father died as a nameless soldier on the battlefield.
Dear!
Farewell, my dear wife... and Seto.
The ones gathered here are our Egypt's finest of the Imperial Court.
Your efforts shall pave the path for the country's future.
Now, brave soldiers!
Watch closely and see the destiny we all bear...and the glorious future!
Listen up, everyone.
My voice is the voice of the skies... and also the voice of destiny.
Nobody can resist this voice.
We shall now head forth for the village of Kul Elna located near the Valley of Kings!
Do not speak of this matter to anyone you see along the way!
Set off!
Dark Alchemy...
In order to complete this ritual, human sacrifices must be made.
Even though this is for the sake of the country...
What I'm going to do is something that I cannot reveal to the King.
Forgive me, big brother!
The village of Kul Elna lies just ahead in sight.
The thieves that have been raiding our royal tombs live in this village.
The foolish things they have done angered the Gods and brought this fate upon the country!
We shall make them pay for their sins!
Don't let anyone escape!
Help me!
Dark Alchemy... It is a ritual conducted between gods and devils.
That the seven Millennium Items were forged using the villagers of Kul Elna...
And the soldiers that assisted in the preparations would remain a secret.
But at that time...!
What's going on?
We didn't know the true dark secret behind the seven mystical treasures...
Why is there a tablet with engravings on it where the seven items can be placed?
Suhen! Sekhen!
Now then, place the items in their respective places!
Be gone, devil!
Lord Akhenaden!
Let's get out of here immediately!
Okay!
Suhen!
Get a grip on yourself, Suhen!
Do not concern yourself with me.
Bring the seven mystical treasures back quickly...
The fewer people who know about this, the better.
Suhen!
Suhen...
I have returned...
...with the Millennium Items in hand!
Look! There's no army protecting the royal palace!
This country is ours!
What kinda joke are these guys?!
What can seven people do?
Seven treasures... Protect my country and my people!
Spirits! Give us your power!
With that, the country was protected.
I listened to the late King Akhenamkhanen...
By concealing my identity and stayed in the palace.
I've served the country all my life and I have no regrets... apart from one thing...
Seto... I have destroyed your future with my own hands.
He is the new wielder of the Millennium Rod, High Priest Seto.
His parents died when he was young...
He came from a poor background, but he worked hard.
Passing all the grueling exams and came in the top.
He is truly a rare talent that only shows up every ten years.
Lift your head, Seto.
Yes, sir!
As I am now the owner of the Millennium Rod...
I shall put in even more work in creating a prosperous nation.
I will be counting on you, Seto.
One of these days, you'll become my son's right-hand man.
I am deeply touched by your compliments.
Is something troubling you, Sir Akhenaden?
Seto, you wouldn't have known how touched I was at that time.
The son that I abandoned defeated the odds using his own abilities...
And the happiness I feel about him being in such a high position...
Seto, you have the talent and a bloodline that nobody knows about.
The one who should be king is...!
Seto, you should!
This is far enough.
Diabound, let's say hello! Attack him with your new power!
Go, Magic Blast!!
Diabound can take on the abilities of those it defeats.
The power earlier was taken from the dead Mahado.
Mahado...
Osiris!
Summon Lightning Strike!!
What?!
Run! Run!!
See if you can outrun the fuse of death!
Die!
That really hurt, you rotten bastard!
Continue forcing him into a corner, Osiris!
You must've forgotten!
That the battlefield we're fighting on is one I hold the utmost advantage on!
Diabound, do what you like!
Destroy this city 'till there's nothing left standing!
W-What... There are strange monsters in the sky!
Monsters?
I don't see them.
What!?
Come one, come all! It's the Pharaoh's grand parade!
He actually got innocent people involved in this...!
"Oh Great Pharaoh", consider this a game!
See how many of the bystander's lives you can save!
You plan to act as shield for these people and take all the attacks?
But dear King, how long can you last?
Don't even think about escaping!
If you dare take a step, you'll implicate the folks below!
Bakura!
The Gods won't lose to your dirty ways!
Take this! Thunder Force!!
Spiral Wave!!
That's...!
What?!
I won't put the city in any more danger!
Take him into the skies, Osiris!
With that, your attacks won't reach the city!
A battle in the sky is more favorable for a Sky God, is that it?
But even if Osiris can control the skies, my Diabound can control darkness!
It disappeared?
Diabound can conceal itself by blending in with the surroundings in a flash.
O King, the difficulty level of this game has increased!
I still have other secret abilities, but I guess I don't need them today.
I have many options to choose from.
I can decide if I want to do more damage to the city... or kill you immediately...
Nah, I guess it's best to see you surrender your Millennium Puzzle to me.
I want someone like you, whom is regarded as a living God
to stand in the middle of the city and swear to obey my commands!
If I hand the Millennium Puzzle to him, I'd lose.
But I can't put the citizens in any more danger...
Oh, you're really going to give that to me?
But I still have a chance to turn the tables...
To lure the Diabound that's shrouded in darkness... there's only one way...
Right, my King! Get down off the horse and kneel in front of me!
This is it, Osiris!
You have no choice but to get Diabound to protect you now!
Whoever told you that Diabound was hiding in the sky?
In the end, I've still decided to kill you.
Wander forever in the realms between life and death!
That's...!
Seto's spirit, Duos!
Pharaoh!
Seto!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Just as we couldn't enter the royal palace, suddenly
we saw Osiris the Heaven Dragon flying above us.
The one controlling that is definitely the other Yugi!
Bakura's Diabound has been causing destruction to the city...
And the other Yugi can only take a defensive stance.
This is the time for us to give him a helping hand!
Stand up, Yugi! We are by your side!
Next time!
"Turn Back Time"
Please look forward to it!