A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Duel Monsters Quest 3:
Master of Dragon Knight
Hey!
We're flying!
We're really flying in the air!
Yeah!
-We did it!
-Idiot!
Hey!
Iru!
Do you wanna come with us too?
Okay!
Let's go!
To the Dark Castle of the Sky!
Oh yeah!
Let's go!
Onward!
We're counting on you guys!
I pray for your safety, my saviors.
We've got the building completely surrounded!
Give up!
We won't let you guys lay even a finger on Yugi and the others!
They're here!
Let's get em!
We'll beat you to the ground!
Harpie Lady and Rose Whip!
Mage Knight Giltia!
Black Magician!
Oh yeah, man!
Bring it on!
Iru!
Sealing Swords of Light!
I'm sorry...!
I'm sorry!
Because of me...!
Yugi...
I won't forgive you, Big Five!
We've hit the barrier!
Just a bit more...!
Break through!
We did it!
What the?
Shit!
Damn you!
Fire...!
The ship...
You again...?
I sincerely apologize for the wait.
We got our hands on the second sacrifice!
Big brother!
Mokuba!
Why are you here?!
I came to save you, brother!
My, my...
But you've arrived just in time to join him.
It's about time we get the ritual started.
Shall we begin?
Right here and now, you both shall become sacrifices for the Five God Dragon!!
Sword Stalker!!
Brother!
Take this!
Well done, Mokuba!
Y-You didn't...!
It's about time for me to repay your kindness!
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Blow him to hell!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Mokuba, let's go!
Mhm-hm!
The same trick won't work on me!
Come out, Trap Master!
I'll be taking the Blue-Eyes you sealed up before!
Disappear, weaklings!
Double Burst Stream of Anger!!
But Mokuba, how'd you get here?
I asked Yugi and his friends for help.
Yugi, you said?!
Yugi came to this world as well?!
I was worried about you, big brother...
You didn't need to do that...
Let's go!
Wait up, brother!
I didn't expect the "Dark Castle" or whatever to look like this.
No, this presence...
Look at that!
Cocoons of Evolution...!
We can't let those hatch!
Just perfect!
Mage Knight Giltia!
Giltia!
The Man-Eater Bug!
They're trying to protect the cocoons!
Th-They're coming!
Saint Barrier: Mirror Force!
We didn't make it in time?
But we still have other methods!
Kuriboh?
Using this, the Great Moths will be annihilated!
Kuriboh!
Multiply!
-We did it!
Hooray! Hooray!
I can't believe this happened...
For Yugi Mutou to make it this far...
Let's prepare ourselves.
What's that?
Blue-Eyes!
Kaiba!
Mokuba!
So you're safe?
We were worried!
I don't need a loser dog to be worrying about me.
What'd you say?!
You jerk! Who the hell do you think you are?!
You've done well to make it this far!
You failed to sacrifice me!
S-Seto Kaiba!
What are you doing here?
That means the legendary Five God Dragon can't be revived!
This game is officially cleared!
We will not allow you to.
That's correct!
What?!
What the?!
So this is... the legendary Five God Dragon?
That's cheap!
The Five God Dragon shouldn't be revived!
A truly exceptional game always has a surprise ending.
I see.
So I presume this is your way of pulling an abstention?
Fine then.
We'll take on this Duel!
Battle!
Here we go!
The Three Harpie Sisters!
What?!
Behold the symbol below your feet.
What's this?!
The Lord of Dragons!
Right. This is the Dragon's Sanctuary.
Only those of the Dragon-type can fight here!
You dare to challenge me to a duel of dragons?
I praise that optimism of yours!
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
Good! Now it's me!
Get out here!
Red-Eyes!
Harpie's Pet Dragon!!
Curse of Dragon!
Let's go!
I-It withstood the attack...!
I get it!
The fifth head defended the others!
There's still one target left to attack!
We should start with the defenseless one!
Wh-What?
You don't mean...!
Disappear, Mokuba!
Mokuba!
MOKUBA!!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Yugi...
The rest...
...is up to you...!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi...!
Jounouchi...
Jounouchi-kun...!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi!!
That's not fair!
It's against the rules to directly attack the players!
"Not fair"?
We make the rules of this world!
You scum...!
"When the strongest dragon teams up, the Evil God will be destroyed."
What are you talking about?
It's the legend that exists in this world!
It's a hint for us to defeat them!
Dark Knight Gaia!
Become the legendary soldier!
Did you forget about the barrier already?
So long as he is not a Dragon-type,
Chaos Soldier cannot fight here!
That is correct!
We shall get rid of the Chaos Soldier right now!
I won't let you!
I'll be your opponent!
The weak shall disappear!
Mai!
Yugi...
I'm not sure what you're trying to do...
But I believe in you!
You better... win...
...Yugi...
Mai!
I won't let you put your life on the line in vain!
Kaiba!
Use this chance to call the Ultimate out!
Are you trying to order me around?!
Now isn't the time to say stuff like that!
I don't need your power!
I can beat these guys on my own!
Don't fool yourself, Kaiba!
Disappear along with the Blue-Eyes!
Kaiba!
The Ultimate...!
Shut your mouth!
Big brother!!
Mokuba!!
B-Big brother...
MOKUBA!!
You look so pathetic now, Kaiba!
Seto-sama, you shall now grieve in despair over the loss of your little brother.
Stand!
Stand up, Kaiba!
Do you want to waste what Mokuba just did for you?!
Unforgivable...
You'll pay, Big Five!
Come forth! Ultimate Dragon!
Show your ultimate form before us!
If you have the Ultimate Dragon,
it is still not enough to stop our Five God Dragon's attack!
We'll see about that.
"When the strongest dragon teams up, the Evil God will be destroyed."
What?!
You couldn't...!
Chaos Soldier and Ultimate Dragon...!
By gathering these two together, you intend to Summon that Monster?!
I'll show you right now!
Go, Chaos Soldier!
Go, Ultimate!
We won't let you!
What!?
It was negated!
Master of Dragon Knight!
What the?!
From the Graveyard...!
T-The Dragons...!
Master of Dragon Knight gains the Attack Points
of every Dragon on the field.
Can you see this...?
Jounouchi-kun?
Mai?
Mokuba?
This is your power!
Go!
Master of Dragon Knight!!
Galaxy Crusher!!
This is impossible!!
Th-This place...!
You have done well defeating the Evil God.
Now this world has been saved.
But Jounouchi-kun and the others...
This is far from a true victory...!
My saviors, now that the Evil God has vanished,
it is time I revealed my true form to you.
That's... the princess' true form?
Guys!
Mokuba!
Huh?
What happened to us?
Big brother!
That seems to be the exit.
W-Wait a minute, Kaiba.
Shouldn't you at least thank us first?
Had I not been here, you couldn't have defeated the Five God Dragon.
What'd you say?!
Yugi, I would like you to hear me out for a moment.
Did you know about the existence of Master of Dragon Knight from the start?
So long as we believe,
the cards will be sure to answer us.
Back there, I believed in my cards.
And you're the same, aren't you Kaiba?
Let's go, Mokuba.
Big brother!
Just let them go, Jounouchi.
That was splendid, my saviors.
We shall never forget about you.
Meyari, Iru.
Farewell.
See ya!
Take care!
Honda!
Think I'll let you?!
What?!
Jounouchi!
Yugi!
Where's Kaiba-kun?
He's safe!
He should have returned to our world.
Wh-What'd you say?!
Too bad for you, Sawatari!
Your plan just failed!
Sh-Shit...
Withdraw!
We did it!
Serves you right!
Thank god...
Mai!
So you guys were here too?
We came a little while ago!
Guys...
Thanks.
I...
Idiot.
He may be a jerk, but you better hurry and go see your big brother Mokuba!
Right!
We should get back too!
I'm starving!
Me too!
Alright! How bout we get some ramen?!
Sounds good!!
"Preview"
Not good, not good!
Yugi's grandfather has a new rival game store!
It features a new game called Dungeon Dice Monsters!
And a new transfer student named Otogi has come to our school.
They seem to all be related!
Jounouchi challenged him out of jealousy, though!
Bring it on if you think you have the guts!
Next time!
The New Transfer Student, Ryuji Otogi.
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship