Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Noah, you won't be able to surpass me just by calling yourself a "creator" so you can come to terms with your pitiful past!
Even if your Deck Master is the best there is,
I will just have to be even greater!
I'm done with the pity farces.
It's about time we put an end to this Duel!
What?! Mokuba!
You mean to block my path?!
"Save Mokuba! The Fateful Seventh Turn"
Mokuba...!
Looks like Mokuba's forgotten all about you after I took the liberty of sealing his memories away.
Any enemy of my brother's is an enemy of mine!
Mokuba-kun...!
What's the matter, Seto?
You're not going to attack?
If you attack me using the effects of Dragon's Imperial Wrath, my Life will be ancient history!
But can you do that at the risk of harming Mokuba through the battle damage in the process?
Low life...!
That damn bastard...!
It's time for you to get on with your attack already, Seto.
The fact is, Noah hasn't shown us a single flaw in this Duel.
If Kaiba-kun lets this opportunity go, he may not get another chance to win...
But even so...!
Mokuba...!
My turn is over!
Kaiba-kun...!
It sure is, isn't it?!
There's not a thing you can do to oppose me now!
All that awaits you is a cruel and painful future where I take your body and all you stand for!
You did well, Mokuba.
Get back over here now.
My beloved little brother, watch carefully as I dispose of him.
Right, big brother!
It's my turn! And the fourth turn of the creation of Heaven and Earth!
I will now be activating the third Holy Ability of my Deck Master, Ark of Miracles!
Third Holy Ability?
That's right. It's the third Holy Ability of the Ark of Miracles.
And that is...
Life Restoration!
The Monsters in the ark...!
Life Restoration...
If I remove all the Monsters in the Ark of Miracles from the game...
I can increase my Life Points by 500 for each one.
I had six Monsters on board the ark.
As such, my Life will recover by 6000 points.
Noah's Life rose to 6400!
If he had just used Life Restoration from the beginning,
he wouldn't have needed to use Mokuba-kun as a shield, but he wanted to make Kaiba-kun suffer!
That scum bag...!
And then, a Magic Card...
I activate Black Hole!
This Magic Card destroys all Monsters on the field!
Now more Monsters have entered the ark...!
He's set up an infinite loop with his Absolute Protection and his Life Restoration.
It's like that Deck Master is invincible!
There's no way to win this match, ooh!
I think my turn's over.
What's wrong, Seto?
It's your turn now!
Mokuba...
I promised that I would be your
father from now on... That I would protect you from now on.
It's true that I was rough with you on that day...
Big brother...?
Just how far
do you think I'll tolerate this?!
But I did it so that in the worst case scenario, if I were to fail, you would still be a member of the Kaiba's.
Big brother, please believe me!
It wasn't me!
Silence!
Throw him out of here!
But I didn't use you!
I give my two cards to my big brother!
And the two of us pulled something off that baffled the minds of everyone in that room.
Our bond was strong
enough to beat Gozaburo.
It was our willingness to believe in one another that saved us!
Mokuba...
There has to be a way I can save you!
Kaiba-kun, you have to believe in Mokuba-kun!
Yugi!
I had to fight against Jounouchi-kun when Malik set up that trap for us.
And it was my bond with Jounouchi-kun that saved us in that pinch.
You have to keep fighting.
You have to keep fighting, and you have to bring back your memories with Mokuba-kun!
Our bond...?
We have one!
I have a card that represents the bond between me and Mokuba!
Your friend sure gave you a hell of a tip.
Don't misinterpret it.
I take no orders from anyone but myself.
I fight everything on my own!
My turn!
This isn't it!
Return to our dimension,
Twilight Zone Dragon!
I switch Twilight Zone Dragon into Defense Mode!
I'll end my turn with that!
It's the fifth turn of creation!
The field is changing again!
Eventually all living creatures on the planet began to undergo rapid evolution cycles.
Modern civilization was born as a result!
Look, big brother!
That's...
Kaiba Corporation...
Yes, that is the castle I should be reigning in... Kaiba Corporation!
Time has reached its present.
Seto, allow me to show you the most terrifying weapons in Kaiba Corporation's arsenal and the potential they wield.
Super Dimension Fighter Vic Viper, prepare for launch!
And now for the Magic Card Cyclone Laser!
I then equip it with Matter Leveler.
If the Monster equipped with Matter Leveler attacks an opponent's Defense Position Monster,
the card's Attack Power automatically rises to 100 points more than that Monster's Defense Points.
And Cyclone Laser is a card that inflicts damage to my opponent when I attack a Monsters with Defense Power lower than its Attack Power.
The target is Twilight Zone Dragon!
Fire the Cyclone Laser!!
Twilight Zone Dragon is a Monster that can't be destroyed by magic or in battle, isn't that right?
It's the perfect Monster
to torture you with!
That Noah freak's just gonna keep attacking Kaiba until he loses, OOH!
Kaiba, do something already!
Kaiba-kun...!
My turn, draw!
This isn't the card either!
I'll leave Twilight Zone Dragon in Defense Position and end my turn!
Heh, of course you will.
There's not a thing you need to do, other than thoroughly accept the suffering I'm going to hand you, Seto!
I'm going to enjoy the look of agony on your face!
I can't believe you have the gall to call yourself a creator when you get sick pleasure from watching people suffer.
I guess Gozaburo had a reason for abandoning you.
Shut up, Seto!
Father had faith in me
all the way to his death!
I worked so hard for my father.
There's not a time in my life that I betrayed his expectations!
I will be reborn as a human being with superior knowledge!
I'll complete the Kaiba empire my father failed to establish!
Father will happily cheer me on!
And he'll say, "I knew it all along, Noah. You are my one and only son."
It's the sixth turn of creation!
I Summon Option!
Option is a card that mimics the Attack and Defense Points of a Vic Viper on the field with its Special Ability.
Option, transform into Vic Viper!
Fire the Cyclone Laser!
Now watch carefully Mokuba, as we reveal our enemy for who he truly is!
Mokuba...!
Doesn't it hurt, Seto?
It really does hurt, doesn't it?
Being betrayed by the one you love!
I still have a Monster
that is yet to attack you.
Go, Vic Viper!
Fire the Cyclone Laser!
That's a nice expression, Seto!
Go to hell, Noah!
Stand up, Kaiba! Don't give up!
Keep your mouth shut, Deadbeat!
I don't need you of all people ordering me around!
Kaiba! You jerk!!
Big brother!
An argument amongst friends?
Human beings are known to become weak of heart right before they lose everything.
Seto, I think I'll put you out of your misery and finish you off.
You agree, don't you Mokuba?
Mokuba-kun, are you alright with this?!
Doing all this to Kaiba-kun?!
Haven't you and Kaiba-kun always helped each other out, no matter what's happened?!
Isn't your bond with him absolute?!
He couldn't have cracked the seal on his memories...!
Mokuba!
This turn very well might be my last.
There's no way I can fight you.
As long as you're by my side, I can continue to fight!
And that won't change, neither now or in the future!
Mokuba, bring them back!
Surface your memories!
All that awaited us at the Kaiba home was a living hell.
I thought of giving up
countless times.
But then you gave me your cards.
They're all trashy cards...
That was what saved me.
While staring at the paper card you made for me, I swore to myself...
That I would get the real one someday!
That the card was the best suited card for a real man!
Big brother...
If you hadn't made that card for me, I would have been done for.
But do I really deserve that manly card, and to be your brother for that matter?!
My turn!
My deck is linked directly to Mokuba!!
I place one set card!
I'll then activate Kaiser Sea Horse's Deck Master Ability!
My Twilight Dragon counts as two Tributes!
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!!
Blue-Eyes!
Big brother!
Mokuba!
Big brother!!
Why am I...?
The seal on his memories broke...?!
Mokuba! Get away from him!
You were being controlled by him, OOH-AH!
Noah! You...!
Now's your chance, Kaiba-kun!
Take this, Noah!
BURST STREAM OF DESTRUCTION!!
All right! Noah's Life Points took a serious hit!
And Option is automatically destroyed the moment Vic Viper is!
Seto, I praise you for being able to injure me this much!
But I'm invincible!
Ark of Miracles!
Life Restoration!!
Shit...!
Noah's Life went up again...!
And here comes your end, Seto!
My turn!
I've been waiting for this moment, Noah.
This is where we truly settles things between the two of us!
What?!
Me or you - who will win?!
This is the final round!
Trap Card, activate!
Last Battle!
What?
Last Battle's effect...
I select a Monster on the field
I then send every card albeit the one I chose to the Graveyard!
You are then to Summon a Monster from your deck that will engage in battle with mine!
This card makes it so that whoever's Monster remains alone on the field automatically wins the Duel, regardless of their Life Points.
So it basically determines the outcome of this battle.
Kaiba's taking a huge gamble here!
Naturally, I'll be choosing...
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
I'll choose my Deck Master,
the Ark of Miracles!
Noah, take mine and Mokuba's anger!
Go, Blue-Eyes!
Toward our future!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
He did it!
Just kidding.
What in the...?
What's...?
That's hardly enough to beat me!
Be gone, Seto!
Big brother!
Have you forgotten, Seto?
That this was the seventh turn of the creation of Heaven and Earth?
It's the turn that my Deck Master, Ark of Miracles, activates its final Special Ability!
My Deck Master has revealed to you its true form!
Shinato, King of Heaven!
And, as creator,
I rise to the throne of God!
Noah's body...!
This is my true form!
Last Battle automatically disregards our Life scores.
That battle just now determined the outcome of our Duel!
Seto, the result is here!!
Father, are you watching?
I just proved that I'm better at Seto in everything!
Big brother!
I'm so sorry! It's all my fault!
Mokuba...
Seto! Mokuba! I hereby deliver onto thee Heaven's Judgment!
Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun!
Mokuba-kun!
Mokuba!
How lovely!
A pair so close, yet never able to touch one another.
I hereby give this piece of art the name, "Wonder Brotherhood"!
Kaiba-kun... Mokuba-kun...!
You bastard! You toyed with Kaiba's feelings and went so far as to use Mokuba as a shield!
Doesn't your heart hurt, even just a little?!
It was all a part of my studies!
All for my complete victory!
"Complete victory", you say?!
You're the one who lost in this Duel!
What did you say?!
If Kaiba had played Twilight Zone Dragon in his turn just now,
the Monster wouldn't have been able to be destroyed in battle!
If Kaiba hadn't Summoned Blue-Eyes, he would've prevailed by the effects of Last Battle!
Kaiba through away his desire to win and Summoned his Blue-Eyes out of love!
So he could get Mokuba's heart back!
Noah! If that was you up there, would you have chosen the same thing?!
A sad child who can't even comprehend the basics of human nature wanting to run Kaiba Corporation...?!
Don't make me laugh!
You worm!
Kaiba still has some of his Life remaining.
If you want to be the true victor, battle with me now!
Huh?!
Oh? So you intend to take over Kaiba's Duel in such a situation?
I'll inherit Kaiba's entire deck, along with Mokuba's sadness!
Very well then.
Don't be reckless, Yugi! You're talking his 7400 Life Points against your 400 here!
And you don't even have a hand, OOH!
You'll be beaten in one attack!
If you wish it so, I'll be happy to dispose of you, Yugi Mutou!
Stop this, Yugi!
Yugi!
Noah, I won't let you get away with tarnishing Kaiba's and Mokuba's names with your cold-blooded heart!
DUEL!!
With Kaiba-kun's deck and only a few Life Points to fight with,
Yugi engages in a Duel with Noah.
Noah reorganizes his deck with a new type of Monster known as Spirit Monsters to attack Yugi with.
Yugi sees their Special Effects for the first time!
You have to stand strong, even with such little Life and as you're beaten to a pulp, Yugi!
A chance will come sooner or later!
Next time!
"The Inherited Deck: Yugi VS Noah"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise