Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Kaiba, you told me your past is nothing but anger and hatred...
But no one's past is meaningless!
The past, present and future
are what holds you together!
You can pile hatred on hatred,
but it's fragile!
Kaiba, I will defeat you!
As a rival who walked the
road of battle with me...
And as a friend!
"The Deadbeat's Road of Flame:
Jounouchi VS Kaiba"
Kaiba...
Hatred does not lead to true victory!
You had to lose to me...
so you can defeat your own madness!
My...
My Battle City...
The hatred
gouged into me by Gozaburo...!
My monument of revenge...!
Standing at the top
of the Duel Tower...!
Yugi...!
All I ever wanted
was to defeat you...!
My...!
...title of Duel King...!
I...
...lost...
Th-The winner...!
Yugi Mutou!!
Yugi!!
Yugi!
Yugi-kun!
Guys!
Jounouchi-kun!
You did it, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun...!
I believed you'd come back!
Damn right!
It'll take way more than that
to topple Jounouchi the Great!
At least until I fight you as
a True Duelist, anyway.
Right!
Thank goodness!
Really! Thank goodness!
Did you guys see that?
My Red-Eyes stayed on the field with Yugi
'till the very end and won it for him!
It's not yours anymore!
Don't you worry!
I'll get it back soon enough!
I really thank you from the bottom
of my heart, Jounouchi-kun!
Is this the end for me...?
Don't lose, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Didn't you always used to tell me...
...there's always a chance, as long
as you got cards in your hands?
My hand?!
Don't give up, Yugi!
That's what it means to
be a True Duelist, right?
You gave me your power that moment,
along with Red-Eyes!
I can't believe my brother lost...
You're lying...!
This has to be a lie!
My ultimate, untouchable deck...
My strongest servant...
There was no flaw in my strategy...!
My deck should have been
perfect in every way...!
And yet, I lost...
Kaiba...
It's true that I won and you lost.
But there's no difference in our strength!
Is that supposed to be pity, Yugi!?
I recognize your skills as a Duelist!
But let me tell you this...
What you lost to...
...was the Monster called "Hatred"
inside your heart!
What?! The Monster called "Hatred"?!
The Monsters drawn on the cards
we Duelists wield in battle aren't
the only demons in a Duel!
The anger in our hearts...
Hatred...
Desires...
Our worst enemies are inside us!
Only when you overcome all of that...
...can you walk the road to
becoming a True Duelist!
True Duelist...!
And for me, that...
...is Battle City!
Jounouchi-kun is still fighting
to find that place!
Fighting to become a True Duelist...
Fighting to be worthy of his Soul Card!
Kaiba, I would have lost if I didn't
have the Red-Eyes in my hand earlier...
The Red-Eyes!?
The Flute of Dragon-Summoning
lets you Special Summon Dragon-Types
from your hand!
But that effect wasn't just
limited to your hand!
It affected the ones in my hand as well!
The Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
The Soul Card
Jounouchi-kun gave me!
My friend lent me this card.
I won through
the power of my friends!
Yugi...
The power of your friends?!
Nonsense!!
To me, victory is only meaningful
if you've won with your strength
and your strength alone!
That's the only way to win!
I'll never need the power of a friend!
Kaiba...
I was able to win this long
because I had a rival like you...
Striving for a higher place...
Kaiba... I know you feel the same!
If that's true...
Rival and friend...
Where is the line
that separates them?!
A friend's power, you say?
I need nothing of the sort!
I need nothing
but the future I believe in!
To obtain glory
with my own strength!
No! It all means nothing unless I can!
I don't need any one else's strength
on my road of battle!!
Kaiba...
But boasting is the
privilege of the winner...
My Battle City has ended...
I'll keep quiet
and step down for now!
The Ante Rule...
...means this card is yours!
The God Card...
The Great War God Obelisk...
Let's go, Mokuba.
Big brother...!
Hold on, Kaiba!
Duel me!
Sorry about your loss, pal...
But how 'bout
a battle for third place?
Ya jerk!
Didn't I say to hold up?!
What kind of joke is this...?
You don't need a friend's strength,
is that it?
Heh! That sounds just like
how I used to think a while back!
Just hearing those words
would piss me off to no end.
But, you see...
I changed after I met Yugi.
"What you can see, but cannot see."
It's friendship!
I learned that after meeting Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun...
And I'm going to defeat Yugi
in order to prove that friendship to him!
As a True Duelist would!
That's what my Dueling is all about!
It's my Battle City!
I'm different from you, who thinks it's
all over just because of one loss!
Keep this in mind...
I'm in no mood to listen to the
pathetic jokes of some deadbeat...
Jounouchi! I'm not gonna stand here
and let you insult my big brother!
Shut up!
Then tell me, Mokuba!
How about you?
What do you mean by "how about you"...?
How is the feelings we share
amongst friends any different than
how you feel about Kaiba?
Oi, Kaiba!
I honestly thought a man of your caliber
had more of a backbone than this...
But maybe I was mislead by all your
bragging and the cocky attitude?
Say anything more and
you're going to regret it!
Then it's settled!
Duel against me, Kaiba!
Dueling against someone like you
wouldn't benefit me in the least.
It would be a
complete waste of my time.
You sure got
the bragging down good!
But no matter who it is,
I will take on any Duel challenge!
That's my tenet!
Now that's what I'm talkin' about!
Jounouchi...
Big brother...?
A "True Duelist" doesn't need
the power of a friend!
I'm going to show you just how wrong your
ignorant way of thinking really is!
Okay! Right back at ya!
The Final will feature Malik and Yugi.
The moment of destiny
is fast approaching.
You want to be a True Duelist?
Allow me to show you just how
small your chances are.
Okay! I'm all set here!
Ready when you are!
Do you think
Jounouchi will be okay?
He's been this way
as long as I've known him.
He always used to pick fights
with guys stronger than him.
Chew on this, ya bastard!
But Jounouchi-kun's gotten
a lot stronger himself, wouldn't you say?
He has.
Jounouchi-kun has come this far,
after battling against many
formidable enemies in his Duels thus far.
Wyvern!
Use your Dragon Sword!
Damage the player!
Trap Crush!!
Go! Kung-Foo Fighter Ultimator and Swordsman of Landstar!
And he even fought on equal footing
with Malik's dark personality.
Here goes!
I sacrifice three Tributes -
Lava Golem, Panther Warrior
and Rocket Warrior...
...to Summon Gilford the Lightning!
Gilford the Lighting's
Special Ability activates!
There's no question in my mind that
Jounouchi-kun's ability has
increased in the process!
It isn't all that far fetched
to say he can defeat even Kaiba!
I know you can, Jounouchi-kun!
My turn! Draw!
Killing off a deadbeat like you
will take but a few seconds!
I'm going to show you how great
the gap in our skill level is.
I Summon Gargoyle Powered!
I'll then place two cards face-down!
Turn over!
My set cards are
Deck Destruction Virus of Death
and Shrink.
Next turn, my Deck Destruction Combo
of Death will spread the deadly
virus through your entire deck!
My turn! Draw!
Sweet! Nice card!
Gearfried has more
Attack Points than his Monster.
It's my attack!
I Summon Iron Knight Gearfried!
Yo, Kaiba! I see you got two
reverse cards set on the field!
They're probably cards meant to
screw with my Monsters,
but you better hold your horses!
Equipment Magic
won't work on Gearfried!
Nice! I don't get why or how,
but Jounouchi's actually thinking
for a change!
But I kind of feel like if it's Jounouchi-kun
thinking about it, it may be
too soon to take seriously...
Huh?
Where'd Anzu-chan go?
Anzu...?
She probably just
went to the bathroom!
Okay! Keep em comin', Jounouchi!
Hell yeah!
Gearfried! Go on and attack
the Gargoyle Powered!
You put on quite the performance
for a mere deadbeat commoner!
Reverse Magic, open!
Shrink!
You were right on the mark!
Shrink is a Magic Card that halves
the Attack Power of one Monster
on the field!
However...
I won't be using this Magic Card
on your Monster!
What?!
This isn't good! This strategy is...!
You fell for it!
The moment your Monster attacked,
my Trap Card, Deck Destruction Virus of Death, was activated!
Now all Dark-Attribute Monsters with
1500 Attack Points or more...
...will be infected with the virus!
Including your Monsters
on the field, Jounouchi!
Your deck is about to be destroyed!
I knew it!
Deck Destruction Virus of Death destroys all
Monsters on the field, in your
hand and in your deck
with 1500 Attack Points or more!
It's a Sure-Kill Combo!
My Psycho Shocker...!
Gilford the Lightning, too...!
Damn it, Kaiba!
Now your deck contains nothing
but weak Monsters.
Heh, but that's rather suiting for
a deadbeat loser like yourself!
What?!
You can make all the moves you want,
but I can already see the
end result of this match.
If you're going to surrender,
it's now or never.
Don't be stupid!
Nobody's gonna surrender when
they just got started!
Hmm... This is going to be quite
a tasteless Duel...
It's my turn. I draw.
I don't have a single
Monster on the field!
This is really bad!
I Summon La Jinn
the Magical Spirit of the Lamp!
Hey, hey! Jounouchi's field
is wide open, isn't it?!
Not good! Not good at all!
Let's go, La Jinn
the Magical Spirit of the Lamp!
Direct Attack on Jounouchi!!
It's you...
Sister...
Malik?!
You're Malik, aren't you?!
Jounouchi...!
Shit...!
Thanks to that virus, the only Monsters I have in my hand have low Attack Power...!
My turn! Draw!
Angel Dice!
Good!
I Summon the Swordsman of Landstar!
And then a Magic Card!
I activate Angel Dice!
Angel Dice is a Magic Card that increases the Attack Power of a Monster based on the number rolled on the die!
I get it! Because Jounouchi can't Summon Monsters with high Attack Power,
he's going to use the die roll to try and raise its Attack instead!
But La Jinn has 1800 Attack Points!
If Jounouchi-kun doesn't roll a four or higher, he can't beat it!
Don't let me down...!
Goddess of Luck!
YEAH~!!
Angel Dice rolled a four!
So Swordsman of Landstar's Attack Points will quadruple in strength!
Awesome! He really got a four!
Man! Just how lucky
can Jounouchi-kun get?!
That's Jounouchi-kun for you!
Close call!
I barely raises his Attack Points higher than his Monster...!
Your a man who
depends on nothing but luck.
Let's do it! Swordsman of Landstar, attack La Jinn Magical Spirit of the Lamp!
Get it?! A little virus ain't enough to take down someone as great as me!
As they say,
"An idiot can't catch a cold."
The other night...
My sister...
Big sister!
Rishid...!
Malik!
Save Rishid from that man!
You appeared before me that night
in order to get Rishid out of harm way.
You've been hiding within the girl's
mind this entire time, haven't you?
You're right.
You, big sister, as well as myself...
I heard everything through
the ears of this young woman.
When you told the abominable truth
behind the Ishtar's tragedy.
I think this thing accepts me...
Put that down immediately!
SHUT UP ALREADY!
Malik, you bastard!
I can't move...!
Let's start with your bloodbath,
my dear father.
Stop it...!
Why have you kept the truth
from me all these years?
Malik...!
The fact that it was the dark personality
I gave birth to that murdered Father.
You were aware, were you not, big sister?
About this very Battle City...
About the Pharaoh's battles...
About the Ishtar's...
No, about my destiny as well.
The Millennium Tauk showed
all of it to you, right?!
I...!
I just thought that, even if you were
controlled by the desire for revenge...
As long as you lived on,
that destiny could be changed!
But my heart has long since
been engulfed in darkness.
I'm not a strong human being!
If Rishid hadn't been beside me, I...!
Malik...!
I won't let my dark side
do as he pleases anymore.
I'm going to dispose of him
before he does any more wrong!
Wait a moment, Malik!
Where do you intend to go?!
Sister, take care of Rishid!
You can't go there!
Malik!
Because of Kaiba-kun's
Deck Destruction Virus of Death,
Jounouchi lost his Monsters
with high Attack Power!
But Jounouchi will never give up!
He's still chasing after Kaiba-kun!
As for me, still under the control of Malik's memories,
I'm forced to fight against Malik's dark half!
What's gonna happen to me?!
Next time!
"Blue-Eyes White Dragon VS
Blue-Eyes White Dragon"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other