With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
We are…
The guardians of the labyrinth…
The Labyrinth Brothers!
Welcome to our Labyrinth Field!
This…
The Wall Shadow has been trapped!
We’ll show you that we’re the greatest tag-team pair out there!
Let’s go, Yugi!
We’ll win this with our combined strength!
"The Three God Demon Trinity!
The Gate Guardian"
Just wait for me, Mokuba.
It has been quite a while, Seto-sama.
Saruwatari, eh?
It’s tragic that we must meet again under these circumstances.
Don’t think you’ll get off easy for betraying me.
I am but a servant of Industrial Illusions.
Now then, I shall escort you to Mister Pegasus’ castle.
So you're gonna bring me there dead?
If you resist, I will have no choice but to retaliate.
Wanna try?
Then, die!
W-what?
A card…?
Thanks to you, my valuable card’s all messed up!
Damn it all!
If you try anything weird, it won’t be pretty.
Well then, how about you take me to where Mokuba is?
The only monster I have is The Axe Raider.
But it won’t be enough to help Yugi.
Okay then! I summon The Flame Swordsman in attack mode!
I’ll move it 4 spaces forward.
I’ll also move The Axe Raider 4 spaces, putting it on the same space as The Elf Swordsman.
After its Trap Effect ends, The Chained Boomerang becomes a normal Equipment Card, increasing his Attack Power by 500.
I end my turn!
So the prey has gathered together, eh?
My turn!
Advance, Labyrinth Tank!
This tank specializes in murder.
Soon, they’ll become its sharpening stones.
And they’re also near the Trap Card containing the Jirai monster.
Can you survive our labyrinth’s traps?
My turn!
I Summon The Black Magician in Attack Mode!
I’ll move him 6 spaces, in front of The Elf Swordsman.
Now our party has gathered.
Now then, what will you do?
So they aim to crush through the labyrinth with their numbers and attack strength, eh?
My turn.
But that’s all useless.
This card will break your combination.
I play this card!
What the heck?
The Labyrinth is changing shape...!
Damn it! They split our party up!
Now we’ve split their units.
And it’s common knowledge to attack the weaker player in tag matches.
So our target is…
Him!
Shit, it’s my turn.
Calm down, Jounouchi-kun.
Okay.
Advance, Flame Swordsman and Axe Raider!
You fell for it!
Trap card, activate!
What?
Jirai Gumo, the Landmine Spider, eats The Axe Raider!
Due to Jirai Gumo’s Trap Effect,
The Axe Raider’s Attack Power is drained back down to 1700!
What?
The Axe Raider has been defeated!
Jounouchi…
Damn them and their dirty tricks…
That’s not all.
My turn!
Advance, Labyrinth Tank!
And I’ll set one more monster.
The Flame Swordsman has been blocked off by The Labyrinth Tank.
It’ll be killed off next turn.
And I still have The Dungeon Worm face down.
Well, what now?
This is bad…
At this rate, they’ll kill off The Flame Swordsman.
My turn!
I’ll play a Magic Card!
The Magic Box of Death!
I’ll use it as a combo with The Black Magician!
-What?
Swords?
He killed own monster! Why would he do that?
No, look!
There’s one more box now...
I don’t see the Landmine Spider!
His heart has been pierced!!
-What?!
That’s right. The Black Magician used The Magic Box of Death to teleport .
By sacrificing one opposing Monster, it teleports to where it was, starting up a counterattack!
Yugi, thanks!
The Black Magician attacks!
Black Magic!!
The Labyrinth Tank has been defeated!
We’ll show you that our combined strength can overcome anything!
Open it.
You know, we’ll be busted eventually.
Just open the damn thing.
Big brother…
My turn!
The Thunder God Sanga card?
He can be fused with his water and wind-based brethren and become one guardian.
The other two are The Wind God, Hyuuga and The Water God, Suuga.
When they combine, the Demon Protector, Gate Guardian is born!
What are you dazing out over? Hurry up and get on with it!
Have patience.  I set this card and end my turn!
I see now.
What is that?
I dunno what that is, but I’ll probably find out as I get close to it.
My turn!
I’ll send The Flame Swordsman on ahead.
I end my turn.
I can’t let them exit the labyrinth until The Gate Guardian is on the field.
My turn!
I set one card face down.
What are those coffins?
I don’t know.
They’re waiting, and setting something up on the field in the process.
I guess we have to fear more than just the Labyrinth Field!
Do those coffins hold a yet-to-be-seen threat in them?
All that is needed is The Wind God, Hyuuga.
Might as well scare off their attack force.
I flip my set card, The Dungeon Worm, into Attack Position!
I also play this face down card; Plus!
It raises his Attack Power by 400 points!
What did you say?!
Damn, where is he hiding?
What?!
The Elf Swordsman has been swallowed by The Dungeon Worm!
Don’t screw with us! All you’ve been doing is cheating the entire game!
That’s right! You're just trying to slowly torture us!
This…
Is the true strength of the Labyrinth Field!
What now, Yugi?
If it comes from beneath us, then we can’t attack it.
My turn!
To counter that, I’ll play The Magical Silk Hats!
I’ll use it in combination with The Black Magician!
What?
They hid their monsters!
Nice! Now they’re hidden away from that earthworm monster!
The Magical Silk Hats is a card that is used in combination with The Black Magician to trick opponents.
In two of these hats are The Black Magician and The Flame Swordsman.
The Dungeon Worm’s Attack Power is 2200.
If he hits the 2500 Attack Powered Black Magician,
it’ll be suicide.
Then on my turn, I’ll play this card.
I Summon the Hellbeast Controller, Monster Tamer in Attack Mode!
What is the meaning of that card?
Normally I can’t control The Dungeon Worm, which is my younger brother’s monster.
But The Monster Tamer brings up the Worm’s Attack Strength by 600 and allows me to control the card on my turn!
The enemy has higher Attack Points than The Black Magician!
If he’s attacked, he’ll lose for sure!
Dungeon Worm, come on!
The odds are 50/50!
A miss?
What a lucky save!
He may have missed, but he’ll attack again with Dungeon Worm on their next turn!
It’s only a matter of time before he loses!
What should I do?
My turn!
You know, I really hate small and dark places.
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi, what are you scheming?
Feel the wrath of this card!
The magic card, Salamandra!
When this thing is equipped to a Fire Element Monster, its Attack Power is raised by 700.
Go, Salamandra!
What?
I see.
Right now, The Monster Tamer’s Effect is inactive, so The Dungeon Worm’s Attack Power is only 2200.
So the flames of Salamandra can go into the earth and crush the worm!
Later, earthworm monster!
Alright!
Good job, Jounouchi-kun!
-Alright!
My younger brother, don’t drop your guard!
Understood!
My turn!
Finally!
I’ve drawn it!
Good!
Now our victory…
Is certain!
I summon Wind God, Hyuuga! With this, our victory is assured!
W-What?
The Fused Trio Demon Gods…
The Gods of Thunder, Water, and Wind!
Now's the time to gather your power and revive!
That's...!
What is that?
Come forth, Triple Demon God!
GATE GUARDIAN!
Gate Guardian…
That thing’s amazing…
What is that?
The God that guards the two doors of the labyrinth.
“The God that guards the doors?” So in other words, if they can’t defeat that…
Yes. There is no escaping otherwise.
So this must be the boss character of the Labyrinth Field, eh?
Then let's do this!
Too bad for you!
Before you were able to escape our maze…
We were able to summon the great protector, Gate Guardian!
You can no longer escape!
You have no other option…
Except your loss to us by the hands of the Triple God Demon!
Shut up! Quit it with the idle jibber-jabber!
You guys will have to fight our combined power first!
Here I go!
COME!
Still farther?
If you’re worried about Mokuba-sama, then don’t be.
I guess a brotherly bond is truly strong, eh?
Enough with the idle talk.
I see. So you always helped him out any trouble.
After losing your parents early on, you were able to continue on because of your brotherly bond. Touching, isn’t it?
I thought I told you to cut the goddamn chatter!
Well, well, my apologies.
Don’t worry. We haven’t touched your precious little Mokuba-sama.
Just a little farther on ahead.
Big Brother!
We’ll always be together, right?
I don’t want to be separated from you!
Don’t worry.
Okay. It’s a promise, right?
Yeah. I promise.
Don’t worry. My brother will keep his promise.
My brother and I won’t be separated by anything!
Right here.
What do you mean?
I’ll only be leading you up to this point.
What?
You bastard!
The Goddess of luck can smile on anyone.
Soon, the guards will be here.
You scum!
You must really think you can win, huh?
We’ve found Seto Kaiba.
He’s inside of the castle, and relatively close to here.
I know.
Everything goes according to plan!
We’ll capture him, and bring him here immediately.
There’s no need.
Please stop the alarm.
It’s annoying, and I can’t think with them on.
I’ll go meet Kaiba boy in person.
Is it.. my brother?
Good luck, Yugi!
Don’t you dare lose, Jounouchi!
For my turn, I set two cards face-down.
I end my turn!
My turn!
Gate Guardian, attack The Flame Swordsman!
I can’t run. What can I do, Yugi?
THUNDER SHOT!
"Preview"
Yugi and Jounouchi fight against The Gate Guardian, and manage to weaken it!
But, a monster like that does not fall easily!
At this rate, we’ll never be able to leave!
Yugi, Jounouchi, you have to combine together to win this tag match!
Go, Black Demon’s Dragon!
Next time! "The Dragon of the Devil; Black Demon’s Dragon!"
Duel  standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship