A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Toon Demon, you said?!
As long as ﻿Toon World remains on the field, I can't damage him in any of my attacks...
But I can't defend myself either...!
Is there any way I can win in this situation?
No!
You cannot possibly defeat me.
If I give up now, all three of
their souls will he lost forever.
Even if my chances of victory
are low, I still can't give up!
It is no use, Yugi boy.
No matter how hard you struggle,
you are still finished.
"The Counterattack Begins!
The Mind Shuffle"
Black Magician in Attack Mode!
Also...!
Magical Silk Hats!
By using the Black Magician in combo with the Silk Hats, I may be able to stop Pegasus from reading my attacks...
I see.
I'm sure you plan to use this to stall time to
find out a way to stop my Toon World...
But I am afraid that is a waste of time.
Yugi boy...
Your conscious will tell me which Silk Hat you hid Black Magician in.
So that means by you knowing, I am also able to learn which hat he is hiding under.
I'm going to guess that you hid the Black Magician under the Silk Hat to the very left.
I knew it...! He read through me...!
Are you prepared, Yugi boy?
Not even the
Silk Hat combo works against him...!
I can't find a way to defeat
the power Pegasus' Millennium Eye...!
Yugi! Don't give up!
Yugi, don't lose...
Don't lose!
Toon Demon!
Attack one of the Silk Hats!
Black Magician has been reduced to ash.
Why?!
Black Magician's data didn't disappear!
The card is still on the board!
Unbelievable!
Are you telling me that I somehow managed to miss the Black Magician?!
Impossible... I should have read Yugi boys mind perfectly...!
I was able to hide the location of the Silk Hat Black Magician is hiding in...
...using my subconscious!
Looks like you couldn't read the other mind, my mind, after all!
You are...!
Another mind of Yugi boy!
That is...
Anzu... what does he
mean by "another mind"...?
A seperate... mind...
Not long ago, Yugi told me himself he had another person inside himself.
What do you mean by that, Yugi?!
I didn't tell you guys, but the me that Duels isn't the usual me.
I'm always resting in my heart.
I change to my Other Self to fight.
And I just watch from within my heart...
But in this Duel, I couldn't just stay hidden
and watch as my other self suffers!
Not even the
Silk Hat combo works against him...!
I can't find a way to defeat
the power Pegasus' Millennium Eye...!
Other me!
Please! Can you hear my voice?
Other... me!
That voice just now...!
This voice came from within my heart!
This voice is...!
My... other self!
He's calling me!
Other me!
You finally heard my voice!
It's the first time we were able meet in
our hearts. I can finally speak to you.
Until now, my voice never reached you,
no matter how loud I screamed.
I could feel it when you were hurt in battle but I couldn't do anything to help.
But if finally reached!
Why did you call me?
Please! Let me fight too!
You can't handle Pegasus' power by yourself!
But... there's no way to fight against
the power of his Millennium Eye...!
What if...
Pegasus is able to read your mind...
But... maybe he can't read mine!
That's it! If Pegasus can only read one mind at a time...
Maybe if we fight him with two minds...!
Will you lend me your strength?
Yeah!
You may find it hard to believe...
Since I solved the puzzle, me and my other
self have been taking turns at living.
Actually, sometimes I feel like
I have another me inside myself.
Well, that doesn't really matter.
Because Yugi is Yugi.
That...
This "other Yugi" he was talking about wasn't
just his imagination, but it actually exists...?
Multiple personalities switching places?!
Uh, is that what they call....
uhh... split personalities, right?
Is that true?
It's my turn.
I'll play this card face-down on the board and end my turn!
Pegasus, do you know what the card I just drew and played face-down on the board is?
Just try reading my mind.
You'll know once you do, right?
Of course.
Mind Scan!!
Why!?
There's no image of the set card!
Sorry. but... I don't know what that set card is either.
Reading my mind is pointless, Pegasus!
His mind just switched again...!
Pegasus, it seems to take you quite a large amount of time to read the opponent's mind with your Millennium Eye.
I switched minds while you were busy trying to read me.
The way to beat your Millennium Eye is...
...the Mind Shuffle!
Mind Shuffle...?!
That's it! Yugi's using
two minds to fight against him.
Even if Pegasus reads one of them, he can
just switch minds so the other can fight!
Alright! He can do it! He can do this!
You bastards! You no longer have anywhere to run!
Let's play a game!
If your weapons are those steel guns...
...my weapon will be these cards.
What kind of bullshit are you going on about?!
Just give yourselves in!
I've seen this expression before...
That time, it was the other Bakura...
That wasn't just a dream...!
It's my turn!
Man-Eater Bug!
This is...!
What is that?!
He made something appear!
Monster!
It's not working!
And with that, your turn has come to an end.
What's going on?
There's no Duel System around here, and yet they're materializing...
Then next is my turn.
I'm going to save you mortals from the Man-Eater Bug!
Although... Your situation now
may be even worse.
Just who is this guy?
Ow...
Th-this is...
Now then, it's your turn, Pegasus.
Unbelievable!
The Black Magician's location in the hats... even that set card...
For it all to be concealed
by the other Yugi boy's mind...
But...
As long as Toon World remains on my side of the field, your Monsters cannot attack me!
The Black Magician can only hide in the silk hats for three turns.
Pegasus, then pick the correct Silk Hat
and annihilate the Magician!
Or are you just a coward
who can't trust your own ﻿intuition unless you
rely on your Millennium Eye?
Now that you mention it, it has been several years since I relied upon my own instincts...
Toon Demon!
No! I missed again!
What a pity. You've missed again.
Pegasus, since you're the creator of Duel
Monsters, l'm sure you're aware of this.
Every game has to
have a winner and a loser.
So... What do you suppose seperates the two from one another?
It's good judgment needed to know the rules and assess the situation of the game...
And the instincts
to decide when and how to act.
Whoever has these two things is the winner.
Judgment comes from experience and confidence...
Instinct requires divine courage.
But you've relied on the Millennium Eye's power for far too long.
And you've lost the instincts of a Duelist.
When it comes to true courage, my partner is far superior to you.
Here I go!
They switched minds again...!
It's my turn now!
This is a card I can use.
I'll place this card face-down and end my turn!
It's your turn.
I can't see the idenity
of those two set cards...
I don't know what these two set cards are...
But... I believe in the cards my other self played!
My turn.
Great!
My card is Magic Neutralizing Force!
I will activate this card's effect on your side of the field!
This card wipes out the magic effects of every
card on the opponent's side of the field.
In other words, the magical effects of your Silk Hats will disappear!
Dammit! Black Magician has been exposed!
And this is "the end", Yugi boy.
Skilled Duelists don't need instincts.
They use their brains to strategize,
and to avoid taking risks.
Come forth, Toon Demon!!
Only a Toon can defeat a Toon Monster..!
Toon Demon will destroy the Black Magician with that attack!
Toon Demon! Attack Black Magician!
Now!
The other Yugi...!
Set card open!
Magical Effects Arrow!
What?! The Magic Effect Arrow?!
Pegasus, you didn't notice, did you?
While I was drawing cards, the other me was trying to stall you.
What?!
And once you got frustrated, you tried to play a card ﻿that would take out the effect of Magical Silk Hats.
But that was what we were aiming for.
Now all magical effects sent our way are sent to you at the same time!
Pegasus! We're using the Magic Effects Arrow to return ﻿the effects of Magic Neutralizing Force to you!
But you're too late! You can't stop
The Toon Demon's attack!
Black Magician is defeated!
Too bad!
Huh...?
The other card I set...
The Trap Card, Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
A Trap...!
And the magical attack passes through ﻿the barrier and takes out Toon World!
The Toon Monsters return to their original forms and appear on the field!
NO!!
Unbelievable!
My.... my beloved monsters have all...!
This is a nightmare! A bad dream!
No!! This cannot be reality!!
All right! All the Toons were destroyed!
Yeah! It was your courage
that defeated the Toons!
To think Yugi boy's two minds could overcome my Mind Scan...!
Alright! You did it, Yugi!
Yugi...! If you combine your two hearts ﻿together, you can beat Pegasus!
You can save your grandfather
and everyone else!
What's going on?
Just what the hell is happening here?
I remember, Bakura.
That wasn't just a dream.
You aren't Bakura!
You're the other Bakura from deep within Bakura!
I feel so honored that you remember me.
Now hand over Mokuba!
Like I'd hand him to you!
Are you looking to become a sacrifice for the Power of Darkness as well?
Power of Darkness...?
Wonderful!
Exactly what I would expect from
one chosen by the Millennium Items.
It seems I was
playing around far too much.
I must now face you in this Duel
with the power and respect you deserve.
Yugi boy, from now on,
this will be
a fight between two people chosen by the Millennium Items.
Let's settle this in a Dark Game!
Dark Game?!
Locked in the darkness, Yugi and Pegasus continue their battle.
So this is a Dark Game?
I don't believe it, but this isn't a dream!
Just what is happening inside this giant sphere of darkness?
We can feel Yugi's in great pain...
But there's nothing we can do!
Next time!
"The Evil Eye is Activated: Sacrifice"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship