Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Kaiba, are you fighting against Zorc?
But even the Ultimate Dragon isn't enough to beat Zorc.
In that case, I decided to fuse the remainder of my Ba
and bet the situation on Master of Dragon Knight, but...
We still weren't able to defeat Zorc.
Partner, you're our final hope!
"In the Name of the Pharaoh!!"
The light of hope...
That's right... I can't give up yet!
I believe in my friends who came here to fight alongside me!
Fool! Haven't you figured it out?
What grows the darkness...
It is humans who give me eternal power!
What...?
In the midst of light, the only way for men to know themselves
is to turn to the darkness and see their own shadow!
Without my darkness,
you humans would be mere drones, never questioning your own existence...
The never ending wars and slaughter among men...
They are the instincts of mankind,
the regular adjustments
needed to sustain life!
Shut up...!
As such, with my powers I will create a world of eternal darkness!
I'll give you mortals an endless Hell!
SHUT UP!!
Pharaoh! See your land perish with your own two eyes!
Then fall into eternal darkness!
I... won't let myself fall here...!
Partner!!
Other Me!
Yugi!
Part... ner...
I know you all.
You all came here to tell the Pharaoh his real name!
But you shall not!
Other Me!
Yugi!
Partner...
Guys...
It's them!
Damn are they persistent!
Other Me!
This Duel Disk contains the deck you used to fight with!
Each card in this deck
is filled with our spirit!
Partner...
Here I come, Zorc!
Come forth!
Black Magician!
Mahado...
You have rescued me
from the parallel world.
You have given me life once again.
You have my gratitude!
Black Magician!
Awright.
Then count me in too!
Go!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Me three!
Me four!
I Summon Rare Metal Knight!
I Summon Fire Sorcerer!
So that's what you guys are!
Counterattack, Black Magician!
Go, Red-Eyes!
Magic Blast!!
Black Fire Bullet!!
Fire Sorcerer!
Rare Metal Knight!
What?!
Shit!
Let's try again!
Are these guys immortal or something?!
There won't be any end to this!
Master!
Black Magician Girl?!
Is that Mana?!
That girl was able to call out a spirit...!
Master!
Mana!
Prince's friends!
Let us take care of this!
Hurry and return to Prince!
Okay!
Please do!
We will not let you pass!
Magic Blast!!
Yugi!
You okay?!
Stay with us!
Other Me!
Partner...
Guys...
Can you stand?
Hang onto my shoulder.
You will not!
Mana!
Yes, Master!
Magic Blast!!
You little magicians are an eyesore!
Partner, did you find my name?
Well...
Partner...
I see.
You guys managed to find the Pharaoh's true name,
but you are unable to relay that truth to him!
What?!
None of you are able to read the Pharaoh's name hidden within the hieroglyphs!
Is that true?
I'm sorry, Other Me.
Zorc's right.
But I remember what the shape of those characters are clearly.
It's just that I don't know how to get that information to you.
Now that it's come to this, we have no choice but to beat Zorc ourselves.
Right!
Go on!
Red-Eyes!
Black Fire Bullet!!
You're done for!
Honda-kun!
Damned fools!
Be gone!!
Jounouchi-kun!!
Anzu!
When our Monsters were destroyed, we lost a lot of Life!
Does that mean our lives will end when our Life reaches zero?
Guys...
Mana, release the rest of your Heka.
Are you prepared?
I am!
Don't do it, Mahado!
It will end the same,
no matter what you try!
You cannot possibly defeat me!
Zorc's power is just too great...
With our strength alone...
You will perish within
the fires of Hell!
Zorc Inferno!!
We believe in you, my Pharaoh!
Prince!
What a pity it is, Pharaoh.
At the very least, you get to be destroyed alongside your friends!
Isn't there a way to
give Yugi his real name?
This ends here. Give up!
Zorc! I won't give up!
There... There must be a way to get the Other Me's real name to him!
Partner...
That's...
Yugi, please take this.
This is...
A Cartouche pendant.
If you regain your memories and remember your real name...
I hope you'll carve it on there.
There is a way!
A way to tell you your real name!
What?!
Everyone think of those ancient characters!
Visualize it written on the Cartouche!
That's it!
This is the Memory World!
Everything we imagine becomes reality!
Come on! We have to combine our strength as one!
Cool!
Yup!
Yeah!
Be gone, Pharaoh!
Along with the friends of your memory!
Just a little more...
Keep trying!
Yugi!
Other Me!
If this is the last of your hope,
I will strip it from you with my Power of Darkness!
Defense Ring!
You're...!
Do not get in the way!
Partner!
Guys!
I've got it!
Yugi!
Other Me!
Right now, the seal on the Pharaoh's name has been broken!
My name is...
ATEM!!
Atem...
That's your real name...
My son! Justice is in
the name of the Gods!
Father!
The Pharaoh is the living embodiment of the Gods!
Unite the Three Illusionary Beast Gods in the name of the Pharaoh!
Zorc...
With my friends, I can now call forth the Gods!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Obelisk the Great War God!
Ra the Winged Dragon Sun God!
Awesome...
The Three Illusionary
Beasts are back together.
Try again, but it will end the same!
The Three Illusionary Beast Gods are no match for me!
And right now, in the name of the Pharaoh...
...the Gods will join as one!!
This is...
It kinda feels nice...
It's a kind light...
Yeah...
It's warm...
The Creator God of Light...
Horakhty!!
Horakhty...
Disperse the darkness!!
Djeseru!!
["Sublime Light"]
DAMN YOU!!
I-It stopped...
Yeah, I'm all right...
Have we... been saved?
The clouds... disappeared!
She did it!
She beat Zorc!
Yeah...
I always believed Yugi'd beat him.
Are your wounds doing okay, Yu-
Right...
You aren't "Yugi" any more, huh...
I guess I can't call you "Other Me" anymore...
No, I'm fine if you call me as usual.
Mm-mm...
Atem...
That's your real name.
My real...
Atem...
3,000 years ago, you defeated Zorc with your strength alone.
Horakhty...
Then, you chose to kill yourself along with the sealing of Zorc.
But when Zorc revived this time...
You...
Friends who protected you... comrades who cared for you appeared.
That is the true power that defeated Zorc.
If one person's strength alone is not enough...
By combining the power of everyone, the impossible may become possible.
Atem...
It has a strange feeling to it...
I've always carried the name "Yugi" from my partner all this time...
But now things are different.
Atem... That is my name.
Now I am me...
And you are nobody but yourself.
It's kinda sad...
But I'm glad for you.
Anzu... Thank you.
Your Cartouche saved me.
Yeah...
Partner...
Honda-kun...
Jounouchi-kun...
Anzu...
It's because all of you found my real name that I beat Zorc.
I am truly grateful!
C-Come on, man! That's lame!
Atem-kun!
We're friends, dude!
Yup!
Even if your name changed, it doesn't make things any different!
Right!
Kaiba!
Kaiba-kun!
I never thought you'd come to this world.
Don't try to write this off as magic, pal!
There's two Yugis here, you know!
Surprised, ain't you?
Hmph! Like I'd be surprised now after everything I just went through!
For someone who hates occult stuff, you're sure taking this well.
I don't want to hear a lowly deadbeat talking down to me.
Y-Ya jerk!
That again?!
The darkness has been destroyed...
But... we paid way too much of a cost...
And many irreplaceable lives were lost in the balance.
Every living person must keep a light for the fallen in their hearts...
And yet work to build a better future...
Seto...
Yes?
I have a favor to ask of you...
I want you to inherit my throne and become the new Pharaoh!
What did you just say...?
I want you to become the new Pharaoh!
What are you suddenly talking about?
Why do you think I risked my life all this time...?
I am no longer needed in this world.
I have no memories beyond this point...
So I no longer exist in this world...
I have no time left.
I must go now.
Pharaoh...! Your body...!
Seto, you did not give in to the High Priest of Darkness.
You kept the light in
your soul in the very end.
You repelled the darkness admirably.
The light in my soul...?
I leave you the proof of being Pharaoh, the Millennium Pendant.
You will now become Pharaoh and rebuild this country!
Pharaoh...
I'm counting on you, Seto.
It's okay now, right?
Yes.
Awright!
Then let's head home.
Goodbye!
Prince!
Goodbye!!
Pharaoh...
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Zorc has finally been beaten.
The other... I mean, Atem...
...has regained all of his memories!
But what awaits us in the real world is...
Yes, parting with him.
I understand, but does he really have to return to the Afterlife?
And Malik tells us about the Battle Ceremony on the ship
that will return him to the Afterlife.
Next time!
"The Final Trial"
Duel standby!