Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In my Lost Memory World exists Ancient Egypt from three thousand years ago.
A fierce battle between the High Priests and the Thief Bakura was taking place there.
How they each Summoned Monsters to fight was exactly like what Duelists do!
If that's true, I'll Summon the Three Illusionary Beasts...
...and Bakura, I'll beat you!
"Mahado's Resolve"
He... forced the God to retreat?
It was a draw?
I didn't think that he would summon the gods so soon.
If I didn't have that gift from Kaiba...
King, we'll finish this match in the next turn!
You there! You're Mahado, right?
The Millennium Ring you're strutting out on your chest...
That belonged to me originally.
No... I'll be taking it back really soon.
I won't let a lowly thief like you touch my Millennium Ring!
Don't get so worked up!
Eventually, I'll collect all of your Millennium Items!
Later!
Bakura!
Don't let him get away!
Soldiers, give chase!
- Yes, sir!
I'll see myself out!
Bakura...
That's...?
Pharaoh.
Is something wrong?
What... is that?
I don't see anything.
Do you both not see it?
I see nothing.
What did you see, Pharaoh?
Nothing...
What exactly is that?
Is it related to the Dark Game?
The Pharaoh's godly power...
A Ka capable of fighting on equal footing with God?
So the Gods are not necessarily the greatest...?
Seto...
Pharaoh, I'm glad that you are fine.
Burst Stream of Destruction...
Why does Bakura have
the power of Blue-Eyes?
The connection between Blue-Eyes and me...
Words coming from an occult fanatic like Bakura...
...hardly catch my attention.
But... those sad cries of Blue-Eyes...
This can't be... stop!
What... was that?
I'm well aware...
Things like fate...
Things like connections...
I won't be deceived by false sentiments based off of nonsense not supported by science.
But if I ever want to come to terms with these illusions...
Still no word of Bakura's whereabouts?!
No, sir.
However, I have mobilized the soldiers to expand the search area.
The city around the palace, the desert and even the gorge...
It would be impossible for him to through a net this wide.
Yes, but Bakura's Diabound has such terrifying power.
Had the Pharaoh not been able to wield the God...
...the power of us priests would not have been enough to win.
God...
I have an idea... Lord Akhenaden.
There must be people living in the city who have Ka within them.
We should capture those people who look promising...
...and develop their Ka to turn them into powerful weapons!
You're mad!
There is no way any commoners wield stronger Ka than we possess!
But that terrifying power of Bakura's Diabound...
Suppose that power really was born of his hatred...?
You may not know about this...
But if you place the seven Millennium Items on the stone tablet in the village of Kul Elna...
One can gain the powers
of the underworld!
He knows about what happened to the village of Kul Elna...
If he really is a survivor from that village, he no doubt harbors massive hatred.
Lord Akhenaden.
Like Bakura, there must be hatred residing in the hearts of thieves and criminals.
There might be a Diabound amongst them.
Or rather, we might find a Ka that is even more superior than the Gods.
We mustn't.
Using hatred to create Ka is such a terrible thought.
We are doing all of this for the Pharaoh.
We can reduce the
number of criminals as well.
Isn't this killing two birds with one stone?
Seto...
In order to let the country prosper, I don't mind staining my hands with blood.
I heard that my father, who died on the battlefields, was such a person as well.
It didn't work...?
Ever since Bakura appeared, the future is shrouded in shadows.
But I must look through this darkness, and prevent the disaster that befalls the palace.
Please don't push yourself too hard.
In the battle with Bakura, your Ba was greatly reduced as well.
Recovering your Ba is also crucial in preparing for the upcoming battles.
You need rest, Isis.
Thank you, Kalim.
However, Shada, my Millennium Tauk is the only thing that can foretell Bakura's next move.
For the sake of the Pharaoh and the citizens, I will not rest.
Everyone...
Partner...
Which one is the True Door?
More doors appear each time we open one.
There's no end to this.
And my watch has stopped moving from when we were in front of the stone tablet.
You're right!
See?
Are we really able to get out from here?
Wait, that's the one!
I have a very strong feeling about that door!
Cool!
We can only depend on Jounouchi's intuitions at times like this!
Hell yeah!
Ah, wait!
You're shittin' me...!
Help!
O-Oi~!
Huh?
We've saved!
There are traps behind doors as well.
You must be careful.
You should have said that earlier!
But how are we going to find the True Door amongst so many doors?
Maybe Yugi is the only one who knows which door it is.
After all, he's the one who's closest to the other Yugi's soul.
Hey, do you sense anything?
I don't know...
But this place gives me a feeling of loneliness.
As though his heart has been sealed...
Maybe this is the loneliness that the other me is feeling.
Everyone here knows who I am.
But I don't recognize any of them.
As Pharaoh, do I really understand them?
And do they understand the real me?
Pharaoh.
You are...
I'm pretty sure he's...
Mahado.
Pharaoh, how can you be alone in a place like this?
Considering what happened yesterday night, please be more cautious.
You're right, I was wrong.
I'll be more careful.
Ah no, that's not what I meant...
Who's there!?
Mana, what a thing to do!
Stand away from the Pharaoh!
Master, I heard everything!
What's with that?
Why're you acting all weird like that?
You and Prince are alone right now.
You should talk to him like how you used to in the past!
He's not "Prince"!
He's "Pharaoh"!
In the past?
Did you know me in the past?
What are you talking about?
The three of us have always been together.
Learning magic and sparring with each other.
We were as close as real siblings!
We sure had fun together!
Y-Yeah... You're right.
Huh? You're really Prince, aren't you?
There's something... different about you.
Stupid girl!
He's the Pharaoh now!
The prince is carrying great responsibilities that none of us can understand!
Ah, you called him "Prince", Master!
I'm really sorry, Pharaoh.
That aside, how did you come here?!
My magic skills have improved a lot, right?
Binding Spell Technique?
Y-You fool! Undo that at once!
Do you plan to make the palace defenseless?!
Oh... Oops!
Huh?
What's wrong? Hurry up!
The removal spell...
Err...
Please wait a second!
That's enough, I'll do it myself.
Mahado... Mana...
At least I exist in their hearts.
I do have friends.
The seven Millennium Items...
Maybe it's a little tough
to get them all at once, huh?
It's alright as long as I get all seven Millennium Items in the end.
With that, I will know what the Eighth Key that opens the Door to the Underworld is.
If so, I guess I should start by taking the Millennium Ring.
How could you do all this, Bakura...?
Mister Holy Priest!
What's wrong?
Is the city going to burn again?
Do not worry.
I won't let that happen to the city or its civilians again.
Bakura.
I won't let the people suffer anymore.
How boring!
I wanted to get Master to practice magic with me!
As a Priest, Mahado is very busy.
You just have to be more patient.
I got it, Prince!
"Prince", huh?
Oh, whoops! I meant "Pharaoh".
No...
Mana, can you... say my name?
What are you talking about?
Prince is the Prince, right?!
No, I mean the Pharaoh.
You don't know my name?
Well, the Pharaoh is the Pharaoh...
And the Prince is the Pharaoh...
But the Prince is the Prince... eh?
Mahado.
Isis...
Did your Millennium Tauk sense Bakura in any way?
Still nothing...
Did your Millennium Ring sense his presence?
No, it couldn't sense a single thing at all.
Is that so...?
There's no reason to worry.
The future will smile upon the Pharaoh.
Yes...
Darkness...
It still depicts Bakura's evil intentions.
No... A burst of light is piercing through!
Mahado...
Pharaoh.
I, head of the security force, will be heading for Akhenamkhanen's tomb...
To conduct a ceremony to reinstate the barrier of the tomb.
I'll leave it to you.
If you are to fail again, your position as Holy Priest will most likely be removed.
And if Bakura were to appear, you'd better not take him on alone.
He's not someone the likes of you can deal with.
Priest Seto, you speak too recklessly!
Mahado, please protect my father's tomb.
Yes, my lord!
I want to go, I want to go!
I want to go, too!
I want to protect Master!
Come now, Mana!
Ow, ow...!
You are Mahado's student, yet you do not trust him?
That's not it.
But he'll be vulnerable when he's setting up the barrier!
That's why I wanted to go!
Mana, you really don't understand your master.
Mahado is Egypt's number one...
No, even if you looked all over the world, you wouldn't be able to find a better wizard.
You need not worry.
Master Shimon...
That's right... He sealed off a portion of his powers because he was too strong.
But if he were to release all his powers...
He would most likely be more powerful than any of the other six High Priests.
Mahado.
Isis...
You won't change your decision?
You saw my future, didn't you?
Don't say anything further.
Please protect the Pharaoh.
Even so... the one who will emerge victorious... is you.
Pharaoh...
Here!
Thank you!
Prince!
Mahado!
A-Are you all right, Prince?
Please don't let this bother you-
Hold still.
Prince, please stop!
One who will become the Pharaoh doing such a thing...
Just what is the difference between me and you?
Like how you have red blood flowing through your body...
I too have the same red blood flowing through mine.
We're the same, aren't we?
Prince...
In the future, there will be a world where everyone is equal and living freely.
I plan to show you it!
The new world that the Prince was talking about...
It may be idealistic, but you will surely make it into reality.
That's why I want to protect you.
The Valley of Kings
should be on the left path...
Keep quiet and continue walking!
We just need to keep following Lord Mahado!
In order to defeat his Diabound,
I need to unleash the entirety of my magical powers... my Heka!
I'll probably use the forbidden ritual in this battle.
Come on, Bakura! I know that you are following me!
I'll accept your invitation, Mahado.
Pulling such tricks...
I've been waiting for you, Bakura!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
While we were wandering around in the maze of the heart in the Millennium Puzzle,
A fierce battle between Priest Mahado and Thief Bakura is taking place in Yugi's Memory World.
Mahado went to challenge Bakura due to his total loyalty towards the Pharaoh...
But Bakura's Diabound has become stronger than before!
Will Mahado be able to win?
Next time!
"Battle to the Death! Mahado VS Bakura"
Please look forward to it!