The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
The Beautiful Harpie Lady
Two hours have passed since the Duel's started.
Yugi boy...
can you make it to the castle?
Alright!
Now it’s my turn to Duel someone!
I wonder if Jounouchi's really OK?
Because most Duelists here are very good.
Guys, come here!
It’s really amazing!
He's too loose...
Did he think we came here to hike or something?
It's beautiful...
Big brother, I wanna see the ocean!
Yeah, I'll take you there!
Hey, big brother.
What if mom gets mad at us?
Don’t worry, let me worry about that.
Big brother!
It's pretty!
So cold!
We should come back someday.
But...
Even though our parents are divorced...
...It's alright! I will bring you back here.
You promise?
I promise.
Shizuka.
I promise you.
I will let you see that beautiful ocean again, for sure.
Look!
Amazing!
Here and even there...
Everyone is Dueling already.
I have to also...
You'd be best off finding yourself a weak opponent.
Right. Right.
Jounouchi-kun...
You have to choose your Duel location carefully.
'Cuz the Field you pick can give your Monster Cards an advantage.
Right, Yugi?
Most people will know this rule by now...
Where's the best Field for Jounouchi?
Most of my cards are Warriors and Beast-Type Monsters.
So, I think the Meadow.
Then, this place would be Jounouchi's territory.
If possible, only move around this area.
Come on! Gimme your Star Chips and get lost!
That loud voice is...
Mai Kujaku!
Tell me.
How did you know what your cards were when you couldn't see them?
That is...
A se-cret.
A secret.
I'm getting so close to the prize!!
That woman already has 6 Star Chips?
Yugi-chan!
How are the Duels going?
N-Not bad.
So you have 3 Star Chips, Yugi-chan?!
Maybe we should Duel?
Yugi, beat this woman to a pulp.
OK, I've decided who I should challenge to a Duel now.
My opponent should be...
Jounouchi-kun!
'Scuse me?!
Me!?
Are you gonna run away, boy?
Thanks for acknowledging me.
Don’t get me wrong...
As a Duelist, I would rather fight against Yugi-chan.
So, isn't it true that if I lose my Star Chips I'm done for?
To get more Star Chips, I'll Duel against opponents who appear weak.
Then, I will fight Yugi-chan after that.
How can you say that to someone who was in the Best 8?
In the local competition, right?
You can't beat this woman!
Don't you realize it's all over if you can't beat her?
Yugi, accept the challenge in Jounouchi's place.
Jounouchi-kun, you just gotta do it!
I knew Yugi would say something like that.
Yugi!
Jounouchi!
Are you serious?
If I say I'm serious, I'm serious!
From now on, if I run away from this...
...when I look up at the sky...
...expanding to the mountains, or the sea...
...Every time I remember seeing that sight with all of you...
...I will remember this cowardly side of me.
I see... I get it. Sorry Jounouchi.
But you better win!
I accept this Duel.
That's what I'm talking about.
- Jounouchi, fight!
- You can't lose!
OK!
Jounouchi-kun.
You seem to have just 1 Star Chip, boy.
...then I will bet on only 1 Star Chip as well.
If I lose this Star Chip, I'm finished.
Crap!
This field is...
The layout of this fighting Field is...
40% Mountain and 40% Forest...
...and the left-over 20% is Meadow.
Jounouchi-kun, calm down.
It's OK! You can still use the Meadow as an advantage!
Mai Kujaku...
...I wanna ask you one thing before we Duel.
What?
What did you come to this island for?
For fame? Or maybe the prize money?
Both.
Of course, If I get the prize money, I will travel around the world!
Maybe buy a house in France, buy all the luxuries!
For something so worthless?
What the hell does that mean?
Then, why did you come here!?
There’s something I need to protect.
Something that's more important to me than my life!
Jounouchi-kun, show her the difference in your points of view.
Duel!
It's my turn.
The Legendary Swordsman Masaki.
He gets a Power Up from the Meadow Field Source!
Now, it's your turn.
Why aren't you looking at your cards?
It’s a simple reason.
I know what all my cards are.
Impossible!
What did she say?
Here I go, my card is...
Harpie Lady!
She gets a Power Up from the Mountain Field!
I'll take you on!
Go!
No, Jounouchi-kun!
Harpie Lady has the ability of flight!
Monsters with the ability of flight...
...hold a magical advantage over Monsters that walk on the Earth!
What do you mean?
Masaki’s Attack and Defense Power returns to 1100.
It's your turn, boy.
She's not looking at her cards again!
- Jounouchi...
- Does Jounouchi really have no chance of winning?!
Jounouchi-kun.
Don’t be caught by her card trick!
How can she know what those
cards are without looking at them?
That boy seems to be lost due to my card trick.
He’s completely lost himself.
Tiger Axe!
His Attack goes up because of the Field Power!
He'll kill Harpie Lady in a stalemate!
Jounouchi-kun, you forgot about it's magic flight!
Right, Tiger Axe’s attack won’t have any effect!
You can't beat my Harpie Lady with cards of that level.
It’s my turn.
Every turn that passes...
...Harpie Lady will become more charming, beautiful, and stronger.
She played her tricks again...!
What is that?
Now I should defend.
My turn now.
I Equip Harpie Lady with Cyber Bondage!
The Demon Hunter...!
You get it yet?!
Boy, don’t you get its great impact yet?
How can she identify her cards without looking at them?
Is this woman an esper?!
No! Jounouchi-kun, calm down!
Don’t lose to Mai Kujaku's card tricks.
Keep trying, Jounouchi!
You can't lose to that cheeky woman!
You, over there...!
I remember you saying that...
...your hearts are passed through to the Duelist.
Show me an example... Let your "hearts" actually allow this boy to win.
No way...
Don't 'ya get it?
It's impossible.
You have to remember this, too, boy.
If you only fool around with your friends, you aren't a true Duelist.
Even your friends today...
...could become your enemies tomorrow.
This is what a Duelist is.
A Duelist cannot trust anyone but themselves!
You have to remember the Duel today, and remember your loss.
That girl...
I can't stand this! I can't stand this anymore!
Jounouchi-kun will show you just how wrong you are when he wins.
Yugi.
Jounouchi-kun.
I'll only say one sentence:
"Something you can see, yet cannot see."
Something you can see, yet cannot see?
That boy can't win with a sentence!
But it's interesting.
Show me how it works.
I don’t get it.
But...
It's friendship.
Me and you know what the treasure is...
But you can't see friendship, right?
But no matter what, I can’t win.
Sadly, I won't be able to see your face anymore.
I wanted to see your face one last time!
Shizuka...
I'm such a useless brother...
I can't even heal your eyes going blind.
Dammit!
Is the world of blindness really this dark?
I won’t let you live in a world like this.
What's that smell?
I couldn't smell it with my eyes open.
There's a bunch of different aromas mixed together...
Now boy, it's your turn.
I got it!
I figured out her card trick!
She sprayed a different perfume on each card.
So she has to smell to find out what card it is.
Cards can be seen...
...but that smell cannot be seen.
Something you can see, yet cannot see.
You're lying!
I can’t believe that boy could figure out my aroma tactics!
Before the game...
...I was tricked by you completely.
I was 100 percent scared shitless because of it...
But I won’t be falling into your trap again.
You dirty woman!
Jounouchi-kun.
Jounouchi!
Go!
Yugi, thank you!
You found out my trick...!
But you're still a hundred years too early to beat me in cards!
Unbelievable.
Once my friends are supporting me...
...I treat you as a vulnerable opponent.
Although you're a hundred years too early to understand.
Here I go.
My card is the Baby Dragon.
That card is...
What is that weak looking card?!
Leave it, that card won’t decrease my Life Points.
I play the Kaleidoscope card.
This card will make three copies of Harpie Lady!
Wha--What?
Harpie Lady one~
Two~
Three~
There’s more and more!
No way! And he just had the upper hand...!
Jounouchi, don’t give up! There will be a way!
Like what?
Don’t ask me.
Right, Yugi?
It’s too early to tell.
There’s no way to defeat the three Harpie Ladies.
The Harpie Lady Beauty Combo!
Because of this card, they get more charming and stronger...
...but they can’t attack this turn because of Kaleidoscope.
It’s your turn.
But I doubt you'll pull something off.
I can’t win... I'm going to lose for sure!
Don’t give up, Jounouchi-kun.
Mai Kujaku has continually used Magic Cards to increase the power of Harpie Lady,
and then duplicating it into other copies.
But, within lies a weak point you can use to turn the tables.
A weak point to turn the tables...?
I get it!
Because she used those cards...
She doesn’t have any other Monster Cards besides the Harpie Lady in her Deck!
So, once I kill the Harpie Lady, she’ll have no more strategy.
Yes, Jounouchi-kun.
Once more:
"Something you can see, yet cannot see."
Something you can see, yet cannot see?
Now that you mention it...
Salamandra...
Chain-Equipped Boomerang...
Baby Dragon and...
Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand!
With these Magic Cards, you'll get a way more powerful strategy.
Really?
Right, use this one too.
I think it'll give you a hand when you're in trouble.
Right.
Before...
The Millennium Puzzle Box.
The Puzzle that can be seen, but cannot be seen.
Then, it should be the Time Magician!
Why is he staring into space?!
Hurry up and draw a card already!
I don’t have the Time Magician card though...
...I can only hope for it...
...before the Baby Dragon is destroyed.
Please!
Jounouchi-kun.
Believe in your cards.
Here I go!
That's...
Alright! Time Magician!
The Time Magician?
Don’t you know?
We’re going to Duel in another dimension 1,000 years in the future.
Baby Dragon is now the Thousand Dragon!
Jounouchi-kun, that’s not only the thing that the Time Magician does.
Time Magic!
Thousand Dragon arrives!
What the hell?
My Harpie-chan holds much higher Attack Points than that dragon!
Triple Harpie Ladies, kill it!
What?
My Harpie-chan!
They're so old~!
Didn’t he tell you?
1,000 years have passed.
The Harpie Ladies are getting old, and are losing their Attack Power.
Mai Kujaku, for you...
...losing your beauty is the cruelest defeat you can get.
I was surprised by that, too.
Alright, let’s go!
Thousand Dragon!
Thousand Nose Breath!!
Alright!
It’s a miracle!
Jounouchi wins!
Yugi!
I can't believe... I can't believe I lost to a guy like him...!
Mai Kujaku!
Although I am not a Duelist...
...I have to tell you this.
It doesn’t change, even after 1,000 years.
"What can be seen, yet can't be seen."
Jounouchi-kun.
You have a different way of thinking than Mai Kujaku.
That was the key to winning.
I’m hungry.
The organizer of the tournament should've prepared some food! Pegasus is so cheap!
Using the smell of grilled fish to tempt us...
...Appears the Duelist of the Sea, Ryota Kajiki.
Using the Sea Stealth Attack to strike when the opponent is not aware...
Yugi is in a desperate situation!
How can he fight against an unseeable opponent?
Next time, The Sea God Leviathan.
Duel Standby.
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship