Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
So you came, Yugi...
I was a little concerned that the shock of losing Jounouchi would break you...
...but it seems I worried over nothing.
This is our fated Duel!
My Obelisk? Or your Osiris?
The time to settle this has finally come!
And I'll defeat you, Yugi, and gather all three God Cards!
And I'll show you all that I will obtain the title of Duel King!
"The Three Knights Used to Call God"
Using the effects of Exchange, I add Osiris to my hand!
I'll return it to you for now...
But I'm the one who's going to gather all the God Cards in the end.
And even if you're holding the god in your hands, you can't do a thing to play him.
My Obelisk is sealed on the field for another two turns...
But...
...once I complete the XY-Dragon Cannon's Ultimate Fusion, it'll blow away all of your Monsters.
I won't let you sacrifice three Monsters to Summon God to the field.
Two turns for me, on the other hand, is more than enough.
The moment the Lightforce Sword wears off, God will descend!
It's true I got the Osiris card back into my hand...
But Exchange was a dangerous gamble...!
Exchange allowed each of us to take a card from the other player...
You choose one as well.
Life Shaver...
It forces the opponent to discard cards from their hand equal to the amount of turns it was face-down on the field.
A Hand Elimination Card.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack Points are determined by the number of cards in my hand...
If he uses the Life Shaver
to reduce my hand,
it will be rendered useless, regardless of whether it's a god or not.
There's no doubt about it... Kaiba will play Life Shaver face-down this turn!
Okay, Yugi! It's your turn now!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Big Shield Gardna
in Defense Mode!
I then set a reverse card!
Turn over!
All I can do for now is try to defend myself against XY-Dragon Cannon's attacks.
Hmph... Looks like
defending is all you can do!
I can crush you even with my god sealed!
Two more turns.
Kaiba will most certainly
Summon Obelisk the second
Ligthforce Sword disappears.
Once that happens, Yugi will have
no hope of Summoning Osiris.
Nor will he have any chance of winning.
Yugi...
Don't disappoint me now...
You must continue to grow
before I sacrifice you
to the depths of darkness...!
It's no fun crushing someone
who's already half-dead!
You must writhe in
more pain before that!
And I'm going to make you suffer
the ultimate pain, Yugi!
I'm starting to get the creeps...
Anzu-san?
No... Forget about it...
Anyway, Honda sure is running late.
The engine in the Battle Ship
took quite a hit.
Maybe even the radio is down.
Does that mean a
rescue helicopter won't come?
Then... big brother will...!
Relax, Shizuka-chan!
Mokuba-kun will find a way!
But...
He's right. For now, we just have
to wait and believe in him.
Okay...
Yugi...
Sweet! It's my turn! Draw!
I did it! I'm the best drawer around!
I Summon Axe Raider in Attack Mode!
Attack Petit Dragon!
Eh!?
Hell yeah! Now your Life Points hit zero!
I win!
Dammit! This sucks!
I did it! I made it to the second round, Yugi!
Uh... Honda!
An... zu?
Where'd Gramps go?
What the heck... Don't tell me they
didn't stay and watch my match...
Those guys are heartless...
Man...
Guys?
Where'd you all go...?
This is the Battle Ship speaking!
Hey! Someone answer me!
No good, huh?
Wouldn't it be faster to just
fix the Battle Ship's engine?!
We've got someone working on it.
But it'll take a long time.
There's got to be something we can do!
Rishid... The gods are about to arise once again...
Destiny has continued moving
for the past 3,000 years...
And their fight has begun.
Fate itself has forced them to clash.
Right...
Destiny began to
make its move on that day...
That's...!
Yugi!
And the image carved above him is the Black Magician!
And the one standing
beside their king, the Pharaoh...
He is known as the "White Beast Handler".
And the creature carved above him is without a doubt...
The Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
The young Pharaoh controls the Magician of Black Magic...
And one of his own priests, The White Beast Handler.
This palette depicts a Duelist battleground that took place several millenniums ago.
This is what I believe.
Perhaps fate itself leads the souls
of the king and priest depicted here to battle in present day.
Even now, after 3,000 years pass.
What bullshit!
This is nothing but crazy talk!
I overestimated you.
Look closely at the top of the mural.
The three depicted atop the palette, from left to right...
The Great War God Obelisk.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon.
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra.
The Three Illusionary Beasts.
In our present day and age, they have come to be known as "God Cards".
God Cards?
Pegasus created the three rare cards after viewing this palette.
You probably have heard rumors of them.
It is said that whoever acquires these three rare cards
will become a legend among the world of Duels, and be granted the highest ranking Duelist's title...
The title "King of Kings".
Finally...
This card.
That's...!
The Great War God Obelisk!
This is the only card out of the three that was not stolen.
In order to retrieve the other two, I am entrusting you with the Great War God Obelisk.
You're entrusting me with this card?
Are you sure you can trust me that much?
What will you do if I retrieve the rare cards...
...and refuse to give them back?
I trust you.
The battle between
those chosen by the God Cards has
been going on for 3,000 years.
And no one knows
how this battle will end.
Which one of them will achieve victory
and their goals along with it?
Which one of them
will invoke God first?
And what will occur after that?
All we can do is silently watch.
No matter what happens...
Kaiba...! Kaiba...!
Before he can even
think of invoking Osiris,
my Monster will
crush all of his sacrifices.
However I do it, I won't let him Summon his god!
Because I'll be the one
to Summon my god first!
My turn! Draw!
Like strings to a puppet,
everything is moving exactly
the way I want them to!
I set a reverse card!
A reverse...! That card is
most likely Life Shaver...!
You no longer
have no chance of winning!
I hope you are prepared to lose, Yugi!
And now...!
I Summon Z-Metal Caterpillar
in Attack Position!
The third Magnet Monster!
The moment the Magnet Monsters
X, Y and Z are present on the field,
their Special Ability is activated!
And...
Fuse together, XYZ-Dragon Cannon!
2800 Attack Points...!
None of the Monsters on my field have enough points to defend against that!
Plus, the seal on Obelisk
will be lifted next turn...!
And he can use his XYZ
to Summon the god!
Not too shabby, Kaiba!
I'd expect nothing less of the man who defeated my elder sister!
XYZ-Dragon Cannon attacks!!
I'll destroy Big Shield Gardna
with this attack!
XYZ Hyper Cannon!!
I've destroyed all
your Monsters on the field!
Now I'll smash your soul
without a trace!
Kaiba, I knew from that start
that you'd destroy my
lower Defense Big Shield Gardna.
What?!
Now you've given me a chance to win!
Reverse card, open!
Trap, activate!
Soul Rope!
What...?
The moment my Monster is defeated,
this card lets me
pay 1000 of my Life Points,
and call one Four-Star Monster
out onto the field!
And the card I pick...
I Summon King's Knight!
And that's not all!
When the King and Queen
are both on the field...
"King" and "Queen"...
Don't tell me...
Correct.
I can Special Summon
the "Jack" card!
A three-Monster combo?!
Like your Magnet Monsters...
...my deck, too, contains Monsters
to help me Summon God.
Come forth! Jack's Knight!!
And now I have three
sacrifices on my field!
Even in this situation where I
was completely on top of this game...
Yugi somehow managed
to Summon God first?!
My turn!
Draw!
I offer three tributes to the Heavens!
Summon Osiris the Heaven Dragon!!
That's...!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
One of the gods has
finally been Summoned.
Now that was quite a surprise!
To think Yugi would be able to
Summon God first in a situation like this.
Fascinating!
Kaiba! It looks like the tables just
turned when I invoked Osiris.
Hmm, we'll see about that...
Take a look at your hand.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack Points are determined by the number of cards in the player's hand.
And this turn, your hand...
...only holds three!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon
has only 3000 Attack Points!
But your XYZ-Dragon Cannon has only 2800 Attack Points!
I can easily destroy it
on my attack this turn.
And if I do, you'll lose your sacrifice!
Thus you wouldn't be able to
Summon Obelisk next turn!
Then go ahead and try attacking...
So confident, even in his position...
Kaiba knows what will happen
if I destroy his XYZ-Dragon Cannon
with God's attack...
Is he hiding something?
There's only a 200 point difference
between Osiris and his Monster...
I thought his reverse card
must be the Life Shaver
that he drew from my hand...
But if he plays it after only
just activating it this turn,
I won't have to
discard a card from my hand!
Come on! what's the matter, Yugi?!
Go ahead and attack me!
Heh! Is Kaiba merely bluffing?
Or maybe...
Stopping God's attack so easily...
Stopping Yugi from
making a move because of
one mere reverse card...
You're not bad at all, Kaiba!
Whether you attack or not,
you won't be able to stop me
from achieving victory!
Suppose that reverse card
is a card that can raise
XYZ-Dragon Cannon's Attack Points...
Osiris could die!
But...
If I don't attack on this turn...
...he'll Summon Obelisk on his next turn!
And there's a good chance
he's just bluffing and that reverse card
is what I thought it was...
There's a good chance
that it's just Life Shaver...
In that case, I can't
back down at this point!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon! Attack!
I knew you would!
Thunder Force!!
Reverse card, open!
Interdimensional Matter Transporter!
So it... wasn't Life Shaver!?
I transfer XYZ-Dragon Cannon!
Thanks to this Magic Effect,
Osiris loses its attack target!
Its attack is wasted!
What...?!
What in the world happened?!
I'm not sure, but something just came out of the sky!
This is... the power of Osiris...!
What was that just now?
I have no clue...
Something must be happening
at the Duel Tower!
This is Kaiba Corporation speaking!
Please respond, Battle Ship!
Please respond!
The connection...!
We're connected!
They're sending a helicopter
as we speak!
Everything's gonna be fine now!
Yes! I'll go tell Shizuka-chan
and the guys!
All the radioactive interference is gone...
We can send video too!
Okay! I'm off to cheer
for my big brother!
What's that?
XYZ-Dragon Cannon... vanished!
It looks like your turn
was just wasted, Yugi!
So I see.
A reverse to protect
your tributes for God.
But... My turn isn't over yet!
I'll place a reverse card as well!
What?!
He's voluntarily playing
a card from his hand?!
Turn end!
That's absurd...! He only has
two cards left in his hand!
Does he not realize that
next turn I'll Summon Obelisk
with 4000 Attack Points?!
Come on, Kaiba! It's your turn!
XYZ-Dragon Cannon might even be
strong enough to destroy Osiris
without Summoning a god!
This turn it's my turn
to test your will, Kaiba!
Prattle on as you like,
but my next move is already decided!
Draw!
Since it's now my turn...
...Obelisk will return to my hand,
now that Lightforce Sword's effect
has finally disappeared!
I will show you God...
I offer XYZ-Dragon Cannon
as a sacrifice!
Obelisk, the God of Destruction!
Bend to my unshakable will!
And descend to my domain!!
Shake Heaven and Earth
with your unsurpassed power!
And bring me victory!
Summon The Great War God Obelisk!
Here it comes...!
Such massive power...!
I Summon the Great War God, Obelisk!!
So you've finally
shown yourself, Obelisk!?
The battle of gods has finally begun!!
The Great War God Obelisk...
What immense power swells inside it...!
My entire body is shivering
with anticipation and fear
like I've never felt!
Yugi...
The clash of these titans,
the gods, has finally come!
I will defeat your Osiris...
...and gather all the
gods into my hands!!
Along with the title of "Duel King"!!
The two gods have finally been Summoned!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon and The Great War God Obelisk!
Against such excessive power,the sky splits and the Earth trembles!
Both Yugi and Kaiba-kun deploy all of their strongest tactics in this fierce showdown between gods.
Again and again, they are met with a tie!
And just as the two gods are about to clash one final time,
something begins to happen!
Next time!
"Clash! Osiris VS Obelisk"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise