Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Driven by the darkness in my heart, I activated The Barrier of Orichalcos...
And lost the bond I had with my Monsters.
I fell into the trap set by Rafael.
Then, I committed a grave sin that I can't forgive.
Following my defeat, I lost something that was most important to me...
I lost my partner... who was someone irreplaceable to me!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Torn Soul"
Hurry up!
I'm peddlin' fast as I can!
If we let them get away...
...we will stay losers all our lives!
You two...?
Wait!
Let us join your team!
What are you talking about?
Despite how I look, I was the Regional Champion of Japan!
I was in second place that time!
If Mai Kujaku can become your comrade, we can too!
We beg ya!
Let us join you!
Anzu, that...
Everyone's back!
Yugi... Everyone!
They made it back safe and sound!
Darling!
Thank goodness! You won, didn't you?!
Yugi!
I knew you would!
Wait, things didn't go like what you think.
What do you mean?
Yugi-kun...
He didn't win.
Yugi... Yugi lost!
That's impossible!
But if you lose in a match with Doma, your soul will be taken away, right?
Like I said... It's already been taken...
But isn't Yugi standing there perfectly?
Don't tell me....
You're lying... You're lying, right?
Yugi!
Please swap places and let me see my Darling!
Rebecca...
I'm sorry.
Partner, he...
Partner!
I believe in you, Other... Me...
Partner!!
He sacrificed himself in my place.
Why... why?!
Aren't you just a soul
residing in Darling's body?
Why did you remain...
...while Darling's soul disappeared?!
It's all...
It's all your fault!
Give the original Yugi...
Darling back to me...!
Give him back!
Rebecca...
Rebecca is right.
Yugi...
Partner was against me using The Barrier of Orichalcos from the very start.
Still, I...
I'm going to activate this card from my hand!
I deserted my Partner...
Stop it, Yugi!
It's all my fault.
Didn't I tell you to stop?!
Jounouchi!
We still have a chance to get the other Yugi back!
What are we gonna do if you're all depressed like that!?
King of Duelists, Yugi Mutou! Where did all your pride go?!
But nobody has won against the three Musketeers of Doma so far...
You idiot, stop talking rubbish!
I'm so-sorry!
It's okay.
He's saying the truth.
Maybe we really don't have the power to defeat Doma.
Yugi...
Isn't this the center of the business district?
What're we doing here?
I thought since Doma's a shady group an' all...
we'd a' been brought to a secret hideout or somethin'...
So they really are hiding their motives behind such a huge organization, huh...?
What happens to the both of you...
...all depends on what the lord that you're meeting decides.
Please try not to be too impolite.
We have returned.
Lord Dartz.
By your orders,
I have taken the soul of the nameless Pharaoh into our custody.
You've done well, Rafael.
Pharaoh?
What da hell's that mean?
I truly wish I could praise you like that...
Looks like you've yet to accomplish this task.
Watch carefully.
What's that?
That's...
Yugi!
He's indeed "Yugi."
But not the "Nameless Pharaoh."
What do you mean by this?!
There are two personalities in Yugi Mutou's body.
One being the character of Nameless Pharaoh.
And the other one is the personality of the host.
Host...
Yugi's a nameless Pharaoh?!
Personality of the host? What's that mean?
Rafael...
You have indeed defeated the nameless Pharaoh.
But the one captured by the Barrier of Orichalcos was the personality of the vessel.
That means...
The nameless Pharaoh is safe.
Then, please give me another chance.
Hey!
R-Right!
Regarding that mission, please...
Let us do it!
Dumb ol' me...!
No, by that, I mean... Please kindly leave it to us!
You both are...?
Guess we're really nobodies in their eyes, eh...?
They are Insector Haga and Dinosaur Ryuzaki.
They claimed to be the first and runner up in the whole of Japan.
We're not "claiming to be"!
It's true!
We're serious!
We really wanna get stronger!
Ever since Yugi and Jounouchi appeared, we've...
Go, Demon!
Demon Lightning!!
Time Magic!!
What? What is happening?
My Red-Eyes was...
Ever since they've appeared, we've been humiliated constantly!
Our pride as Duelists was totally shattered!
We also wanna become strong!
Just once will do!
Please leave Yugi and Jounouchi ta' us!
We want 'em ta' see us differently!
Please!
Please also give us a portion of your powers!
I beg you!
Both Nameless Pharaoh and Jounouchi are Duelists chosen by the Legendary Dragons.
They won't be so easy to defeat.
That's why we need your power!
If we had power like that, even we'd...!
If you want to obtain our power...
...you must be mentally prepared.
For the sake of defeating them...
We'll do anything!
Very well.
Take this.
What's this?
Isn't this blank?
We're really serious!
I, too, am serious.
That's...
This is what injects "life" into the cards...
A shard of the Orichalcos.
A shard of Orichalcos?!
These shards will test the darkness in your hearts.
If you're worthy enough to join Doma,
you'll be able to obtain these shards.
However...
If you two are deemed unworthy...
...your souls will be sealed in these cards.
Souls?!
What's wrong? Finally chickening out?
H-Hell no I'm not!
We can't retreat here!
If we're afraid,
we'll always remain worthless!
Yeah, we shall do it!
Lets go!
Yeah!
It's impossible.
They don't have that kind of ability to begin with.
Can't...
I knew it, it's impossible for us to attain such powers...!
Idiot, don't give up!
So you're just gonna be a loser and let them take your soul away?!
Just a little more...
Damn! Shit!
We must get hold of this power!
So this is The Barrier of Orichalcos...?
With this card...
With that, the both of you are now members of Doma.
You can use any of the cards here.
Go on and create the strongest deck.
There's simply too many cards here!
Are there really all kinds of cards here?!
We have all the cards here except for the God Cards and the Legendary Dragon cards.
What is this, no God Cards?
Even if there are, you guys will never be able to use them.
Well... Even if there is no God Cards...
We're all good wit' the cards we got here!
Insector Haga... Dinosaur Ryuzaki...
With your new-bound power, show me the defeat of Nameless Pharaoh and Jounouchi.
The power of Orichalcos is now within the both of you.
-Yes!
You're saying that the aim of Doma is to clear the history of mankind?
It's true.
He did say that was the case.
But there's no way anybody could do that so easily!
That's right!
No, they can do it.
We have all seen how they can do it, haven't we?
Don't tell me...
I see...
They will be using that monster.
Having said that, The Three Musketeers of Doma said that they needed your souls before.
They want to use our souls as sacrifices to revive that monster
How can... we go against people like them?!
We better report this to the police or some other people who can deal with this!
That's pointless.
Because Grandpa's research lab was burnt down.
We have no proof to show.
Such absurd things... Who do you think will believe us?
You're right, but...
There must be some proof left of the underwater relics...!
That has already been claimed.
Is this Doma's doing again?!
It's true that if we have no proof...
We cannot give up.
G-Grandpa...!
Are you alright?
Sorry for making you guys worried about me.
I couldn't get back to sleep when I heard Rebeca crying.
I have already heard roughly the gist of what happened.
Professor.
Do you have any new insights?
Although I have not fully deciphered the cipher texts...
But the real identity of "Doma" may be from the ancient past...
They may be the decedents from the land called Atlantis that was considered to be a paradise.
It can't be...
By "Atlantis", you're referring to that rumored legendary city that was submerged underwater?
Atlantis is not merely a legend.
The relics found underwater contained texts that were historical records of Atlantis.
Which also meant that they are the history of the place.
Atlantis's history...
In the past, Atlantis was rather highly civilized and they controlled many lands.
The people there thus termed it as "paradise" and thought the peace would last forever.
But Atlantis was suddenly destroyed by a monster that was summoned by a certain king.
A certain... king?
Nameless Pharaoh...
There should be "darkness" that lies dormant within the deepest thresholds of your heart.
Can you dare say that you were a good king?
Yugi, is something wrong?
No...
It has been said that Atlantis has been passing a magical stone
that has been bestowed with the power of God down to their decedents.
So this is that stone that those guys have?
And then?
Unfortunately, this is as far as I could decipher.
Damn it all!
Why are you feeling so frustrated?
Because if you think about it...
They purposely destroyed the professor's research lab because of all this!
I know it!
I see! Those cipher texts may have contained some things that were unfavorable for Doma!
So that's why.
Jounouchi, at your mental level, such an intuition is quite remarkable!
But most importantly, the relics are...
Not to worry.
Florida Museum acted as a base for the studying of the relics.
There must be some research information that was left.
If that's the case, then there's still a chance for us to decipher the texts?
Lets go, Yugi!
We'll unveil the secrets of Doma.
And rescue the other Yugi, Mai and everyone else!
Those're some good words, Jounouchi!
Since we've decided, we just got to get there before Doma!
But it's quite a distance from here to Florida.
R-Really?
Our company's stocks have been falling since those Duel Monster's happenings.
And 40% of our stocks have been bought up by some unidentified person...
If this continues, our company...
Of course I know what's going to happen!
That aside, haven't you guys uncovered the true background of Doma yet?!
Those are the capital sources that have been trying to buy up the stocks of Kaiba Corporation!!
The mastermind must be somewhere!
I want you guys to find out where they are with all your might!!
Damn...
Big Brother...
Are you going to Duel with that guy again?
I can understand that guy's feelings...
This is a...
...memento of my little brother!!
My little brother was...
...killed by your company!
If something like that happened to you, I would have reacted in the same way as him.
So I wish you wouldn't fight him...
He's just thinking about his brother!
He's definitely not a bad person!
Mokuba...
If we don't defeat Doma, there will be no future for both Kaiba Land and Kaiba Corporation.
Big Brother...
What is it?
You have a phone waiting from someone referring to themselves as "Jounouchi-sama."
Jounouchi called?
From the deadbeat?
Put him through.
Yes.
Looks like we're connected!
Is that so?
Kaiba! I have a favor to ask from you!
Jounouchi...
You should be standing further away from the camera.
S-Sorry! Sorry...
What business do you have with me?
We got some clues about Doma.
Did you say Doma?!
The clues are in Florida Museum.
Please use your resources to bring us all there.
I'm begging you, Kaiba!
Please hurry up!
If you don't hurry up, the soul of the other Yugi...
Oi!
Are you stupid?! Jounouchi!
The soul of the other Yugi?
I-It's nothing!
Because Kaiba hates talk of the occult, after all!
That's right!
Yugi...
Don't tell me you lost!?
Wh-What are you talking about, Kaiba?
Don't mess around with me!!
You're saying that the Duel King title I gave you on the Duel Tower...
...has been taken away by some nobody we know nothing about?!!
Kaiba...
I've misjudged you, Yugi!
I've got nothing more to say to a loser like you!!
Big Brother...
Doma...!
But because of this, I now have one more reason to defeat you people...
Kaiba...
What's with... that bastard...?!
Shit!
If that's the case, we can only go there ourselves now!
Yeah.
It's better for the professor to continue resting here.
We'll proceed first and ascertain the research lab information.
Otogi, you'll join us later when the professor has fully recovered.
OK!
As for us, the means of getting to Florida...
The only way to get to the closest airport from here is by train.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Still recuperating from the shock of losing his partner, the other Yugi is unable to stand up again.
But we have to get him to snap out of it before dealing with Doma again.
We have to get to Florida Museum in order to protect the few remaining clues we have left.
So we head there by train.
Oh, by the way, we can't seem to find Haga and Ryuzaki anywhere...
I wonder where they went.
Next time!
"The Runaway Train Duel"
Duel standby!