Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
In order to bring back Mokuba's memories, Kaiba used his Blue-Eyes in the final battle.
But Noah took advantage of Kaiba's feelings and beat him.
Now he's turned the
both of them into stone!
Noah, I won't let
you get away with this!
I'll inherit both Kaiba's pride as a Duelist and Mokuba's sadness!
Let's battle, Noah!
If you want to call yourself the true winner, defeat me first!
"The Inherited Deck: Yugi VS Noah"
I'll be creating a new deck to match your deck type.
But Yugi... You use a Strategical Deck.
And Seto used a Power Deck, designed to call forth powerful Monsters.
You're mixing together two completely different deck types.
Trying to make a strategy with the both of your cards together will only serve to slow you down.
What was that light just now?
After Shinato appeared, the Ark of Miracles' Effect disappeared.
So all the cards used before have been returned to the Graveyard.
But even with the ark's Effect gone, Yugi still has no Monsters on the field and no cards in his hand!
And Noah's Deck Master
has 3300 Attack Points!
If Yugi doesn't draw a Monster Card this turn, Yugi's gonna be wiped out! OOH-AH~!!
Yugi!
Now then, Yugi!
It's your turn!
Don't tell me you decided to back out last minute.
I'll let you change
your Deck Master if you like!
That's not necessary!
I can feel it clearly... Kaiba and Mokuba's heart beat pulsing in this deck!
Here goes, Kaiba! Mokuba!
My friends, walk with me down this road!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Illusion Beast Gazelle!
Defense Position!
Good! He got a Monster out!
Just as expected, your luck is impressive.
No, you could call it "delaying the inevitable."
But regardless of whether you called a Monster out, if I get a Monster now, this Duel is done!
My turn!
Huh, too bad for you.
Seems you're going to have to wait a while before finishing me off.
My my absolute advantage
hasn't changed a bit.
I, Shinato, King of Heaven, will attack you!
Six Paths of Reincarnation!!
This can't be! My Monster should have been in Defense Position...
Why did my Life...?
Was it...?!
That's correct. Shinato's Special Ability just activated.
When Shinato destroys one of the player's Defense Position Monsters,
their Life Points halve as a result.
And thanks to Shinato's Deck Master Ability, the damage the player received gets added to my Life Points.
That Deck Master is totally unfair! OOH-AH-OOH!!
Damn it all! This Duel was hopeless from the start!
Yugi, I can't comprehend your suffering.
Why would you take on such a reckless Duel?
Are you and Seto not enemies?
You're right. Me and Kaiba are rivals!
We just may be enemies bound to fight by a fate driven for thousands of years.
But we can't let that hurt what's even more important than that!
Hmm? And what would that be?
It's the bonds between Duelists!
"Bonds"...?
What nonsense!
What a ridiculous answer!
You used Mokuba...
You chose to use cheap methods, while Kaiba chose to fight you fairly.
All Duelists are bound by the same desire to protect their pride!
And I'll take those bonds!
And I'll beat you with them!!
My... turn!
I'll place a Monster in face-down Defense Position! My turn is over!
You pulled another Monster Card?
But I wonder how long you can survive this Duel relying on luck alone.
My turn!
I pity you, Yugi.
It looks like this turn will be your last.
I think it's past time I show you what my deck is.
I Summon the Spirit Monster Yata-Garasu on the field in Attack Position!
A Spirit Monster!
Here goes! I start things off by attacking with Shinato, King of Heaven!
Six Paths of Reincarnation!!
What the hell?! That elf...!
Retrained Elf Swordsman can't be destroyed in battle by any Monster holding 1900 Attack Points or higher, Noah!
His luck disgusts me!
In that case, I activate the Magic Card Element Fountain from my hand!
Element Fountain increases my Life by 500 points every time a Monster returns from the field to a plater's hand.
Return, Yata-Garasu!
And Element Fountain activates this very moment.
My Life rises by 500 points.
How the heck did he return a Monster to his hand?
I get it. Yata-Garasu!
That card is part of the rumored Spirit Series I've been hearing about!
Right you are!
Pegasus of Industrial Illusions once traveled to the Orient of far Eastern lands, where he learned of ancient Japanese mythology.
and a legendary series was inspired.
One of the more distinguishing features of the Spirit Monsters is an Effect they all share.
Spirit Monsters are unable to be Special Summoned.
And they are returned to your hand at the End Phase of the turn they are Summoned.
I get it! Element Fountain was created as part of a combo!
Even if his Life Restoration isn't in effect now that Ark of Miracles is gone, his Life Points still increase thanks to his Spirit Monsters!
And with that, my turn comes to an end.
My turn!
This is Kaiba's...!
He's currently inside of his Deck Master, and on the field as well.
Kaiba, I may be able to beat him using your card.
I place a Monster in Defense Mode!
And I'll end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
I will Summon a Spirit Monster known as Asura on this turn!
Asura, attack Retrained Elf Swordsman!
Thousand Handed Knives of Hell!!
Retrained Elf Swordsman's Special Ability only activates when up against Monsters who hold under 1900 Attack Points.
So the Effect can't be activated against Asura, who holds only 1700 Attack Points!
Now be gone!!
And I also activate Asura's Special Ability!
What?!
The Monsters got more swords, like he's going to attack again!
Asura's Special Ability allows him to attack every single Monster on your side of the field every turn it attacks.
And with all your Wall Monsters gone, you'll be defenseless!
This is all I need in order to defeat you!
Maybe you'll learn your place once you realize I've beaten you.
Go, Asura!
Thousand Handed Knives of Hell!!
Disappear!
You fell for it, Noah!
The card you just attacked was a card Kaiba left behind!
It's Cyber Pod!
Cyber Pod is a card that destroys all Monsters on the field!
All Monsters on the field.
And Noah, that includes you as well, as you've merged with your Deck Master and you're now on the field!
Awesome, Yugi! You just pulled off a huge comeback!
Now Yugi wins!
Booyah!
I activate my Deck Master's Final Ability!
Reincarnation of Soul!!
He's gone...
Yugi-san won, didn't he?
It can't be! He's safe!
Does this mean that you were unaffected by Cyber Pod's Effect?
It means I was careless, Yugi.
I can't believe I had to use my Deck Master's Final Ability against you...!
Reincarnation of Soul is activated the moment the Deck Master is targeted for destruction on the field.
It's an Ability that negates that Card Effect and returns the Deck Master to his original position on the field.
With the cost of me not being able to call Shinato to the field again.
Noah, Cyber Pod's Effect isn't through yet.
Both players draw five cards from their respective decks.
You then Special Summon any low-level Monster Cards among them.
I Special Summon Critter and Magnet Warrior Gamma in Defense Position.
Now go on and Summon your Monster Cards already, Noah!
Damn you, Yugi...!
What the heck's wrong with Noah now?
You can't, isn't that right?
Part of the requirements for using a Spirit Monster is that it can't be Special Summoned!
Here goes! It's my turn!
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Gamma and Critter!
This automatically activates Critter's Special Effect!
I can add any Monster Card with 1500 Attack Points or less from my deck to my hand!
I add Big Shield Gardna to my hand!
And the Monster I Summon to the field is...
Come forth, Black Magician!
The Black Magician?!
Noah, your field is empty!
Go on, Black Magician!
Direct Attack the player!
Black Magic!!
Nice move, Yugi!
Once you figure out the drawbacks of Noah's Spirit Monsters, coming up with a strategy is easy!
Good job, Yugi-san!
That's our man!
Yugi...!
What's the matter, Noah?
This match is just getting started!
Yugi, how dare you humiliate me like this!
"Humiliate"...?
After all the humiliation you and Gozaburo put Kaiba and Mokuba through, you have no room for mouthing off!
This is the world I created!
Regardless of what you ants think, it's completely unforgivable to harm me, the creator!
I've never heard of a creator that uses people as stepping stones!
Noah, everyone has a home for their soul to return!
A home for their soul to return...
And that steel sun is not the home you're meant to return to!
Noah! I'm going to release your soul through this Duel!
Silence, Yugi!
I'm the one who's going to eliminate you!
My turn!
I activate a Magic Card!
Next Word!
Black Magician!
This Magic Card reflects the image of one chosen Monster on the field in the Rug of Hell
and using that spiritual energy, I can Normal Summon a Spirit Monster with the same Level from my hand.
And the card I choose to Summon is the Spirit Monster, Yamata Dragon!
What!?
What the hell is that thing?!
And it's got 2600 Attack Points, OOH-AH! OOOH-AHHH!
Eat this! Scotching Flame Thrower!!
Black Magician!
And my Deck master Ability activates.
Return, Yamata Dragon!
Because a Monster just returned to my hand, Element Fountain activates.
My Life goes up by an additional 500 points!
Now that Shinato is gone, that outrageous Effect that cuts your Life in half is gone,
but all the damage I inflicted on him...!
Yugi, you've got a mere 100 Life Points remaining.
What can you do with that?
It's alright! Yugi, you just have to believe in yourself!
Anzu!
Yugi, you're just getting warmed up!
Jounouchi-kun...
As long as I still have a small 1% chance of victory, I'll keep on believing in this deck!
My turn!
I activate the Magic Card Sealing Swords of Light from my hand!
How fearsome.
Great! Sweet move!
Now he's on even ground with him!
Oooh-ah! OOH!
You're doing great, Yugi-san!
Sealing Swords of Light stops him from attacking for three turns!
Don't let this chance slip by, Yugi!
Are you telling me this group is responsible for raising his spirits?
I'll also Summon Kuriboh!
Kuriboh! Direct Attack Noah!
Did something touch me just now?
What an utterly pitiful attempt at an attack.
Very well. Stand there, helplessly prodding your head for a way to attack me.
But I hereby make a prophecy sating:
"The moment the Sealing Swords of Light ware off..."
"...you will be killed in an instant!"
There hasn't been a single prophecy I've stated that hasn't come true in this Duel.
My turn!
I place a Monster face-down in Defense Position.
I then end my turn as well.
Now the first turn of Sealing Swords of Light is done and over with.
My turn!
Black Magician Girl...
Unfortunately, I can only activate my Deck Master, Kaiser Sea Horse's Special Ability for Light Monsters.
I can't use his Deck Master Ability to Summon the Magician Girl!
For now, I just need to focus on getting a Monster on the field.
Big Shield Gardna in Defense Position!
And I pull Kuriboh into Defense Mode as well!
That puts an end to my turn!
My turn!
I Summon a Monster face-down in Defense Mode!
I'll then set a card face-down, ending my turn.
We've now made it to the second turn of Sealing Swords of Light.
My turn!
None of the cards in my hand can turn this around!
I'll set one card face-down and finish my turn!
To think you only got a couple of cards out, despite the situation.
We only have one more turn before my prediction becomes a reality.
I suggest you mentally prepare yourself!
Don't give up, Yugi-san!
Yugi will win this!
That's right, dammit! OOH!!
Cuz we believe in him!
Heh, such foolishness.
How can you believe in a victory with no supportive reasoning?
We don't need reasoning!
We couldn't expect a lonely bastard like you who's been alone your whole life to understand how we feel!
Our willingness to believe in the bonds we share has turned the impossible into the possible time and time again!
Guys...
Humph. Just as Seto had Mokuba, Yugi has you guys by his side.
I just can't allow that...
Then allow me to test whether your "bonds" are truly what you say they are!
Otogi!
OTOGI!
That's a great look on his face!
And when Yugi loses, you'll all have the same expressions!
You could almost call him lucky to not have to feel the terror you guys will suffer!
Bastard! How could you go this far!?
The moment Yugi's Life Points hit zero,
you fools will rue the day you ever believed in such a pathetic Duelist
from the very bottom of your hearts!
And the whole lot of you will remain permanently trapped in those wave of emotions,
just as Seto and Mokuba stand before you!
And while surrounded by your frozen bodies, a look of hatred planted on his face...
Yugi, I wish you could stay like that!
I want to see you trapped with that look on your face forever!
And what exactly is so funny?
You're pitiful...
Your spirit hasn't matured at all since the time of your accident!
You're still just as childish as ever!
What did you just say?!
Look at every one of them!
Yugi, we believe in you!
We're not scared of you, even with your cheap tricks!
What's with... their eyes...?!
Noah, burn this image deep in your mind!
Those are eyes that believe in the bonds we hold dear!
Then allow me to send you all to hell one by one!
My turn!
Trap Card, activate!
Pyro Clock of Destiny!
What?! The Sealing Swords of Light...!
Pyro Clock of Destiny is a Trap Card that pushes the turn count of our Duel ahead by one.
Now you've lost your barrier.
I place a Monster in Attack Mode!
Come forth, Otohime!
I'll then activate Otohime's Special Effect!
When Otohime is Summoned, I can change the Battle Position of any Monster on the field!
And the one to feel that effect...
...will be you, Kuriboh!
Dammit! Kuriboh's been forced into Attack Mode!
I'll then sacrifice Otohime and my face-down Monster...
Come forth, Yamata Dragon!
With this, our match has been decided!
Attack, Yamata Dragon!
Now vanish from my sight, Yugi!
Yugi knocks Noah down with an incredible attack from his Monsters!
But Noah just recovers his Life Points using his Deck Master Ability and his Life Recovery Combo.
Now his Life Value has reached 10,000!
And Noah begins turning us to stone one by one at the end of his turns!
But we still have faith in him!
In Yugi's victory!
Next time!
"1000 Life Points VS 100!!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise