Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
In order to regain the reputation of Kaiba Corporation,
we must make the KC Grand Prix Duel Tournament we're holding this time a success no matter what.
Someone is plotting against me, but it's all pointless.
I'll send them home with their tal between their legs!
Now, chosen Duelists!
Duel standby!
"Jounouchi VS Mask the Rock"
I'm fired up~!
What an great atmosphere!
For real!
Look, Jounouchi-kun's trying to tease them all.
C'mon~!
Man, is he that stupid?
Peace!
Peace!!
OW!
What are you doing?! It's embarrassing!
That's...
Mokuba-kun?!
Starting now, hosted by Kaiba Corporation,
the most prestigious Duel Monsters Tournament, KC Grand Prix, will now begin!
The rules for this tournament are quite simple.
The world's top level Duelists fighting in this tournament
will be divided among two categories, A and B, for the preliminary matches.
And the one remaining will gain the glory of the KC Grand Prix winner!
Furthermore, the one to win KC Grand Prix
will be given the chance to fight the Battle City winner,
who holds the title of Duel King, Yugi Mutou, for a shot at his title!
Yay!
Everyone, please take a look at the screen!
We're gonna announce the players of the tournament's first round!
First up is the A Block!
The first challenger...
Katsuya Jounouchi!
Awright! I'm up at the start!
And my opponent?
The challenger...
Mask The Rock!
Hey, you jerk!
If I win the Duel, I get to take off that mask and reveal your true face!
What "real face"?
Yeah...
The first match up in B Block will be...
Leon Wilson VS Richard Goat!
Leon-kun's also in the first round, huh?
Try your best, Leon-kun!
The pairing for the second match will be announced once the first match ends!
Yugi, please come up and greet everyone!
Partner, I'll leave this to you.
Yugi! Yugi! Yugi!
Go on up, Yugi!
Come on!
Wh-What should I do?
No one can see you from down there!
Come on up here!
Kaiba-kun!
Brother!
Ladies and Gentleman!
I just have one thing to say.
This is neither a celebration nor a show!
It's a survival game with the Duelists betting their pride!
You will witness the loud cries of agony from many of the Duelists gathered here now...
...and the victorious cry of but one from this group!
Chosen Duelists!
Right now, my Kaiba Land has become a Colosseum!
Will you obtain glory or total defeat?
In order to survive, you must win!
Show me just how determined you all are to survive!
Kaiba! Kaiba! Kaiba!
That bastard...! In the end, he stole the spotlight for himself!
Where are you, you rat?
I won't let you do whatever you want in this tournament.
And the first round of the tournament will now commence!
All matches will be held within the various stages within Kaiba Land!
Only the winners from A and B may leave their selected stage victorious and return to this very arena.
The first game in A Block will be held in the Amazon Cruise Zone!
The first game in B Block will be held in the Water Coaster area!
The participants may now move from the stage to the appointed locations!
Leon-kun!
Deck.
My sweat.
Leon-kun.
Y-Yes, sir!
I won't give you any anesthesia in today's operation.
R-Right...
Duel!!
Hey, think he's just someone identical to him?
Come on, there's no mistaking him for someone else.
Partner...
Y-Yeah...
Huh?
Where's Jounouchi-kun?
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi?!
You want some of this?
J-Jounouchi! Why the hell are you here?!
You wanna know why? Cuz I'm starved as hell and I need my strength!
No way am I gonna fight this on an empty stomach!
IDIOT!
The first game is about the start!
Listen, if you don't show up at the appointed location within 10 minutes,
you're disqualified!
WHAT DID YOU SAY!?
We can make it if we leave now.
Don't look down on the Amazon Cruise.
It's a jungle, and you only have 10 minutes!
You're screwed!
There's no helping it...
In that case...
Jounouchi?!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Wait!
Idiot...
I was about to...
The right path appears to be that one.
Let's go!
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
Be careful! There's traps all over the place!
T-Tell me sooner next time...!
This way.
That's Solid Vision, isn't it?
Yeah...
Shit!
Stop it!
I thought we said it was Solid Vision...
He's a good customer...
How much time left?
Just 20 seconds!
Ten seconds left.
Nine...
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
Five...
Four--!
You satisfied now?!
Huh? Why are you here before me?
There's a path set aside just for staff!
I was gonna guide you there, but you went and left before I could!
Tell me earlier! Making us rush for nothing...
We made it.
Jounouchi!
Good job making it here on time! I expect no less from my student!
N-No! I-I'm not your mentor or anything!
I have no idea what you're on about!
Let's just get started!
Jounouchi doesn't notice?
Probably...
Grandpa...
So you really noticed, eh?
Professor Hopkins!
Professor, you knew?
I told him this definitely wouldn't work.
It's all right! No one will know!
But, it's just...
Arthur, I'm sick and tired of just staying home all the time!
I'm not so old that I'll lose to a bunch of youngsters!
Hey, Arthur, I got something else to tell you!
Sugoroku...
Grandpa...
But why's he wearing that weird disguise? And it's totally obvious!
If anything, at least Jounouchi didn't discover him.
And he calls him his student?
How will Sugoroku-san Duel?
I'm looking forward to it a bit.
Yeah... My grandpa's strong.
Is he really that strong?
You called him, didn't you?
No... Your old man called us up and begged us to include him.
Huh?!
He said he taught Yugi to Duel, so I thought it'd be alright.
Come to think of it, I've never seen your grandfather Duel before...
Here I go, masked bastard!
Okay!
Duel!!
I'll go first.
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Swordsman of Landstar in Attack Mode!
Also, I set two cards. Turn end.
My turn! Draw!
I set two cards on the field.
And Summon Wandering Mummy in Attack Mode!
I end my turn.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Little-Winguard in Attack Mode!
And I attack Wandering Mummy with Swordsman of Landstar!
Idiot! Doesn't it have more Attack Points than yours!
Shut up! I know that!
I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Angel Dice!
I can double my Monster's Attack Points based on the number I roll on the dice!
I read right through that!
Reverse card, open!
The Permanent Trap, Legendary Gambler!
Hey! What are you doing!?
This card activates whenever the opponent uses dice.
If my roll is higher than my opponents, I cancel out the effect.
What?!
Four!
Six!
It's not over yet!
If the angel didn't work, let's have a match with the devil!
Demon Dice! It reduces the opponent's Attack depending on the number I roll!
The Legendary Gambler is a Permanent Trap!
I roll the die once more!
Five!
No good! I got six!
Damn shit!
Thus the battle continues with their original Attack Points!
I have read entirely through you!
Due to Little-Winguard's Special Effect, at the End Phase, I can switch it to Defense Mode.
Turn end.
As expected of Jounouchi's mentor.
He's not bad.
Grandpa.
My turn! Draw!
Reverse card, open!
Non Aggression Area.
This card must be activated by discarding a card from your hand in the Standby Phase.
On the opponent's next turn, their ability to Normal Summon and Special Summon is sealed.
What?!
I'll also activate the Continuous Magic Card, Mirage of Nightmare, from my hand!
With this card, during the opponent's Standby Phase,
you can draw from your deck until you hold four cards,
and during your Standby Phase, you are to discard the same number of cards at random.
So this is Grandpa Sugoroku's way of Dueling.
Other Me...
As expected. He's always two steps ahead of Jounouchi-kun.
Yeah...
But I don't think that's all Grandpa is aiming for...
I'll set a card and end my turn.
My turn! Draw!
Wait a moment!
Because of Mirage of Nightmare's effects, I draw until I hold four cards.
So I draw three cards.
But on your turn, you have to discard the same number of cards in exchange, right?!
No.
Reverse card, open! Emergency Provisions!
This card lets me send any number of Magic and Trap Cards on my field to the Graveyard,
and recover my Life by 1000 for each in return!
What?!
And the card I send to the Graveyard is... Mirage of Nightmare!
Now when it is my turn, I don't have to discard any cards.
Those are some cheap tricks you keep using!
I'll beat the hell out of you for sure now!
Don't forget that Non Aggression Area is still in effect.
You can't Summon any Monsters this turn!
I know that!
Turn end!
Now then, it's my turn. Draw!
I activate the Field Magic from my hand, Metropolis of Ancient Times - Ancient City!
Wh-What is that?
I also sacrifice Wandering Mummy...
...in order to Summon Ancient Giant in Defense Mode.
However, if this card doesn't attack the opponent's Monster in a turn...
...the player controlling this card suffers 300 points of damage.
Old man, what high Attack it has!
And also the Continuous Magic from my hand! Ancient Key activates!
Due to this card's effect, I can Special Summon two Stone Giant Tokens in Attack Mode!
In the event these Stone Giant Tokens are not used to attack the opponent's Monster,
the player will receive 500 points of damage.
I use Ancient Giant to attack Little-Winguard!
And then I'll use the two Giant Stone Tokens to direct attack the player!
I set one card...
...and end my turn.
Grandpa.
Shit!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Because of Sugoroku-san... No, I meant to say because of Mask the Rock's tactics,
Jounouchi is greatly affected by him!
As expected of a mentor, he has Jounouchi completely read!
The impetuous Jounouchi is losing himself in the Duel.
Calm down! This isn't like you!
You have to enjoy a Duel more!
Next time!
"The Illusionary Ancient Dragon"
Duel standby!