A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Yugi's Desperate Battle:
Orgoth's Violent Attack"
Go, go, Otogi!
L-O-V-E, Otogi!
Beat that treacherous Yugi!
Shut up!!
Wh-What's that, all of a sudden?
You promised us you wouldn't talk!
Just let me say this one thing!
I won't forgive you!
Don't you dare call Yugi's soul battle in the Duelist Kingdom treacherous!
That's right!
Actually, Pegasus was the treacherous one, using his Mind Scan and all that crap!
Nothing you say to Otogi-kun will get through now.
Because Otogi-kun strongly believes Yugi ruined his dream!
Then what can we do?
There's only one way.
He has to feel Yugi's soul through the game!
Yeah! This battle ain't just about me anymore!
Yugi, this is a battle to protect your manhood!!
Stop talking!!
Lo-
ser-
Dog!!
Lo... ser... dog?!
Right, right. I'm a loser dog alright...
Loser dog~! Loser dog~! Loser dog~!
Man, Jounouchi lost whatever shred of dignity he had left.
"Loser dog" sure hits the nail on the head, huh?
He sounds just like a loser dog.
How do I make Otogi understand?
There's got to be a hint in this game!
Dice Roll!!
How can I make Otogi understand the heart of the game he made himself?
There's only one way to reach Otogi's heart.
I gathered what I need to activate an Effect!
Using two Magic Crests, Gorogon moves forward in a straight line,
destroying both enemy and ally Monsters.
Isn't that right?
Yeah.
I use two Magic Crests!
Rolling Crush!!
I activate its Special Ability!
I use three more Magic Crests and use the Rolling Crush once more!
No~!
Bow wow!
Alright!
What's with all the commotion?
Is it coming from the new game store?
-Who the hell's doing that?! Stop touching me!
-Sorry, youngsters!
Go, go, Otogi!
You can do it! You can do it, Otogi!
It's so good my heart almost stopped!
Wha-?
Yugi!
Damn you!
Why are you in the enemy's Duel Ring?!
Quiet down, old man!
We're trying to watch here!
What the hell?!
You're blocking the screen!
I-I'm sorry...
Monsters can only attack once per turn.
But a Monster's Special Ability is a special exception.
Yugi, the fact that you actually discovered that...
I thought you were nothing but a shy nerd at first, but...
Frankly, I thought this game was nothing but nonsense when I first heard about it.
However...
I finally get it!
Dungeon Dice Monsters is really fun!
I can sure see why you wanted to spread this game over the entire world.
Of course...
You really think you can get out of this by praising me?!
A match is a match!
Yeah, and the game is only getting started!
It's my turn!
Dice Roll!!
So my Summon failed?
It's my turn now!
Dice Roll!!
Yes!
A successful Summon!
Dimension Dice!!
Duker of Twin Swords!
Summon!
I can't launch an attack on any of your Monsters yet.
I'll store my Movement Crest in my Pool.
You seem to be finally getting used to the game, Yugi-kun.
What are you talking about? I don't really get it.
You still don't get the rules of this game?
If you don't want to use the Crests you rolled when you Summon a Monster,
you can store them away in the Crest Pool.
I see! So that's what you mean?
God, you're slow!
I can't believe you challenged Otogi-kun in the first place!
That's why we called you a loser dog.
This guy's seriously hopeless.
For real...
That Yugi...
He's started to learn this game at an amazing speed!
I've got to completely crush you before you learn all the rules of the game!
It's my turn!!
Dice Roll!!
I got a pair of Summon Crests!
Dimension Dice!!
I Summon the Level 2 Minotaur!
Moreover!
I use four of my stored Movement Crests to move Minotaur into position!
Minotaur!
Attack the Duker of Twin Swords!
It gets stronger when fighting against Warrior-types!
It's Attack Power rises from 10 to 30 points!
I use Duker of Twin Swords' Defense!
It's got 10 Defense Points!
Duker of Twin Swords has 10 Defense Points, and took damage of 30!
So it now has 10 Hit Points!
He's completely mastered Defense!
It's my turn!
Dice Roll!!
As the cost for its Special Attack,
I use two Attack Crests!
Twin Sword Multiple Slashes!!
My... Minotaur got...!
No~!
Otogi-kun~!
Woof!
He just started playing, too! That's our Yugi!
Yugi! Keep it up!
Otogi, it seems we've come right back to the start line!
I admit it was really magnificent for you to be able to beat my Minotaur!
But you're hugely mistaken if you think some newbie
can completely master Dungeon Dice Monsters!
What?
This game isn't decided just by Monster battles!
What are you trying to say?
Still haven't noticed?
Take a close look at the field.
Oh no!
Oh, no!
What's going on?
Did Yugi discover something?
I guess I'll have to explain it to you.
Listen.
You use the dice to Summon a Monster, as well as expand the field.
You're meant to connect it to your own Dungeon corridor.
Before when Otogi-kun kept dimensioning the dice, he completely locked Yugi into a corner!
Meaning Yugi already...
Right!
That means Yugi stands no hope of winning against me!
Isn't there any other way?
Well, he just has to find out how to Summon his Monster in the enemy's Dungeon.
The enemy's Dungeon?
But to do that, he'd have to defeat my entire Monster army,
and get himself within striking distance of me, the Dungeon Master.
No way!
That's impossible, even for Yugi!
My turn!
I got it!
Yugi-kun...
Look at this die.
A black... die?
This is known as the "Rare Black"!
Take a good look at what happens when you roll the black die!
Dice Roll!!
The Summon's a success!
Dimension, Rare Black!!
I Summon the Level 3 Warp Hole!
That's...!
This is a Warp Item!
Warp?
I can warp a special Item,
and one of those things...
But the true power of the Warp Item...
...is the dimension the Rare Black places on the field.
It's an entrance...
a warp leading directly to another location, becoming an exit!
I get it!
There's still one place left on my field where I can play the Dimension Dice!
When two Warp Holes are on the field, his Monsters can teleport between them!
So you finally realized?
Once I get my other Rare Black,
I can teleport my Monster army to your side of the field in an instant!
Using this Rare Black combo,
my victory is assured!
Warp Hole...
All I can do is strengthen my defense.
Dice Roll!!
The Summon's a success!
Alright!
Dimension Dice!!
I Summon the Level 3 Swift Black Ninja!
The Black Ninja has arrived!
The Black Ninja...
Nice Monster.
But can he beat the speed of my Rare Black Combo?
It's here! The black die!
Once I Dimension it, the Rare Black Combo will be complete!
No way!
Go! Go! Otogi!
Dice Roll!!
Not good...
If he completes the Rare Black Combo...
Your life is spared for now.
That's...
Otogi, it seems you've overlooked something.
I have one as well!
The Rare Black!
What'd you say?!
-Yugi!
Oh yeah!
Dice Roll!!
A successful Summon!
Dimension, Rare Black Die!!
I then use Swift Black Ninja's Instant Movement!
What?!
Swift Black Ninja, attack the Gargoyle!
Assassination complete!
Yes!
You did it!
Hell yeah!
He got him~!
Because Otogi's Dungeon covers the entire field,
my Dungeon space connects to it.
Using the Warp Hole to get past his battle line is the only way to prevail.
Before he Summons the Warp Crest,
I have to stop his Warp Hole!
Black Ninja is an especially tricky Monster due to its Instant Movement ability.
He moves three spaces when you use a Movement Crest!
Yugi's bound to attack me next turn!
If I don't Summon a defense Monster this turn, I'm screwed!
A failed Summon...?!
Dice Roll!!
Yes!
It's a Movement Crest!
Run, Black Ninja!
Black Ninja, attack Dungeon Master Otogi!
I shall take your life!
No~!
How cruel~!
Bow wow!
He did it!
Now this is in the bag!
Alright!
Well done!
That's my grandson for you!
Outta the way!
Move it, old fart!
To harm me in Dungeon Dice Monsters...!
Just as I expected of the Duelist Kingdom victor!
You're making me really excited, Yugi-kun!
But...!
You won't be touching me again!!
Good!
I got some Summon Crests!
Here goes!
Dimension Dice!!
I Summon the Level 3 God Orgoth!
God Orgoth's Special Ability allows me to take three Magic Crests
and raise its Attack from 10 to 20!
And then...!
I use a Movement Crest on God Orgoth!
God Orgoth!
Attack the Swift Black Ninja!
Diamond Blade!!
If I don't do something, I'm done...!
I beat him!
You really think so?
What?!
Take a good look at the Dungeon.
Impossible!
The moment God Orgoth attacked,
I used a Trap Crest to activate his Special Ability!
Swift Black Ninja has the Effect to dodge any attack!
Invisibility...
It camouflaged itself like a chameleon!
He was able to avoid the attack that way!
He's no longer like the person who could hardly play D.D.M...!
Yugi Mutou...
Is it possible he beat Pegasus without tricks, but with pure talent?
It's my turn now!
Swift Black Ninja, attack!
What!?
No~!
Nice one!
Great job!
Just one more attack and I win!
Yugi...
I won't let you do as you please!
This is a fight for me to get my broken dream back!
My turn!!
God Orgoth, attack the Swift Black Ninja!
I don't have any more Trap Crests in my Crest Pool...!
I no longer have a way to stop his attacks!
Diamond Blade!!
My only Monster in enemy territory was beaten...
My opponent has four Monsters at his disposal...
And I only have three Monsters.
What can I do?
"Preview"
Using the Warp Hole, Yugi's Dungeon is invaded.
God Orgoth has begun to eliminate all of Yugi's Monsters!
If he doesn't Summon a Monster soon,
he'll lose all of his Life Points!
He doesn't even have a space to Summon a Monster in anymore...!
Don't lose, Yugi!
There's still a chance!
Next time!
"The Miracle Dimension:
Summon the Black Magician"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship