A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Kaiba boy, if you can defeat me,
I will release Mokuba boy's
soul from the sealed card.
My turn!
Stop!
That card has 3000 Attack Points, and it is your most trusted card.
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Impossible!
Did Pegasus see my hand somehow?!
Kaiba Falls!
The Invincible Toon World
That power...
Pegasus is reading Kaiba-kun's mind...
That's not possible!
Oi oi, if that is true, doesn't that mean it's impossible to defeat that bastard?
No, It's the power of his Millennium Eye...
But there must be a way to defeat Pegasus...
Kaiba-kun can do it.
Damn you, Pegasus.... are you really reading my mind?
Impossible!
None of the cards in my hand can beat Dark Rabbit...
I play another card in Defense Mode.
Turn over!
Then it's my turn.
Say, Kaiba boy... do you like cartoons?
Is that so? It seems you don't.
What a pity.
But I love them!
As a boy, I used to watch "Funny Rabbit" all the time!
All those great characters running on the TV were the best!
During those days, they were like my best friends!
To this day, they still run around in the little garden in my heart.
So what?!
They will never betray me.
What are you getting at?
And they can never die...
I'll invite you to their world!
My card is...
Toon World!
Toon World?!
What's that?
It looks like a pop-up book or something.
I've never seen a card like it...!
Toon World... what kind of card is it...?
Oi, when that thing appeared, Pegasus' black rabbit disappeared.
Where did your Dark Rabbit go?!
Now all my cards have become Toon cards.
They now live here.
If you can't see them, they must be hiding somewhere in this world.
See, he's about to show himself.
Dark Rabbit, attack.
Toon Attack!
What's that?!
Hey hey.
Dark Rabbit has gone back
to hiding in the picture book.
Yes, I forgot to tell you,
once Toon World is closed...
no monsters are able to lay any damage to them.
What did you say?!
No way!
Kaiba-kun can't attack him back!
My turn.
I'll set a card face-down, and end my turn.
It seems to be my turn, Kaiba boy.
Let me show you something interesting.
This is the Blue-Eyes White Dragon I got from you.
I'll play this card in Attack Mode.
My... my Blue-Eyes...!
All of my monsters have become residents of Toon World.
What do you think?
Isn't it more lovable than before?
What's going on?
Kaiba's Blue-Eyes...!
That's the power of Toon World.
Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon!
Attack Rude Kaiser!
What's this? I feel anger in your heart.
Pegasus... it seems you already know what cards are in my hand...
If that's the case, I'll discard my entire hand.
What?
I'm going to play the first card I draw from my deck.
In other words, even I won't know what it will be.
And I'll play it on the field in Attack Mode!
Kaiba-kun!
That Kaiba bastard's pretty much given up to resort to this.
No.... I can kind of understand what Kaiba means...
What do you mean?
He's betting everything on the card he'll draw.
Kaiba trusts in his deck with all his heart.
Imagine the burden he's shouldering to go this far.
You've matured a lot, Jounouchi.
Kaiba-kun...
Here I go! I'm betting everything on this card!
The card I believed in....
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
This guy is great!
To draw Blue-Eyes in this situation...!
The card Kaiba called with his heart.
That Kaiba bastard...!
I hate to admit it, but he's really a first-class Duelist!
Pegasus, you said you could feel my anger...!
I'll teach you what anger really is!
It's a fight with the real Blue-Eyes against the Toon Blue-Eyes.
Kaiba-kun, be careful.
His Toon World is unlike anything I've ever seen...
Wonderful!
Kaiba boy.
To draw another Blue-Eyes... you're truly a lucky boy, aren't you?
Changing my proud monster
into that disgusting thing...!
I'll never forgive you, Pegasus!
Oooohh nooo~
Here I come!
Blue-Eyes attack!
Burst Stream!!
It evaded the attack!
It missed?
What?!
Did you see that just now?!
Pegasus' Blue-Eyes stretched out of the way!
Funny Rabbit aired a total of 583 episodes on TV.
In all of which the bad guy fired a total of 26000 bullets at the good guy...
And not a single one ever hit Funny Rabbit!
It's a miracle!
As long as Toon World remains on my board...
every card I play will become a Toon Card.
Toons are the perfect form of being!
That means he can't defeat any of the Toons!
That bastard Pegasus...!
Even if he is the creator of Duel Monsters
using that card is cheap!
Yugi, did you know about them?
Yeah... but those cards aren't sold to the public.
There's only one of each in the world.
Original cards meant for Pegasus.
The only ones in the world...
Making cards for himself is too dirty!
Well then, it's my turn.
Kaiba boy... you realized I could see your cards through your eyes so you abandoned your hand and drew from your deck...
But even that is useless...
When players assemble their decks...
they memorize all their cards, even if only subconsciously.
In other words, I know every
card assembled in your deck.
My turn!
I play this card!
Shine Palace!
A new page in Toon World!
A Light-Attribute monster receives this and powers up by 500 points!
A new page in Toon World?
That's right!
The chapter of your defeat has been written in Toon World.
My Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon, receive the light's energy and power up!
Pegasus' Toon Dragon...!
Has more Attack Points than Kaiba's Blue-Eyes!
Kaiba-kun...
Blue-Eyes Toon Dragon attack!
Burst Stream!!
Magic Card activate!
Attack Nullification!
Alright! Pegasus' attack was blocked!
Of course, I knew you had that Magic Card...
Attack Nullification is a one-time only card.
Next turn, there's no way you'll block my Toon Dragon's attack.
My turn!
If this continues, my Blue-Eyes will be killed by the Toon Dragon...
If that happens, I have no chance of winning.
Mokuba... I'll stake our fate on this card!
It's here!
My card is...
Spell of Darkness!
Spell of Darkness stops the enemy from moving
and decreases their Attack down by 700 points!
There was only one card in Kaiba boy's deck that could defeat the Toon Dragon...
To draw that card now of all times...
Great...!
Even your Toon can't move once bound by the Spell of Darkness!
Prepare yourself!
Burst Stream!!
Alright!
He defeated Pegasus' Toon Dragon!
Seto Kaiba.... you're very good.
Blue-Eyes...!
I couldn't let you live as a pathetic Toon...!
I've put you out of your misery...!
Thank you, Kaiba boy.
Right now I felt love for
your Blue-Eyes in your heart.
As the Duel Monsters creator,
I feel very complimented.
But...
that love for your Blue-Eyes will be the trigger of your defeat.
The card I've played... is the Dragon-Type Sealing Jar!
All Dragon-types will be sealed in this jar!
The Sealing Jar gains the Defense Points of the dragon it absorbs.
Damn you Pegasus...
I have to destroy that jug before he uses the second Blue-Eyes...!
My turn!
A monster in Defense Mode!
It's my turn.
I place this card Face down...
Also, the Jar Genie in Defense Mode!
This is the combo Pegasus...
Are you going to revive the Blue-Eyes as your servant...?
That's right!
And...
I'll turn it into a Toon to deliver the final blow.
Your ending will be very miserable.
You bastard!
I'll crush that measly Jar Genie first!
Sword Stalker the Avenger! Attack!
Turn that Jar Genie into pieces!
I activate the Magic Card Copy Cat!
What?!
This card can copy any you've played on the board!
The card I'm going to copy is the Virus Card!
And I infect Jar Genie with the virus!
What!?
Pegasus made the virus holder Jar Genie!
Don't attack, Kaiba-kun!
Once you say "attack", it can't be stopped!
At this moment...
The Virus Card destroys every monster in your deck with over 1500 Attack Points!
All the Monsters in my Deck were destroyed...
Your deck is made up almost entirely of over-powered Monsters with brute strength.
I don't believe it!
For Kaiba's powerful deck to crumble this easily...!
Kaiba-kun...!
Even if he's still got Life Points, he's got no cards left!
This is the only card I've got left...
Resurrection of the Dead!
I use this card to revive Saggi the Dark Clown!
I praise your ability to play out this game to the very end.
If I should defeat that card on my next turn, I shall win!
Mokuba...
Forgive me...
My attack!
Devil Box!
Goodbye, Mokuba...
Goodbye, Yugi...
Kaiba-kun!
Kaiba!
You have no cards left in your hand.
Therefore, you lose.
Kaiba boy, I presume you are aware of what it means to lose a game?
The loser loses everything.
What is precious to them...
And even themselves.
You shall suffer the same fate as Mokuba boy!
Mokuba...!
Mind Card!!
Your mind has now been sealed within this card.
You will now eternally become my servant,
forced to carry out my every bidding.
The elder brother and younger brother...
The two cards are this close,
yet their souls are separated by what almost seems like infinity.
To think you'd have enjoyed a better meeting had you gone to the other world instead.
Remove the corpse from my presence!
Kaiba just ended up the same as Mokuba...!
No way...!
Kaiba-kun...
Kaiba-kun fought with his life on the line in order to save Mokuba-kun!
Yugi...
He's no different from us, trying to protect those important to him!
Pegasus! You...
You have no right to take away what's precious to us!
All that remains now is Yugi boy...
So you've shown yourself, other Yugi?
Pegasus! I'll defeat you with my own hands!
Yugi boy, if you desire to fight against me,
you must win the tournament first.
I know that.
But you'd better prepare yourself!
My anger won't submit until I've beaten you!
The final tournament shall begin!
In this very Duel Ring!
Only one of the four remaining Duelists shall earn the right to challenge me for eternal fame and glory!
Yugi boy... Even if you wield the Millennium Puzzle...
It is all but ineffective before my Millennium Eye.
Allow me to prove this to you.
"Preview"
Yugi and the gang enjoy much needed relaxation and prepare for the finals!
But Pegasus' Mind Scan sure is suspicious, isn't it?
See! Isn't that a peephole?!
He must be spying on the opponent's hand from that tower over there!
Honda! Bakura-kun!
Let's go investigate that tower for Yugi and Jounouchi!
Next time! The Night Before the Finals! Pegasus' Secrets
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship