Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Challenge From the Past:
The Horrifying Zera"
Good morning, Gramps!
Oh, good morning!
Anzu-chan, you look nice as always!
What's he saying?
Where's Yugi?
Oi, Yugi! Anzu-chan is here!
Oh, okay! I'm coming now!
That doesn't look half bad, partner.
Huh? You think so?
It isn't too flashy?
Actually, I was thinking
it's not flashy enough!
You should try wearing a bracelet or something.
But that wouldn't suit me at all!
Go. Anzu is waiting.
Show her your cool side.
What are you talking about?
Were you just talking to someone?
Er... N-Not really...
I'm off!
If you stick by me, I'll make Anzu fall for you in no time!
Eh? Stop picking on me, would you?!
Yugi...?
Good morning, Yugi.
Sorry to keep you, Anzu.
Oh, a chain.
This is really important to my other Self, so I want to make sure I don't damage it.
Yugi and the Other Yugi...
It's the outer and inner
sides of Yugi's heart...
I met the Other Yugi in Duelist Kingdom.
I didn't tell you guys, but the me that Duels isn't the usual me.
I'm always resting in my heart.
I change to my Other Self to fight.
His other heart is inside the Millennium Puzzle... So says Yugi.
What's wrong, Anzu?
Oh, nothing.
Let's hurry to school!
Okay.
We're off, Grandpa!
Oh, take care!
Is that kid okay?
What do you mean?
He's been talking to himself lately.
Yeah, he's going through a lot.
He's at that age, you know!
I was that way, too!
That's why I'm worried.
What was that?
Hey, Yugi. Do you have some free time this Sunday?
Why?
It's not like I have anything to do, so if you have some time,
want to go do something somewhere?
Is that okay, Yugi?
Yugi?
What are you doing?
I'm getting my fortune told!
Geez... That's so childish...
You have something quite magnificent there.
R-Really?
May I see it?
Not this! It's very important!
It'll only be for a moment.
But...
I've studied countless rare treasures from around the world.
I may just be able to determine what I'm looking for!
C'mon!
As long as it's really just for a moment.
This is incredible.
I've never seen any quite like it!
Are you okay, Yugi?
Anzu, go to school before me!
I'm going after him!
I'll get the others!
Is he leading me somewhere?
Good!
Oh, Anzu-chan!
Good morning.
Oh, Bakura-kun.
Yugi's puzzle was stolen!
Huh? Where?
Over there!
I have to get everyone!
Then I'll try looking for Yugi-kun.
Please do!
Stolen...?
What the hell is he doing?!
What's going on here?
The Millennium Ring senses a bad omen...!
The Millennium Items contain memories of the past.
Yugi Mutou must be the one to hold the Millennium Puzzle.
Any person who makes themselves his enemy becomes mine as well.
Is anyone here?
Give me back my Millennium Puzzle!
Yugi Mutou.
The Millennium Puzzle!
You want me to give it back?
Give it back!
Give me back my Millennium Puzzle!
If you want me to give it back, defeat me in a Duel.
Who are you?!
Why are you making me Duel you?
There is no need for me to answer you.
You have but two
options to choose from.
Will you accept the Duel? Or will you not?
So that's Yugi Mutou?
The person who defeated Pegasus and became the winner of Duelist Kingdom doesn't look like much.
Was it the power of the Millennium Puzzle and the other Yugi that defeated him?
Who exactly is residing within the Millennium Puzzle?
And what is the identity of the other Yugi?
That alone is my objective.
If he really is who I think he is...
Why do I have to Duel you?
Can't you just return my Millennium Puzzle?
What will you do?
I get it!
But you better keep your promise!
Sure.
Other me... can you hear me?
Yugi.
Thank goodness.
I'm still able to call to you.
You can't!
You have to fight this Duel alone!
Why?
I sense something strange...
Someone is trying to see my true identity.
So you can't lend me your power like usual, can you?
Yeah.
Okay. I'll fight for you.
And I'll surely get back the Millennium Puzzle!
I'm counting on you, partner!
Good. You're ready to Duel now.
Yugi, it's your turn first.
I play Elf Warrior in Attack Mode!
My turn is over!
I place a monster in defense.
Turn over.
I think I've heard that voice somewhere before.
Hey, what is it?
It's your turn.
Elf Warrior, attack the Defense Mode Monster!
When Cyber Pod is attacked while in face-down Defense Position,
Cyber Pod's Effect activates.
When this card is flipped from reverse, all Monsters on the field are destroyed.
And both players are to draw five new cards from the top of their decks.
We then both Summon any Level Four or lower Monster Cards we've drawn to the field in Attack Mode.
Silver Fang in Defense Mode.
Mecha Hunter and
Ground Attacker Bugroth...
And the Cyber Pod he played earlier...
Is he playing a Machine Deck?
Could it be...?!
Could you be Bandit Keith?!
It's Keith!
He really seems like a different person, but there's no mistaking that bandana!
He was defeated by Jounouchi-kun in Duelist Kingdom and then ejected from the island by Pegasus for using dirty tricks.
Why are you here?
It is true that this man is known as "Bandit Keith".
"This man"?
After the fact, Keith was thrown into the sea.
Shit...!
Why does he call himself "this man" as if he's talking about another person?
And why is he after me...?
It's not surprising that he has a grudge against you.
Had you guys not been there,
Keith would have gotten his hands on a large cash prize,
as well as earning back the title of "Number One U.S. Champion Duelist".
Goddamn you, Yugi!
My turn.
I Summon Machine King.
Attack Position.
By Machine King's Effect, its Attack goes up by 100 points for every Machine-type Monster on the field.
Attack Silver Fang.
Jet Punch!!
Turn end.
My turn!
A Monster in Defense Position!
So it seems you're quite scared of my Machine Monster Army.
I'll play an Ultra Rare Card and scare you even more!
Megasonic Eye in Attack Mode.
And by Machine King's Effect, its Attack goes up by 100 points.
Machine King, attack his Defense Monster!
Yugi, your Monsters are being annihilated one by one.
What's the matter?
Why don't you call out your other like you did back in the Kingdom?
Keith shouldn't know about my other self.
Why does he?
Isn't that Keith?
What?! Yugi's Millennium Puzzle was stolen?
It must be some guy after the title Yugi earned in Duelist Kingdom!
They must be after Yugi. Let's hurry!
Right!
You guys! Where are you headed?!
Hasn't class already started already?!
M-Mutou's really sick!
It's so painful, all he could do was call our names!
If we don't hurry up and go, Yugi-kun will...!
I see! So that's what happened?!
Hurry up and go visit him, you guys!
Yes, Sensei!
Bring Mutou-kun back with you safe and sound~!
Too easy!
But if he finds out, we're in trouble later!
It can't be helped. It's an emergency.
Liars smell worse than piss, right?
That's just wrong!
Then how about "shi-"
Don't even say it!
Yugi.
Reach out to the Millennium Puzzle...
...and call out the other soul within.
I won't let things go your way!
My turn!
Curse of Dragon, in Attack Position!
And Dark Knight Gaia as well!
I polymerize Curse of Dragon with Dark Knight Gaia!
Now his Attack Power will be greater than Machine King!
Dragon Knight Gaia, attack Mecha Hunter!
Double Dragon Lance!!
Now Machine King's Attack goes down by 100 points!
My turn. Mode Change.
Mega Sonic Eye and...
Ground Attacker Bugroth will be switched in Defense Mode.
And I play the rare card known as Machine Conversion Factory,
which increases the Attack and Defense Points of all Machine-type Monsters...
...by 300 points.
Damn!
As of now, Gaia the Dragon Knight is...!
Go, Machine King.
Attack Dragon Knight Gaia.
What's wrong? Are you gonna just sit and watch while you lose?
If you wish to keep the title you earned from Duelist Kingdom...
Or could it have been another man that defeated Pegasus?
Be serious! Like you usually are!
If it were the other me,
he wouldn't give up even when driven into a corner.
He would calmly analyze the enemy.
The Machine Army has to have a weakness.
But...
Demon's Summon...
I see!
Even machines have a weakness!
I'll show you what that is right now!
Combo Attack!
Makiu!
Wh-What's this acid rain?
Then I play Demon's Summon in Attack Mode!
While weakening your Machines, the rain increases Demon's Summon's electrical attack power!
Demon Lightning!!
I did it!
A turn around!!
What?!
He is much better than I anticipated.
I've been holding back so far in order to see the other soul within the Millennium Puzzle...
It's about time I dropped the act and got serious!
I'll use our special
replica cards to attack him...
...and force out the other soul!
From here?
Yeah.
Could these be arrows...?
Yugi went this way, right Anzu?
But who would...?
Hey. Look at that.
I don't get any of this.
Go. It's your turn!
The Magic Card Angel's Charity.
I draw three cards from my deck, then discard two after the fact.
Ultra Rare Card! Ritual of Zera!
Eh? Ritual of Zera?
It's a card that lets you initiate the advent of Zera once you sacrifice Monsters equaling 8 stars or more.
Exactly that.
Zera is the strongest Monster of the Demon-Fiend Class.
B-But...!
There's only three original cards in the entire world...!
I've never even seen it!
It's an ultra rare card even among other Ultra Rares.
My grandpa told me himself!
It can't be!
I Tribute Ground Attacker Bugroth and Megasonic Eye in order to Summon Zera!
Demon's Summon can't win against Zera!
Devil's Claw!!
Such an Ultra Rare Card...
...I can't beat it!
This is no ordinary Duel.
The Power of Darkness is present throughout the entire area.
Yugi, where are you?
Yugi! Answer us!
Yugi!
Yugi...
Come on, what's the matter? Just reach out your hand.
Reach out to your other self in the Millennium Puzzle.
I want to know that man's true form!
Yugi...!
What's wrong? There's nothing left.
Where did that invincible Yugi from Duelist Kingdom run off to?
My other self... At this rate, I can't get the Millennium Puzzle back!
Go on! Come on out, other Yugi!
What should I do?
What should I do?!
In order to prove Yugi's true identity, Keith appeared!
No matter what he does, Keith overwhelms Yugi with his rare cards.
But isn't he acting a bit strange?
What's that?!
Yugi's Millennium Puzzle has been smashed apart!
Yugi hurries to put together the Puzzle in a raging fire...!
Please! Hurry and run!
Next time!
"The Broken Millennium Puzzle"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...