Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Deck Master:
Judge Man's Judgment"
Putting Yugi Mutou aside...
To think he would be defeated by that amateur girl, when she barely knows how to Duel…
What a useless bunch.
I feel so ashamed.
Noah-sama, you were right. We deserve punishment.
Ouka, is it...?
Don’t get the wrong idea.
I’m not really all that angry.
Just disappointed.
My apologies.
Being one of the Big Five, the group that betrayed the Kaiba Corporation,
I was planning to put you to work as my chess pieces, but I guess that isn’t happening.
I no longer have any use for you.
You may as well
give up on getting a body.
H-Hold on Noah-sama!
The truth is, out of the Big Five, those two are the most useless idiots.
However, I am completely different.
If you give me one more chance, I will meet your expectations, Noah-sama.
You’re pretty confident.
So, when I am
done beating these people,
will you please
grant me with a new body?
Okay.
I'll give you one more chance.
Leave this to me.
Tricky bastard...
But I’ll let him do as he wants.
In the end, you guys are only responsible for getting rid of the small fry.
Pick any weakling
you want to face.
This is the man that
I'm really interested in.
Battle Ship, do you hear me?
Battle Ship?
So I guess it won’t work, big brother.
Yeah.
I suppose we’ll have to get out of this annoying Virtual Space first.
Hey! Shizuka! Yugi!
Damn, I’ve been separated from everyone,
And those Big Five old bastards aren’t in sight, either.
Just what is going on?
I can’t just laze around here!
Wh-What the?
A door behind the wall?
This is suspicious.
Ohhh! That’s the Battle Ship!
And I’m out to the real world!
Lucky!
Maybe everyone’s made it back already?
Hey Yugi, Shizuka?
That's strange, nobody's here?
Isn't that room…
Mai...
I plan on letting you enjoy the inside of the world in your mind to the fullest!
Wait for me, Mai.
I'll definitely defeat Malik so that you'll be able to wake up.
Mai!
You're awake?
It's a shame that you're still in our Virtual World.
I am so sorry to have lied to you, Jounouchi-kun.
You're not Mai...
Who are you?!
You're one of the Big Five!
Sorry I waited to tell you.
Yes, I am one of the Big 5.
I am a lawyer for Kaiba Corporation.
My name is Ouka Chikuzen.
Nice to meet you.
You say you're a lawyer?
Yes.
I am a man capable of turning black into white, so long as it benefits Kaiba Corporation.
I guess you can say that because of me, Kaiba Corporation has became such a big industry.
Huh? You can turn black into white?
I don't get it at all!
You'll have to pardon me.
It appears that comparison was a tad bit too difficult for you to comprehend.
In short, regardless of what our company is charged with,
so long as I am in on the lawsuit, the end result will charge the suer is guilty.
How could that make you feel so proud?!
A lawyer's job should be to tell the truth to everybody.
The truth?
Let me ask you then, what exactly is ''the truth''?
Well, the truth means you have real facts.
Sorry, I guess my question was a little too difficult for you.
Well, let me teach you something.
The truth is whatever my legal argument says it is.
We're talking about different things here!
You're really pissing me off!
You lying trickster!
I'll just take that as a compliment.
Regardless, you're here to Duel me, right?
If that's the case, let's get going!
Are you sure?
If you lose, I'll take your body.
Don't say stuff like that.
If I want to escape from this Virtual World, I gotta beat you, right?
Come on, let's start.
Very well. Then let us begin.
This will be our Duel Field.
Where the hell are we now?
As you can see, we are in the Grand Court Room.
I am the Judge and
you are the accused.
I'm the accused?
I am usually the defender of the accused person,
but today I will
be making an exception.
I shall deliver to you your judgment, acting as Judge Man!
Judge Man?!
You just keep changing forms!
And you just had to
pose as Mai before...!
You made me think
she was really waking up.
I won't forgive you.
I will never forgive you!
Now will the accused, Katsuya Jounouchi, please build yourself a deck.
F-Fine.
Good... this one and this one...
And...
Katsuya Jounouchi, I'm predicting you'll be playing a "Gamble Deck".
Judge, I'm done.
Good, now you pick one of those cards to serve as your Deck Master.
Oh, that's right. Let's see...
The Flame Swordsman?
I've been fighting beside this guy for a long time now.
He's a Monster I can trust.
This guy should be just right to be my Deck Master.
Good.
My Deck Master is the Flame Swordsman.
I'm counting on you, Flame Swordsman.
Please tell me what your ability is as my Deck Master.
My Deck Master Ability allows me to slash my own Attack Power by intervals of 100,
and add them to another Warrior-Type Monster's Attack Points.
As you can see,
my Deck Master is Judge Man.
It is now time
to begin our Duel!
It's my turn.
Draw!
I Summon the Hysterical Angel!
This Monster really pisses me off...
1800 Attack Points, though?
I'll keep her in Attack Mode
and finish this turn!
Here comes my turn! Draw!
Iron Knight Gearfried...
It has the same amount of Attack Points as his Monster, right?
Good! Time to use
my Deck Master's Ability!
I Summon Iron Knight Gearfried!
I'll also use use my Deck Master Ability to raise his Attack Points by 500.
Here goes! Iron Knight Gearfried, attack!
Kill the Hysterical Angel!
Alright! Turn over!
You used your
Deck Master Ability so soon...
You learned the rules faster than I anticipated.
My turn.
Draw!
I set a Monster in Reverse
and end my turn!
My turn.
Draw!
He probably set a Monster with a Reverse Effect...
But Master Jounouchi
don't fear nothin'!
I'll just keep playing carefully.
I Summon Little-Winguard!
I use my Deck Master Ability!
I increase his Attack Power
by 300 points!
I use Little-Winguard to attack your Reverse Monster Card!
I activate the Reverse Effect
of Helping Angel!
I get to draw another card.
Either way, I got rid of your Monster.
Here goes. I'll use Gearfried to Direct Attack you!
Y-You have remarkable skills.
Well? You finally understand how great my skills are?!
At your current level, you cannot beat me no matter how hard you try.
Go on and smirk all you want!
You still can't do anything!
Enjoy your arrogance
while you still can.
Letting your enemy get caught up with success is my gambling theory.
Well, it's your turn.
This way I can make you wait longer and you'll be too shocked to relax and think straight.
Draw!
I Summon Holy Elf
in Defense Mode!
And I'll cover another card
to finish this turn.
Playtime has long past!
I'm about to get serious with you!
It's cold.
Here.
Thanks, Yugi.
But...
I wonder if the others
are doing alright?
Yeah, I'm sure they'll
also be forced to Duel.
I'm sure Kaiba-kun and Jounouch-kun will be okay.
It's Shizuka-chan's and Honda-kun's amateur Dueling skills that worries me.
You're right.
Honda has no talent
in Dueling whatsoever!
Are you okay?
It's okay, it's not serious.
Don't give Shizuka-chan your cold!
It's not a cold!
Someone's just talking about me!
Right, and I don't think that Shizuka-chan understands the rules of Dueling yet.
See! She caught it already!
You need to stay away from her.
Wh-What's with you, Otogi?
Damn it! I'll spread it to you too!
Just knock it off, will ya?!
If we don't hurry and find them soon, Shizuka-chan and the guys will be in danger.
Let's hurry, Yugi.
Right.
Damn, where does this forest lead to?
Damn you, Noah...
Just you wait...
I will escape from this ridiculous Virtual World and show you who's boss.
If you want out of that forest so bad, I'll let you have your wish.
Brother.
Yeah.
This place...!
The President's office
at Kaiba Corporation!
You need something from me?
Gozaburo?
Yes, I want to talk with you about the Virtual System I created.
Brother, these are Virtual Images as well!
I remember this.
It happened two years before I became the president of Kaiba Corporation!
If that's what you want,
I have nothing to say to you.
Seto... I'm busy now,
so please leave.
I invented that system so everyone could enjoy games!
But Father, you want to use it for war!
I said get out.
Didn't you hear me?
The system is not a war tool!
I invented it for people to use in the future Kaiba Land!
I said get out already!
What Kaiba Land?!
Hmph! It's all nonsense!
Such ridiculous games
have no use for man!
Listen very carefully, Seto!
Whoever inherits Kaiba Corporation must make things that are of great use to mankind around the world!
I myself must dominate the world with my military business.
I want to use the Virtual System you developed to reproduce the territory of world.
But you're wrong!
Let go of me. Let me go!
I am not finished yet!
Father...
Father!
That was the last day I addressed that man as my father.
He was willing to let countless numbers of people die in wars with the Virtual System just so he could make a fortune.
I couldn't hand it over to that evil man.
On that day, I totally lost my respect for him.
And I made up my mind that Kaiba Corporation would belong to me.
Brother...
Regardless of that... it's unforgivable to go into our memories
and secretly watch our reactions and make fun of them.
Noah, you won't get away with this!
Listen, Noah!
If you're cooking up some foolish plan with that low-grade brain of yours
to steal Kaiba Corporation,
I won't let you succeed!
I will completely
destroy your ambition!
"Steal Kaiba Corporation?"
My turn!
Draw!
That guy only has
one Monster on the field.
I am a little worried
about that set card...
But the manly Jounouchi never backs down from a fight!
I Summon Rocket Warrior in Attack Mode!
Well? Are ya scared?
This match is done!
I'm gonna use my three Monsters to beat the crap outta your weak Wall Monster!
Then I'll smash you with a Direct Attack, winning me the match!
Go, Gearfried!
Attack Holy Elf!
Deck Master Ability, activate!
Crap, I forgot!
He has a Deck Master Ability too!
Just how foolish can you get?
My Deck Master Ability
is perfect for someone like you!
Life Sentence!!
L-Life sentence? What is that?
It's a sentence reversing victory by sacrificing 1000 Life Points!
It removes every Monster on your side of the field from the game!
What? No way!? Just hold on!
Is that even possible?!
Not only that, but for every Monster I erase, the opponent takes 500 points of damage!
Eh? What?!
That means... I had 3 Monsters erased.
So I lose 1500 Life Points?!
You calculate well.
Shit!
But it's nothing to
really worry about.
Now that guy only
has 200 of his Life left...
It's an easy win.
Pitfall of Hades...
This card can destroy any Monster Normal Summoned, Reverse Flip Summoned or Special Summoned Monsters
with 1500 or greater Attack Points.
It's a Trap Card that
removes them from play.
I assume that he'll use Holy Elf as a sacrifice to Summon a stronger Monster.
I'll just have to spring this Trap!
Perfect!
I cover one reverse card,
then end my turn!
Yugi, look! There's a door over there!
You're right! Let's check it out!
You guys?!
Jounouchi?!
Jounouch-kun!?
Hey! Yugi, Anzu, you guys alright?
Silence.
Observers, go and sit
in the spectator seats!
Y-Yes.
You guys arrived just at the right time.
Just stay over there and admire the moment that I beat this guy.
Lets resume the Duel.
Draw!
Jounouch-kun doesn't have any Monsters on the field...
And it's his opponent's turn.
Will he be okay?
I Summon the
Magic-Type Black Curtain!
And I open my reverse card! Fusion!
By fusing Holy Elf
and Magic-Type Dark Curtain,
I Summon the Chaos Wizard!!
By Summoning that Monster,
you fell right into my trap.
1300 Attack Points?
If his Attack Power isn't at least 1500, the Trap Card won't activate!
I'll then activate the Magic Card, Plea of Darkness!
This lets any Level 4 or lower Fusion Monster I control attack in the turn they are Fusion Summoned!
Chaos Wizard, Direct Attack the player Katsuya Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi!
-Jounouchi-kun!
Plea of Darkness...
If I remember correctly,
it's a Continuous Magic that also increases the player's Life Points by 800 whenever they attack with a Level 4 or lower Fusion Monster.
What did you say?
Exactly!
I'll then place one card face-down and end my turn!
I didn't expect that guy
to recover his Life...
It took so much effort to back him into a corner in the first place!
With Judge Man's Deck Master Ability and the effects of his Continuous Magic Card, Jounouchi's in hot water!
He tries to bet on his Gamble Cards,
but he fails every time, putting him in a dire pinch!
Jounouchi starts to think luck is no longer on his side,
but isn't something
strange going on here?
Next time!
"Betting on Victory"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise