Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
In order to get his brother, Sieg, to accept him, Leon-kun struggles.
He has activated the card Sieg gave him, Golden Castle of Stromberg.
But it was really a trap he set in order to infect Kaiba Corporation's computers with a virus!
If we don't destroy the Golden Castle, the computer virus can't be stopped.
But how do we destroy a card that is immune to Magic and Trap Cards?
"Closing of the KC Grand Prix"
You say you are going to destroy Golden Castle of Stromberg?
I did!
But if Leon-kun can't surrender and he ends up losing, the virus program can't be stopped!
Plus, Traps and Magics can't be used against that card!
How's Yugi gonna do it?!
Huh? Brother?
You choose to run away, Kaiba?
This Duel is Yugi's battle.
And I have my own battle to fight.
Wait up, Brother!
Anything you try now is a waste of effort.
Now then, let's continue the Duel, Leon.
I want you to come at me with everything you've got.
And I'll fight you with all I've got in return.
For all of the Duelists, we can't lose!
And we'll save Leon-kun!
Yeah.
Yugi-san...
I almost lost something I couldn't get back...
But if I've still got a chance to save it...
I'll just believe in Yugi-san!
My turn. Draw!
How utterly futile!
At this moment, one of the effects of Golden Castle of Stromberg activates!
Black Magician Girl's moving against her will...!
Black Magician Girl was...!
On top of that, Yugi lost more of his Life Points!
No way...
As long as Golden Castle of Stromberg exists, both parties are forced to battle one another.
And when the opponent's Monster attacks,
half of the Monster's Attack Power is taken to the player as damage, and the Monster is destroyed.
An ability like that isn't even possible!
That's overpowered, isn't it?!
Yes. That's why there is supposed to be risks involved with using it.
Yeah. It's supposed to come with a very high maintenance cost.
Delete all programs infected by the virus!
We must prevent anything else from being infected!
-Yes, sir!
Brother, let me help out!
Mokuba...
Good. I want you to handle raising the security to its highest level.
Okay!
Let me take care of that!
Leon was willing to do anything to win for Sieg...
I won't forgive anyone who betrays their little brother's feelings!
I'm not gonna let that guy do what he wants!
Magics and Traps won't work...
The moment I Summon a Monster, I lose a great deal of Life Points and it's destroyed.
But unless I Summon, I'll be Direct Attacked.
I can't win like this... But still...!
Yugi-san!
Leon! Don't give up!
Neither will I! I'll fight until the very last moment!
And break this horrible trap!
I place a card face-down and finish my turn.
Yugi-san is a True Duelist, whom I've admired for so long...
That same person is asking me to fight him with everything I've got...!
That's why I'm going to believe in him and fight!
My turn!
Draw!
I told you, did I not?
Everything you do is meaningless.
This card is an invincible castle!
In order to keep Golden Castle of Stromberg in play,
you must discard half of your deck into the Cemetery every turn.
And the opposing player is to pay that maintenance cost!
What?!
Why the hell does the opposing player have to pay the maintenance cost?!
Don't tell me he's altered the text data again...!
Originally, that outrageous maintenance cost was placed to make it a difficult card to use in a Duel.
I can't believe he changed it so the opposing player bears the burden...
Brother, how could you?!
Na, Yugi Mutou. You are to place half of your deck into the Cemetery.
Shit! He can't do anything now!
Dammit!
Leonhart, Special Summon a Level Four or lower Monster from your deck!
Brother!
No matter what the outcome of this Duel, no one can stop the virus from invading.
It is only a matter of time before Kaiba Corporation's main computer comes crashing down.
Sweet! Ruiz, attack!
Huh? That's odd...
My guy's acting weird too...
Why not continue this farce before everything disappears?
Na!
Let's continue, Leon!
I attack Forest Wolf in Attack Mode!
According to Golden Castle of Stromberg, an unavoidable battle will begin!
God! Yugi doesn't have a Monster on the field!
Yugi!
And now, the grand finale!
Yugi-san!
Reverse card, open!
Retribution of Black Magic!
When my opponent attacks, this card allows me to Special Summon a Spellcaster from my Graveyard!
Come forth, Black Magician Girl!
The Spellcaster-Type Monster revived by Retribution of Black Magic
is destroyed at the end of the Battle Phase.
He made it though somehow!
But if this continues...!
If he's able to get through one turn, the situation only gets even worse.
My turn is complete.
My turn. Draw!
It's been three turns since you activated the effects of Spinning Wheel Spindle!
That means Queen's Knight is returned!
I place two reverse cards...
Then I activate the Magic Card, Treasure from Heaven, from my hand!
Using this effect, both players draw from their decks until they have six cards in their hands!
I Summon King's Knight in Attack Mode!
And when Queen's Knight and King's Knight are both on the field,
I can Special Summon Jack's Knight from the deck!
Regardless of how many Monsters you Summon, they are all wasted before Golden Castle of Stromberg.
And you're certain of that?
Magic Card, activate!
Royal Straight!
This card lets me sacrifice Queen's Knight, King's Knight and Jack's Knight...
...in order to Special Summon Royal Straight Slasher from either my deck, hand or Graveyard!
Then, I activate Royal Straight Slasher's Special Effect!
By sending Monsters to my Graveyard consisting of Level One through Level Five respectively,
I can destroy every card on my opponent's side of the field!
I didn't think of that!
Since it's a Monster Effect, he can destroy that irritating card!
Level One!
Kuriboh!
Level Two!
Old Vindictive Magician!
Level Three!
Giant Soldier of Stone!
Level Four!
Big shield Gardna!
Level Five!
Curse of Dragon!
Go, Royal Straight Slasher!
Ultimate Five Crush!!
Yes!
He did it!
Why?
Why wasn't it destroyed?!
That's not right!
A pity it is.
Don't tell me, it was you?!
Since he already manipulated the text data,
it's only natural that he would make it immune to Monster Effects.
You asshole! That's going way too far!
So that means we're out of options?!
I activate the Worm Slip Magic Card from my hand!
I can remove a Monster on my field from the game until my opponent's next Standby Phase.
Turn end.
So you're erasing your own Monster to prevent it from being killed in the next battle?
You waste your time.
Na, Leonhart! It is not time for you to drop the curtain!
Yugi-san...
I... believe in you!
My turn!
Draw!
Na, Yugi Mutou!
As per the cost of Golden Castle of Stromberg, you are to send half of your deck into the Cemetery.
Well, that's a shame.
Because I can't do that.
What?
Take a look!
I only have one card left in my deck!
In this situation, I can't meet the requirements for the maintenance cost.
As a result, Golden Castle of Stromberg will be destroyed!
What?!
Absurd!
Yugi-san!
So that's what Yugi was after!
Magics and Traps won't work.
His Monsters are forced into battle and destroyed.
But there is no card that is completely untouchable.
Right.
That's one of the traps set in this game.
That's the other Yugi for you.
Brother! The virus program stopped!
So you were able to find the card's weakness.
I see! It was Yugi!
Make a copy of every program
on the backup system!
Then set up a system restore!
This instant!
How's that?
That's as far as your plan goes, pal!
Honestly speaking, I am quite surprised.
That you could manage to destroy Golden Castle of Stromberg...!
However, my victory has not changed!
Freakin' sore loser.
My virus program has already deeply invaded Kaiba Corporation's main computer!
There is no doubt in my mind that it has already reached the Duel System.
It simply means that you took too long to destroy Golden Castle of Stromberg!
Plus, you only have a single card remaining in your deck!
The next draw you take will be your last.
As soon as you draw your next card, you admit your loss at the same time!
Yugi-san...
I'm satisfied enough to have made it this far in the battle...
I think I will, after all...
Leon, no matter how impossible the situation may seem,
I will fight on until
I have no more cards in my deck!
Now that I've gotten rid of that unsightly trap, our real battle is about to begin!
Come!
Yugi-san...!
Yes!
According to Worm Slip's effect,
Royal Straight Slasher, who vanished into the worm hole, will return to the field!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Resurrection of the Dead!
I Special Summon Cinderella from my Cemetery!
And when Cinderella is successfully Summoned,
the Pumpkin Carriage can be Special Summoned!
I then sacrifice Cinderella and her Pumpkin Carriage!
I Summon Hexe Trude in Attack Position!
I'm going now, Yugi-san!
Hexe Trude attacks!
Destine Crush!!
When Hexe Trude destroys one of the opponent's Monsters,
her Attack Power goes up 400 points.
My turn is over.
Yugi's up against a Monster with 3000 Attack Points, with only one card in his deck!
Can he even do anything with that one card?!
He's got no choice.
If he doesn't draw a card, Yugi-kun will lose!
But Yugi hasn't given up!
I believe in my deck until the very end.
My turn!
Draw!
I set one card in reverse!
And a Magic Card from my hand!
I activate Emergency Provisions!
By sending a Magic or Trap Card to the Graveyard while this card is in play,
my Life Points increase by 1000 per card!
And then, a Magic Card!
Resurrection of the Dead!
You aren't...!
Come forth, Black Magician!
Black Magician!
But Black Magician only has 2500 Attack Points.
He's still no match for Hexe Trude.
Reverse card, open.
Necromancy!
This card lets me select up to four Monsters from my opponent's Graveyard at random,
and Summon them on my opponent's field in Defense Mode.
And for each one of these Monsters that is destroyed, Hexe Trude loses 600 Attack Points!
And I open my reverse card!
Diffusion Wave-Motion!
I pay 1000 Life Points
to use Diffusion Wave-Motion,
It allows a Level Seven or higher Spellcaster-Type Monster on my field
to attack every one of your Monsters at once!
What did you say!?
Go! Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
Awright! He did it!
-Yugi!
Mhm! That's my grandson for you!
That was a magnificent Duel.
Impossible...!
Leon.
Yugi-san...
I...
I...!
You did an excellent job not giving up until the very end of this Duel.
You are a True Duelist!
Yugi-san...!
It matters not who the winner of the Duel was!
Sieg!
Brother!
In order to fully restore Kaiba Corporation's computers infected by my virus program,
a great deal of time is needed!
And during that time-
You really think I don't have the skills for this?!
You overestimated your own ability and made a serious miscalculation.
What?
From the moment you first made your move,
I was analyzing all possible scenarios and making necessary preparations.
Restoration of the main computer has already finished.
It no longer poses a threat!
T-There's no way that's true...!
I... I...!
Give up already, Brother.
Leonhart...
I'm sure you know deep down, Brother.
That doing things like this won't get us anywhere.
Does this mean that I was unable to beat Kaiba from the very start...?
Not "I".
No one can!
Say, Brother...
I've come to understand something after the events today...
You can give up and let it all end.
But as long as you never give up and keep trying, you'll be able to get somewhere eventually.
I may not be able to do exactly what you'd like me to do...
But I really would like to be of help to you, Brother.
Please share your suffering with me from now on, Brother.
Leonhart...!
Isono.
Yes, sir!
Sponsored by Kaiba Corporation, the KC Grand Prix - the greatest Duel Tournament ever held!
The Duel King is Yugi Mutou!
Man~!
Finally we get to return to Japan!
I'm eating a Japanese-style meal the second I get home!
I've got some work to take care of here, but I'll return to Japan eventually as well.
Sure! We'll be waiting for you!
I really want to see Shizuka-chan again.
-Don't come back!
Don't strain yourself too hard, Sugoroku.
C'mon! I'm not ready to lose to these youngsters just yet!
See? You're all bark and no bite.
Yugi, we didn't get to this time, but I'd like to Duel you again one of these days.
Sure!
I'm looking forward to it!
Take care, Darling!
R-Rebecca...!
I'll stop by Japan one of these days so we can play a bit!
Sure...
I'll be waiting.
Hey! What're you guys waiting for?!
We went through the trouble of preparing a plane for you...
You don't want a ride anymore?
It's this late already?!
Shoot!
Let's gun it!
Yup!
W-Wait up!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
A lot happened during the KC Grand Prix, but everything ended okay I guess.
And we finally made it back to Japan!
Oh yeah! Kaiba Corporation made a huge climb back into business after that!
And it looks like the Kaiba Land plan will be successful.
But I'm only able to be happy for a little bit...
After all, the other Yugi is getting ready to set off on a journey to find his lost memory.
Next time!
"The Ultimate Game"
Duel standby!