With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Mokuba, are you okay?
Big brother, I didn't give anyone the key!
Mokuba!
I protected Kaiba Corporation!
Wait, I'll get you out!
Bravo!
It's touching to see you two together!
Pegasus...!
Mokuba!
That's...!
This is a Soul Sealing Card.
I'll be looking after Mokuba boy's soul for a bit.
What did you say?
If you want Mokuba boy back,
you'll have to defeat me in a Duel.
Fine! I challenge you right now!
You can't fight me right now.
First you must fight with Yugi boy.
You can only face me
if you defeat Yugi boy.
"The Destined Battle!
Yugi VS Kaiba"
If you cannot defeat Yugi boy,
you will never get a chance to fight me.
And of course, Mokuba boy's soul
will never be released from this card.
Pegasus... you bastard...!
Why are you doing this?
You should be aware of this...
Just like the ends of this tie,
tightly pulling against each other, sharing the same fate...
Bound together in a fate of fighting one another.
The time has come for two Duelists
to intersect once again.
You can't mean...!
Yes!
You must bet those Star Chips in your fight with Yugi boy.
If you win, Kaiba Corporation's reputation
will surely be returned to what it was.
I am positive they eagerly await your return...
Pegasus... right now I have no choice but to do what you say...
but while I have no clue
how you've done this trick...
If anything happens to Mokuba...
Don't you forget that "tie of fate"
is wrapped around your neck too!
Alright! We're out of that cave at last!
Where on the island are we?
T-this is...
Hey, look!
Isn't that Pegasus' castle?
It really is!
We finally made it here, Yugi.
It's almost over!
Yugi, you appear so gentle right now...
But when I watch you in a game...
you have a look on your face that's almost scary...
There's one Yugi who's gentle and sweet...
and that scary looking Yugi...
as if there really were
two separate Yugis...
That was my first time seeing
both Yugis at the same time...!
There's two Yugis?
That's the other me.
I really didn't get it, but to put it simply, there's a cool Yugi and a normal Yugi here.
It's not like that!
My bad!
All right! I'll show you that I can be cool too!
Hey! Yugi!
I'll defeat the hidden enemy!
Battle!
Wait, Yugi!
Black Magic!!
Another Yugi...?
Was that all just a dream?
Must have been...
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Oi! What are you doing?!
If you slow us down we're gonna
go on without you!
But it'd be pointless for us to enter
Pegasus' castle by ourselves.
That's true.
Now, let's go!
-Owww~
-Geez...
Back then, you were more reliable.
Back then...?
Hi! Welcome!
Two customers, right?
Why are these two guys here?!
It's against school rules to
have a part-time job!
I'm in big trouble now that
that big mouth Jounouchi has seen me!
So she's been working
at Burger World, eh?
Alright! I know her secret!
Knock it off! Anzu's getting mad!
Enjoy our special hamburgers.
Please have lots of our popular ketchup!
Tell and you're dead!
W-why are you doing this...?
Well, you already found out,
so there's no need to lie.
I'm saving money so I can go
to America after I graduate.
America?
What for?
Don't laugh!
Umm....
To study dance in New York!
You're not laughing?
Why would we laugh?
It's your dream.
Amazing! That's amazing! We'll support you!
"After school, meet me in the gymnasium.
If you don't come,
I'll tell everyone your secret"?!
It can't be...!
Jounouchi! Or Yugi!
I know what you guys are planning!
Stay quiet.
You'll be expelled if your school
finds out you've been working!
So you'd better keep your mouth
shut and do what I tell you!
You think I'll just keep
quiet about it later!?
You're in no position to be making threats!
Anzu!
What did you do to Anzu!?
Yugi!
OWW!
Bitch!
If you want to play this sick game,
play with me instead.
What?
What do you say to having
a little game with me?
Game, you said?!
We both draw a card.
The loser is the one with the weakest card.
A one draw match.
However, the loser will be
sent to the Dark World.
Stop joking.
Are you scared?
No!
I got this powerful card,
Curse Of Dragon!
I drew it.
Black Magician!
I win!
What a ridiculous game!
Let's see how you win a man's fight!
I wonder?
Mind Crush!!
A demon was running around here while you were asleep.
Yugi, do you remember?
You saved my life in the gym.
When I woke up, that guy
was already knocked out.
I can't remember now...
Yugi, it's kind of crazy.
It's like there's two separate Yugis.
A cool but scary Yugi.
and a gentle, but not so reliable Yugi.
Actually, sometimes I feel like
I have another me inside myself.
Well, that doesn't really matter.
Because Yugi is Yugi.
Anzu.
OI! YUGI! ANZU!
What are you two doing? Hurry up!
Let's go, Yugi.
Kaiba-kun!
Yugi, as I thought you've earned 10 Star Chips.
As I'd expect.
Kaiba-kun!
I'm not letting you pass.
What's wrong, Kaiba-kun?
What do you mean?
I finally understand my fate on this island.
Yugi.
As long as you live,
you'll always be a thorn in my side.
The winds of battle blow when we fight
like a powerful tornado!
Forever!
Kaiba-kun, stop starting trouble!
Kaiba! I'll be your opponent!
I'll punch your lights out!
YOU BASTARD!
Jounouchi, stop it!
He showed you up the last time you fought!
That's true...
Bakura-kun, that went too far.
I can't believe this loser dog also collected 10 Star Chips.
In that case, I promote you from "loser dog" to "nobody"!
Nobody, you said?!
You sunova...
This is what they call a miracle.
I was searching for an answer after my last match.
"Why did I lose to Yugi in that Duel?"
"How did Yugi summon a miracle at that time?"
And I think I finally found an answer.
At that time, Yugi possessed
something I didn't have...
Is a person stronger when they shoulder
the weight of protecting someone?
The only way to find out is to defeat
you in a Duel.
Yugi, if you want to enter the castle,
you have to defeat me first!
This is a Duel of fate!
Kaiba-kun!
The Kaiba-kun standing before me is different
than the Kaiba-kun in the past.
Something is hidden in those eyes...!
Yugi-kun! You can't accept this Duel!
You already collected
10 Star Chips, it's pointless!
Yugi, you should know!
Our Duelist blood has brought us together
once again!
Duelist... blood?
The other Yugi...!
Kaiba, I understand!
I accept this Duel!
and I will defeat you!
Follow me to the stage of our fight!
10 Star Chips.
Indeed.
Very well. I permit you to enter
Pegasus' castle.
Looks like I'm the first one
to enter Pegasus' castle.
Yugi, we'll each bet 5
Star Chips on this Duel.
Only the one who wins may
enter Pegasus' castle.
Fine!
We'll use Duel Disks for this game.
Shuffle your cards and place your
deck in the Deck Holder on your left arm.
Life Points 2000!
Counter set!
Yugi, don't you lose.
Kick that Kaiba bastard's ass!
Yugi...
Now then, I wonder who my opponents are.
I think I'll enjoy this match from the
castle's balcony.
Those brats!
They got out of the cave?!
That guy's...
The runner of Kaiba Corporation!
This should be an interesting show.
Fine with me.
A great way to kill some time.
Here I go, Yugi!
It's time to determine the strongest!
We'll use these Duel Disks to have the
ultimate card battle!
I'll accept any Duel!
And Kaiba, I will defeat you!
DUEL!!
Here I come!
It's my turn!
Gargoyle Powered in Attack Mode!
The cards...!
It wasn't like that when I fought him!
My turn!
Curse Of Dragon in Attack Mode!
Yugi, though we are enemies now,
we both share the same objectives.
To beat Pegasus!
That's right. But if you really want to
see him defeated
your only option is to lose to me here.
Because it's impossible for you to beat Pegasus!
What?!
Pegasus' card strategy is to read people's minds.
I'm not sure if it's some psychic power,
or a trick of some kind, but it works.
In this card battle, I can use the Solid Vision
to hide my body and face, and keep out of range.
Pegasus' power is useless in front of the Duel Disks!
Kaiba doesn't realize Pegasus' power comes
from the power of the Millennium Items.
I don't think the Duel Disk system will
have an effect on a Dark Game...
Yugi, what's wrong?
Come and get my Gargoyle Powered!
Alright! All there is to do is attack!
Go, Curse Of Dragon!
Attack Gargoyle Powered!
Hell Flame!!
Alright! Gargoyle Powered is beaten!
As I thought, you came at me with no fear.
It was worth taking the first hit and losing Life Points to make sure you're taking this seriously.
It's fine! Don't be scared of Kaiba's bluff, Yugi!
My turn. I'll draw a new card.
Come forth, Swordstalker The Avenger!
Swordstalker the Avenger channels the anger of his fallen comrades into his sword,
and increases his Attack Points up by 20%.
What?
Revenge actually makes his Attack Points stronger...!
Is that why he let me destroy
Gargoyle Powered so easily?!
Now my monster's Attack Points are
greater than Yugi's Curse Of Dragon!
Go, Swordstalker The Avenger!
What?! Curse Of Dragon disappeared!
That's because I have the
Monster Replace card here!
This Magic Card switches a Monster targeted on my board
and switches it with a Monster in my Hand with higher Attack Points.
Monster Replace...!
The Monster in my hand with
the highest Attack is...
Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
Black Magician beat
Swordstalker The Avenger!
Oh yeah!
Kaiba, don't you underestimate Yugi!
Yugi, fighting you again...
makes my heart beat faster.
It's my turn!
I replay Curse Of Dragon in Attack Mode!
Turn end!
It's my turn.
La Jinn, The Genie Of The Lamp!
Yugi, it's your turn!
Black Magician, attack La Jinn,
The Genie Of The Lamp!
Black Magic!!
Trap Card, activate!
Magic Lamp!
What?!
The lamp deflects your attack
at your own Monster!
Curse Of Dragon is destroyed!
Kaiba! To trap me...
I applaud you!
Yugi, the real trap I've set for you
is just beginning..!
The heart of the world's strongest Monster
has already begun to beat in my hand...
That's right...
I'm going to fuse 3 Blue-Eyes!
"Preview"
Kaiba-kun and Yugi continue their Duel.
Be careful!
We don't know what Kaiba-kun is planning!
Deck Destruction Virus of Death!
All of Yugi's Monsters with more than
1500 Attack Points are destroyed! No way!
Wait a minute! What's that?!
Has the fusion of 3 Blue-Eyes
White Dragons been completed?!
Next time: "The Strongest! The Magnificent!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon"
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship