Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Behold!
Magic Card! Cup of Sealed Soul!
Then I open my reverse card!
Seal of Selket!
And the Temple of the Royal Family!
When I gather these three Magic Cards together,
I can Summon the Mystical Beast, who protects the secrets of the alter!
Mystical Beast?
That's right! The guardian of the temple!
The Scorpion God that shall devour your Monsters!
Show your glorious form before us!
I Summon the Mystical Beast, Selket!
What the hell?!
Another monster just appeared!
The Mystical Beast Selket exists to guard the sacred card sealed in the ark!
Sacred card?
So then, the card you sealed in that ark...!
Yes! It's the God Card!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
"Summon the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra"
Mystical Beast Selket is only a demigod who protects the true god within the shrine!
Are you freakin' serious...?!
I've only got 200 Life Points left...
I can't stand up to such a powerful Monster...!
What do I do...?!
He tried so hard to push Malik into the corner...
Jounouchi...
Yugi-san, is there anything my brother can do to win this?
The Monsters Jounouchi-kun has on the field don't stand a chance against Selket.
If he doesn't think of something fast...
Malik will destroy every single one of Jounouchi-kun's Wall Monsters!
By the way, Yugi...
That ark...
The one the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra is in...
His God Card...
So I guess he is Malik...
But why don't I consider him the real Malik...?
Lord Malik, why did you place the God Card in my deck?
Rishid... you must play my role more realistically.
But...
That is a Ra copy card!
A duplicate card?
Right! With the Ghouls' "Rare Card Duplication Technology",
even God Cards can be mass-produced!
But of course, my card is the original card.
In that case, this card...
Indeed, even the copy card is the type of card that chooses its owner.
In the past, a number of Ghouls experimented by playing with decks of copy God Cards.
And as a result, some were killed the moment they played them.
Some even went crazy and lost their minds!
Perhaps this is what they call "God's Curse"?
After more experiments, one fact became clear...
Copy God Cards react to the hearts of their wielder.
But a descendant of the Tomb Guardians that have thrived for 3,000 years might succeed!
Rishid, you have lived among the Tomb Guardians.
If your heart as grown strong enough as a result,
you should be able to control the god!
I'm very sorry, Lord Malik...
I don't need God's help to win this Duel!
Because Selket was Summoned using a Ritual Magic Card, it cannot attack this turn!
Therefor my turn shall now end.
That saved me!
I'm gonna take a bet here!
My turn! Draw!
I don't have a high-level Monster to stop his attacks.
I don't even have a Magic Card to turn this around!
All my Monsters go to Defense Mode!
And my turn's over!
The Sealing Swords of Light...!
Now he at least has a chance to fight back...
Then it is my turn.
Draw!
Here I come, Jounouchi!
I attack you with Mystical Beast Selket!
Your target is Psycho Shocker!
I-It's eating it!
I know it is an unpleasant sight to behold,
but that is Selket's Special Ability, which has now activated.
Special Ability?
Selket takes enemies inside itself,
and adds half of their Attack Points to its own!
3700 Attack Points!
And it changed to a different shape!
A Monster with the ability to add its enemy's power to its own?
In that case...
It's gonna get stronger and stronger if he doesn't do something soon!
Jounouchi-kun...
My turn!
No good... I couldn't do a thing this turn...
Turn end!
My turn! Selket attacks!
Our next sacrifice shall be the Insect Queen!
Insect Queen has been defeated!
It now absorbs her Attack Power!
Sorry, Haga...
Your card was...
Endure it, Jounouchi!
Believe in the card you draw next turn!
Big brother...!
I can't! I just can't watch anymore!
Don't you run, Shizuka!
Look at me!
I might lose this, but...
I want you to watch until the end!
Big brother...
You found light in the deep darkness.
A light called courage!
So no matter what happens, don't you run back there!
Okay!
Light in the deep darkness...
That "light" is the story of my life.
When I met the Ishtar couple,
I was given light.
It was a deep, dark world with no contact to the outside world...
And one night I accidentally overheard the secret of the Ishtar family...
...the fate of the Tomb Guardians.
The Millennium Rod
and the Millennium Tauk...
Both the Millennium Items and the Pharaoh's memories that sleep in darkness.
Protecting them is the duty of us Tomb Guardians.
I must not fail to pass down this 3,000 year history to the next generation.
Dear, if we are not blessed with a boy...
When Rishid becomes ten...
let's accept him as our son.
But that child is not a true member of our clan.
But perhaps God meant for him to be!
Perhaps the Rite of the Tomb Guardians could be performed on Rishid!
Let's name her Ishizu...
The successor of the Tomb Guardians must be a boy!
Rishid... I have something important to tell you.
When you turn ten,
we would like to make you a member of our tribe.
But to do that, you must undergo the Rite of the Tomb Guardians.
The rite of the Tomb Guardians...?
The Rite of the Tomb Guardians is a cruel trial!
Despite that...
Despite that, are you prepared to undergo the ritual?
Yes! So by doing it, I can become your real son?!
Yes!
Dear...!
You've done well!
It's a perfectly healthy boy!
Mother!
Rishid...! Please take care... of your little brother...!
Mother!!
The successor of the Tomb Guardians!
The pedigree of darkness!!
Wow! You're amazing, Rishid!
I'm next!
Lord Malik!
How the hell did this happen when you were right by his side?!
If anything happens to Malik,
I'll rip out your heart and tear it to pieces!
I'm very sorry!
In order for our family to live on the next generation,
it's not you we need!
It's Malik!!
Don't you dare leave this room until Malik regains his conscious!
I'm sorry, brother...
I'm so sorry... You're always getting beat up because of me...
Did you just address me as your brother?
I've always thought
of you as my big brother...
Lord Malik...
Lord Malik!!
Lord Malik, here is your dinner.
I'm not hungry.
And why not?
You should at least have a little soup.
Leave me alone!
Lord Malik...
I'm sorry, Rishid...
Rishid...
Have you ever seen my father's back?
No.
He's got the markings of the Rite of the Tomb Guardians.
The successor of the Tomb Guardians
had the secrets of the Pharaoh's memories carved onto his back...
And he must protect
these secrets with his life!
I had no idea...
I have to undergo the ritual on my birthday next week!
They say the pain is so bad you'll scream for a month!
I'm really scared of it!
Lord Malik...
I don't think I can take it!
I might even die!
Why...?!
Why do I have to go through with it?!
Lord Malik, please be at ease.
I will ask Lord Ishtar to allow me to take the ritual in your place.
B-But...
It is fine.
I have been
prepared for a long time now.
What?!
You'll undergo the ritual?!
I know it's an unreasonable request!
But Lord Malik is too scared to take the ritual himself!
I felt very bad for him!
I will protect the secrets of the Tomb Guardians!
I only have one wish...!
All I wish is to undergo the ritual and be called your son!
Nonsense!!
You're just a servant!!
If you ever talk of our secrets again,
I'll cut off your miserable tongue!
Out of my sight!!
Help me! Help me, Rishid!
Rishid, help me!!
Rishid!
RISHID!!
Malik...! My dear little brother...!
It hurts...! It really hurts...!
I have come to change your bandages...
Don't touch me!!
Please tell me...
Please tell me, Rishid...
Who do I hate for this?!
Rishid...
Your face...
I cannot share the pain that you are suffering from, Lord Malik.
Rishid...
Then at the very least...
I shall swear allegiance to your family with this scar.
Rishid...
We will eliminate Yugi and anyone else who stands in our way!
This is our revenge on the nameless Pharaoh...
of the clan of the Tomb Guardians!
As you wish, Lord Malik...
Don't give up.
Jounouchi...
My turn!
Give up your hopes of defeating me.
Mystical Beast Selket keeps growing by absorbing my Monster's Attack Points...
It grows into a stronger Monster each time...!
Its Attack Power is already 4900!
No good... I don't have any cards that can turn this around...
I'll switch my Fisherman into Defense Mode and end my turn!
You...
Despite this situation,
you actually plan to continue Dueling?
That's insulting, Malik!
It may be useless to continue fighting,
but I have something
I want to accomplish!
So I'll fight on until my Life hits 0!
I respect your spirit.
Big brother...
Yugi, I'm sure you know...
No matter how hard Jounouchi may try to turn this situation around...
...this is just one
match Jounouchi can't turn around...
Jounouchi can't win this Duel.
Mai...
Look at him.
Bring it!
What's that... look?
But there's no way he can win the Duel!
But his fighting spirit still hasn't disappeared from his eyes?!
Those are the eyes of someone prepared for anything!
This...
That's right.
The tension on this battlefield reflects both of their Duelist's pride.
They are both honored
they met each other.
Their fighting spirit is flooding
throughout the entire field...
No matter what happens in this Duel,
these two will not stop fighting until the very end.
My turn.
Here I come!
Attack, Selket!
Devour the Legendary Fisherman!
Now grow, Mystical Beast Selket!
Please forgive me, Kajiki...
I couldn't protect your card...
Now, Jounouchi, it's your turn.
Your last one, that is.
There's nothing I can do...
Turn over!
Jounouchi!
Big brother!
When Malik attacks on his next turn, Jounouchi...
I suppose I should at least praise you for fighting as a lab rat.
At this point, Jounouchi's chances of winning have fallen to zero!
Well done, Rishid!
It's your victory!
"What you can see, but can't see..."
I got a funny feeling...
A little while ago, I reached the point where I was resigned to losing...
And just then, when winning or losing didn't matter...
...it's like I saw something
I couldn't see before.
Why didn't I figure it out sooner?
Must have been the heat of battle...
Malik brainwashed me.
He forced me to fight my friend in a Duel to the death...
A pointless battle that
only hurt our hearts.
I can't forgive the bastard who set up that Duel and forced us to fight!
Then go ahead and curse me.
But a match is different.
That anger is not enough to defeat me.
That's not what I'm trying to say!
When this Duel started,
I really hated your guts!
But I've lost that hatred now...
And I tried to remember...
How terrible it felt when that bastard took over my mind and implanted his memory!
But you didn't use any cheap tricks and fought me fair and square!
I may lose to you...
...but while fighting against you in this Duel, it became one of the best I've had!
You're the real deal!
You're a True Duelist!
I may not know your reasons,
but I do know one thing!
You aren't the guy who did that before!
You aren't Malik!
Impossible!
He's not Malik?
He's not the wielder of God?!
Just as I thought...
His strategies are much different than the ones I faced before.
And more importantly, I don't feel a Power of Darkness coming from him.
An enemy you can see, but can't see!
He's somewhere else!
Then where's the real Malik?!
Could it be...?!
This is bad...
If this goes on, my plan will be ruined!
If my identity as Malik is discovered,
I won't be able to probe Kaiba's mind
and find out if he was the previous wielder of the Millennium Rod.
And I won't be able to learn the secrets of that palette...!
What utter bullshit!
This Millennium Rod is proof that I am Malik!
This Duel shall continue as I have foreseen,
and no one listens to the words of a loser!!
My turn!
Finish him off, Mystical Beast Selket!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!
Sorry, Yugi...
This is as far as I go!
-Jounouchi-kun!
-Big brother!
Jounouchi!
Wait, Rishid!
Don't attack him!!
Why, Lord Malik?!
Kill Jounouchi...
by the hands of the God Card!!
In order for our plan to work,
you must prove you are the wielder of a God Card!
You are Malik, Rishid!
Summon Ra from
within the ark in the temple!
Use the Counterfeit God Card!!
"Preview"
After finally Summoning the third God Card, Winged Sun Dragon of Ra,
Jounouchi can't do a thing!
Is it all over, Jounouchi?!
Ra won't attack?
Suddenly, a huge thunderstorm roars across the Battle Ship!
Is this "God's wrath"?!
Next time!
"Ra's Anger!
Stand Up, Jounouchi!"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise