Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Rebeca and Otogi
challenged Varon to a Duel.
But up against the mysterious abilities of Varon's Armor Deck, they were defeated in an instant.
Is he aiming for Jounouchi-kun?
At the same time, Kaiba is taking his own private plane towards the museum in Florida.
But the aurora appeared in the sky again and hindered the path ahead with a veil of haze.
"The Revenging Amelda - The Great Airborne Duel"
The icy waters are so comfortable~
Are you okay?
Y-Yeah.
No problem at all.
If I just soak my feet for a bit,
the pain should-
Please don't force yourself.
Let's rest here for a bit.
I'm sorry, Yugi.
We shouldn't be wasting time like this...
Don't let it bother you. Jounouchi-kun and Honda-kun should already be close by.
Yeah.
Hey, Jounouchi...
You go ahead first!
Y-You should...
Didn't you say you ain't afraid of nothing?
But long and soft things are an exception!
When we lost control of Duel Monsters, auroras also appeared all over the world.
Seto...
What's happening, captain?
Answer me! Hey! Captain!
Let me go and have a look.
How weird... There's no one onboard!
Big Brother...
Humph! What's the matter, Kaiba?
What are you worrying about?
This voice is...
You bastard...!
Looks like you finally realized what's going on, Kaiba.
Amelda, where are you?! Come out!
Seto, the cockpit!
Brother...
The plane is set to autopilot mode...
Kaiba!
Not there.
This way.
Tch... What dumb tricks he's pulling...
What are you doing? I am over here.
You scumbag...! You'll pay for this!
Being able to see you again makes me happy, Seto Kaiba.
Amelda!
Where'd the rest of the crew run off to, you lowlife?
I have no need for people unrelated to our conflict to be in the middle of our battlefield.
There was never anyone of the sort onboard from the getco.
What?
As long as we have the power of Doma, such a thing is a simple task.
Now, Kaiba...
Shall we settle our Duel once and for all?
My little brother was...
...killed by your company!
Stop it, Amelda! Your fight against my brother was a mistake to begin with!
I told you before that this is revenge.
Amelda...
Hmph...
I don't care what intentions you have...
But in a Duel, only the one that is calm and collected can be the victor.
Yes, only the strong can win.
Big Brother, please stop!
I will accept this Duel!
Hmph, as if you had a choice...
Kaiba, I'm going to watch as your soul is taken from you...
...and give Miruko peace of mind!
Seto...
Duel!!
I will go first. Draw!
I Summon Science Special Soldier in Defense Position.
Turn end!
My turn, draw.
I Summon X-Head Cannon in Attack Position!
Attack Science Special Soldier!
Why must Amelda and Big Brother do such a thing?
My turn, draw.
I Summon Machine Soldier of the Demon World in Defense Position.
Next I set one card and end my turn.
My turn, draw.
I Summon Y-Dragon Head in Attack Position.
Y-Dragon Head, attack Machine Soldier of Demon World!
Next, I use X-Head Cannon to Direct Attack the player!
I set one reverse card, ending my turn.
My turn. Draw.
As expected of you, Kaiba.
To think that you can Summon two Monsters in such a short time and give me a Direct Attack.
And you've got much more to show, I bet.
But if that's the case, then this place will be a little cramped.
We will need a more spacious room to fight.
Don't tell me... you've drawn that card?!
Stand back, Mokuba!
Stand back!!
Activate this instant!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!
You bastard...
What is this?
This card that has been tainted by everything will awaken the darkness in your soul.
I will let you see what both me and my brother saw from Hell.
Amelda, you...
Seto?
Amelda!
Where are you, Big Brother?!
The plane's altitude has fallen.
Don't tell me...
Autopiloting has been deactivated.
It's no use, I can't move it.
Oh yeah, the control station! Gotta contact the control station!
Please, you must be connected! Please!
This is?
Hey, hurry it up.
Please be careful.
Wait for me...
I won't be deceived.
This is the occult supernatural illusions that Amelda wants me to see.
Hey, looks like you've woken up, mister.
If you're awake, get on outta here.
This is our hiding spot.
You guys...
What's all this garbage?
That ain't garbage! We picked them up from the city streets.
Many useful things are dropped in the war.
Dennis!
War?
They drop things like this...?
We're gonna pass those things to our own people protecting the city.
So we can get the enemy outta our city and put an end to this war.
Chess, huh...?
Mister, you can play chess?
Your name is?
Yuan.
What are you doing, Yuan? If you're not gonna eat, then go back to the streets and collect some more stuff.
Your "collection" is the worst.
But...
Just get on with it!
I know...
I know that all of this is just an illusion.
I also know that Amelda wants to use these illusions to waver my thoughts.
But I...
What's wrong, mister?
Tony and Dennis both lost their parents in this war.
And it's not just us. Almost half the kids living in this city are like that too.
But for me, I still have Tony and Dennis.
So I'm not lonely at all!
Amelda, what do you want me to see here...?!
Mister, you know how to play chess, right?
That chess board belongs to me.
Wanna play me, mister?
This big one is the King, and this is the Queen.
Now, I will move this here.
Stop it...
Checkmate.
Again...
You're just as
good as always, big brother!
It's your turn now, mister.
Come on!
So you're playing it like this!
Then I will play like that.
That came from the Church!
Tony! Dennis!
Wait, it's dangerous!
Let go of me!
Big Brother!
Mokuba...
This is all just a deceiving illusion!
I won't believe in this, Amelda!
End this dirty trick immediatly!
Amelda!!
Amelda!
Yuan...!
You actually created such a ridiculously fake illusion?!
That was not fake. That was based off of real events.
That kid died after being struck by military fire soon after that.
What?
In this city, such a sight is not rare.
My little brother, Miruko, also died like that.
Now, let us continue with the game, Kaiba!
I used KC-1 Clayton and the Trap Card on my field, Tank Corp,
to Summon three Tokens and attack your Y-Dragon Head.
KC-1 Clayton's ATK will increase by 500 for every Token on the field.
And so, your Life will decrease by 2000 points.
Next, I set one card face-down and end my turn!
Kaiba, it's your turn!
My turn!!
I activate a Magic Card!
Resurrection of the Dead!
I will revive Y-Dragon Head and next, I Summon Z-Metal Caterpiller!
I will combine all three - X-Head Cannon, Y-Dragon Head and Z-Metal Caterpiller!
To Special Summon XYZ-Dragon Cannon!
Activate XYZ-Dragon Cannon's Special Effect!
By discarding one card from my hand, I can destroy one of my opponent's cards on the field!
Because the Tokens have disappared, KC-1 Clayton's ATK will go down.
Next, I will use XYZ-Dragon Cannon to attack KC-1 Clayton!
Eliminate the enemy! Go, XYZ Hyper Cannon!
Kaiba.
I can feel your anguish and sorrow.
That is what happens to us in the midst of war!
I... I'm just battling during my turn!
This is a "Duel"!
To me, this is reality.
But even so, I am still praying from that war.
I am praying that all weapons will disappear from this world.
I am praying for a peaceful world with no war to become a reality.
But this is not possible at all.
There are people like Gozaburo Kaiba crawling all over this world.
Back then... and now as well!
Weapons will not disappear and humans will never stop fighting.
Thus, this kind of world might as well be destroyed!
And from the scraps of "zero", a world with no war can be built!
I realized this one day...
No, I realized this because I was awoken by Doma!
And for that aim, I will need your soul!
Mokuba!
That's right...
Kaiba.
We're in the middle of a match here!
In my next turn, I am going to draw out my key card that will send you to your grave.
I am going to use that card to take your soul away!
This is all for the sake of returning the world to zero!
My turn! Draw!!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Because of Amelda's attack, Kaiba-kun's plane has lost control and is decreasing in altitude.
Mokuba-kun can't regain control by himself!
But unless Kaiba-kun beats Amelda in this Duel, he can't escape from the barrier!
And then Amelda finally plays his trump card!
What's that Monster...?!
Next time!
"Sky Devil Fortress Ziggurat"
Duel standby!