Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Retrained Elf Swordsman, attack Ipiria!
At this moment, I activate my Deck Master Ability!
So he did it?
I sacrifice Ipiria and Youi!
And launch the Reflector Hole!!
Which makes the attack of the enemy Monster invalid
and in return steals the Attack Points from the opponent's Life Points!
He's coming...!
''Counterattacking Rainbow Arch''
I have to endure this!
Draw!
Not too shabby. It holds 2200 Attack Points, so it could be useful.
But using Eingana to give a fatal strike is not entertaining in the least.
I Summon Melchid, the Four-Faced Beast in Attack Mode!
I don't think I'll have to attack you anymore this turn,
but your Retrained Elf Swordsman is really an eyesore on your side of the field.
Since I can't defeat him with a Monster holding 1900 Attack Points or greater,
it's a really irritating Monster.
However, a less powerful Monster
will be more than enough to strike down that Retrained Elf Swordsman of yours.
Go!! Melchid, the Four-Faced Beast!!
Attack Retrained Elf Swordsman, then use your
remaining power to strike the enemy player!
Where am I?
Ouch.
Right then, I couldn't touch the flower.
What's going on this time?
Isn't this all just virtual images?
Or will I be... by them...?
Is it over?
I can't just sit here.
Somewhere out there... the others are trying their hardest!
What?
I-It's not over yet!
I still have... 400 Life Points left!
This guy still has the strength to stand up?
This is no joke! I can't take any more damage or it'll be bad!
If I take just one more hit, I'm in trouble!
I can tell my body is throbbing in pain!
It would be much easier for you to stay down on the ground.
But since you did stand up, I have no choice.
I'll beat on you until you never get up again!
Thanks to that Deck Master Ability of his,
no matter which of his Monsters on the field I attack, I'm done for!
Plus, my hand is at zero.
What should I do?
I end my turn.
Allow me to give you a small present of hope as you wallow in despair.
A Prussian General once said:
"The crown of honor belongs only to the final victor.
The end justifies the means.
Thus, only the one who stands victorious when all is said in done is the true winner.
So try your best.
My turn! Draw!
Rainbow Blessing?
Unfortunately, this card won't be enough to get me out of this...!
Yeah, keep thinking about it.
But there's another saying...
"When you have the upper hand in a pinch, you gain the courage to carry on.
But when you face a pinch you have no control over, you lose all hope."
So do you have
control over the situation?
It's not good to think too much.
Kuriboh... what are you trying to say?
I think Kuriboh's telling us to set it face-down on the field.
I think the only way to change this situation is to use your Deck Master Ability, Kuriboh!
Mmm-hmm!
I'll set one card on the field in reverse position!
Turn end!
Where's my opponent?!
How long do I have to wait?
Get out here already so we can start the Duel!
This isn't a joke.
I have to get away from here!
You want to... rescue me?
What's going on with this sense of reality?
Is this Virtual Reality really this revolutionary of a system?
This Virtual Reality that imitates feeling...!
You're still way too naive, Seto...
The system that you built had a safe-guarding device that didn't harm the human brain or body.
But this Virtual Reality...
It's like there's no safe-guard installed at all...
There is a dangerous atmosphere everywhere around this space.
What is this Noah thinking?
If you've got something to say, say it to my face!
Mokuba.
What's up, Brother?
On the road we're walking now, we have no need to look into the past.
Even now, the things I care the most about haven't changed.
Let's go, Mokuba.
Big Brother!
Well, it's my turn.
Draw!
I activate the Instant Quick-Play Magic, Offerings to the Dead, from my hand!
I destroy the only thing you've got to attack me with, Chimera!
Because of the effect of Offerings to the Dead, I can destroy one of your Monsters!
But... the Special Ability that activates only when Chimera is destroyed...
...lets me Special Summon Berfomet!
Heh. Your situation hasn't changed.
Rather, you could even say it's getting worse for you.
What?!
I'll then sacrifice Melchid the Four-Faced Beast and Wall of Illusion...
...to Summon Rainbow Snake Eingana!
I use Rainbow Snake Eingana to attack Berfomet!
Now then... You've lost your wall.
Just like a castle that has had its walls breached.
I only have 400 Life Points left.
And after being attacked by his Ruklomba, I'll be dead.
It's time to really put an end to things.
They see me!
Now then, let me launch the final attack.
I will finally get a body back.
I must thank you.
I use Ruklomba the Spirit King to directly attack the player!
Go, Ruklomba!!
Is this the end?!
I did it.
What in the world?!
Damn you... reduce his Life Points!
Thank you, Kuriboh!
You changed to Type A Yugi!
Why aren't your Life Points gone?!
It's because my Deck Master's, Kuriboh's, Ability lets him multiply and create the Protection Wall for the player!
Partner... why did you switch with me?
Because if you take any more damage from him, your mental state will suffer.
And I haven't taken any damage yet.
Partner... thank you.
You should be thanking Kuriboh.
Because of Kuriboh's Protection Wall, my Life Points were protected.
You're right.
I guess that's Kuriboh's Deck Master Ability.
Under this system... the Duelist who can unite with the heart of their Deck Master has the upper hand.
But, it's only natural for a Duelist to bond with the heart of their Monsters.
Yeah...
Perhaps I've forgotten
the most important part.
Partner!
Although our Life isn't gone, the mental trauma was too much.
Leave the rest to me and Kuriboh!
Saved by your
Deck Master's Ability, were you?
But don't forget about the risk of Summoning your Deck Master.
When your Deck Master is destroyed,
regardless of whether you have lost all of your Life, you lose the Duel.
Kuriboh can't be compared with my Monsters. It cannot withstand my next attack.
This time, when I deliver the final attack, you really will be finished!
I won't give this Duel up!
They're coming!
No way...
Look! This is the proof of our friendship!
Right! Even if we we're apart, we'll be marked and tied to each other!
Everyone's trying there best out there somewhere!
You have to be courageous, Anzu!
Go away!
Wait... I told you to go away! The bridge will collapse!
Come on already~!
Like hell am I gonna die here!
I won't lose!
Just like he said... if I don't win the match this turn, I have no hope of winning.
My turn!
I know, Kuriboh.
The Duelist and their Deck Master share one heart!
I'll decide this with one draw.
Draw!
I have something to tell you.
No matter how many ancient proverbs you've memorized and recited, they aren't your own words.
You should mold them into your own words.
"The crown of honor belongs only to the final victor."
Those are the words you said yourself earlier.
Right now, I'm gonna make them into my own words and give them back to you!
Don't be euphemistic.
Just what are you playing at?
This.
Gale Dark Knight Gaia?
Did you forget?
My combo is perfect.
No matter how powerful the Monsters you play may be, your attacks still won't work on me.
As long as there's a gap between your Life Points and mine, you cannot turn the tables.
Is that so now?
Reverse Card, open!
Magic Card! Rainbow Blessing!
I will then proceed to equip Rainbow Blessing with my Deck Master, Kuriboh.
What are you trying to do?
Go, Kuriboh!
Rainbow Arch!!
Rainbow Arch?
What the hell are you trying to pull?!
I'll then Summon Gale Dark Knight Gaia in Attack Mode!
Come forth!
Gale Dark Knight Gaia!
The Rainbow Arch created by Rainbow's Blessing
allows him to pass over enemy Monsters and Direct Attack the player!
What?! There's no way Kuriboh has such an Ability!
Go! Gale Dark Knight Gaia!
Direct Attack the Deepsea Warrior!
O-Oh no!
I can't use my Deck Master Ability against Direct Attacks!
You're exactly right.
Your Deck Master Ability is only effective when I attack your Monsters!
D-Damn you!
I almost got myself a body...
...and came so close to returning to the real world!!
I managed to win...
This damage... is way too dangerous.
Do all the others have to take part in Duels like this?
Thank you, Kuriboh.
So Yugi really was as strong as the rumors state, eh...?
Or perhaps the prestigious Big Five members who wandered the Cyber World for so long...
...were only capable of this much.
Well, I do hope they will entertain me more in the upcoming Duels.
It's an exit! We made it!
Yeah.
Let's go, I'm worried about the others.
That's right.
If we don't hurry and find and help them soon, their Duels might be too much for them.
"Preview"
Just when I finally escaped the Cyclops that were chasing me,
a bunch of penguins
appear before me.
"Follow us"?
Where exactly are you taking me...?
Hu- what's that?
There's so many penguins!
Could this really be
one of the Big Five's traps?!
Hey! If that's the case, whether it's a Duel or whatever, I'll take you on!
Next time!
"Iceberg Duel: Anzu Targeted"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise