Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Nameless Dragon Timaeus"
Yugi-kun...
No, Nameless Pharaoh...
When I looked at this palette, I confirmed my theory.
I believe you are the only one who can solve the current crisis...
...and save mankind from their coming downfall of destruction.
Mankind's downfall of destruction?
What exactly do you mean by that, Professor?
I've been recently studying the origin of Duel Monsters.
There's much to tell from what I've found in the Ancient Egyptian tablets.
High officials used spells to seal wicked spirits within stone tablets.
I've come to understand that these high officials
called the spirits from the stone tablets in order to protect themselves.
Are those... Dark Games?
These wicked spirits grew stronger until eventually they emerged from the stone tablets,
and evil power was created as a result.
Because of this, an unbelievably tremendous power was born that threatened to destroy the world.
The nameless Pharaoh was the one who brought this evil power under control.
Something like that happened in my other self's past...?
But that was a long time ago, wasn't it?
How is it related to what's going on right now?
I recently joined a research team while in America and may have discovered a lost civilization.
Ah! I saw that in the news.
Eh? Really?
I myself closely examined the carvings resting there...
But what I found was... far beyond what I expected.
Take a look at these.
This is...!
Duel Monsters!
Those engraved markings we found suggest that Duel Monsters existed long before Ancient Egypt.
10,000 years ago, to be exact.
10,000 years ago?!
If that's really true, your discovery could completely rewrite history!
Yes. This stone tablet is quite the find.
This is...!
The Monsters appear to be attacking!
Those engravings depict the part of my theory that suggests the Monsters tried to destroy the world.
The Monsters did...?
So that means the Monsters we saw recently are also trying to destroy the world?!
The omen has begun~
Soon this world's gonna be destroyed~
Is this what Haga-kun and Ryuzaki-kun were taking about?
10,000 years ago, as shown on these palettes...
3,000 years ago in Egypt...
And the current situation just now.
Is it all just a coincidence?
Or...
Just wait a minute!
Duel Monsters is just a game created by Pegasus, isn't it?!
Someone must be playing a trick with the Monsters using the Duel Disks.
But Kaiba-kun said his Solid Vision System wasn't the cause...
Anzu, you're not gonna try and tell me Monsters are real, are you?
W-Well...
Monsters are real.
E-Eh?
They are depicted within ancient drawings...
The many gods, rituals, magic and spells are examples
of human being's desires to awaken the Monsters from a different world.
They are trying to use this power for the sole purpose of proving their existence, or so I believe.
Wait, wait!
What a joke!
What the hell are you doing?!
What?!
Don't you insult Grandpa's theory!
Pegasus himself got his inspiration to create Duel Monsters after viewing the ancient stone carvings!
E-Even so...!
It's fine, Rebeca.
I myself feel it's all a bit far fetched.
Grandpa...
I believe you, Professor Hopkins.
Jounouchi-kun!
The Dark Games we fought with Malik in Battle City...
And the God Cards...
After being attacked by Ra, I know.
That wasn't just Solid Vision.
And others besides the chosen ones were able to use the God Cards...
There might be a
world that we're unaware of.
The Duel Monsters world...?
Now that you mention it, there's many theories relating to this.
Theses stating there may be other worlds other than our own.
Time, space, different dimensions...
Entirely different worlds.
Some think there's
even parallel universes.
You have quite the vocabulary
for a little kid.
How rude!
I'm a university student!
University?!
This child is something else.
I've told you before.
That I'm a genius.
Tensaiyo!
T-e-n-s-a-i!
This brat ain't cute at all...!
What did you say?!
Calm down now, Rebeca.
You're not acting like a lady.
I-I'm sorry.
Most likely, what happened back in Ancient Egypt as well as now...
...has something to do with the Duel Monsters that almost destroyed the world.
However, no one knows for sure.
That's something only the nameless Pharaoh can tell us.
Why have you appeared in our era?
What is the meaning to your rebirth?
Now that you mention it, those "Musketeers of Doma" said something like that...
When the forbidden door is opened...
...the light of Orichalcos shall punish this sinful world!
We are the Musketeers of Doma!
Just who are those guys...?
Professor, there's something else I'd like you to look at.
Pretty...
Yugi-kun, what is this...?
The man who attacked us yesterday was wearing it.
It looks just like it...
Just like a similar stone
in the ancient ruins...
May I study this for a bit?
Yes. Please do.
I'm heading back to America in order to further investigate these ancient ruins.
If I find something out, I'll contact you.
I'm going to take Arthur and Rebeca to the airport.
Okay.
Darling, see you!
Bye bye~!
I can't believe all this happened to the other me in his past...
Yeah, but I don't remember any of it.
Help!
Hmm? What's wrong, Yugi?
I just heard someone say "help" just now!
No one's here.
But...
Maybe you're just tired, Yugi.
I'm headed home.
Yeah.
Right.
I can't stop wondering about everything the professor said.
Can't sleep?
My other self...
Yeah, I have a lot on my mind.
Me too, Partner.
My lost memory and the events occurring right now...
Is there something connecting them?
As I thought, the nameless Pharaoh's power cannot be underestimated.
I am very sorry.
However, the God Cards are right here.
I can feel it...
There's an enormous power
within these cards.
This power must not be wasted on something as trivial as the nameless Pharaoh's lost memories.
These shall act as the keys required to open the Forbidden Gate.
When these cards
are placed as offerings...
...the sealed gate will open...
And our god will revive once again!
Our supreme God.
We grant upon you the power of the three gods!
And accepting this powerful offering, grant us your blessing and open the door!
With this, the Forbidden Gate has been opened.
Help!
Partner...
Other Me...
Help!
This voice is...
This way!
Someone's asking us for help.
Help!
Other Me...!
Let's search for them!
Yeah.
Did you find them?
No.
Where could they be?
Kuriboh!
What's he doing in this place?
Kuriboh's trying to guide us!
Follow him, Partner!
Yeah!
Kuriboh!
There was a place like this in my room...?
Help!
This place is...
Partner, look at that.
That is...!
Three dragons...
Master!
Chosen Duelist!
You finally came!
Black Magician Girl!
You were the one calling us?
Yes!
Right now both our world and your world, Master's, is on the verge of being destroyed!
What did you say?!
Please tell us!
What exactly is going on?
Our world and your world coincide with one another through different dimensions.
Our world was created by your world's Thought Energy.
Therefore, our world depends upon your world.
Both worlds rely upon each other.
But something is causing the balance between both worlds to collapse.
The Dark Sun has taken over our world.
All of our companions are being devoured.
All that's left are...
Partner...
Is there a way to save our world and your world?
These are the three guardians of the Duel Monsters World, the Legendary Dragons.
They exhausted all of their power in their last battle,
and they're now sleeping here.
When did they get here?
No one here even remembers their names.
Nameless dragons...
All that is left behind of these dragons is a prophecy.
Prophecy?
Yes.
"When our world and our Master's world is on the verge of collapse,
only the True Duelists
will awaken us dragons."
Only the True Duelists...?
I believe that you can cure these dragons, Master!
Partner!
Yeah!
Look.
The ice is...!
My other self...!
Yeah!
Nameless dragon!
We know your name!
Your name is...
Timaeus!!
I feel it...
The Monocle of Timaeus...
He has the power to bring out the hidden strength of all other Monsters.
Master!
That power...!
No way!
An aurora!
Grandpa!
Just what is going on here?
I'll check it out!
Yugi!
What's happening?
W-What?!
What's that?!
Something came out!
O Nameless Pharaoh!
Become the offering
for our God's revival!
Not good!
Run!
Yugi!
Run away!
That wasn't just a dream!
Lend us your power, Timaeus!
What's that dragon?!
Timaeus!
Timaeus...
Thank you, Master!
The portal to your world has been closed once again.
But the evil power has escaped somewhere in your world.
Our companions are also still captured...
Then...
The Evil God will surely revive.
Master! Defeat that Evil God!
Otherwise, both of our worlds will enter a path of doom!
This is...
Our inherited power.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
That giant eye monster appeared last night.
Is that the monster Professor Hopkins mentioned that will destroy the world?
Yugi received the power of the Legendary Dragon from the Duel Monsters World.
I don't know what's going on, but whatever it is, it can't be good.
At that moment, Yugi gets a video.
The sender is...
Eh!?
Pegasus!?
Next time!
"Invitation From Pegasus"
Duel standby!