Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Escape!!"
A missile?!
So that means Gozaburo wasn't bluffing!
But why is it coming here?!
I don't have enough time to explain the details!
You have to go to the game center immediately!
I can't make another exit to the Real World over there!
Should we... trust him?
Big brother!
Damn that Noah bastard...
But I don't wanna die as a monkey, OOH-AH!
I trust Noah.
You're right.
Noah! You'll be sorry if you lied to us again!
Is Mokuba safe?
He is! Don't worry about him!
Noah, what the hell is the meaning of this?!
Did you redirect the missile's target?!
Yes, that's what I did, Father.
I'm sorry, but the Virtual System is now completely under my control.
Now you can't access the network from any area of the program.
Wh-What did you just say?!
Are you intending to betray me?!
You intend to blow up your own father with a missile?!
I'm sorry, Father.
That's a pretty good plan you thought up.
I may have underestimated you, Noah!
Just hurry up and get out of there, Seto! There's no time!
D-Don't screw with me!
In that case, Seto, I'll steal your body and escape to the Real World!
Back off, Gozaburo!!
Anyone who calls himself a Duelist must not leave the arena until the Duel is over!
Noah, how many minutes do we have left?
You've got about eight minutes and forty seconds.
That's more than enough time.
Let's continue the Duel, Gozaburo!
If you beat me, I'll let you take my body.
Me? Or you?
It's a Duel that determines which of us returns to the Real World!
A Death Game!
Don't you dare forget what you just said!
I will be the one
returning to the Real World!
Here goes!
My turn! Draw!
Bow down before the mighty Exodia, Seto!
Exodia Crush!!
No you don't! I activate my Reverse Card, Attack Nullification!
Exodia Necross' attack is negated!
Just as I thought. It may not be destroyed by Magic and Trap Cards, but it's not completely unaffected by them.
You sure have a hard time excepting that your enemy is stronger than you, Seto.
Never mind it. I would be delighted to show you that it's impossible for you to surpass me!
Don't underestimate me, Gozaburo.
Exodia isn't as immortal as you would like to think.
I just figured out how to beat it!
What was that?!
They're chasing us again!
Shit!
Let us handle this and get going!
I won't go without you, big brother!
Don't be stupid!
Anzu, take Shizuka and get out of here!
O-Okay.
But don't overdo it.
Big brother!
Don't worry!
I'll be back!
Leave this to us! OOH!
Don't even think about it!
You'll stay right by my feet!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Shrink!
It cuts the Attack Power of Exodia Necross in half!
I then sacrifice Blood Vorse in order to Summon Emerald Dragon!
Go, Emerald Dragon!
Attack Exodia!
It's true that Exodia Necross is the ultimate Monster that stands on the same level as the gods.
But it has a weakness, as I figured.
Interesting! Let's hear it!
With the amazing Attack Points Exodia Necross possesses, it's obviously going to be put in Attack Position.
As such, so long as you attack it with a Monster holding higher Attack Points than it, the player takes the difference as damage.
So what does that have to do with anything?!
Exodia Necross may indeed be immortal,
but you, Gozaburo...
You're about as mortal as they come.
Then just try and beat me!
Exodia Necross' Attack Points go up because of the battle it just had!
My turn, draw!
Go! Exodia Crush!!
So what now? Exodia Necross' Attack Points will go up even further!
The exit is in that Dance Battle Game up in front of you!
Let's hurry, Shizuka-chan!
Right!
Where...?
I must be inside the
floating mobile fortress.
That means we made it back, doesn't it?
H-Hey, take a good look at me!
Am I still a monkey?
You look fine! You're a human again, Honda-san!
OOH!!
Oh yeah!
You don't look all that different to me...
Anzu!
Mokuba!
Good. Now to get Jounouchi and the others.
Step on the Dance Battle Game!
That it?
Otogi-kun, Jounouchi-kun! Go now!
Okay!
Yugi! You better hurry up!
Yeah!
Quickly, Yugi!
Yugi, I have a favor to ask of you.
I'm back in the Real World alright...
Big brother!
Shizuka!
Thank goodness! You okay?
Yeah!
Six minutes, eighteen seconds until missile launch.
Seto's in the Battle Dome of Kaiba Corporation!
He's Dueling against my father!
What!? Kaiba's seriously Dueling when a freakin' missile's about to hit?!
Is he dumb or what?!
Seto doesn't plan on escaping until they settle the Duel.
Kaiba-kun...
I'm going to create an exit leading to Kaiba Corporation!
I'm begging you, Yugi!
Please bring Seto back!
I will!
Yugi, I'm coming with you!
No, I'll be fine on my own!
You get ready to leave with the others!
Yugi...
I understand. But you better return, Yugi!
We've still got our battles as Duelists to deal with, you know!
Yeah! I will!
I'll be back with Kaiba-kun!
Yugi! There's no time for this!
I'm creating a path leading straight to Kaiba Corporation!
Let's go, Black Magician!
But why, Noah...?
Why go so far for Kaiba-kun...?
Even though you hate him so much...
This body... Mokuba's body is pleading with me...
"Please save my big brother!"
He's begging me!
I'm... sorry...
For doubting you...
Of course you would.
Three minutes and fifty seconds until missile launch.
We're out of time.
You all had better get back to the Battle Ship and prepare to leave!
Okay!
Let's move, Shizuka!
Noah, you're the only one who can save Yugi and Kaiba.
We're counting on you.
I know!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
It lets me draw two cards from my deck!
I play a Monster in face-down Defense Position!
Followed by setting a reverse card on the field!
Turn over!
Exodia's Attack Power has increased to 4800 Attack Points!
If you've got a Monster with higher Attack Points than that, let's see it!
Gozaburo! You're nothing more than a third-rate Duelist!
I'm going to show you how foolish it is to rely on nothing but powerful Monsters to win a Duel!
Kaiba-kun!
My turn! Draw!
Exodia Crush!!
What now? He's got 5800 Attack Points now!
One minute until missile launch.
Hurry, Yugi!
My turn!
Draw!
Yes!
Magic Card! Resurrection of the Dead!
I revive Magic Lamp from my Graveyard!
And thanks to Magic Lamp's Effect, I can Special Summon La Jinn, the Magical Spirit of the Lamp!
I've been fighting nothing more than Exodia's ghost up until now!
There's no point in fighting
a deceased spirit!
What I need to beat is its very soul!
Soul Crush, activate!
What?! You aren't...?!
With a cost of 500 Life Points per card,
the Trap Card, Soul Crush, lets both players remove the Monsters in each other's Graveyards from play.
Oh no...!
I have only three cards in my Graveyard... Emerald Dragon, Blood Vorse and Spirit Dragon!
But the number in your Graveyard, Gozaburo...
...are five!
Damn you!
We'll start with the first one! The Sealed One's Left Leg!
Next up is The Sealed One's Right Leg!
The Sealed One's Left Arm!
The Sealed One's Right Arm!
And now to finish this!
Exodia the Sealed One!
Next, I sacrifice La Jinn, the Magic Genie of the Lamp along with his Magic Lamp!
Come forth, Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
And that's checkmate, Gozaburo.
Take this!!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
Ten seconds remain until missile launch.
Now initiating final countdown.
Eight...
Seven...
Six...
I lost...?!
Absurd!
I spent hours on end sorting through data files to create the perfect strategy!
I suggest you keep in mind that my strength can't be measured by data.
Damn you! Unforgivable!
Don't think you'll be
leaving that easily, SETO!!
Have you lost your mind, Gozaburo?!
Yugi!
Three, two, one...
Ignition.
Missile launched.
The missile was just launched!
You have nowhere left to run!
Jump!!
But...!
Let's just do it, Kaiba-kun!
What?!
Missile approaching.
This place...
The Real World!
We made it back!
Mokuba!
I apologize, Mokuba.
I'll give your body back now.
Noah... What are you going to do?
I'm going back to Father.
But...! You...!
It was only for a short while, but I got a real body again.
I was happy.
Don't go, Noah!
I think I've been able
to get my heart back.
It's all thanks to you, Mokuba. Thank you!
Noah!
I'm a human. Not a machine.
Noah!!
Mokuba!
Mokuba, open your eyes!
WAKE UP!
Mokuba...
Big brother! Noah...!
Damn you all! You won't get away, Seto!
It's no use, Father!
Noah!
I deleted all of the exits.
You can't get out of here now.
Missile approaching. Missile approaching.
Noah went back to the Virtual World!
He said he can't abandon Gozaburo!
Geez, what are you guys doing, Yugi?!
If you don't hurry, the missile...!
Hurry up, Yugi!
Missile approaching. Missile approaching.
Hurry up! Make haste!
Or we all blow up.
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING, NOAH!?
CREATE A PATH RIGHT THIS INSTANT!
I finally understand.
Huh?
Seto has Mokuba and Yugi has all his friends.
I always thought I was alone.
But I was wrong!
I DON'T RECALL ASKING SUCH A RIDICULOUS QUESTION!
I have my father!
SILENCE! JUST LET ME OUT OF HERE!
The only family I have...
I mean, we're brothers and all.
Father, let's put an end to all this!
I want you to stay by my side forever!
WHAT DO YOU THINK YOU'RE DOING, NOAH?!
LET GO OF ME!
I STILL HAVE SOMETHING I NEED TO DO!
We died a long time ago, Father.
LET ME GO!!
There they are!
Yugi!
-Hey!
-Come on!
-Yugi!
You can make it!
Run faster, Yugi-kun!
Grab my hand, Yugi!
Hurry!
Grab on!
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
NO!!
I DON'T WANT TO DIE YET!!
Goodbye, Mokuba.
Noah...!
Seto-sama! The ship!
The ship won't be able to withstand this!
Transfer the system to me!
SETO~!!!
Gozaburo!
I will not be swallowed by the likes of you!!
Noah... When you think back on it, he was a really poor kid.
All he wanted was for
his father to love him.
Noah was a victim in all this too, in the end...
Noah...
Both Noah and Gozaburo were foolish beings right from the start.
Now that the hindrance is out of the way, our fight is just getting started!
The location of the Tournament Final, Alcatraz, is waiting for us!
On to the real path to Alcatraz! Full speed ahead!
Yes, sir!
I am human. Not a machine.
Does everyone still remember?
We were on our way to the final stage of the Battle City Tournament!
So much happened while we were in the Virtual World,
but it looks like not that much time passed in our own world.
The Battle Ship lands on the island of the tournament final round.
Alcatraz!
And on it stands a giant tower, almost seeming to engulf you.
Is that the battlefield of the finals?
Next time!
"Location of the Finals - Alcatraz"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise