Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
The Great Wicked God Zorc ended up reviving after all.
The skies have been cast in darkness.
The Earth has begun to shake.
That power has transcended the world of memories
and has started affecting the real world.
We must defeat him, no matter what it takes!
But all our strength is nothing in front of Zorc's great power!
And even Shada has now been sacrificed!
"The Great Protector God:
Exodia Revives!"
Do not back down!
If this creature passes this entrance, the royal palace will be in his reach!
We must hold him back at all costs!
If I had even a little more Ba left,
I could call out the White Dragon and destroy this beast in seconds!
Kisara...!
Shada...
This feels good...!
Both worlds appear to be in grave peril!
Bakura...
Come to think of it, if the Millennium Puzzle had never been put back together,
and you had never been reborn...
...none of this would have happened in the first place.
Fate sure is ironic, isn't it?
Of course, it was because of that I was able to be reborn.
So I'm rightfully grateful!
But it's about time you cease the futile resistance.
Sink into the darkness...
That is your only fate!
A fate where everything is painted in darkness...
Fate...
It's probably true that everything started because I was resurrected...
That's all the more reason
I can't afford to lose!
Until I settle this with my own hands!
You just don't know when to call it quits.
Forget it.
But how long can you keep up this obvious bluff?
Pharaoh... Zorc's power is far too great.
If this keeps as is,
we hold no hope of victory.
But...
However, supposing we do have at least a sliver of hope on our side...
There is no other way but
to summon the Gods.
The Three Illusionary Beasts...
But...
Without the Millennium Puzzle, I can't summon the Gods.
I don't even have enough Ba to summon them...
But there is no other way
to defeat Zorc...
We must recover the Millennium Items.
Isis...
After fulfilling their role in resurrecting Zorc,
the Millennium Items were blown into the desert
along with the Stone
Tablet of the Underworld.
It is hard to say whether we can find them or not.
Okay! I'll go!
No, you must remain here, my Pharaoh.
Your presence is vital for those fighting.
My Spiria will most certainly be able to find the Millennium Items.
Please allow me to handle this.
Yes, yes!
I will accompany you!
Mana.
I will do my best in Master's absence!
Pharaoh...
Please do, Isis. Mana.
Yes.
Please leave this to us!
All of you, get going.
We will draw Zorc's attention.
Seto.
Very well.
Then...
We're counting on you...
Listen! Show him our absolute authority!
Slow him down!
Fire!!
Foolish cretins!
Come forth! Winged Dragon, Guardian of the Fortress!
Lady Isis!
Are you all right?
Yes... Let us go.
You're putting on quite a show for a mere vessel!
I won't lose for the sake of my other self!
Yes! Yugi's taken the lead!
Yugi!
Hmph. Very well.
I'm going to thoroughly enjoy this!
My turn!
Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand.
Spirit Sword of Sealing!
This card removes from play one Monster on the field!
Silent Swordsman was...!
The trapped Monster can't be called back using Monster, Magic or Trap Cards.
And its own effects can't be activated.
Oh shit!
I then Summon Taoist Spirit - Discredited Mage in Attack Mode.
Discredited Mage attacks Marshmallon!
I activate Marshmallon's Special Effect!
Marshmallon can't be destroyed in battle!
Such a pity...
Had Marshmallon gone to the Graveyard just now, Silent Swordsman would have come back.
If the opponent whose Monster is sealed by Spirit Sword of Sealing
has one of his Monsters sent into the Graveyard off of the field,
the sealed Monster will return to the owner's field.
In other words, your own Monster's Special Effect just crushed the only chance you had.
Give up the futile resistance and perish along with the rest!
Foolish human beings!
That Bakura-kun's pretty weird...
That dude's always been a freak.
Goddammit! Acting all tough...!
That's true, but...
He seems much different than the usual Bakura-kun
possessed by the personality of the Millennium Ring.
He feels more cold hearted than ever...
My turn is over.
My turn!
Draw!
Hold on!
The Special Effect of the captured Silent Swordsman
has also been sealed by the Spirit Sword of Sealing.
You can't increase his Attack Power.
I know that.
I Summon Blocken in Defense Mode!
Only got 300 Defense Points?!
Can't even call that thing a wall!
That ends my turn.
Hey now...
There seems to be quite a few pathetic Monsters in that deck of yours.
My turn.
Draw!
Let's put an end to this!
Discredited Mage, go on and attack Marshmallon!
Not good!
Its Attack Power is way higher!
Yugi!
Guess this means a vessel will always be nothing more than a vessel in the end...
I use this moment to activate Blocken's Special Effect!
What?
When one of its ally Monsters is targeted in an attack,
Blocken can switch the attack to itself!
Sweet!
Now that Yugi's Monster was sent to the Graveyard,
the effects of Spirit Sword of Sealing will wear off and Silent Swordsman will return!
It won't be that easy!
What?
I activate Taoist Spirit - Discredited Mage's Special Effect!
The Monster destroyed by this card is returned to the deck!
Meaning it won't go to your Graveyard...
A combo to strengthen the effect of Spirit Sword of Sealing?
But Blocken has another Special Effect!
When Blocken leaves the field,
Lenguard can be Special Summoned from the deck in Attack Mode!
Yet another low-level Monster!
I set three cards.
Ending my turn!
Millennium Items...
Millennium Items...!
I've found them.
We found them!
The Millennium Scales!
The Millennium Staff!
The Millennium Ring!
The Millennium Pendant!
The Millennium Eye!
The Millennium Ankh!
I found the Millennium Tauk.
We must hurry and deliver them to Prince!
Yes...
I refuse to lose!
For the Other Me!
My turn!
Draw!
I use Marshmallon to attack the Discredited Mage!
Say what?!
That's reckless!
His opponent's Attack Power is higher!
You're so desperate now that you've resorted to suicide?!
Yugi!
What?
His Life is intact...!
Because I activated Lenguard's Special Effect.
When an ally Monster receives damage from battle,
this card is destroyed instead and all damage is reduced to zero!
And because a Monster just entered my Graveyard,
the effects of Spirit Sword of Sealing vanish,
and Silent Swordsman LV. 4 will return to the field!
Now I see!
So that's what Yugi was aiming for?!
I use Silent Swordsman LV. 4 to attack Discredited Mage!
What?
His Life Points didn't change!
Whoa, now that was that a close one!
Good thing I also used a Special Ability!
When Taoist Spirit - Discredited Mage is destroyed in battle,
I can return my entire hand along with this card into my deck...
...and reduce all damage to zero.
What?!
Hmph. What useless struggling...
But try all you like, because it's pointless!
There's no way you can beat me!
Just calm down...
I can't let Bakura-kun rattle me...
I have to remain calm and wait until I calmly analyze the situation.
A chance will surely come.
If this was my other self here, he would say the same thing!
My turn's over!
Then it's my turn!
Draw!
I'll activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
So I'll draw two cards!
I'll then open my reverse card!
Cursed Necro Twins!
What are those?!
Two creepy dolls...!
Both players must choose between these red and black boxes.
But one of them is a cursed box!
So, Yugi, which'll it be?!
So one of them is a cursed box...
Okay...
I'm choosing the red box!
Guess I'll be choosing the black box...
The red box's effect is...
Good for you, Yugi.
Whenever a card is placed in either of our Graveyards,
you gain 200 Life Points.
You did it, Yugi! You hit the jackpot!
Bakura-kun... What does the black box do...?
Thank you for the curse...
The player who chooses the back box has their entire Graveyard destroyed.
Your Graveyard is destroyed?!
What does that mean...?!
That's...
The Monsters from his Graveyard...!
Well, well...
Without a Graveyard, my dead Monsters have returned as ghosts...
God, that is freaky!
What's with the pathetic whimpering?
I'm no good with this kinda stuff...!
But don't worry.
The ghosts may be here on the field, but they can't attack or defend.
There's no reason for you to be scared.
I Summon Necro Soldier in Defense Mode!
I end my turn!
I... have a bad feeling...
Your end is close at hand...
We made it in time!
The royal palace hasn't been destroyed yet!
I thought I sensed something, but it was merely those Millennium Items?
What a shrewd little trick you pulled!
Isis!
Get down, Mana.
I will act as bait.
Lady Isis!
I will also fight!
You must hurry along and deliver the Millennium Items to the Pharaoh!
But...
We must protect the Pharaoh.
That is our duty as his High Priests!
Mahado would say the same thing.
And I must see Kalim and Shada's wish to the very end.
So off you go, Mana!
Using the remainder of my Ba...
For a mouse, you are quite the eyesore...
Now where did you run off to?
You will not escape!
Now you've done it, woman!
Kalim...
Shada...
I am sorry I couldn't protect our Pharaoh until the very end...
Mahado...
That is...
Isis...
Lord Shimon!
Lady Isis has...!
Mana... If you wish for Isis' sacrifice to not be in vain,
you must deliver the Millennium Pendant to the Pharaoh no matter what!
Yes...!
Lord Shimon...
I will hold onto this.
I am this Millennium Ankh's previous owner.
Lord Shimon...!
Now go, Mana!
Go to our Pharaoh!
Yes!
Will you still lend your power to this old man...?
Demon God of the Palace...?
Five sacred parts sealed into stone slabs, I release you!
Defend us in our hour of need with your sacred power!
Come forth!
My ancient spirit...
Exodia!!
That's...!
That is Lord Shimon's Ka...!
The legendary protector guardian that defeated 1,000 armies in a single night!
Exodia...!
This Ka fought alongside Akhenamkhanen in the past
against enemy armies that tried to take over the country.
I swore to never again wield such massive power.
I sealed it away to
protect the city, however...
The time to release it has come!
Go!
Exodia!!
Good!
Futile!
For I am immortal!
What?!
If you are immortal, then Exodia is also immortal!
I didn't realize Lord Shimon's Ka was this powerful...
Shimon...
Immortal, was it?
My power comes from the very infinite darkness itself!
But human Ba has its own limitations!
You cannot truly surpass your deaths!
Exodia! Burn the Dark God with the fire in your soul!
Exodo Flame!!
He did it...!
Did he beat Zorc...?!
Just a little more, flames of anger!
Use me for fuel, while my soul still burns!
No fire on Earth can light my darkness!
I am impervious!
Dark Phenomenon!!
Pharaoh...
I gave my best...
Exodia was...
Lord Shimon was...
You pitiful humans will never be able to defeat me!
I am the darkness!
You mortals fear the dark.
Yet you allow the darkness to rule you!
Human beings are all but powerless before the darkness!
That's not true!
The soul in this body is the light of life!
It will never go out in the darkness!
It's the very light that illuminates my soul!
Prince!
Mana!
Here...!
The Millennium Puzzle!
Lady Isis and Lord Shimon gave themselves so I could give this to you!
In order to get this to me, Isis and Shimon...
Zorc, I fight along with the souls of my comrades, seeking the light!
I will not allow this world to be consumed by your shroud of darkness!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Even the Exodia was toppled by the Great Wicked God Zorc!
But after getting back the Millennium Puzzle,
the Pharaoh Summons the Three Illusionary Beasts.
At long last, a massive battle of Gods emerges as the Three Illusionary Beast Gods fight Zorc!
At the same time, Yugi continues his Duel with Dark Bakura,
as he falls into a horrible trap set by the effect of Necro Twins.
Next time!
"Summon! The Three Illusionary Beast Gods"
Duel standby!