A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
I get it!
Rebeca!
You're...!
You finally found out.
Yes!
My name is Rebeca Hopkins.
I'm Arthur Hopkin's granddaughter, the man you stole his precious Blue-Eyes White Dragon from!
You're the granddaughter of my grandpa's best friend?
That's right!
Now! I'm going to avenge my grandpa!
Prepare yourself!
"The Deadly Shadow Ghoul"
Grandpa didn't steal anyone's card!
No! He did!
You don't know how much my grandpa cherished that card...
I will never forgive you!
Rebeca.
What do ya want?!
Can I say something about an important friend of mine,
as well as your grandfather, Arthur Hopkins?
It'll just be more of your excuses!
I don't wanna hear it!
Rebeca...
Since you want to protect Arthur,
you must hear me out.
Fine! Geez!
It happened several years ago.
When I was in Egypt.
I was interested in Duel Monsters, which wasn't very well-known back then...
I heard that you could find many rare cards in Egypt.
So I left Albal.
And that's where I met him.
If you'd like, you can have some of my water.
That's so kind of you!
Arthur was there to excavate.
He's a good man with a youthful smile.
But the archaeological world saw him as a heretic.
Why?
Well, you see...
Just like me,
he was also interested in Duel Monsters.
Isn't that right, Rebeca?
Grandpa, what do you mean?
In his research of ancient writings,
he discovered that a particular word was used over and over.
And that word is...
"Game".
Game?
That's right. Game.
With that keyword in mind, he retranslated the Egyptian Hieroglyphics.
And so, he made a startling conclusion.
This is the shrine.
According to the ancient text,
the people exchanged scrolls in order to predict the future.
Predict the future?
That's right.
To make prophecies of the government and people,
they often held rituals.
And that was what it meant by exchanging scrolls.
It was a game.
What was that?
I guess you could call it a sort of ritual card game of some sorts.
Look at this.
That's Duel Monsters.
This was its inspiration.
The card game is the same.
Ancient Egyptians played games like this.
This will overturn Ancient Egyptian history.
We'll see...
Unfortunately, the scientific world...
...thought of Arthur's theory as far fetched.
Despite all that, he never gave up his research to find the truth.
I agreed with him.
And so, we became good friends.
Also, he believed in the existence of God Cards.
God Cards?
One who is able to collect the gods located around the world
may replace the Sun God Ra...
...as the ruler of this world, like a king.
King of the world?
According to the prophecy,
the moment all the cards are collected...
...will have the power needed to control the world.
The puzzle of the God Cards is not so easy to decipher.
I want to use the rest of my life to research them.
The God... Cards...?
So Professor Hopkins gave you the Blue-Eyes White Dragon after that, right?
Yes.
You're lying!
Liar! Liar! Liar!
You must have stole Grandpa's card then!
That must be it!
Right, Teddy-chan?
Rebeca...
The truth is, Rebeca, a cave-in occurred not long after that.
A cave-in?
Are you alright, Sugoroku-san?
I'm fine.
But...
No good.
We seem to be trapped.
The rescue team didn't come.
We ran out of food and there was only enough water for one person.
And then...
Sugoroku-san.
What is it?
Why don't we play a game?
We shouldn't give up our hope until the very end,
but nothing in life is certain.
At the very least, playing a game will help us to not think about dying as we await our fates.
You're right about that.
Professor Hopkins...
What do you think about this?
About what?
We've only got a little bit of water left.
But if we want to save one of our lives,
only one of us can drink it when the time comes.
I propose that the winner of this Duel gets to drink that water.
How's that?
Okay.
Okay! Let's Duel!
In the first turn of the Duel,
Arthur played Witch of the Black Forest.
Witch of the Black Forest...
That's correct!
Arthur taught you this strategy, right?
So how did it end?
Well, it went like this...
I don't wanna hear it!
There's no proof to back up any of what you're saying!
What kind of attitude is that?
Now then! It's my turn!
Oi! Gramps ain't finished yet!
It's okay. Let her continue.
The both of you may continue!
Goddamn!
You're the one who interrupted the game in the first place! How arrogant!
It's incredible though.
It's as if it's Arthur playing in that ring.
Okay! I'll use this!
Catapult Turtle!
Attack Mode!
Catapult Turtle sacrifices one of the Monster on my field...
...and the opponent takes half of its Attack Power as damage to their Life Points.
And your point is...?
Also, the Magic Card Brain Control.
Anything but that!
This lets me control an enemy Monster for one turn.
Come here, Millennium Shield!
And then the Catapult Turtle launches the Millennium Shield!
Oh no!
My turn's not over yet!
Battle!
Cannon Soldier is defeated!
Not fair! Not fair!
-Great!
-Nice one, Yugi! Get 'er!
- Great attack combo, Yugi!
As expected of Yugi Mutou.
He surely has the skills to be the Duelist Kingdom winner.
There are six Monsters in the Grave.
But it's not enough.
Great! Fantastic!
We did it, Teddy-chan!
-Bravo! Bravo!
What's with this girl?
Yay! I'm gonna win for sure!
Magic Card! Judgment Bomber!
What did you just say?!
This card lets me discard five cards from my hand...
And in exchange...
I get to destroy every Monster you have on the field!
Next, I Summon Shadow Ghoul to the field in Attack Mode!
Now my favorite number-one cute little baby, Shadow Ghoul, is up to play!
For every Monster in the Graveyard,
this sweety's Attack Power goes up by 100 points!
For each one?
She has how many Monsters in her Graveyard...?
E-Eleven?!
Wh-What's one hundred times ten?
Eh... the ten goes on the bottom...
1,100...
Well? Now Shadow Ghoul has 2700 Attack Points!
You sent your Monsters to the Graveyard
just to increase Shadow Ghoul's Attack Power?
Damn right I did!
Did you just realize that?
God, you're slow!
Rebeca.
What?
The most important thing in a Duel
is one's belief in the Heart of the Cards!
Don't you think it's too much to send your Monsters
to the Graveyard just to gain more power?
Are you stupid or something?!
There's no "heart" in a Duel!
Win at all costs! That's how a real Duelist should be!
You're just making up lies
to cover up for stealing the card!
Grandpa taught me these tactics.
Monsters are just meant to be sacrificed and used as weapons!
Really now?
Grandpa, I know the ending of this Duel now.
Yugi, do what you have to do to finish this Duel.
I know, Grandpa.
Hey!
How long are you gonna keep a lady waiting?
Hurry up, Yugi!
I Summon a Monster face-down in Defense Mode.
Yugi, did you know that luck is what determines the outcome of a game?
Magic Card! Defense Seal!
Shadow Ghoul, attack!
The Wrath of Cemetery!!
Bye bye, Black Magician.
Gramps, can't you do anything?!
You still remember how you played this Duel, right?
Yeah.
Then hurry!
Just sit tight and watch for the moment.
The outcome of this battle may yet surprise you.
Sealing Swords of Light!
This will block the opponent's attacks for three turns!
What a pain!
Forget this!
I'll pass this turn.
That's easy for you to say.
Then I'll use this!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Revive Black Magician!
You want to block my attacks while preparing for a counter, huh?
It's no use! No use!
I'll win in the end.
So I don't really mind telling you what the card I put face-down is.
It's Cannon Soldier!
Trying to lure me out?
But I can't just leave Cannon Soldier alone.
It can't be avoided!
Attack Cannon Soldier!
Black Magic!!
Shadow Ghoul's Attack increases even further up by 1000 points!
Yugi seems to be waiting for some card.
Some card?
Yeah.
He's waiting for a big turn around.
I'm well aware!
He's waiting for some card while the Sealing Swords of Light keeps me trapped,
but it'll be over by the time Shadow Ghoul is done attacking you~!
I pass this turn as well!
Then Sealing Swords of Light will disappear.
Now your Sealing Swords of Light blocking my attacks will disappear.
I'll pass again.
Then next is my turn.
What are you waiting for?
That's a secret~!
Well? Has the card you've been waiting for shown up yet?
I surrender.
Arthur, you win.
Yugi, why?!
Why did you quit?!
What's going on?!
I won!
Yeah, I lost.
Bravo! I'm the best!
Isn't that right, Teddy-chan?
I did it! I DID it!
The card he was waiting for didn't show up?
Are you serious, Yugi?
Give me Blue-Eyes!
You tore it up! The Blue-Eyes my grandfather cherished more than anything!
I'm really sorry about this...
So that's why you wouldn't give it back?!
Goddamn! I won't forgive this!
No, I really would have given it back from the start, but...
I don't wanna hear your excuses!
That's enough, Rebeca.
Grandpa!
Arthur! Is that you, Arthur?!
Long time no see, Sugoroku.
It has been a long time.
My wild granddaughter caused you a lot of trouble.
My most sincere apologies.
Grandpa?
Rebeca, Yugi-kun won the Duel just now.
No way that's true!
Yugi-kun, that was a nice Duel.
You're a great Duelist, just like Sugoroku.
Just as I thought.
Rebeca, take a look.
This is called Soul Release.
If Yugi-kun used this in his last turn...
...it would have removed five cards, along with their very souls, from the Graveyard.
Had he used it, Shadow Ghoul's Attack Power would have dropped from 2800 to 2300,
and then if it battled with the Black Magician, holding 2500 Attack Points...
Then why did Yugi surrender?
Why?!
Don't you get it yet?
Yugi-kun is a boy with a kind heart, just like Sugoroku.
He wanted to save your heart from corruption.
In the cave-in, Sugoroku lost the Duel on purpose
and he let me drink the last of the water, saving my life.
I was growing very weak back then...
Why did you surrender?
Winning is not important.
Life is.
Sugoroku...
I found them!
Are you okay?!
We're on our way down!
Just sit tight!
Rebeca, I did send my Monsters to the Graveyard,
to make Shadow Ghoul more powerful.
But you need to show respect to the Monsters you sacrifice.
It's the same in both Dueling and in archeology.
Duelists must have a caring heart, even in battle.
I gave the Blue-Eyes White Dragon to Sugoroku with a thankful heart.
But Sugoroku went and torn that very same card that's so important!
I'm sorry Arthur... The truth is...
It's okay, Sugoroku.
You've kept it for me all these years.
Even if it's torn,
our friendship is still intact.
Listen, Rebeca. The cards have hearts.
A good battle is like a good friendship.
Hearts?
Yes! Hearts.
If you can't understand that much, you may as well be disqualified as the American Champ.
Yugi, I...
It's fine, Rebeca.
Thank you, Yugi!
Rebeca, take this.
The Bonds of Friendship?
I hope you'll accept it.
Yugi!
Sugoroku, it's been so long since you and I Dueled.
Yeah, and I won't surrender this time!
This'll be fun! Go for it, Master!
Huh? Gramps, your back is alright?
What? As you can see, I'm healthy and ready to-
Grandpa!
Hey! Are you alright?!
Kaiba-kun is set up by the Big Five's trap,
and is trapped in the Adventure Game World?
To save Kaiba-kun, Yugi and Jounouchi
enter the game with Mokuba-kun.
Be careful. If you don't win the game, you'll never return to the Real World!
Next time!
"The Big Five's Trap: Duel Monsters Quest"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship