Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Bakura has left the city along with me,
but he's started using his Diabound to launch attacks all over the city!
That's low, Bakura!
I won't allow you to involve innocent bystanders who have nothing to do with this!
But I have no idea where Diabound,
who can now hide in the darkness, is going to attack from.
If this keeps up...
"Turn Back Time"
Are you all right, my Pharaoh?!
Yeah!
Tch... Those priest scum...
Diabound!
Hold it!
It's vanished!
Don't let your guard down.
Diabound's going to hide in the darkness for another surprise attack!
The cavalry is to follow Bakura!
The Guard is to evacuate the city!
Open the palace to refugees!
- Yes, sir!
Hurry to the royal palace!
Don't dawdle around!
Where? Where the heck did they go?
Over there!
Even if we can't see the enemy, we must not fear!
Go forth, Duos!
Helimhay!
Bakura! I swear I'm going to defeat you!
Just you try!
Evade it!
Kalim!
Don't give in yet, Kalim!
The moment we turn our backs to the darkness is the moment the kingdom falls!
I-I know...!
I-I'll be fine!
Make haste!
You're not in yet?! Hurry it up!
Hurry!
- This way!
- Hurry!
Do you see anything, Isis?
The Sky God is being engulfed by a dark shadow.
What?
The Sky God?
There has to be a way...
to drag the enemy out of the darkness!
Pharaoh!
Let's follow him, Kalim!
Right!
Bakura!
I won't let scum like
you get the best of me!
I swear on the name of my ancestors that I will beat you!
We settle things up here!
Get yourself ready, Yugi!
Go forth, Osiris!
In the name of the Pharaoh!
The moment he attacks, Diabound's sure to reveal itself.
Let's fight, Bakura!
You idiot!
I've already taken measures in an area you have no clue about!
The God is about to be destroyed right before our eyes if he leaves it like this!
Does the Pharaoh intend to use the Sky God as bait to lure the enemy out?
Die alongside your god, Yugi!
Diabound, attack!
Spiral Wave!!
Over there!
Fire!
Super Conductor - Thunder Force!!
Lord Akhenaden!
Se-Seto...!
Now!
Duos!
Aura Sword!!
That worked!
D-Did you get it...?
Are you guys blind or something?
Take a closer look!
A different Ka...?
Impossible!
I've seen through everything you guys were planning!
B-Bakura...!
Go to Hell, Pharaoh!
The Millennium Puzzle belongs to me!
S-So... This is... it...?
Pharaoh!
Other Me!
My... Partner...?
You all right?
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun...
Honda-kun...
Anzu...
Wh-What the hell...?
How?!
Why are those guys in the Memory World?!
Pull yourself together, Other Me!
We're here with you!
That's right...
I still have power remaining...
Power within my irreplaceable friends!
Bakura, you've surrounded yourself with the madness of darkness!
I will disperse it with
the descent of God!
Come forth, The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Sunlight in the dead of night...?
This light...!
This light pierced through the darkness that surrounded us moments ago...
Could this be the third God?!
That's...!
The Sun God!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
The Sun God...?!
This can't be!
Yugi's Ba was finished when I destroyed the Sky God!
He didn't have the power to summon a new God...
Is it because those guys appeared?
Yugi's getting power from his vessel?!
I can feel it...
The presence of my partner...
The other soul within me!
Night is changed into day...!
It's the power of the Gods...!
Without the darkness, Diabound can't conceal itself!
Now's our chance to defeat it!
Like hell I'll let you!
Diabound already has the power of a God!
Take this!
Thunder Force!!
What?!
Pharaoh!
Go forth, Duos!
Aura Force!!
By emitting all of my Ba and absorbing it with Aura Force,
I shall change the course of Thunder Force's strike!
Even though it was a God's attack!?
Now if your chance, Great Pharaoh!
The effects of my flaming soul!
I pour them all into this God's one blow!
Ra, attack!
Go, God Phoenix!!
God's flames are burning Bakura!
This will end it, Bakura!
We won!
The Pharaoh, our God on Earth, has brought the light of peace to this land!
This time, things were way too close...!
It's only because my weakened soul was given strength...
Partner...
And my friends!
You did it, Yugi!
Yeah, all thanks to you guys!
If you all hadn't come, about now I'd have been...
We already told you!
We're your friends!
Thank you. I'm grateful from the bottom of my heart, Partner!
Other Me.
Don't forget that we're here, too!
You can say that again!
That's right!
Right!
No matter where you are, we're always with you, Yugi!
Bobasa really loves...
seeing all of you smile!
D-Don't bullshit me...!
I can't... allow myself... to die in a place like this...!
Wh-What the...?!
An earthquake?!
What's going on?!
Impossible! Time is going backwards!
Partner!
Guys!
Yugi!
Partner! Everyone!
Pharaoh!
Damn it! What the hell is going on here?!
Why the hell did we come back over here!?
Ba-Bakura...!
Yugi!
Whoa there.
I won't let you interfere this time!
Sick him!
Diabound!
Spiral Wave!!
Pharaoh!
- Pharaoh!
Bakura...!
I'll be taking this!
Senebti, Your Highness!
- Yugi!
Other Me!
NOO!
Hurry!
We must search for Pharaoh at once!
Bakura!!
YOU BASTARD!!
Do you have a death wish!?
L-Let me go...!
You asshole! Let go of Honda!
You weaklings are an eyesore!
What...?!
Run, all of you! This instant!
Hurry, hurry! Here, here!
He returned just in time...
My cry must have
radiated through the skies...
I called forth a miracle!
It looks like he's set up quite an unbelievable game!
We should be okay now! They left!
That was way too close!
Dammit! That freakin' Bakura bastard!
Yugi... lost the Dark Game.
Anzu...
Dark Games are death games with your life on the line.
Then that means that Yugi...
Don't worry! I'm sure he's alive!
Shadi told us before we came here.
That this is the Pharaoh's world of memories.
Yeah... And?
But we're all still here.
This world hasn't collapsed.
I get it. You mean Yugi's memories haven't disappeared yet?
Mm-hm! So I'm sure he's still alive!
Let's all go look for him!
Okay! Since we decided that, we can't waste time here!
Let's hurry!
Mhm!
You've gotten stronger, Yugi.
Isis' premonition bothers me... Since I found him at the Pharaoh's Shrine of Wedju...
What was Lord Akhenaden doing there?
Have you awaken, Lord Akhenaden?
Shada... How is the Ka hunt going?
Yes...
The truth is, we found a foreign woman whom contained Heka unmeasurable
even using my Millennium Ankh.
Heka not even the Millennium Ankh could measure...
You would be wiser to get some rest.
Move aside!
Lord Akhenaden!
You still haven't located the Pharaoh?!
Yes! I still have heard no reports of it!
I want you to search until you've turned the Nile upside down!
Sir!
Listen! The Pharaoh is most certainly alive!
His dream to protect this kingdom has not yet faded!
What do you see, Isis?
I see a single ripple in dark waters...
If only one, it will soon fade...
But... If two or three ripples overlap,
they will become a great swell that will drown us in tragedy.
Is that... the future of our land?
Yes... That prediction has already begun.
Does that mean the divine order of Ma'at upheld
by the seven Millennium Items has already begun to unravel?
And all by the hands of a single thief?!
You say Lord Akhenaden has been acting strange?
Yes. When I told him of the foreign woman we found,
he was acting as if he was another person.
What happened to the foreign woman?
Yes, sir. Lord Akhenaden took the woman to the Underground but moments ago.
Lord Akhenaden did?
The Underground?!
Yes, that is correct.
Just as you ordered us not long ago.
Now. Please come with me.
What is...?
I've been waiting for you, Seto!
Lord Ahkenaden!
What is the meaning of this?!
Whatever is the matter?!
This is not the time to be resting!
If you wish not to die, you must fight!
If your opponent is still breathing, you shall not be allowed to live!
You must kill! Kill each other!!
Have you snapped, Lord Akehnaden?!
Forcing prisoners to kill one another in meaningless combat is nothing but slaughter!
Listen! What are you waiting for?!
Stop this at once!
Be silent, Seto!
This is what you yourself wished for! Now behold!
The Ka grew...!
Seto... The owner's desire to live is what makes these Ka grow in power!
The will to live...?
The fear of death...
Those feelings of wanting to avoid death!
These things enable growth and give birth to new more powerful Ka!
You're next!
NO! I don't wanna die!
Seto... Without the Pharaoh present,
the kingdom is in need of a Godly figure to keep things in order.
I feel the same way!
That is why we must focus on finding the Pharaoh!
That alone will not be good enough!
What we require now is not the current Pharaoh...
...but a new Pharaoh!
A new... Pharaoh...?
Only the missing Pharaoh can summon the Three Illusionary Beast Gods.
Unless you acquire Ka even greater than that of the Three Illusionary Beasts,
you cannot become the new Pharaoh!
Seto! Gain the power surpassing the Gods!
Lord Akhenaden... wishes for me to be Pharaoh...?
Our entertainment has ended.
Toss that woman over there into the ring!
Yes, sir.
You mean to treat that woman in the same manner?!
Is she not the same woman whose Heka
could not be measured by Shada's Millennium Ankh?
Then she must be hiding a very powerful Ka within her.
Please wait!
You cannot possibly put her through this!
Even if it's you, Lord Akhenaden, I will not just sit by and-
Huh?! How naive! You are too naive, Seto!
If do not have resolve on par with that of the Gods,
you will never be able to obtain power surpassing the Gods!
Open your eyes and watch that woman tremble in fear!
Watch her shiver, cry and plead for her life!
Seto...
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Bakura was beaten!
Or so we thought!
Somehow, time was turned back
and the resurrected Bakura threw Yugi into the Valley of the Kings.
We believe Yugi is safe within the Memory World,
but we're so worried, we have to search for him right away!
Huh? I feel like we've seen that girl somewhere...
Could she be Black Magician Girl?!
Next time!
"The Pharaoh is Still Alive"
Please look forward to it!