Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Kaiba gave me the card needed to battle against Ra!
Devil's Sanctuary!
The card allowed me to escape the effects of One Turn Kill!
Malik, it will lead you down the path of defeat!
What!?
He used Fusion Cancel to get out at the last second?!
However, Devil's Sanctuary is meant to defeat God and to call God!
Come forth! Obelisk!!
Direct Attack Malik!
"The Eternal Wall - God Slime"
Thanks to Obelisk's Direct Attack,
you've taken 4000 points
of damage, Malik!
-Oh yeah!
You did it, Yugi!
Yeah baby! Malik's only got a little bit of Life left!
Did you see Obelisk send Malik flying
halfway across the stage?!
It really makes you feel good,
you know?!
If he keeps it up, he'll win in no time!
That's Yugi for you!
Is this the same Malik we know taking
an attack from Obelisk head-on?
Something's wrong...
The face-down card on Malik's field...
Could it be...?
Yugi... Look out!
Malik purposely took Obelisk's attack!
If that's the case, he could only have two reasons for doing that...
It hurts... It hurts...
One: To trick you into thinking you backed him into a corner, and then cause serious mental damage by revealing otherwise.
And the other reason is...
Hey... look.
What's with Yugi's face...?
Huh, what's up now?
What's wrong with him?
He's this close to winning, but he looks like he's worried something's wrong.
Oh yes, you got me
real damn good in that one, Yugi...
That one hurt!
It was beyond painful!
But you know, Yugi...
I'm not the only
one who's hurt here...
I sure hope you haven't
forgotten about this guy...
Thanks to that attack, his body is
being eaten by the darkness...
Malik!!
What a pitiful fool this man was!
As a Tomb Guardian,
he's given his whole life to protect
the Pharaoh's memories.
And this is the end result...
Destined to die
by the Pharaoh's own hand!
You could laugh from the irony...
Agreed?!
Spiced with the flavor of your hatred,
he must be a delicious sacrifice!
Other me!
If you attack him any further,
Malik's dominant half will be killed!
But if I'm defeated, you will
be swallowed by the darkness...!
I'm still fine up here!
The true enemy
we must defeat at all costs...
...is Malik's evil heart!
We have to save Malik's
dominant half for Ishizu-san!
There has to be a way to do it!
Yeah.
But what should I do...?
Yugi...
I will devour your spirit...
...and feed the scraps
to the darkness!
Now then... I will pay you back
for the pain Obelisk gave me...
I will give it back to you
twice as hard!
I thought so.
Malik let Obelisk attack him because he has another strategy...
I'm going to show you
that I let you Summon God
in order to trigger my trap!
Ri... shid...
Rishid!
Rishid...
Soon I'll be
headed to the Dark World...
Before I do, there's something
I want to tell you.
I disobeyed the laws of my clan
and committed a terrible sin...
Eternal darkness isn't enough to
punish me for what I did to Father.
Let's start with your bloodbath,
my dear father.
Stop it...!
It was really the dark side I was
unaware of that committed the act...
But it was my heart that
gave birth to my dark half.
My hateful fate...
My hatred for the Pharaoh...
A perfect creation for such
a crude heart like mine...
Rishid...
When I went through
the Ritual of the Tomb Guardians,
you endured the same pain I did...
Rishid, help me!!
Rishid!
RISHID!!
It hurts...! It really hurts...!
I have come to change your bandages...
Don't touch me!!
Please tell me...
Please tell me, Rishid...
Who do I hate for this?!
Rishid...
Your face...
I cannot share the pain that you are suffering from, Lord Malik.
Rishid...
Then at the very least...
I shall swear allegiance to your family with this scar.
Rishid... You made a choice then to
share my sin and share my destiny...
You decided to live
with me in the darkness.
It was those feelings you had that helped
keep my dark side at bay all this time.
I don't know where your soul
is wandering right now...
But there's no need for you
to suffer anymore...
Whether I live or die...
Whatever the outcome,
you need to head toward the light.
Thank you... Rishid.
Yugi, in that attack from Obelisk,
you certainly took a
huge chunk of my Life Points...
But in that very instant,
you activated my reverse Trap!
What?! A Trap?!
Impossible! Traps aren't supposed to work on the gods!
Indeed.
A god won't trigger a Counter Trap.
However, this Trap activates
when I lose Life Points!
Now watch closely!
My horrifying trap!
Metal Reflect Slime!
A Trap Monster?!
This Slime Token has
the Reflection Ability.
It becomes a duplicate of the
Monster that attacks it!
It becomes a Wall Monster with Attack
and Defense Points equal to that Monster!
A copy of God?!
What's it doing? That's really gross!
The slime's starting to change form...
It's getting bigger!
It can't...!
It's...!
That's right! It's the Eternal Wall!
God Slime!!
There's two Obelisks on the field!
But one's just some fake slime version!
And if it's only got 3000 Defense Points, Obelisk's 4000 Attack Points can take it out easily!
I can't believe he
copied Obelisk so easily...!
Yugi's gonna beat that impostor in five seconds flat! Right, big brother?!
No!
I don't think he copied Obelisk for the sole purpose of defending.
A God Copy...
But even with that ability, he can't copy the power of the god...
If it's just a Defense Monster, I can easily beat it on my next turn! But...
I play a reverse card card...
...and end my turn!
My turn! Draw!
I don't have a card in my hand to bring
Resurrection of the Dead back
from the Graveyard...
I'll use God Slime as my wall until I get
the chance to Summon Ra again!
If I can make Ra appear,
Obelisk will be wiped out in an instant!
Yugi, I'm going to tell you something!
The theme of my deck is "Immortality"!
It's designed to bring back God over and
over again until my enemy is defeated!
And that includes
this God Slime as well!
And then I'll Summon this Monster...
I Summon Revival Slime
in Defense Mode!
Revival Slime!
The Monster with regenerative powers
that gave me a lot of trouble when
I was fighting the brainwashed doll!
Can I defeat a god?!
The Slime even blocks
redirected attacks?!
Revival Slime reforms.
Then I activate
a Magic Card from my hand!
Fusion!
I polymerize God Slime
and Revival Slime!
A fusion between two Slimes?!
What the? Isn't it still God Slime?!
No, there's got to be something
different about it!
Monsters combined together can't
attack on the turn they were formed.
My turn ends with that!
Malik must have increased the abilities
of God Slime somehow in that fusion...
I wonder...
It's my turn! Draw!
I Summon Big Shield Gardna
in Defense Mode!
And The Great War God Obelisk,
attack the God Slime!
God Hand Crusher!!
He freakin' did it!
Did I beat it?
God Slime is regenerating itself!
I knew it!
That's useless!
Now that God Slime has inherited
Revival Slime's Regeneration
Ability after fusing with it,
it has become
an impenetrable Wall Monster!
To be more specific...
Immortal God Slime!
Immortal God Slime?!
Shit...!
As long as that slime is there, he won't be able to damage Malik!
He has to do something about
that Regeneration Ability!
Yugi...
That damn Malik knew Yugi was going
to Summon the third god, Obelisk...
Taking that attack was all a ploy to get
the Immortal God Slime on the field!
Malik's terrifying strategy has even
rendered Obelisk powerless...!
Is there even a way for Yugi
to turn this around?!
I end my turn!
My turn!
Draw!
Malik must be using
the God Slime as a shield.
He's waiting for a way to get Resurrection of the Dead back into his hand.
If he revives Ra,
Obelisk will be destroyed!
Even if I get rid of the Slime,
it won't damage Malik himself.
What can I do...?
There's nothing to think about, Yugi.
Just wait until
the darkness consumes you!
That is your fate!
Here we go!
I set a reverse card, and then...
I Summon Bowganian in Defense Mode!
Bowganian?
As long as this Monster remains alive
on the field, it does 300 points of damage
to my Life Points every turn!
Partner!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I place a reverse card!
Then I sacrifice Big Shield Gardna!
And Summon Black Magician Girl!
If I don't defeat Bowganian this turn,
my Life Points are going to be harmed!
I can't let my partner suffer anymore!
Black Magician Girl! Attack Bowganian!
Black Burning!!
Not so fast!
That's far enough!
Reverse card, open!
Permanent Trap! Defender Slime!!
Thanks to the effects of Defender Slime, all attacks sent to the Monsters on my field will be
absorbed by the Eternal Wall - God Slime!
Here! You can have it back!
Black Magician Girl!
As long as I've got the Permanent Trap,
Defender Slime, on the field,
none of my Monsters can be defeated!
Even if you attack me with Obelisk,
the Permanent Trap's effects
will activate immediately!
So as long as God Slime
exists on my field,
myself and my Monsters
may as well be treated the same as
having the ability of immortality!
Partner!
And now, before your turn ends,
Bowganian activates its Special Ability!
Crossbow Bolt of Hell!!
Other me!
Partner, are you alright?!
Yeah... How about you?
I can't let my partner take any more of this! But what can I do?!
Hey! Hey! Looking like that,
you're still worrying about others?!
Don't even bother!
Your fate has already been decided.
Even God...
Even the Pharaoh...
They are powerless when faced
with my untouchable power!
All that awaits you
is the entrance to Hell!!
Before long you will all bow before me,
because everyone fears their death!
Yu... gi...
Damn it all! Can't he do something
against that stupid slime?!
Yugi! Pull yourself together!
What's wrong with you?
Y-Yu... gi...
Yugi, there's no need to hold back.
I am already prepared to die!
Oi, Anzu?
What the heck're you talking
about out of the blue?
Crush me along with the evil
heart I bred inside of me!
Anzu...?
No, it's not her! That's Malik!!
Malik!
Anzu, what's wrong with you?
So my dominant persona still had some
traces of himself hidden inside of her?
What a persistent fool!
Yugi, I swore I would get revenge
on you for killing my father...
I formed the Ghouls
with the desire to kill you.
But I didn't know the truth...
The one who killed my father was
my other self inside of me!
That's right! It was you!!
Hey, Anzu?
Well, mister "dominant personality"...
You should have realized that
before this body became mine.
But now all you can do is gather up
all that guilt inside yourself...
...and take it with you to your grave
as you enter death!
I'll take you along with me!
That's impossible...
No one can destroy me!
Certainly not some deceased Pharaoh!
What's wrong with her?!
Get a grip, Anzu!
Anzu-chan!
Malik!
Ishizu!
Malik...!
My sister!
What are you trying to do, Malik?!
I'm sorry, sister...
This is all I can do now!
Yugi!
I know you can send my
dark heart to the darkness!
That is your final test as Pharaoh!
Malik...
Give it up!
And go die in a ditch
somewhere by yourself,
my "oh so great Dominant Half".
There is no way for Yugi
to beat me in this situation!
Now then... Shall we continue the Duel?
My turn!
Draw!!
Here it is!
The card that will put
Resurrection of the Dead
back into my hand!
Magic Card, activate!
Magical Stone Excavation!
Magical Stone Excavation?!
Thanks to the effects
of Magical Stone Excavation,
I discard two cards from my hand...
...and in exchange, add a Magic Card
from my Graveyard to my hand.
Without a doubt, the one I pick...
...is Resurrection of the Dead!
On my next turn,
I will Special Summon Ra!
And when I do,
it will be the end of you!
Other me!
We've got to... There has to be a way!
Right! I know, Partner!
This will be our last gamble!
Yugi...
Are you prepared yet!?
The darkness of death
is right in front of you!
If he can't beat Malik, Yugi is going to be offered to the darkness!
But if he manages to beat Malik, his dominant personality will be offered instead!
Unless he can find a way to attack Evil Malik while sparing the good one, Yugi won't be able to attack!
And then he Summons Ra again!
Please! You have to bare through it, Yugi!
There has to be something you can do!
Next time!
"Obelisk's Anger: Soul Energy MAX"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other