The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
It's been a while, Yugi... Jounouchi-han.
Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
You're Mai Kujaku's servant?
Useless! Here's the attack!
Nightmare Shadow Sonic!
W-What happened? The Shadow Sonic was reflected!
My Barbarian Number 1!
Honda's card helped me.
I'm grateful, Honda!
Dark Fire! Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
A monster in defense mode.
Go! Barbarian Number 1!
All right, Jounouchi-kun!
The two Barbarians powered each other up! Now there's a great chance!
Go, Jounouchi! Show this dinosaur bastard the power of our friendship!
Power of friendship, was it? What bullshit!
My ultimate card is still in my deck.
All right! Here it is! My ultimate card!
Show yourself, Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
What?
Red-Eyes?
It's very rare for someone to see this card.
So, even if ya lose, you can still feel honored.
It's the first time that I've see it...
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
This one, just like the Blue-Eyes...
..it's a legendary card.
Ryuzaki had a card like this?
I have traded almost all my cards for this super-rare card!
I use the magic card Dark Dragon Clan Claws
and give it a power up!
Go, Red-Eyes!
Dark Flame Bullet!!
Mine and Honda's Barbarians!
The strength of your friendship is so small.
Damn!
So you can do it when you want, servant!
Now then, Jounouchi... it's your turn!
Is this the end?
Jounouchi!
Yugi... is there a way for Jounouchi to win? If this keeps up, he will lose...
In this situation... The way for Jounouchi's victory...
I can just think there's only one...
But I promised that I wouldn't give any advice to Jounouchi-kun....
Jounouchi! An amateur like you beating me is impossible!
I have no more cards that can defeat Ryuzaki's monster.
Will I lose here?
Jounouchi, don't give up!
It's not like you to give up!
That's right, Jounouchi-kun!
Go for it! There must be a way!
Believe in yourself, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi! There's no way for you to defeat...
Oh yeah... Jounouchi set the Time Magician card on the field.
No one can predict what happens when the Time Magic of the Time Magician card is used.
But, I don't think that he knows that it can be used like that.
Now, servant! Finish him off quickly!
Wait a minute...
That's right... Mai Kujaku lost to this amateur thanks to the Time Magician.
Which means that if I have the Time Magician I can't lose to Mai Kujaku.
Jounouchi!
In this duel, what do you think about the winner getting one of the opponent's rare cards?
If I win, I'll take your Time Magician....
Okay?
Time Magician?
Speaking of it... I played it...
On the other hand, if I lose, I'll give you the Red-Eyes card.
Hey! What are you doing? Don't joke around!
Ryuzaki! I don't agree with this kind of condition!
Shut up!
As my servant you have to obey my orders!
Who's yer servant? Ye're annoyin' me! Be quiet!
What's going on...? Red-Eyes is a super-rare card...
For him to bet it...
The Time Magician must...
be more valuable than it...
It's true that I don't know what will happen if I play this card alone... But...
Fine, Ryuzaki! In this duel, if I lose, I'll give you the Time Magician!
All right!
Jounouchi-kun?
What a fool...
But before that happens... I'll use this card!
What?
He discovered it, didn't he? His only possibility!
That idiot! He said too much!
But wait! The possibility to activate Time Magic is 1 in 2.
It isn't you who decides for the Time Magician!
Time Roulette!
The roulette started to spin!
If it is good, it's Time Magic, otherwise it'll self-destruct.
Please! Hit the good one!
The pointer...
...is stopping.
It's good!
Time Magic!!
What? What is happening?
Yugi... That's...
That is...
What happened?
In an instant, millions of years passed and Red-Eyes became a fossil.
My Red-Eyes was...
Ryuzaki... as promised, give your star chips and Red-Eyes to me!
All right! Jounouchi-kun won!
Honda!
Jounouchi!
What a good feeling...
Y-You... came back just to beat me!?
You really worried me...
So this beating was obvious, wasn't it?
I am not so bad that I need for you to worry about me!
What did you say?
That's right!
Stop that! Jounouchi-kun! Honda-kun!
Leave them be, Yugi...
That's the way they show their gratefulness.
I-Is that so?
But...  they really are like Idiot number 1 and Idiot number 2.
It's getting dark already, isn't it?
And it seems there's no duelist in this side...
There's no duelist that would battle at night, isn't that right?
What will we do now?
Find a good place to spend the night.
Eh? Really? This isn't good...
I'm hungry!
Jeez... They invite us to a tournament where we have no meals... it's unbelievable!
Well... Besides Yugi, not one of us was invited, isn't that right?
Now, I don't care about star chips, I want food!
I would like a bed to sleep in.
Found some mushrooms!
I'll help myself!
Stop it! That's poisonous for sure!
Don't do something like that, Jounouchi-kun!
Well... You are all together this time too, aren't you?
What? You again?
You! Did you come here to eat in front of us?
What about it, Jounouchi? Want to trade this chocolate for your star chips?
Don't joke around! These star chips are my life!
It's a joke! A joke!
As a duelist, I didn't feel that you would degrade to that level.
Jeez...This person really pisses me off.
What about this...? We'll have a truce for tonight. We're all tired, aren't we?
That's right. We've been dueling all day.
I can't trust her. Isn't she planning something?
So, you don't want anything to eat, right?
Amazing!
Food and a tent, you have a little of everything.
You brought all this for yourself?
A duelist can only depend on himself. It's only natural to be prepared.
Cooking is your duty.
You two, go get water.
OK.
Obeying that woman's order annoys me a lot...
Fool... She's giving us food! Don't worry about it!
I'll go get some wood.
Ok.
It's Anzu-chan, right?
There's a shower over there, so, when they return with the water you can use it.
Really?
There are things that only girls can understand.
Mai Kujaku...
She seemed to be a annoying woman, but she has a good side...
Hey, boys! No peeking!
Prepare the food quietly.
Anzu-chan! I'll be on guard, so rest assured.
Thank you.
There's no need to thank me.
Mai-san, why did you come to this island? It is really for the prize money?
I was a dealer on a cruise ship that traveled the world.
Day after day, I met people with money that played cards.
These people only thought about money and power. These kind of people are stupid.
But, I became fed up with that and started to hate people.
Hey...
Why are you always together with the others?
Why? We're friends, so...
It's a mysterious thing....
When I look at you, I feel like I have lost something.
Mai-san...
What is it?
There was a sound coming from the bushes.
There's no one here.
What happened?
Something happened?
Hey! Can we get in and see?
No, of course!
Seems good!
Let's dig in!
It's delicious!
It's good, isn't?
It's true.
Mai-san already has 8 star chips?
Tomorrow, you'll be the first one to get to the castle!
Yeah.
But, eventually we'll duel with each other, Yugi.
Hey, can we forget about duels just for now?
That's right. Or we will not enjoy the food properly.
Now, we're together but tomorrow everyone will be enemies! That's to be a duelist!
Thanks for the food.... I'll take some fresh air.
Jeez... That woman isn't cute at all!
To remember about the past.... I'm not like this...
Almost time to sleep.
Where did Mai-san go?
That's right.
She's a really arrogant woman.
Leave her be.
But...
Anzu!
Who is it? Show yourself!
If you don't, we will come!
Bakura-kun?
Then...
What I saw wasn't an illusion, isn't that right?
You got on board too?
Ah... yes.
We didn't meet for all this time.
Really?
Well... we now have another supporter, so let's be grateful....
What the heck? Everyone brought you their cards.
I understand the feeling.
After all, we are in the Duelist Kingdom.
That's right!
Yeah... In this island everyone put their hearts in their cards.
Just joking...
What is the card you like the most, Jounouchi-kun?
Of course, it's this one!
From now on, I am the Flame Swordsman!
I am this one!
Commander!
Really... they are like kids...
But what Jounouchi-kun said is true.
Anzu, you too. What is the card you like the most?
That's right...
For me, it's this card.
Saint Magician?
A weird woman that draws a lot of attention....
Idiots!
Yugi-kun, what is the card you like the most?
Mine is, surely, Black Magician!
Somehow, I understand a little of everyone's feelings.
Having a card you like, gives you a feeling of believing in a duel.
As my grandpa says... cards have a heart.
And when you find the card's heart, the true duel can start.
Bakura-kun, which card do you like?
I like this one.
The Change of Heart card?
You like a weird card.
Oh yeah, Yugi-kun.... Why not duel with me?
Of course, we won't bet any star chips.
Isn't that good Yugi? Since we got in this island we just had serious duels.
That's right. It would be good to duel without any pressure.
How about you put your favorite cards in Yugi's deck?
- That's a good idea!
- Yeah!
All right! Then let's get the cards from everyone and build an original deck!
All right! All the preparations are complete!
Try your best, you guys!
Yugi probably will win, but... Try your best too, Bakura!
What...?
What is this sound?
T-That is...
What is this?
This is a Dark Game!
What complete fools you are.
With this the Millennium Puzzle is mine.
What?
If it's a Dark Game, I'll be your opponent!
You have appeared... Other Yugi!
I was waiting for you!
What? Why is everyone doing cosplay of Duel Monsters?
Ah... Even me?
Due to Bakura-kun's power, we were sealed in the game.
If we don't win the game, we'll not be able to come back to the real world!
I'm sure that this is a dream! Guys, let's go!
Next time: Trap of the Metamorpot! Flame Swordsman in Danger
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship