Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Bakura's Diabound attacked while hiding within the darkness.
He was able to defeat Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
But after we gave him strength,
my other self managed to Summon Ra!
Bakura was beaten.
Or so we thought.
Somehow, time began flowing backwards!
Bakura was revived and my other self...
"The Pharaoh is Still Alive"
A woman?
It doesn't matter who it is!
Let's take her out first!
Yeah!
Woman... Show me the power of your Ka!
Lord Akhenaden...
What are you waiting for?
Call out your Ka!
If you don't, you'll....
This is strange...
Even on the verge of death, she's still resisting...?
Is there really a Ka
in this woman's body...?
What.... is this light...?
Woman! Call out your Ka!
Now! Do it now!
What are you doing?
You're going to die if you keep this up...!
Don't you have a Ka...?
Duos!
Seto.... what do you...
Woman... What is your name?
Kisara.
Kisara, don't leave my side.
Never woulda guessed a priest would be joining us here!
We got grudges worth years of suffering!
Ain't it about time you pay for it!?
That woman can't even call out a Ka...
Since it's two-on-one, we hold the advantage!
Yeah!
You scum! Don't you dare harm Seto!
Don't move a muscle, geezer!
We're as good as goners!
So who the hell cares if we drag one little "Holy Priest" down with us to Hell?!
Humph. Then give it a try!
- What?!
Duos!
Aura Sword!!
Impossible!
Seto!
Kisara, are you alright?
That was close!
I was saved thanks to this guy, Mister "Holy Priest"!
And as you can see, your Ka wound up like that!
Duos!
I bet a Holy Priest's gotta
be scrumptious!
Gobble 'im up!
SETO!!
That's.... the white dragon from that time!
The hell's up with that dragon?
That white dragon is the Ka
this woman gave birth to...?
Shit...! KILL THEM!
Seto!
This is the attack of a God...!
What is that light?
Let her rest in her room for a while.
Yes.
Seto.... that white dragon's power may exceed that of Bakura's Diabound...
No... Even the Three Illusionary Beast Gods of the Pharaoh.
That Ka is different from any other!
It is most likely that
the White Dragon is a Ba!
Seto! You must steal
the Ka from that woman!
But... if her Ka really
is connected to her Ba,
stealing the White Dragon
means the death of that woman!
Why are you hesitating!?
Kill that woman and extract the White Dragon from within her!
You will wield a God!
Lord Akhenaden...!
Only at that moment will the throne accept you!
As the new Pharaoh!
P-Please wait a moment!
We are still yet to locate the missing Pharaoh...!
It matters not where the Pharaoh is.
If the current Pharaoh does not return, who will inherit his position?!
Don't you understand, Seto?! It's you!
Lord Akhenaden! The Pharaoh is still alive!
There is no way someone as I, who does not wield a God, could ever replace him!
This land needs the Pharaoh's authority!
All we can do right now
is look for the Pharaoh!
Seto...
Please excuse me.
That is enough for now...
The time will come sooner or later...
Where you come to
learn your destiny, my son!
What a nice view.
I can't believe I got my hands on the Millennium Puzzle this quick.
Akhenaden has already
become my game piece.
All that remains are the remaining priests and the other small fry.
You can all just sit quietly
and await your deaths.
You're ecstatic, aren't you?!
And with good reason.
When all the Millennium Items are gathered, the Door of the Underworld will open.
And my original body, the Great Wicked God Zorc, will revive!
And when that moment comes, the Eighth Key will appear as well!
Once I know its location,
I'll be able to break the seal and revive Zorc in the real world.
Why are you getting so irritated?!
I said that hurts...!
What are you not happy with?
Wait...
The Eighth Key...
Damn it!
Wasn't the Eighth Key the key that sealed Zorc away 3,000 years ago?!
So that means...
The moment the seal on Zorc is broken and he emerges back into this world...
We need the Pharaoh!
But that Pharaoh was just killed!
No... wait!
The game still continues...
So that must mean the king left a clue behind in his death.
Let me think...
3,000 years ago, the Pharaoh used the Eighth Key to seal everything inside of this.
After that, he wouldn't want anyone to find the Eighth Key ever again....
If it was me, what would I do...?
That's it.... I'd erase all the evidence.
Erase...?
That's it... I know what it is now... the Eighth Key.
I'm hungry! Now I'm thirsty~!
Owww~!
You're so damn heavy Bobasa! Get off!
Water, water~!
Oi, hold it!
Wait!
What the?
The Nile river?
It's huge!
Where is my other self?
That cliff lead to the river....
so if we follow the Nile, we might find him!
Mmm.
Water, WATER~!
Wait for us, Bobasa!
It's here!
I did it!
How's that!?
Lightly... Lightly... Lightly~!
It's floating!
Good! Progress, progress!
Hey! What's wrong?!
Hey! Move, will you?!
OWW!
I failed again~
No matter how hard I try, I just can't make it...
Master...
That's Black Magician Girl, ain't it?
Like hell!
But she looks just like her!
Prince!
Why is the prince here of all places?!
And why are you dressed in this weird outfit and with these weird people?
W-Weird people?!
Is it possible this girl can see us?
Could she be Bobasa's friend?
The "Bo" in Bobasa~
Stands for the "Bo" in "Bobbing Glutton~"
Hey, Bobasa!
Where the hell have you been?!
Cool?
Isn't that Yugi's cape?!
Where'd you find it?!
Bobasa wanted to eat fish.
It's not a fish! It's a cape!
Where'd you find it?!
But the cape's not edible.
I didn't mean that!
The cape was floating along the river, right?
Yeah. Yeah!
Does that mean Yugi's around here somewhere...?
I hope so... But he may have been washed away by the river...
Don't make things more complicated!
My other self must be close!
Let's find him!
Yeah!
Wait a minute! That's Prince's cape, isn't it!
- Prince?
Uhh, that's not right.... I meant Pharaoh!
Pharaoh?!
You....! You know my other self?!
Are you really not Prince?
Yeah, we.... We're the Pharaoh's friends!
Friends?
Yeah!
Anyway, since you know Yugi...
No, the Pharaoh...
Help us find him!
What happened to Prince?
We don't know, but he's missing!
Why didn't you tell me sooner?!
I'll help too!
They followed us!
Those guys are the one who killed Master, Bakura's...!
Are you guys really Prince's friends?
Yeah!
Then you're my friends, too!
Amazing!
Now let's go look for Prince while we have the chance!
Pharaoh!
Pharaoh!!
Lord Shada, we searched all over the surrounding area,
but we haven't found the Pharaoh anywhere.
I see...
Has the search team for Bakura reported yet?!
Lord Shada!
We've found Bakura's footsteps!
What?
That is.... Spiria!
Isis.... You must find the Pharaoh.
That's the Millennium Puzzle...
I see...
The Millennium Puzzle has been stolen by Bakura...!
Cut the bullshit!
"Holy Pharaoh", my foot!
Akhenamkhanen...!
He's the last person I'd call that!
Didn't he create the Millennium Items you're all wearing to gain evil power!?
It's true that the holders of the Millennium Items gain great powers.
But those items also respond to the darkness in the holders' heart...
...and drags them into
the World of Darkness!
Quite the problem-makers they can be!
Father, why did you create the Millennium Items?
Didn't you know these items would bring nothing but pain and misfortune to the world?
Is there no way you can answer me now?
Because I have no memories of my father.
What's this...?
The prince is so healthy!
Your heir as Pharaoh has finally been born!
Heir as Pharaoh?
So this is the passion I felt as he comforted me...?
My father?
Father...! I don't wanna go!
As the heir to the throne, you must not say this!
Yes... Father...!
I understand...! I feel it! Your voice is shaking, Father...!
In fear...
Father...! I can't do this!
No! Now let's go!
Wait, Father!
Father...!
Souls of our great ancestors....
I have committed an unforgivable sin...!
This thousand-year sin...
No....! Please put the blame of the creation of seven the Millennium Items on me!
I beg you! I pray that my son does not inherit my sins!
Please let me take all the suffering!
Father...? Are you crying...?
I.... I will take all the consequences on my shoulders!
That's right...
I know how much father loved me...
Who are you?
My name is Hasan.
Hasan?
Pharaoh, the Great Evil God Zorc is about to revive.
Only you can defeat Zorc!
Zorc?
The former king Akhenamkhanen is also watching over you.
You knew my father?!
Hasan!
So you're studying magic?
But I'm not good enough.
I always used to hold my master back.
Back in our world, there's
this thing called a card game.
There's this card character
girl who looks just like you!
Looks like me?
She's called Black Magician Girl!
She's a very powerful girl spellcaster!
If you work hard, you can be just as strong as Black Magician Girl!
Yeah!
And your name is?
I'm Mana!
Black Magician Girl, eh?
That has a cool ring to it!
Yeah! I'll try my best!
The "Bo" in Bobasa~
Hey Bobasa, don't just stop!
Oi! Are you listening?!
Yugi!
Hey~!
Partner!
Guys!
Other Me!
Yugi!
You're still alive after all!
Yeah!
Yugi... Thank God...
PRINCE~!
YUGI~!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
You're okay, Yugi!
Even if we believed you were alive,
until we saw it, we were really worried!
But Bakura has stolen
your Millennium Puzzle...
And you haven't regained your memory.
Priest Shada knows where Bakura is...
And Yugi is heading
for the Kul Elna village....
Be careful! We don't know what traps are waiting for us!
Next time!
"The Village of Dead Spirits"
Please look forward to it!