Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Kaiba-kun suddenly came into the Final Match of the KC Grand Prix.
With the fate of Kaiba Corporation at stake, he faced off against Sieg.
He attacked over and over with the Goddess Combo he used to torture Jounouchi-kun...
But Kaiba-kun's confidence never wavered.
And he defeated Sieg with a final winning attack.
Well, that is indeed something Kaiba-kun would do...
"The Final Battle for Duel King -
Yugi VS Leon"
I'm never pleased when Kaiba wins,
but we can't let that arrogant bastard do whatever he pleases.
In the end, he was just doing this because of some grudge he had, right?
What a troublesome guy.
But he's also a very strong Duelist...
Why must he resort to this?
Other Me?
Kaiba, you showed me your strong spirit as a Duelist in this Duel.
Yugi, now the trouble-making rat is gone.
Now it's your turn to show me a Duel fitting the Duel King.
Brother!
You're really great, Brother!
With that, I've shown rivaling companies all around the world
just how foolish it is to oppose Kaiba Corporation.
Meaning that wasn't just a waste of time.
Yup!
Isono.
Yes.
Hurry up on the preparations for Yugi and Leon's Duel.
Roger.
And what should we do with that person?
Let him be! He can't do anything now!
Brother!
We'll show him how successful Kaiba Corporation is!
Now, I shall announce it again!
The KC Grand Prix held by the Kaiba Corporation...
An outstanding participant has emerged!
Leon Wilson!
He will be granted the most honorable right as a Duelist!
That is, the right to challenge the Duel King, Yugi Mutou!
The most exciting match is about to start!
This is the stage for the final battle, Blue-Eyes Castle!
Great! There are priority seats!
Are you sure this is fine, Mokuba-kun?
To invite us to watch from here...?
Of course!
You guys helped me out a ton of times when I was in trouble.
The least I can do is give you the best seats to root for Yugi!
Thank you, Mokuba-kun!
The battle for the title of the true Duel King is about to start!
Yeah...
Other Me, it's finally here.
Yes.
The opponent is Leon-kun...
I'm sure it will be an interesting Duel.
Let's do our best to have a Duel with no regrets!
Yup!
Let's go, Partner!
To the viewers all over the world, can you feel it?
The excitement! The anticipation! And the cheers of the huge crowd here!
Here comes the Duel King, Yugi Mutou!
Yugi-san, I finally made it here.
It's been my dream to have a Duel with you.
I've gone through countless Duels to fulfill my dream.
But today...!
Now the match of the century, the battle for the title of Duel King is about to start!
Who will emerge the winner? Will it be Leon Wilson?! Or Yugi Mutou?!
Let's have a great Duel!
Leon...
Now the two of them are ready.
And this person shall announce the start of the Duel!
I'm gonna?!
Like hell you would! It'll be my big brother! My big brother!
Kaiba...
The KC Grand Prix is organized by Kaiba Corporation!
This program is also brought to you by Kaiba Corporation!
Oh man.
Kaiba's hogging the spotlight again.
That can't be helped.
This Duel tournament is an important event that concerns the future of Kaiba Corporation.
But rather than standing there, wouldn't Kaiba-kun want to battle with Yugi again?
Yes... In fact, my big brother is the only one who is most qualified to Duel with Yugi.
But Kaiba Corporation is what's most important right now...
Or rather, he's standing there for our dream.
Yeah, as a Duelist, I understand his feelings of wanting to fight with Yugi.
I want to fight him as well, you know!
But Leon earned his right by having the skill to defeat all of us.
That's right, I hope he'll do his best on behalf of the Duelists who were defeated.
You stand before us, having survived intense battles with Duelists from all over the world!
It is your greatest honor to be able to stand there!
And within this battlefield,
you must show the world a battle worthy of the title for Duel King!
Now, as you seek the greatest victory...
The Duel starts now!
Here I come!
I'll attack first!
Draw!
I Summon Forest Wolf in Attack Position!
Forest Wolf? What kind of card is that?
That is...
Turn end.
My turn!
Draw!
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card...
Fusion!
I will fuse two Monsters I have in my hand.
I fuse Illusion Beast Gazelle and Berfomet together!
To Summon Winged Phantom Beast Chimera!
I use Chimera to attack Forest Wolf!
Way to go!
Great! Yugi's in the lead!
Turn over!
Yugi-san is indeed strong.
By Dueling with you like this, I can really feel your oppressive aura.
I have always dreamed about dueling with you like this, Yugi-san.
No matter what form it may take, my dream has come true!
My turn, draw!
I Summon Little Red Riding Hood in Defense Position!
So cute!
Seems like Leon has many cards like that in his deck...
Yes, it feels like a deck full of childhood tales!
Don't get deceived just because they look cute.
Eh? What do you mean by that?
You wouldn't know how strong he really is unless you've fought with him.
Turn end!
Eh? He's not placing any reverse cards?
This really is strange.
He's different from how I felt when he fought with me.
Leon Wilson...
Eh?
I've gotten a feel of his Dueling style while monitoring the Duelists.
There is something different about him now...
Or does it mean he wasn't serious before now?
What's going on with Leon-kun?
Partner...
He always looked like he enjoyed the Duels before...
But now...
Yes, there's certainly something different about him.
Those are not of same eyes Leon had when he was enjoying his Duels.
My turn! Draw!
Th-This...!
How is this possible?!
Anyway, I better go inform Seto-sama right away!
I Summon Retrained Elf Swordsman in Attack Position!
I use Retrained Elf Swordsman to attack Little Red Riding Hood!
Great! Yugi had yet another successful attack!
I feel bad for Leon, but I think Yugi's gonna emerge as the winner!
It's not going to be so easy, though.
Leon's deck is full of Monsters with Special Effects.
I activate Little Red Riding Hood's Special Ability!
When this card is destroyed in battle,
I can Special Summon a Level Four or lower Warrior-Type Monster!
I Special Summon Forest Hunter in Attack Position!
And when Forest Hunter is Summoned successfully...
One Monster on the opponent's field will be removed from the game!
What?
That's right! Forest Hunter, get rid of Chimera!
Yugi!
Like I said, there are many Monsters with unknown powers in Leon's deck.
And the Leon now is different from the Leon that I fought with.
What do you mean by that?
He's probably just nervous, don't you think?
When he was Dueling with me, he seemed to really be enjoying the Duel.
But now that he's finally fighting with his idolized Yugi, he doesn't seem happy at all.
I end my turn.
Yugi-san!
The True Duelist whom I've admired...
It's been my dream to fight with you.
But now, I'm fighting with you for the sake of my mission, Yugi-san!
Mission?
This is bad, Seto-sama!
P-Please look at these!
To prevent further incidents, I continued checking the backgrounds of the Duelists.
And this is what I found!
Hmph, so that's it.
Looks like you finally get it, Kaiba.
Sieg, is this your strategy?
That is right. Everything is going according to my plan.
To think that another son of the Schroeder family
would enter this competition with a fake name.
What?!
Yes. He is my authentic younger brother as well as a genuine Dueling genius.
Leonhart von Schroeder!
Now, Leonhart! Playtime is over!
Show him your true abilities!
Yes, Brother!
Brother?!
Leon-kun, what's going on here?
Leon-kun...
It would appear that you not only got cocky,
but you let your guard down after defeating me, Kaiba.
But I have already prepared my next move.
On this grand stage that Kaiba Corporation has painstakingly set up
for the entire world to see...
The Duel King, Yugi Mutou, will be utterly defeated by my Leonhart.
What would everyone think after witnessing that?
Naturally, the name "Schroeder" would be deeply etched in their hearts.
And at that very moment, we Schroeders will announce our new game product to the world.
After making such an impact,
everyone around the world will be very eager to purchase games made by the Schroeders!
In short, you're going to copy my company and do the exact same thing?
Looks like you are finally getting it, Kaiba.
If my synopsis proves accurate, the outcome of our Duel earlier will hardly matter at all!
As long as I can prove that I am a superior enterpriser to you!
What the hell do you think a Duel is?!
You're the worst!
Seto-sama, should we stop the Duel?
You cannot disqualify Leonhart like how you did I.
The Duel has already gotten underway.
If you stop it now, the KC Grand Prix will stumble at its climax...
and the reputation of your company would be lost.
But doing that would also be to my benefit.
How is this going according to your plan, you damned simpleton?!
Yugi Mutou is the only person in this world who is qualified to be my rival!
There's no way the likes of your little brother can beat him!
And if Yugi is not defeated, your plan would be meaningless.
Because there's no Duelist in the world capable of defeating Yugi other than me!
What terrifying confidence!
For real.
That's Kaiba for you.
This Duel will continue!
Stand here and watch as your planning and effort goes to waste!
Yugi, I won't allow you to lose to any other Duelists.
Kaiba.
Leonhart!
As a member of the Schroeder family and as my little brother...
You must defeat Yugi Mutou!
Do not dare to betray myself, nor your mother and father!
I understand, Brother.
Here I come, Yugi-san!
Leon-kun...
But I don't think he got close from the start in order to deceive us.
Yeah, I feel the same way.
Leon, are you really okay with this?
Is this kind of Duel really what you wish for?
Are you not a True Duelist?
Do not listen to him, Leonhart!
Right now, you need to do your best to defeat Yugi Mutou!
You will be recognized as a member of the Schroeder family when you win!
Think of how happy our mother would be!
Do not forget this!
Yes!
Leon...
Yugi-san, I understand what you're trying to tell me.
I became a Duelist because I admire you.
But now I want to be of help to my brother.
My brother needs me now... Me, who has no place in the Schroeder family.
That's why...  That's why I have to...
Sieg... Siegfried! The home tutor is waiting for you.
Brother!
Please teach me! Brother-
That won't do, Leonhart.
Siegfried has lessons now.
Yes...
Come now, Siegfried.
I'm sure you'll become a worthy successor and bring glory back to the family!
Yes, Mother.
Leonhart, you mustn't interfere with Siegfried's studies.
You got that?
Yes, Mother...
That's right, my brother was the star of hope for the Schroeder family.
And without disappointing anyone, he has also shown his talent.
I'm very proud of my brother.
But I couldn't help him in any way.
However, my encounter with Duel Monsters changed my life greatly.
Awesome!
He really created them!
I couldn't tear my eyes away from my favorite cards and Yugi-san's Duels.
That's because the world that I'd imagined was becoming a reality.
The more I got exposed to Dueling, the more obsessed I became with that wonderful world.
Draw!
The winner is, Leon Wilson-kun!
Brother!
Th-This is...
I have been aware for quite some time that you
have been participating in such competitions.
And that you have hacked into their systems to make up fake names and experience.
I have investigated everything.
I-I'm sorry! I really wanted to be a Duelist!
But I knew Father and the rest wouldn't approve of this...
It isn't as if I'm angry about this or anything.
On the contrary, I am very proud to have such an outstanding brother.
Leonhart...
Although your computer skills and hacking skills are impressive...
Your Dueling skills are far more crucial to the Schroeder family.
I'm... crucial?
That's right.
The time has come for you to use your skills for the greater good of the Schroeder family.
I'll do anything, Brother!
In order to be of use to you, I'll do anything!
So.. So for the sake of my brother, even if my opponent is you, Yugi-san...
I'll defeat you!
Leon...
But this doesn't seem right.
Other Me, do we have no other choice but to fight him.
But Leon is serious.
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Iron Hans in Attack Position!
And when this card is Summoned successfully,
I can Special Summon Iron Knight from the deck!
Watch me.
For the sake of my brother who needs me, I'll win this no matter what!
I Special Summon Iron Knight!
That is correct, Leonhart.
Let's fight!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The climax of the KC Grand Prix has begun!
But to think that Leon-kun is actually Sieg's younger brother...
I can't believe it!
He enjoys his Duels so much...
But now he's treating Yugi as an enemy.
Leon-kun, are you really fine with this?
What we are more concerned about is the card he took from Sieg...
What card is it?
Next time!
"Golden Castle of Stromberg"
Duel standby!