Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
This is...!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...!
Behold.
These 5 cards gathered on the field make the Ultimate Combo.
The God Five!
Perfect and completely invincible!
These complete every flaw the god has and make it untouchable!
I can't win...
I can't... defeat Osiris...
Stand up, Yugi!
If there's a god standing in your way...
Mow the god down!
Overcoming God!
The Ultimate Infinite Loop
Now!
Stand up, Yugi!
I understand, Kaiba!
Just you wait!
I will now...
Defeat God!
How convenient.
The one who wields the final God Card, Obelisk, Kaiba Seto has appeared!
After I crush Yugi...
It's your turn, Kaiba!
I'm the one who will defeat Yugi.
Here I go!
My turn!
I have just 3 cards in my hand.
Magnet Warrior Alpha...
Alpha the Magnet Warrior
Baphomet...
And Big Shield Gardna.
But these Monster Cards can't even touch Osiris's current Attack Points.
Draw!
Resurrection of the Dead?
This turn I set a reverse card!
Also, Big Shield Gardna in Defense Mode!
The moment you Summon a Monster, Osiris's Special Ability activates.
Summon Lightning Shot!!
The very moment a Monster is Summoned,
Osiris gives it 2000 points of damage.
Did he say 2000 points of damage?
What a fearsome ability.
So the moment the Monster is Summoned onto the field, it's eliminated.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
The moment I were to Summon my Obelisk to the field,
half its strength would be halved in an instant.
Big- brother!
Yugi's Monster is safe!
I somehow managed to hold on this round...
but that alone won't let me win.
Next turn, Big Shield Gardna will be defeated without a doubt.
And all the Monsters on my field will disappear.
If I run out of Monsters,
Osiris can directly strike the players...
If that happens, I'll lose!
Is there really know way to defeat a god...?
That's right.
Suffer in the moment of despair.
And quiver in fear before me!
My turn!
Draw!
This turn, Lightforce Sword's effect disappears!
Now that I have 11 cards in my hand,
Osiris's Attack rises to 11000 points!
11000...?!
Big- brother, that Monster gets stronger for every card he has in his hand!
No, that's not just it.
With the Infinite Hand on his field,
he can hold as many cards in his hand as he wants.
Then it can have infinite Attack Points...?!
Is there a way to defeat that Monster?
Infinite Attack Points....
Infinite...
Infinite, right?!
That's it!
"Infinite" is just a deception of God.
Yugi, I just realized the god's flaw!
Here I come.
Osiris attacks.
Annihilate Big Shield Gardna!
If you give up now,
you're no longer worthy of being my enemy.
If so, then go ahead and disappear.
Then I will defeat that guy and take Osiris for myself.
Did you see?
God's power is infinite!
His hand gives the god infinite strength...
Is there really a way to defeat such an enemy...?
Infinite?!
That's it!
I know the god's flaw!
So you realized?
Yugi?
It's "flaw", you said?
Yeah.
Everything will be decided on the next turn..
Within this one turn,
We will determine which one of us is stronger!
What nonsense are you babbling?
Are you saying that there's a way to escape the hole I've trapped you in within just one turn?
There is!
Impossible...!
There's no way he can turn the tables.
My victory is guaranteed.
But just what is that confident look for...?
He can't win unless he defeats Osiris, holding 11,000 Attack Points...
Then that guy's Life would hit 0.
But still...
That's definitely impossible.
B-Big brother!
Don't say anything, Mokuba!
Watch carefully.
This is the power of possibility only a True Duelist wields!
A True Duelist's possibility?
Here I go!
The final turn!
The one key card is somewhere within my deck...
It all depends on whether or not I can draw it.
Draw!
I win!
What?!
Did he draw his key card?
I knew the God Cards only choose the proudest Duelists as their owners.
Here I go!
Reverse card open!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Resurrection of the Dead, you say?
I use this card to revive a Monster sleeping in the Graveyard.
The Mighty Dragon Slayer Buster Blader, return to the field!
I can tell you plan to bring him back from the dead in Defense Mode just to protect your Life Points,
but you can't win like that.
Defense Mode?
That's wrong, Malik.
Buster Blader!
Attack Mode!
What?
Attack Mode?
Is he actually planning to attack Osiris?
If you counter against the 11000 Attack Osiris,
are you planning to reduce your Life Points to 0 this way?
Malik, I just drew the key card.
This completes the infinite combo beyond the limits of God.
Infinite combo, you said?
Beyond the limits of God, you say?!
What bullshit are you on about?
There's no power stronger than the infinity of God in this world!
Behold the lineup on my field.
The Continuous Magic Card of Safe Return.
The effects of this card reach the entire field.
That means even when one of your Monsters is regenerated,
I can draw 3 cards from my Deck.
I just brought back Buster Blader to the field.
Right.
That means I get to draw 3 new cards from my Deck.
And...!
14000 Attack Points...!
Also...
When you Summoned Buster Blader,
Osiris's Special Ability was activated!
Shooraiden
Endure it, Buster Blader!
You have 3100 Attack Points.
2000 points of damage won't do you in!
It seems he managed to live,
but Buster Blader's Attack Points have fallen to 1100.
Do you still plan to attack Osiris?
It's not too late now.
I'll let you switch it to Defense Mode.
Buster Blader is in Attack Mode, Malik!
Just what is he planning?
I'll show you, Malik!
This is the Infinite Combo that goes beyond the limits of God!
I don't understand...
How can Yugi win in this position?
God's infinite power...
Break that illusion, Yugi!
Here I go! My Battle Phase!
Bring it on! You won't know you're dead until it's too late!
This Duel will be decided this turn!
Buster Blader, attack Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Dragon Buster Blade!!
I don't know what you're up to,
but you can't even scratch God with that kind of Monster!
Permanent Trap, Defender Slime, activate!
Revival Slime, become God's shield!
Every time your attacks fail,
Osiris will immediately follow with a counter-attack.
With any kind of sword, Osiris won't be harmed!
No, you won't even scratch him!
You've truly waisted your last chance at a counter-strike!
I was well aware that Revival Slime would become Osiris's shield!
And...
I was waiting for this moment!
This is my trump card!
The Magic Card Brain Control!
Brain Control?
That card lets you control an enemy Monster,
and you get to control it for one turn!
I see.
But let me tell you.
It's a pity, but that won't against God!
Buster Blader's counter-attack against Osiris has come to an end!
Wait, Malik.
Who said I was using that on Osiris?
What?!
Don't misunderstand me.
The one I used that against this turn is...
Revival Slime!
I Regenerate Summon this guy on my field!
What did you say?
You controlled Revival Slime?!
Now a Monster on the field has regenerated, Malik.
Due to the Continuous Magic Card Card of Safe Return, draw 3 cards from your Deck!
I don't know what you're planning,
but all you've accomplished is increasing Osiris's Attack Points even further!
Fool.
Now Osiris has 1700 Attack Points.
Counter-attack, Osiris!
Deliver the final blow to the nameless Pharaoh!
Don't rush.
Before you counter-attack me with Osiris,
I just Regenerate Summoned Revival Slime on my field.
And that means Revival Slime has activated Osiris's Special Ability.
What do you think happens next?
Revival Slime will revive again...
Because a Monster has been regenerated this turn, you're required to draw another 3 cards!
Damnit!
Osiris's Special Ability will activate again,
Revival Slime will be destroyed,
and then regenerated...
I then will have to draw 3 cards...
And then Osiris will attack once again!
This will continue infinitely...!
In an infinite loop!
H-He pulled this off...?!
One who can no longer draw a card from his Deck...
Can no longer continue playing the game!
Malik!
You said this, didn't you?
That if your hand was infinite, Osiris's Attack Points would also be infinite.
But that's wrong!
God's power is not infinite!
It's limited by the number of cards in your Deck!
I win, Malik!
Shit!
For me...!
For me to lose!
He did it!
Yugi won!
Now hand over your rare card and Puzzle Card.
Oi... Oi, come on...
What the?
He's not moving as if he were a doll...
I guess he must be pretty shocked after losing like that.
This is Osiris the Heaven Dragon...
The second God Card, eh...?
Yugi, as the winner, I'll give you this Osiris the Heaven Dragon according to the Ante Rule.
Here.
Take the Puzzle Card too.
But soon the Osiris card will belong to Big- brother!
This is a God Card...?
Yugi.
Now you've become one of the chosen ones the God Cards have selected.
For me, I want my enemies nothing short of the best.
Kaiba...
Otherwise, there'd be no point in defeating you.
Could it be...?
Big-sama's going to challenge Yugi to a Duel right now...?
Yugi, you know this, right?
In Battle City, when Duelists come face-to-face,
it becomes a field of battle!
Let's Duel, Yugi!
Right now the ones I need to fight are the Ghouls!
Not Kaiba!
But...
Do I have no choice?
Yugi!
Are you gonna try and take back the God Card?
You don't give up easily, Malik!
What?
All the God Cards will soon return to my hands.
I didn't give it a moment's hesitation.
But there's something I forgot to mention...
I will arrive shortly in Domino City.
And once I arrive, my plan will be set into motion.
Your plan?
Right now, I am seeing three visions.
One is you standing before me through the eyes of this doll.
Another is the port harbor of Domino City.
And the other is downtown in the city...
Through the eyes of some Rare Hunters stationed there.
Damn it!
Just a little bit more and I would've taken Kaiba down.
If you're saying stuff like that, you must be really scared!
What was that, Anzu?!
Bulls-eye, right?
I can see your friends.
The Duelist called Jounouchi...
And the rest...
Jounouchi-kun!
Guys!
Using your friends, I can easily take back the God Cards.
The Ghoul Rare Hunters have been keeping a close eye on your friends.
I can use them whenever I want.
How far will you fall, Malik?!
It's your fault.
If you had lost to me here,
your precious friends would have been left out of this.
I won't forgive you!
The one who can't forgive is me...!
The suffering my tribe endured is much more than this!
Now then, Yugi!
If you don't hurry up and find your friends,
something bad might happen to them!
Malik!
Jounouchi-kun!
Are you running away, Yugi?!
Kaiba, I can't fight you right now!
Jounouchi-kun's being targeted by the Ghouls!
I can't let them harm my friends!
Yugi...
He chooses his friends over his pride?
I will get Osiris the Heaven Dragon back soon enough.
Using the power of my Millennium Rod,
I will turn your friends into my underlings!
Jounouchi-kun...
Where in the city are you?
I hold the most destructive God, Ra in this Deck of mine!
I hold the power of the Pharaoh!
When two Rare Hunters appear before Yugi,
"Then we'll come at you with as a Tag!"
He says... eh?!
Kaiba-kun will Tag with Yugi?!
Meanwhile, unknowingly being targeted by Malik, in search of a challenge for Jounouchi,
we run into Ryouta Kajiki-kun by chance.
Jounouchi, he's too strong of an opponent for you!
Next
Time
Unseen Enemy
Sea Stealth II
Next time!
Unseen Enemy
Sea Stealth II
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...