Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
In exchange for a return flight, we came and joined the KC Grand Prix.
It's really exciting to be able to Duel top Duelists
that were selected from around the world.
But in the first match of the competition,
Jounouchi-kun's opponent turned out to be my grandpa!
As I'd expect from Grandpa, he was a tough opponent.
In the face-off between teacher and student, Jounouchi-kun emerged victorious!
Now, who will be next?
"Hot Battle! Rebecca VS Vivian"
Seriously! There's no one like Jounouchi!
Don't you think normal people would'a seen through such an obvious disguise?
Say that one more time!
B Block's second match is about to start!
In B Block's second match...
She's the youngest person to become the American Champion, a girl genius!
Rebecca Hopkins!
Rebecca!
Against her is one who dominated the Asian Duel Tournament...
The beautiful Duelist, Vivian Wong!
That person...
Oh, how cute!
Let's support her! Let's go cheer for her, everyone!
Support? Whose side are you on?
Don't tell me you'd cheer for a pretty lady
instead of supporting your best friend's granddaughter.
O-Of course, I'm going to cheer for Rebecca...
Okay, let's g-
G-Grandpa?!
Owie, owie, owie...
Are you alright, Grandpa?!
I think he sprained his back.
This is bad!
I'll call the medics right away!
Grandpa, hang on!
Yugi, don't be bothered with me.
You guys better go and support Rebecca.
But...
Yugi-kun, I'll stay here and take care of Sugoroku.
Can you guys help cheer her on on my behalf?
Professor Hopkins...
That child will surely feel more at ease if she hears your cheers.
Alright, let's target that guy.
Is it really okay to do this?
We came this far! What're you saying?!
Don't you want to take revenge on Yugi and the rest?
I know!
This time I'll make 'em all pay for the humiliation I've suffered!
Okay!
The hell am I doin' at the bottom?
Stop talking already... Let's get out of here!
This is so boring.
To think that my opponent is a small girl like you.
If my opponent was either Yugi or Kaiba...
Then I'd be able to use my fabulous Duel tactics and make them my love slaves!
And then we'd call ourselves the "Strongest Duelist Couple"
and be known all over the world!
Doesn't that sound just lovely?!
If you're talking about the "Strongest Duelist Couple", then you're already too late.
Gosh! How cheeky!
No matter how hard you try,
you won't stand a chance against my beauty and wits.
I'm gonna teach you this!
Here it comes!
Duel!!
I'll go first.
Draw!
I Summon Kung-Fu Nyan Nyan in Attack Position.
Turn end.
My turn! Draw!
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Angel's Charity!
I can draw three cards from my deck and then discard two cards from my hand.
Then I Summon Big Bang Girl in Attack Position!
Next, I set two reverse cards, ending my turn!
Hey, there she is! Over here!
Hey, Rebecca!
Ah! Darling-
Yugi!!
Are you here to support me?!
I'm so happy!
Hey! Darling is here to support m-
You better watch really close as I gracefully defeat this little girl, okay?!
You're pretty darn popular lately, ain't ya Yugi?
Heh, I'm so envious of you!
I-I'm not exactly...
Will you guys shut up?!
Rebecca, do your best!
Don't you dare lose to that tramp!
Of course! Leave it to me!
Suddenly I'm pretty fired up.
My turn! Draw!
At this instance, Kung-Fu Nyan Nyan's Special Effect is activated.
When she is in Attack Position and did not attack in that turn,
her Attack Power will increase by 300 points.
Next, I Summon Master Kyonshee in Attack Position.
Then I'll use Kung-Fu Nyan Nyan to attack Big Bang Girl!
I won't let you do that!
Trap Card, open!
The Permanent Trap, Gravity Bind!
When this card is on the field, all Level Four and higher Monsters are unable to attack!
She activated this Trap even at the expense of her Monster's movement...
I'll complete my turn.
That's our Rebecca!
But as long as Gravity Bind is on the field,
Becky is unable to use any Level Four or higher Monsters.
That means...
I'm sure Rebecca is most aware of that.
She must be planning something.
Mmm-hmm!
My turn. Draw!
And at this instance,
I activate the Special Effect of Fallen Angel Marie in the Graveyard.
As long as this card is in the Graveyard,
I can regain 200 Life Points during each of my Standby Phases.
Next, I'll activate Big Bang Girl's Special Ability!
Every time I regain Life Points, the opponent will be inflicted with 500 points of damage!
I was right.
Yeah! And with that, you don't need High-Level Monsters to inflict damage to your opponent.
I set one reverse card and end my turn.
Well, it's your turn now.
It's too quiet...
I don't think that the person who hacked into Kaiba Corporation's main computer
will just leave it at that.
Don't tell me the enemy is already amongst the contestants?!
Quickly re-check the identity of all the Duelists!
Yes.
You sneaky rat, I'll definitely catch you.
How dare you...
How dare you... make me lose face in front of Yugi!
My turn! Draw!
I guess I really am the Goddess of Victory herself.
Magic Card, activate!
Cyclone!
This card can destroy either one Magic or Trap Card.
Naturally, the one that I want to destroy is...
Gravity Bind!
Oh no! If the Monsters are freed, Rebecca will..!
Permanent Trap, activate!
Imperial Command of the Royal Palace!
When this card is on the field, it can negate all Magic Cards on the field!
A Trap again!?
Next I activate the Quick-Play Magic, Scapegoat!
How about that? Your Cyclone was useless.
Huh? Won't Scapegoat disappear too?
No... If I remember correctly, for a case like this...
It was a Quick-Play Magic used first, and then...
When you activate a set of Magic or Trap Cards in a chain reaction,
the card that was activated last will have its effect activated first and so on.
Rebecca made good use of that.
What's that supposed to mean?
This means that Scapegoat can be successfully activated since the card was used last.
The next card in order would be Imperial Command of the Royal Palace,
which thus negated Cyclone, as it was used first.
That's why Cyclone was destroyed.
I see...
So that's how it was.
Yes sir-ey.
Do you really understand?
Okay... I get it now.
So now I can't use any Level Four or higher Monsters and I can't use Magic Cards, right?
Sounds good to me!
I'm going to Summon Gyaku-Gire Panda in Attack Position!
Activate Gyaku-Gire Panda's Special Effect.
For every Monster on the opponent's field, it can increase its Attack by 500 points!
Its Attack Points increased to 3300 in a flash?
Gyaku-Gire Panda is a Level Three, so it can attack.
Go! Attack a Scapegoat!
When Gyaku-Gire Panda attacks a Defense Position Monster
whose Defense Power is less than its Attack Power...
...the difference in points will be inflicted on the opposing player as damage!
Rebecca!
Looks like it won't easy defeating her.
Why do you say that, Otogi?
She is also one of the strongest Duelists chosen by Kaiba-kun.
I've heard some rumors about her before.
She used her beautiful tactics and attacks to completely defeat her opponents.
During the Asian Tournament, she defeated the supreme Clan of the Nine Dragons.
The Duel Queen, Vivian Wong.
The Duel Queen of Asia?
Turn end.
How was it? You can't win, no matter what tricks you have.
Why don't you just give up and surrender?
Little girl.
My turn! Draw!
You're not good at admitting defeat, are you?
I choose not to pay the up keeping cost for Imperial Command of the Royal Palace
and will destroy it!
Eh?!
Because of the effect of Fallen Angel Marie in the Graveyard, I can recover 200 Life Points!
Next, because of Big Bang Girl's Effect,
I can inflict 500 points of damage to the opposing player!
GOD! This is so frustrating!
It's not over yet. I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Token Harvest Festival!
This card can destroy all the tokens on the field
and restore my Life by 800 points for each token destroyed!
Big Bang Girl's Special Effect will once again inflict 500 points of damage onto you!
Next, I Summon a Level Three Monster, Injection Angel Lily, in Attack Position!
I'll use 2000 of my Life to increase Lily's Attack Power by 3000!
Injection Angel Lily, attack!
Injection time!
Great! She turned the tables!
Les'see... Ah!
There's so many changes happening in this Duel, I can't keep up with 'em!
Turn end!
How dare you...! How dare you...!
My turn, draw!
I activate a Magic Card! Luminous Cloud!
This Magic Card will use Master Kyonshee and Kung-Fu Nyan Nyan as tributes...
...to Special Summon Dragon Lady!
That Monster is a Level Seven!
Even if she is able to Summon it, it won't be able to attack.
Partner...
Don't tell me...
Once per turn, this Monster exchanges its battling
so it can destroy one Magic or Trap Card on the opponent's field.
And then, I'll activate the Magic Card, Mystic Eruption.
If a Magic or Trap Card was destroyed in this turn,
the player will be inflicted with 1000 points of damage!
Rebecca!
Crap!
She turned it back around in a second!
Turn end.
Well? Have you gotten a taste of my strength?
It's hilarious you're even called a "girl genius" in the first place!
You'll lose in the next turn.
I'm more suited to stand beside Yugi!
Wh-What nonsensical chatter!
Before you get defeated by me, do you have any last words?
You're finished this turn.
My turn! Draw!
Because of the Effect of Fallen Angel Marie in the Graveyard, I can recover 200 Life Points.
Due to Big Bang Girl's Effect, 500 points of damage will be inflicted on the opponent.
But you are unable to defeat my Dragon Lady.
I sacrifice Big Bang Girl and Injection Angel Lily!
To summon Guardian Angel Jeanne in Attack Position!
Thanks for destroying my Gravity Bind.
Now I get to attack with my Jeanne!
But... But... Even if you defeat my Dragon Lady, I still have Life Points left!
I already calculated you would.
Magic Card! Silent Death!
This card can revive one Monster from the Graveyard to my field in Defense Position.
Revive, Big Bang Girl!
No way!
I'll use Guardian Angel Jeanne to attack Dragon Lady!
I activate Guardian Angel Jeanne's Special Effect!
My Life Points increase by the total Attack Power of the destroyed Monster!
And Big Bang Girl's Effect activates!
Your Life Points will be slashed by 500.
It can't be...
Yeah Rebecca, you did it!
You did it, Becky.
Darling, I won!
Darling belongs only to me!
This is so frustrating!!
Oh, that side's done, too.
The A Block's second match has ended with Paul McGregor as the winner!
The winner of the third match will go up against Jounouchi-kun, right?
Featured in the third battle is Sieg Lloyd versus Fortune Salim!
It would be best for you to watch this carefully.
Psh, what a flashy bastard.
I-I still can't accept this! I wanna be up there Duelin' 'gainst him!
Stupid! You think we can switch positions now?!
O-O-Ow, damn...
Huh?! It's them!
It's Ryuzaki and Haga!
What are they doing there?
Oh shit! We exposed ourselves!
You stupid fool!
What'd ya say?!
You idiots! Where's the real Salim?!
O-Oh, his stomach wasn't feeling well, so he asked us to take his place.
Isn't that right?
Y-Yes, That's right! That's why we came here...!
Like hell that's true!
If you aren't legitimate competitors, this Duel is canceled!
-Oh, c'mon...!
I don't mind at all.
It would not be beautiful at all to win without a fight.
I came all this way, so please humor me.
But...
Either way, I am going to be victorious.
As compared to a disqualified win,
it would be far more comical to engage in combat for entertainment's sake.
I would prefer that the both of you come at me together.
You're saying that we're only good for entertainment?
We're the Japanese Champion and the runner up here, don't ya know!
We're gonna make ya regret lookin' down on us!
I will pass onto you some enlightenment, Kaiba...
A fragment of my true strength.
We're going!
Yeah!
I'll attack first! Draw!
I Summon Pinch Hopper in Attack Mode!
Next I activate the Magic Card, Insecticide.
I can destroy one Insect Monster!
Pinch Hopper's Special Effect will be activated.
When this card is sent to the Graveyard,
I can Special Summon one Insect-Type Monster from my hand.
Come!
Insect Queen!
How was that? It's too late to be scared now.
Turn end.
My turn, draw!
I Summon Balloon Lizard in Attack Mode!
Then I activate a Magic Card, Ultra Evolution Pill.
By sacrificin' one Reptile-Type Monster,
this card can Special Summon one Dinosaur-Type Monster from my hand.
Come out, Black Tyranno!
Whaccha think?! Turn end!
Our enemies're those fiends Yugi an' Jounouchi, an' no one else!
Weak nobodies we've never even heard of will be eliminated in a second flat!
It is my turn. I draw.
Wh-What's so funny?
You throwin' in the towel 'cause you know you won't win?
No, victory has already been placed in the palms of my hands.
I activate a Magic Card. Walkuren Ritt.
Na! Expose yourselves before us!
Maidens of Walkuren Ritt!
Guide the souls of the warriors to Valhalla!
Th-The hell is...
Th-The hell was that...?
What just happened...?
This is impossible!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
After Jounouchi, Rebecca has also gotten into the Best Eight.
Looks like Leon-kun also won. That's great!
But if all of them go through to the Best Four...
Then out of the three, two of them will be facing each other.
This gives me mixed feelings...
But before that, they have to win their next Duels!
Especially Jounouchi...
His opponent is the one that defeated both Haga and Ryuzaki in an instant, Sieg Lloyd!
Don't let your guard down!
Next time!
"Jounouchi VS Sieg - A Beautiful Duel"
Duel standby!