Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Fierce Fight! Battle City Begins"
The light in Yugi's room has been on all night.
Those two boys must've been up all night
putting their decks together for today's tournament.
I know! I'll close shop today and watch Yugi's Duels!
And I'll call Anzu-chan out too!
There! I did it!
It's morning already!
I can't believe we spent all night deciding whether to put that Magic Card in or not.
Partner...
Before the contest, I have something I need to tell you.
What?
The Battle City we're about to fight in...
...is also a battlefield to find myself.
Find yourself?
For me, it's not just any tournament.
But I won't be able to win that fight without your help.
No matter what happens...
I will have faith in this deck we put together.
Keep my words in your heart.
I know.
You're not going to ask for details?
I know you'd never fight to get rare cards.
But for an important reason. That's already enough.
Whatever you're fighting for,
I won't ask, and I'll let you tell me yourself.
And I will always believe in you... believe in the deck we made.
Partner!
-Let's go!
Ah! It's useless!
Without Red-Eyes, I can't think of a way to beat that guy!
I want to defeat the enemy myself,
That's why I didn't tell Yugi about his deck.
If I talk with him now, it's still useless.
That's right! At times like this I should get comfort from Shizuka!
She'd say "Do your best, big brother"! Or somethin' like it!
Yes? This is the cute Shizuka-chan's room.
W-Who the hell are you?!
Who?
Oh! That's Jounouchi's voice.
It's me, Honda.
Honda?!
Why are you over there?
You're busy with Battle City's things,
So I'm looking after her in your place.
You jerk!
I don't need your help!
Big brother?
Honda-san was telling me a lot about cards.
He said that he taught you how to play.
That because of his training, you were able to enter Duelist Kingdom's finals.
Brother, you need to do your best!
Hopefully you can be as good as Honda-san.
Anyways, thats how it is.
Do your best to get Red-Eyes back.
See ya.
HONDA!!!
I'll kill you the next time I see you!
Who're all these people?
Yeah. All of them are carrying strange machines on their wrists.
You guys don't know?
What?
Starting today, this street will become a Battle City!
A battlefield for Duel Monsters!
-Battle City?!
If you don't wanna get hurt, norms like you better keep the hell away!
The Duel Disk came with some weird plate.
A section of the Domino City map's drawn on it.
I heard this was the starting point.
Yugi!
Mai-san!
It's finally about to begin, Yugi!
Where's Jounouchi?
He should be here by now.
So he is participating!
So he's also one of the chosen Duelists!
Long time no see! Yugi! Mai!
Insector Haga? Dinosaur Ryuzaki?!
Listen up, you guys!
Ya'll are gonna pay up for what you did on the Duelist Kingdom!
You better remember that!
If you think I'll be as easy as before, you're sorely mistaken!
My Insect Deck has powered up quite a bit since our last encounter...
I figured you guppies'd be out here causin' trouble again!
Kajiki-kun!
What "Insect Army"?! That's a load of fish shit!
Fish shit?!
That's right! My Sea Deck inhabitants'd swallow them in one gulp!
If we're comparin' sizes, my Dinosaur Deck wins over em all!
What "Dinosaur Deck"?! My whale's gonna fly right over em through the sky!
I have something in my deck far superior to the Great Moth...
Whoops! The rest is a secret.
Don't stop spoutin' nonsense now, ya cockroach!
Ah~ These guys really tire you out.
Yugi Mutou and Mai Kujaku, huh?
They do have some pretty good rare cards.
Kay! I'm gonna head east of the city!
I'm gonna head to the ocean!
See ya!
Yugi.
I'm going too.
I'll see you at the finals!
My starting point is here.
Kaiba-kun should broadcast the starting ceremony soon.
How do you Duel at places like this?
My fellow Duelists, welcome to the Battle City!
That's Kaiba's voice!
Where is he?!
Where?!
Where is the voice coming from?
Kaiba-kun!
I will now explain the contest rules.
Those who come here are all chosen by Kaiba Cooperation,
as Level 5 or higher Duelists.
The Duel Disks on your arms are proof of that.
The stage of this tournament is the entire town of Domino City!
No matter where you are in the city...
...if two Duelists come face to face, you may fight!
The whole city will become a stage?
Each Duelist will use a 40 card deck!
The loser must surrender a rare card of the winner's choice!
In this Battle City...
...as you win, your deck will become stronger and stronger!
The Ante Rule...
All the contestants will want to protect their rare card.
I must not lose.
This battle...
...will become a very intense fight.
Only eight contestants
participating in the Battle Royal
will make it to the Finals!
Only eight?
As for the location of the Finals...
Its location is hidden somewhere within the city!
Hidden?
Because I plan to enter this contest along with everyone fairly,
even I don't know where the Finals will be held.
What's going on?!
What do you have to do to know where Finals are?
Before we get started, take a look at this plate.
This plate is a Puzzle Card.
When all the Puzzle Cards from the 48 participating Duelists are gathered, a map of Domino City is revealed.
The Puzzle Cards have a special prismatic coating.
If you stack six of them, a light will shine in a certain spot on the plate.
That spot is the location of the Finals!
And, there's one more rule.
The winner of each Duel will get their opponent's Puzzle Cards!
Only those who collect six Puzzle Cards
can reach the unknown location of the Finals!
The unknown location...?
I will...
-...reach it!
Now, the Battle City will begin!
Duelists!
Scatter across this city and locate your enemies!
Alright! I can't let my guard down!
Jounouchi-kun!
Now then, my first prey will be...
Finally found you!
I knew you would appear in Battle City!
My my...
You think I won't be able to find you by hiding in the city?!
So the loser dog hasn't forgotten how to bark, huh?
Loser dog?!
Don't call me that! You're pissin' me off!
Jounouchi-kun.
Yugi!
Yugi Mutou, huh?! This is perfect!
This bastard stole my Red-Eyes!
He's one of the Ghouls! A member of the dark syndicate that rules the Gaming Underworld...!
Yugi! Don't try and fight this bastard!
Oh? So you want to fight me once more?
Even though you already lost the Red-Eyes from your deck?
But I'm afraid without rare cards, I no longer have any interest in you!
Yugi Mutou! You'll be my opponent!
Wait! This is my problem!
No. I accept this Duel.
Yugi!
Duelists put their life into their cards! Those who try to steal them...
I won't forgive them!
Garbage like you is a disgrace to the city!
I'll clean you up right now!
You really think you can win?
Against my unstoppable Exodia Deck?
Yugi. They'll do anything to win.
They've gathered hundreds of powerful cards and bootlegged rare ones to make their decks!
In his deck-
Don't say another word about it, Jounouchi-kun!
But...!
No matter what cheap tricks the opponent uses...
...I have no right to know the enemy's strategy before a game!
Rare Hunter!
Use your strongest tactics on me.
My deck will crush you into oblivion!
Yugi...
I admit I like guys with high fighting spirit and confidence like you...
But that's all but useless in a Duel!!
I'm going to teach you...
...that your worthless talk of justice means absolutely nothing in front of us Ghouls!
All that awaits you is the despair of losing your rare card and falling into a pit of darkness!
Well now, is that so?
Sheesh, where is it?
They said the stage was in the city, but where do I go?
Solid Vision System!
Fire!
Big brother, the first Duel has begun.
It's Yugi!
It's Yugi's Duel!
Starting already, Yugi? Let's take a look.
Okay Search Team, keep all eyes out for those God Cards!
A Duelist holding two of the God Cards has to be hidden somewhere around the city.
Thoroughly check the data being received by the Duel Disks!
-Duel!!
My attack first.
Draw your hand!
I already have two of the Exodia Sealed Parts in my hand.
All I need is three more pieces and I win!
Yugi! Please notice his strategy!
Let's go! I set 2 cards on the field.
I Summon Magnet Warrior Beta in Attack Mode!
My turn is over.
What is that?
A Monster came out of the card!
That's a Duel Monster.
Starting from today, us Duelists will take over this whole street.
Eh?!
My turn. Draw.
Angel's Charity!
I Draw 3 cards from my deck.
Then discard 2 cards.
Now it's 3.
A card that allows him to draw from his deck.
He must be planning something.
If it's like that,
Trap Card Open!
Light of Intervention!
As long as this Trap Card is in play,
All Monsters can't be Summoned face down.
Useless effort!
Stone Statue of the Aztecs in Defense Mode.
A Defense Monster.
If I don't destroy the defending Monster, than I can't damage the opponent's Life Points.
My turn!
I sacrifice Magnet Warrior Beta,
to Summon Baphomet!
Next, I use Baphomet's Effect to call Gazelle to the field.
Also, set card open! I use the Fusion card to fuse the two monsters together.
I Summon the Fusion Monster, Winged Illusion Beast Chimera!
According to Battle City rules,
Fusion Summoned monsters have to wait until next turn to attack.
That's why, next turn my Chimera will destroy your monsters.
That won't work Yugi! Don't bother with his monsters anymore!
He probably already has Exodia parts in his hand!
All he sees is the defending monster.
While he does that,
I'm about to collect all the Exodia parts.
Though you don't notice it, you're walking towards failure.
Next, I set one card.
Turn over.
My turn. Draw!
Magic Card, Angel's Charity!
I draw 3 cards and discard 2 cards.
Changing cards again?
In my deck, I have 3 sets of Exodia part cards.
Now there's 4 cards.
All I'm missing is Left Arm of the Sealed One.
What the? What is he planning?
This man uses a very weird style.
Seto-sama!
The player's deck isn't recorded.
What?!
God Cards?
No, I'm afraid they are fake cards.
What?!
This man is from Ghouls?
Brother!
Wait.
This is interesting. Let them continue playing.
So it's like that.
That kind of deck.
Slowly think it over.
You don't have much time anyways.
I'm wearing special contact lens that lets me see through cards,
which are dosed with a special ink.
Through this lens, I can see what card it is!
Next turn, the first card I'm going to draw...
Is Left Arm of the Sealed One!
Then Exodia will be complete!
You have no chance of victory anymore!
In front of Exodia, all attacks are useless.
Yugi.
Next, I Summon Gear Golem the Moving Fortress in Defense Mode.
Like this, I end my turn.
Another Defense Monster.
Why? I can't sense his attack strength.
He's using strong defense the whole time.
Creating a defense line to defend against my monsters.
He's not relying on monster's attacks to lower my Life Points.
What's wrong? It's your turn.
Then how is he going to defeat me?
An attack that has no way out, an attack on me....
Yugi!
Yugi! There's no need to fight him anymore!
You're fighting a rigged Duel set up by the Ghouls!
That's where you're wrong, Jounouchi-kun.
I will continue fighting fairly until the end.
To defeat him!
A True Duelist,
No matter what the opponent is like, must not underestimate.
Yugi...
Jounouchi-kun.
For you, I will win.
That time, you didn't care about your life to protect my cards.
Right now, I will repay you.
Continuously changing hand cards.
Has copy cards.
I found out
It's this type.
I already saw through what your plans!
I won't let you Summon Exodia!
What?! How did he see through my plan?!
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun. Your words have made me realize his battle style.
Though you have seen through my style, you no longer have any time.
The sealed cards in my hand are almost complete.
Right now, what else can you do?
Interesting.
Can people like you really control Exodia?
I'll wait and see.
Next Time
Yugi struggles in order to stop the Rare Hunter from Summoning Exodia.
But the Rare Hunter has almost completed all Exodia Pieces,
While stopping Yugi's attack one after another.
Yugi must win before he collects all Exodia parts.
Or else Yugi will lose!
Is there no way to turn the situation?
Next Time: "Turn the Tables: Chain Destruction"
Duel Standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...