Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Here goes!
Wyvern Warrior!
Attack Kuriboh!
Reverse card, open!
A Trap Card!
Kuriboh is shielded by the Hexagram Curse!
And so what of it?
It doesn't matter whether I play a Monster or not...
All I need to do is drain your Life Points!
So why don't you...
...eat this once again?!
FIREBALL!!
""Take It Back! The Red-Eyes Black Dragon
of Friendship"
NO!!
YUGI!!
My deck's been powered up way too much with these banned cards!
I don't even need Monsters!
Jounouchi-kun...
D-Don't you feel pain in your Duelist's heart...?
"Duelist's heart?"
I don't even know what you're talkin' about!
The pain I'm feeling right now isn't from the burning sensation of your cards...
It's the pain of my sadness seeing you lose your heart as a Duelist!
It's pointless no matter how much you scream.
I've implanted Jounouchi with the memory of my hatred.
He's become my loyal puppet, living only for the sole purpose of killing you!
Yugi...
I will crush you!
Jounouchi-kun...
It's your turn!
What do I have to do...?
What do I have to do get your heart back, Jounouchi-kun?!
Jounouchi! Wake up already!
Other... me...!
Partner?!
This is the first time I've felt you hurt this much...
Yeah...
Maybe I can cut that pain in half.
So I have a favor to ask.
Let me fight Jounouchi-kun!
Partner!
A long time ago, when I was afraid of everyone, Jounouchi-kun called me his best friend.
And Jounouchi-kun risked his own life to save me from that fire!
Jounouchi-kun's always helping me...!
So this time it's my turn...!
But... this Duel is too difficult!
I know that.
But you once told me this...
That it wasn't the power of the Millennium Puzzle that allowed me to make friends...
That I made it come true on my own.
Yes...
I want to prove that in this battle.
If I can get back Jounouchi-kun's heart...
Then I really will make a wish come true on my own...
I'll then feel... I can say that proudly...
Partner...
All right...
But if I ever feel your life is in serious danger,
I'll be taking over that very instant!
Jounouchi-kun, I'll be your opponent now!
Wh-What?!
That's Yugi's vessel!
He's going to fight?!
Sh-Shit...!
A vessel's nothing more than a mere vessel and nothing more!
Just destroying the vessel....
Unless I beat the hateful Pharaoh face-to-face, I won't be able to satisfy my grudge!!
Never mind. Forget it...
If I beat his vessel to a bloody pulp, there's no way he'll be able to just sit and watch.
Kill Yugi!
Crush him! Crush him!
And drag the Pharaoh out once more!
It's my turn!
Partner! There's only one card
sleeping in this deck that holds the ability to awaken Jounouchi-kun's heart!
Right.
I better draw that card!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Dammit...!
Honda-san...!
Got no choice...?
Shizuka-chan, stay right here!
Okay!
If you wanna get outta this in one piece, you better do as we tell ya!
Keh! Aren't you guys cocky?!
I can beat these guys, but Shizuka-chan...
Damn you!
Let me go!
No!
Get your filthy hands off Shizuka-chan!
Honda-san?!
Shizuka-chan...!
That's...
What're you people doing huddling together like this during the day?
Who the hell're you?!
You're Ryuji Otogi!
Honda-kun! Grab the girl!
Let's get outta here, Shizuka-chan!
Okay!
Just who are those guys?
We'll talk later!
Right!
Shit...
Don't let em get away!
After them!!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon...
Partner, Jounouchi-kun's Duelist's heart dwells within that card!
Yup!
The card Jounouchi-kun fought with for so long!
Everything depends on it!
Crush him!
Crush him!!
Crush them both, Jounouchi!!
I'm gonna fight!
To get your heart back!
To prove our friendship!
Please, red-eyed dragon!
Speak to Jounouchi-kun with your soul and awaken his Duelist's heart!
Come on already!
What are you waiting for, Yugi?!
It's your turn, ya know!
I have two Monsters on the field... Kuriboh and the 2600 Defense Power Big Shield Gardna.
If I sacrifice these two Monsters, I can Summon the Red-Eyes Black Dragon.
Partner!
We only have 1300 Life Points left.
Proceed with caution.
Right!
This is a Death Duel where the player whose Life hits 0 loses their life!
If I don't find a way to settle this and save both my partner and Jounouchi-kun in time...
Hey! Hurry the hell up, Yugi!
Five cards in my hand...
There's something I want to make sure of
before I play the Red-Eyes this turn.
But... if it doesn't work, I'll...
Now, Yugi...
How will you get out of this situation?
It's about time you show me what you've got planned!
Yugi's expression changed this turn...
Did he switch places with our usual Yugi?
In order to get Jounouchi's heart back?
Please, both Yugis!
Get Jounouchi back to normal!
You've gotta remember, Jounouchi!
About the "circle of friendship" we made together!
Look! This is the proof of our friendship!
What's... this?
The magic marker ink will eventually fade away...
...but our hearts and our friendship will never disappear!
The bond of friendship we swore then hasn't disappeared!
That's right!
Anzu's right!
The vow of friendship we swore then should still be in our hearts.
I'm certain it's in Jounouchi-kun's as well!
I... believe in Jounouchi-kun!
Other me, I'd like for you to not say anything and just watch what I'm about to do!
That card...!
Here I go!
Exchange!
"Exchange"?
A card that allows you to exchange cards...
Yugi, what the hell are you playing at?
I take it your hand must really suck.
Well, if I must...
Show me your hand.
I bet you only got junky cards...
Red-Eyes...?
C'mon Jounouchi-kun...
Take whichever card you want out of these five cards.
Partner...
I knew the vessel was inexperienced as a Duelist,
but I never imagined he was this bad!
Giving us his rare card just like that...
Jounouchi! The Red-Eyes!
Take the Red-Eyes!
Damn right I will...
I've got nothing to be afraid of if I have this card!
I'll take my Red-Eyes back!
It really didn't work...!
Jounouchi-kun!
If he takes the Red-Eyes, we won't be able to get Jounouchi-kun's heart back...
Wh-Why can't I take it?!
Why?!
What's wrong?
Take that Red-Eyes Black Dragon, Jounouchi!
D-Damn it all!
Jounouchi-kun!
What?
You didn't take the Red-Eyes?!
Why?!
I-I don't need Monster Cards to beat you...
My player-damaging banned Magic Cards are more than enough to crush Yugi!
I get to draw a card from your hand now too, Jounouchi-kun.
Jounouchi-kun!
I know for sure now.
That you haven't lost your true Duelist's heart.
You swore to battle me in Battle City with your pride on the line.
And you swore not to use the Red-Eyes Black Dragon until that time came.
Shut up.
So...
So that's why you couldn't take the Red-Eyes!
I told you to shut up!
What a load of crap!
I confirmed it!
With this Red-Eyes card, I can call back your heart as a Duelist!
Fine by me, Yugi.
But before you try that shit against me...
I'll bring your Life Points to 0 and sink you into the sea!
My turn's not over yet.
Jounouchi-kun...
We'll always be friends.
I'm gonna use your card now!
I sacrifice two Monsters!
To Summon the Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Red-Eyes... Black... Dragon...!
Why?
Why didn't you choose the Red-Eyes like I told you?!
Is he breaking free of my spell over him?
Or was Yugi's pathetic blabbering stronger than my ability?
Lord Malik.
It seems that Yugi's friends have gotten away.
Don't come and report that to me personally!
You think I'll forgive your failure?!
Hurry the hell up and bring them to me!
Red-Eyes...
Sharing a rareness almost equivalent to my Blue-Eyes... Red-Eyes Black Dragon...
That used to be Jounouchi's rarest card...
Yugi's trying to use that Red-Eyes to get Jounouchi's heart back!
But will it work?
Jounouchi-kun, you should see the color of sadness died in the Red-Eyes' eyes...
Red-Eyes wants to get your Duelist's heart back!
To do that...
To do that, we'll fight!
Red-Eyes, attack!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Jounouchi-kun! I have faith in you!
Jounouchi-kun!
What the hell are you doing, Jounouchi!?
That attack was nothin'!
It's my turn again...
And I'm gonna use my illegal Magic Cards to kill you!
You're finished, Yugi!
That's right!
Very good!
Crush him!
Crush him!!
CRUSH HIM!!!
Partner, it's getting too dangerous!
I'll take it from here!
No...
Let me fight 'till the end!
Partner!
When I solved the Millennium Puzzle, I wished for a friend.
And when I met you within my heart, I learned to have courage.
And I made important friends too!
But... somewhere inside me...
...I think that if I hadn't met you, I would've stayed a coward.
I still feel that way sometimes...
That's why I have to get Jounouchi-kun's heart back in this Duel with my own strength!
Partner...
So I ask you to just watch, my other self.
But this is an incredibly dangerous fight,
and you could die if you make the slightest mistake!
I know that...
But I'll trust Jounouchi-kun until the end!
I get it...
If you insist on going that far, I'll back off.
But...
Don't let yourself die, other me!
Mhm-hm!
Thank you, other me!
If I keep the Millennium Puzzle away from me,
my other self can't switch minds with me.
Yugi! How long are you gonna stand there for?
You've always protected me up until now, other me...
But if I don't get stronger, you'll never be able to leave me heart!
You'll have plenty of time to think when you're dead!
From here on, this is my battle!
Here goes! My turn!
I don't need Monsters!
Fireball!!
Directly attack the player!!
Yugi!!
They ain't here, either!
Shit! Those guys sure are fast at running away!
Find em!
Search the entire vicinity!
Looks like we dodged them for now...
We should hide out here for a bit longer.
But really, you sure saved my butt, Otogi!
Huh?
By the way, I thought you were in America contracting Dungeon Dice Monsters?
Yeah!
I just returned to Japan briefly.
I heard about the Battle City tournament being held here.
I figured I'd meet Yugi-kun in all this commotion.
So what's going on here, anyway?
Come here...
That girl's Jounouchi's sister named Shizuka-chan.
Wha?
You're kidding!
I didn't know Jounouchi-kun had a sister that cute!
Don't let Shizuka-chan here you say that...
Right...
So who were those guys back there?
Why were they after you guys?
They're with a gang of thugs called the Ghouls.
They're a filthy group that steals cards from Duelists.
Right, they're also known as the Rare Hunters.
I've heard countless rumors about these guys.
I'm betting they're after Yugi.
But I have no clue why they want us...
We don't even have any rare cards.
So my big brother's in danger as well?
Well...
More than likely.
If they're after us, then Anzu and Jounouchi...
Oh come on! What's wrong?!
It's way too early to be on your knees!
Please! Just stop this already, Jounouchi!
Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun, too!
Don't just stand there! Hurry and stop them!
But if we try, Anzu...!
If he activates that switch,
the container above Anzu...!
These scum...!
I just... can't bring your Life Points to 0 after all...
So... I'd like for you to just hear my wish...
Keep quiet!
My turn ain't over yet!
I Summon Rocket Warrior!
Any Monster this guy attacks...
...has their Attack reduced to 0 for the duration of the turn!
Jounouchi-kun...
I...
I then play the Magic Card Attrition!
I want you to take this precious puzzle of mine...
Here I go!
This is my Battle Phase!
Rocket Warrior!
Transform into your Invincible Mode!
Attack the Red-Eyes!!
I don't want the Millennium Puzzle to sink into the sea...
And the Permanent Magic, Attrition!
I activate it's Effect!
It receives damage equal to the difference of the attacking Monster's Attack Points!
How 'bout it?
So when the time comes, you...
I-It hurts...!
Wh-What the hell is this pain?!
Jounouchi-kun...
I want you... to keep my Millennium Puzzle.
In my place...
"Preview"
Yugi gives Jounouchi the Millennium Puzzle to keep it from sinking into the sea!
That still isn't enough to stop him!
But Malik's control over him seems to be weakening!
Jounouchi has started to disobey his orders.
But there's hardly any time left before the time bomb goes off!
If they don't finish their Duel in time,
they'll both fall into the ocean!
Next time!
"The Countdown to Despair"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...