Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Varon from the Three Musketeers of Doma...
His Dueling strategy is far from incomplete!
His attacks strike me one after the other...
My body aches... and my insides are tearing apart...!
But I'm not so weak that I'd be finished with a few shots like that!
If I want to get Mai back and defeat Doma at their own game...
I can't allow myself to be defeated by the likes of you!
"Reverbarating Soul"
Here we go...
I got it, Grandpa!
Oh, you connected!
Man, I'm so at my limit!
I'm gonna go look for Jounouchi!
Just calm down, Honda!
She's right!
If you randomly search the streets, you'll only waste time and energy!
But it's not just that Varon punk who's after him!
Mai's also out there looking for Jounouchi!
Damn them!
Yeah... If he ends up fighting with Mai-san again...
Right... Jounouchi-kun can't fight Mai.
He knows what will happen if he clashes with Mai again.
It won't be settled so easily.
True...
I found it! Jounouchi's location!
Really?
Um, let's see... he should be downtown!
You guys go to find the safest spot you can.
I'm going to search for Jounouchi-kun.
You can't do that!
I'm going with you!
That's right! Take me along, too!
Anzu... Honda-kun...
All right. Let's go together!
Otogi, sorry... but I need you to stay with Rebecca and Professor Hopkins.
Wha...?
No way! Take me along wit-
Grandpa...
This is as far as we go.
We can't afford to slow them down.
Okay...
Rebecca... Can I ask you to have faith in me?
Other Yugi...
I will save my Partner, no matter what I have to do!
Okay...
You better come back here safe and sound.
I'll be responsible for their safety!
Right! Please do!
Let's get a move on, Yugi!
Be carefull, you guys!
We will!
Don't worry.
He is no longer lost in the darkness.
Grandpa...
Just believe in him... in the other Yugi-kun.
I will...
Everything is now up to you...
Save this world, Nameless Pharaoh.
Save my Darling, Other Yugi.
I'm staking everything on this card!
That card...?
I...
I Summon Rifleman of Landstar in Attack Mode!
And then I activate the Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead!
And the Monster I'm bringing back...
Rocket Warrior!
Then...
Claw of Hermos!
I thought so!
You finally got out here, did you?
That's it! Come at me with all you've got!
And the moment I beat you...
I will achieve the ultimate victory!
It... should be somewhere around here!
Jounouchi! You better be safe!
This...!
Jounouchi-kun...!
Using the effect of the Claw of Hermos, I fuse him with Rocket Warrior!
Rocket Hermos Cannon!
I equip it to Rifleman of Landstar!
It combined?!
Something outside of my Armor Monsters is capable of that?!
Don't go wetting yourself just yet!
Go, Rifleman of Landstar!
Attack, Rocket Hermos Cannon!
Destroy all the enemies in front of you!
Emergency!
Bracing for impact of enemy attack!
Changing to defensive armor for damage absorption!
Did I get him?!
Booyah! I beat him!
I won this!
Huh? Why didn't the boundary disappear?
You're...!
I sure felt that one!
I'd expect no less from the power of Hermos.
But why? I attacked you directly!
Yeah, you certainly nailed me good there.
But I can't have you forgetting...
...about Active Guard's Special Ability!
That's because I've got this.
This Active Guard holds an Effect that makes all battle damage received on my end reduced to zero.
That's right...
What a shame it is, Jounouchi!
Turn end...
But I broke that impregnable armor of yours!
You sure did, but in exchange, I got my hands on something nice...
Something "nice"?
What the heck's that?
It's on the Rocket Hermos Cannon!
Data Brain ain't your average Equipment Magic!
Whenever the Monster this card
was equipped to is destroyed by the opponent's magic effects,
this card shows its true ambitious effect!
What'd you say?!
Yes sir! It copies that same magic effect so I can use it for myself!
My turn!
Draw!!
Using that Special Effect on my Standby Phase,
I Summon Pyshic Armor Head from the Cemetery in Attack Position!!
Then I Summon my Burning Knuckle Armor in Attack Position!!
Thanks to Burning Knuckle Armor, for every Armor Monster on the field, it receives a 200 Attack Power boost!!
Afterwards...!
This here's a pretty sweet lookin' weapon.
I'm gonna give it a test drive!
Here goes!!
Blow 'em all to hell!
Rocket Hermos Cannon!!
Just now...
That's what a weapon created from the Legendary Dragons is all about!
'Tis a pity I can only use it for one turn.
How you feelin', Jounouchi?
Being shot at with your own weapon and all...
Think you'll be able to get back on your feet before your Life Points drop to zero?
You're pretty tough.
Allow me to end my turn!
But I doubt you'll be able to fight for much longer with the state your body's in.
What'd you say to giving up and making it easier on yourself?
Who...?
I said this from the start, didn't I?
That I ain't runnin'...!
No matter how bad the situation may be...
I never give up until the very end!
This guy...
He's not afraid of my attacks...
I've never met anyone who could put up a front like him...!
So this... is the man Mai's been chasing after for the "truth"?!
I'm still rarin' and ready to go!
My turn!!
Draw!!
This is where we start the battle for real!
Varon!!
Okay. Let's go, Mokuba.
Right, Brother!
Now hold it right there!
What on earth are you people doing?!
We just bought this car!
This should cover it.
W-Wai...!
"Bought"...?
Just you wait, you Doma punks.
Critias was resonating just earlier...
Did something happen to the deadbeat?
But I have no time to worry about others right now.
Wait right there, Dartz.
I'm going to shove that pathetic plan of yours right down your throat!
If I use it... one more time... I can do this!
I place one reverse card face-down!
Turn end!
I guess you couldn't even manage to Summon a single Monster!
This useless resistance of yours is wasted effort!
Be it a Trap, be it a Magic...
I'll destroy it with all my strength!!
My turn!
Draw!!
I Summon Black Hole Shield Armor in Attack Position!!
This increases Burning Knuckle's Attack Power even further!
Opposing player's field: Zero Monsters.
One reverse card.
Probability of being Trap Card: 50%.
Even if it is a trap, I only know how to attack!
I attack with Burning Knuckle!
Direct Attack Jounouchi!!
This... ends it!!
What?!
I activated a Trap Card!
The Trap Card, Aura Armor!
Shit...! That's...!
Level Four Monster.
Attack Power: 400.
I decided to fight the same way you do!
Aura Armor activates when I take a Direct Attack while I have 2000 Life Points or less.
By halving my Life Points, I negate that damage...
...and I get to Special Summon a "Monster"!
And that's what this here is!
It can attach itself to the player just like my Armor Monsters?!
It's different than your Armor Monsters.
Its Attack and Defense Points are equal to the player's Life Points.
In brazen terms, if I fall, I lose!
Simple enough, right?
Heh, so I see.
Basically, whoever remains standing wins.
That what you meant?
I like it!
I set a reverse card!
Turn end!
My Timaeus responded to Hermos.
Did something happen to Jounouchi-kun?
Please be safe, Jounouchi-kun!
My turn!
Draw!
Sweet!
Magic Card, activate!
Roll of Fate!
By the effects of Roll of Fate,
I draw cards equal to the result of the die roll!
I then discard the same number of cards from the top of my deck!
Four!
What did he get...?
Let's do this! I activate a Ritual Magic Card!
Red-Eyes Transmigration!
I have to sacrifice Red-Eyes Black Dragon along with a Warrior-Type Monster from my hand or on the field!
You got a Ritual Magic?!
I use this Red-Eyes...
...along with the Aura Armor attached to me... Or in otherwords, I sacrifice myself!
Come forth!
Lord of the Red!
What!?
Here goes! I attack Psychic Armor Head!
And this... decides the match!
Black Hole Shield!!
Lord of the Red's attack...!
Its Special Ability activates!!
By sacrificing Black Hole Shield, all damage done to the player is reduced to zero!!
I thought I had that thing beat!
Barely made it out in tact...!
I'm shaking...?
Me...?!
Am I actually afraid of the bastard?!
No, that's not it...
It's been so long since I've felt like this...!
I've never felt such a passionate desire to grind someone into the ground!
Katsuya Jounouchi!!
This is the best! My fight with you!!
Same here! I'm getting pumped up!
This is a real Duel!!
It's too bad I have to fight you under these circumstances!
Mai!
Don't go acting on your own, Varon!
I'm Jounouchi's opponent!
Mai!
Switch with me!
I have to fight Jounouchi!
Move along, Mai!
Wha-
There's no way in hell I'd switch places with someone when I'm enjoying this Duel so much!
Even if it's you, Mai!
Varon!
I finally understand...
Why you're so bent on pursuing Jounouchi...
I finally began to understand
while Dueling him.
He holds something we don't.
You know what it is, right?
To face one another in a Duel...
...with a genuine straight-forward passion.
We don't have that ability, do we...?
Varon...
Now! Let's get on with it, Jounouchi!!
I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
My turn! Draw!!
Magic Card! Resurrection of the Dead!
I'm going to resurrect...
Buster Pyle!!
If this attack makes it through, I win!!
Whoa there! Allow me!
Reverse card, open!
Scapegoat!
You really think your little sheep can block my fists?!
I didn't play my Scapegoats so I can hide behind them!
Lord of the Red's Special Ability!
If two Magics are used in the same turn...
...after the second Magic is activated, I can destroy all Monsters on the field!
"Second"...? You didn't...!
Yup! Your Magic Card, Resurrection of the Dead, as well!
What?!
No you don't!
Buster Pyle!!
I never expected my invincible Armor to be shattered...!
But there's still more!
I still have more of my Life Points left!
Turn end!
Bring it, Jounouchi!!
Sure!!
My turn! Draw!
My attack!
Here I go, Varon!
Direct Attack!!
Trap Card!!
Activate!!
Extinction Fist!!
This card automatically ends a Ritual Monster's Battle Phase!
But before that, I return the assault!
Extinction Fist!!
Lord of the... Red...!
Varon and Jounouchi...
Whichever one of them wins... it'll be decided with just one more strike.
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Admist a painful and emotional battle, Jounouchi and Varon have come to understand one another.
But Mai-san's the only one they're seeing now!
But both their health and Life Points are at their limits!
More than likely, this next attack will decide the match!
And then Varon brings out his Full Armor once again!
Pitting their last bit of strength into their fists,
which one of them will remain standing in the end?
And then, what will Mai-san do...?
Next time!
"The End of a Painful Battle"
Duel standby!