Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Bakura turned out to be the one who got my stolen God Cards back.
But he said that an "Ultimate Dark Game" existed in my Lost Memory World.
Bakura, I may not know what you're up to...
But I accept your challenge!
Now we're finally here in Egypt.
It's finally time to open the door to my Memory World.
"The Door of Memory Opens"
We finally got here! Egypt sure is really far!
So, what are we going to do now?
Sorry, just hold on for a second.
Hey Anzu, you can buy souvenirs later.
Let me see...
Here is it! I'll take this.
Oh man, we're not here for sightseeing!
Sorry, sorry!
Yugi! Everyone!
Ishizu-san! Malik!
Have you all been well?
Yes we are. You guys look as energetic as always.
Yeah! We came all the way to Egypt with tons of energy!
We've been waiting for you.
Yugi...
No, my Nameless Pharaoh.
We will guide you to where the stone palette resides.
Thanks. And sorry for the trouble.
They're huge!
So these are real pyramids, huh?
Look at that! It's the Sphinx!
Amazing! Ah, it really is missing its nose!
The stone tablet that unlocks the door to my memories lies inside here.
We'll stop here.
When the three cards are placed on the Memory Tablet...
...the door to your lost memories opens.
Nameless Pharaoh, from this point onwards, you'll choose your own path.
Yeah, we'll move on now.
Sister, with this, our mission is accomplished.
The fate that our family of Tomb Guardians have borne for three thousand years.
Yes.
Every soul has its own place to return to.
The Pharaoh has now started on this road.
It's finally time for the door to the Nameless Pharaoh's memories to open.
It's here.
The Memory Tablet...
Yugi...
I called him "Yugi" like always...
Even though he's in Yugi's body,
he's a completely different person.
But I don't even know his real name.
Yugi, please take this.
This is...
A Cartouche pendant.
The ancient Pharaohs always had their names written on them, I hear!
But there's no name engraved on this one...
If you regain your memories and remember your real name...
I hope you'll carve it on there.
So you'll never forget it again.
The portion on that palette with the Pharaoh's name got worn off, right?
At the very least, I want to know your real name.
That's is a good idea!
Once you engrave your name on it, you'll never forget your name again!
That's right.
Thank you, Anzu.
I'll treasure it always!
Okay!
I'm back here again... with the three God Cards in my hand.
What will happen from here on out?
The answer is here!
Here I go.
The start line has come.
The clone of myself I left within the Millennium Puzzle
has given the gong announcing the start of the game.
Th-This is...
This is... the door to my memories!
At long last, the time has come!
What the heck was that just now?
There was a sudden burst of bright light.
Yugi!
Yugi?
Hey... You alright?
He's gone...
What do you mean he's gone?
My other self...
He's not in the Puzzle or in my heart anymore...
Other... Me...
The Pharaoh's soul has left the host.
The Pharaoh has embarked on a journey to the Memory World.
Who's there?!
You...! Shadi!
Ah! You were the one back at Battle Ship..!
You saved me and Otogi!
What are you doing here?
Wait.
He's also a Millennium Item wielder.
Pharaoh! Pharaoh!
What's going on..?
Pharaoh, the people are waiting for your answer.
Please give them a response.
I'm... the Pharaoh....?
Pharaoh! Pharaoh!
Now, my Pharaoh.
Everyone at the ceremony are also waiting for the new Pharaoh to arrive.
Pharaoh, here, to the throne.
This is my Memory World?
Everyone, raise your heads!
The new Pharaoh has arrived!
Kaiba...!
Ishizu!
Grandfather!
"Ji-Jii"?
Sir Shimon, is the Pharaoh perhaps a bit fatigued?
N-No, I'm fine. Please continue.
Yes.
Everyone, continue the music and dance!
Show the vitality and strength of the Pharaoh!
What's happening? What's going on?
Those are... the Millennium Items...! They're...
What are you talking about?
Is that not because they are the six High Priests chosen by the Millennium Items?
The six High Priests chosen by the Millennium Items?
Come! Get moving!
The guy's passed out again.
What bad luck. There's a big feast being held in the main hall.
You said it.
Of all the days for a graverobbing, he decided to pick the day the new Pharaoh got crowned.
What's that?!
Dammit.
To think I'd start off looking like this after finally getting the game started...!
But there's no doubting it.
This is in his Memory World.
I see. This must mean you've came here for me.
That's right, huh?
I'm slowly recalling all the small details from three thousand years ago.
But he's the Pharaoh...
and I'm only a lowly bandit.
The difference in our rankings is too big.
He's looks a lot like Grandpa Sugoroku.
Ishizu...
Could the reason Grandpa Sugoroku found the Millennium Puzzle be because...
And the fact Ishizu comes from a family of Tomb Guardians...
Maybe they weren't just mere coincidences?
And...
There's no doubt about it.
He's the priest that is also carved on the Memory Tablet.
Mahado!
Insolent scum!
Catch him!
To aim for the Pharaoh's life...
What a terrible act to commit!
However, we are amidst celebration.
To the dungeons with him!
No, wait.
Isn't this a good chance for us to show our powers to the new Pharaoh?
Wouldn't you agree,
Sir Akhenaden? Sir Shimon?
I see! That is a good idea!
We shall punish this man in the presence of the Pharaoh.
Yes!
We shall hereby start the Repentance Ceremony for this man!
Repentance Ceremony?
Our new Pharaoh.
Egypt has now become a big country.
But along with that comes bad people who are jealous of our success.
But rest assured, Pharaoh.
As long as us six High Priests are around, nobody will lay even a finger upon you.
Now your crime will be judged by the seven Millennium Items!
They're using the Millennium Items to judge people?!
High Priest Shada!
Using the power of the Millennium Anhk, I look into this man's heart!
I see the shadow of an evil abrasion residing in this man's heart.
To reveal the true form of that abrasion...
I, High Priest Akhenaden,
...will use the power of the Millennium Eye to expose it!
What is that?!
Pharaoh, I believe this is your first time seeing the extraction of Ka from a criminal.
Ka comes about from the anger and hatred residing in people's hearts.
Ka?
That's right.
In order to become stronger...
...these evil Ka make these people commit crimes to increase their anger and hatred.
Watch carefully!
The priests chosen by the power of one thousand years
have the power to exorcise these Ka and seal them within stone slabs!
Stone slabs...?!
Priest Seto!
Use the power of your Millennium Rod to seal the Ka within the stone!
A Ka of this low level
isn't even an amusement.
Evil Ka, dark spirit of chaos!
Be gone and enter the holy stone!
This... is the true power of the Millennium Items..!
Shadi.
Host for the soul of the Pharaoh...
The soul of the Pharaoh no longer exists within your body.
The Pharaoh has embarked on a journey into his Memory World.
Memory World?
The Memory World is a place the Pharaoh
created based on his experiences three thousand years ago.
Has he forgotten about us?
No.
He should still have his present memories even when he's in his Memory World.
But the Pharaoh is experiencing his fate once again.
Then, the mystery as to why the Pharaoh's soul was sealed
in the Millennium Puzzle will be revealed.
That means...
The soul of the other Yugi will be sealed in the Millennium Puzzle?
Hey, won't that mean that the other Yugi will never come back again?
You...!
My physical body has already been destroyed.
We... are talking to a ghost..?!
My physical body was killed
by Bakura's hands.
Bakura?!
By Bakura-kun?
The spirit residing in Bakura's body is that of a very evil person.
Soon, the nameless Pharaoh will be in danger.
These Millennium Items told me...
That in order to know the truth,
the nameless Pharaoh and Dark Bakura have traveled to the Memory World.
Together with the Dark Bakura-kun?
Over there, the two of them will start the Ultimate Dark Game.
What did you say?
I didn't hear anything about that!
Yugi!
I didn't know that...
Why... Why would he not tell us such an important thing...?
The other Yugi probably didn't want us to be worried.
Shadi!
Hey! Can't I be of any help to the other me?
You must know something, or else you wouldn't be here.
I beg you, please tell me.
I want to help the other me!
There is indeed a way to send you all to the Pharaoh's Memory World.
That is...
And that is?
The labyrinth of the Pharaoh's heart that exists within the Millennium Puzzle.
We must find the Door of Truth.
The maze of his heart...
The Pharaoh's Memory World lies behind that door.
How's this?!
Now I look a bit kingly myself, right?!
I'm about to bring you to Yugi.
I'm sure he'll be overjoyed!
Now then, let's give our greetings to the Pharaoh, you scoundrels!
Well done, Seto.
Please. I'm sure it was dull for the Pharaoh...
Shall we draw and quarter this prisoner for his amusement?
The evil abrasion in that man's spirit has been completely removed.
Part of our duties as priests is to show mercy to sinful criminals.
Yes.
Take him away!
Mahado, supervision of security within this city is the duty of your guards, is it not?
And the royal tombs are being defiled too often these days...
You should take responsibility for not doing the job well.
You have my deepest apologies.
However, for the last few days
the auguries I receive from the Millennium Ring have been extremely erratic...
The evil intents of the criminals are unfathomable.
My Pharaoh.
In order to protect this city,
I beseech you to allow an increase in the number of guards.
E-Er, yes. I leave it to you...
Take the newly sealed Ka Tablet to the Shrine of Wedju!
I don't understand a single thing.
Is this really the Ultimate Dark Game that Bakura was talking about?
Please do not worry, great Pharaoh!
I, Shimon, have taken personal responsibility
to design the tomb where you will have your eternal rest!
M-My tomb...?!
I've placed numerous traps in the tomb and no bandits will be able to break in.
After your death, Pharaoh, I guarantee you will rest in peace!
I-I see...
Now Everyone, please continue the celebrations!
Please hold on!
What's wrong, Isis?
My Millennium Tauk foretells a disturbing future.
What?
A disturbing future?
An evil shadow approaches this palace...
Someone with incredible powers of Heka!
Now then, Yugi...
Let's get this started...
the Ultimate Dark Game!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
The other Yugi has finally arrived in his Lost Memory World.
We were told that he needs to experience the fate he went through three thousand years ago.
But the Dark Personality Bakura-kun is there with him as well.
We didn't know about that!
A duel with Bakura-kun in the Memory World begins.
Please wait for us!
We'll rush to your side!
Next time!
"Enter the Thief King, Bakura!"
Please look forward to it!