A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
You have no cards left in your hand.
Therefore, you lose.
Mind Card!!
Your mind has now been sealed within this card.
Pegasus! I'll defeat you with my own hands!
The final tournament shall begin!
In this very Duel Ring!
Only one of the four remaining Duelists shall earn the right
to challenge me for eternal fame and glory!
Yugi boy... Even if you wield the Millennium Puzzle...
It is all but ineffective before my Millennium Eye.
The Night Before the Finals!
Pegasus' Secrets
Woo-hoo! Delicious!!
The best I've ever had!
Please enjoy yourselves and prepare for the tournament tomorrow.
Please help yourselves. We have prepared you all a very special meal in celebration.
Now then, I have something I must address with you all.
You will all be required to have one of these cards
you received in your invitation during the final tournament tomorrow.
One is "Glory of the King's Right", and the second is "Glory of the King's Left".
Those cards...?
The ones holding Glory to the King's Right can seize the grand cash prize.
Those wielding Glory to the King's Left may challenge Master Pegasus directly for his title.
I didn't know that!
Not good!
Of course I don't have that after barging in the way I did...!
What'da I do?
And one more thing.
Please look down at the soup we have prepared for you.
What's that?!
There's nothing in mine...
You asshole! Ya think we're gonna eat this?!
Please look inside them.
What's this?
We shall now begin selecting the tournament matchups.
I wonder who's going to face who...
No matter who I face, I'm going to win!
Anyone but Yugi...!
Who's got C?!
I do!
You?!
I couldn't ask for a better opponent!
You might wanna back outta this while ya still can!
I've got you, Mai-san!
Yugi, I'm not holding back.
Of course. I'll fight my hardest.
The results have been decided.
The first match will be Master Yugi Mutou versus Lady Mai Kujaku.
Followed by Master Bandit Keith versus Master Katsuya Jounouchi.
Now then, we sincerely hope you enjoy your meal.
What a beautiful sunset!
I'm stuffed!
Man, I can't eat another bite!
I can't believe you still ate that after finding an eye in it!
Jounouchi-kun.
Huh?
We have to win Pegasus' tournament!
Right...
But I don't have the card...
When we came to this island, we split our Star Chips in half, right?
Yugi!
Yugi... You...
So this Glory to the King's Right card belongs to you.
But...
If we win this tournament,
you can use the prize money for Shizuka-chan's eye operation, alright Jounouchi-kun?
Yugi...!
And I'll hold onto this card, Glory to the King's Left.
To get Grandpa back, I've got to beat Pegasus!
Yugi!
You're right...
Then I'll take it with deep gratitude.
It's about time for me to head off on my own.
Yugi, I'm looking forward to our Duel tomorrow.
Mmhm!
Goodnight, guys!
Goodnight!
Goodnight.
Goodnight then-
Yugi!
Tomorrow, let's get those honors!
Mhm-hm!
Goodnight.
Goodnight, Anzu.
Yugi, you'd better win!
Right!
See ya.
Grandpa... Kaiba-kun... And Mokuba-kun...
I'm going to save you no matter what!
Yugi... It's finally time for us to settle things.
I'll beat you for sure...
Shizuka!
Yes?
What's wrong?
Can we have a moment?
Honda-kun, let's just let it be!
Come on!
Eh? You think Kaiba-kun lost because he cheated?!
Yeah. If you think about all the times Pegasus messed with us up until now,
there's a high possibility.
That's true.
We want to find out for sure.
He is our enemy, after all.
It wouldn't surprise me if he's tweaked the situation to his advantage.
If that's the case, Yugi and the others were bound to lose from the start.
Hey Anzu, you gonna allow that?
Well, if that is true, of course I won't stand for it.
Right? So let's go find the proof we need to stop him!
Everyone should fight this match fair-and-square!
But it'll be bad if we get caught while searching for clues.
We can't bother Yugi and Jounouchi the night before the tournament.
We've gotta do this on our own.
Let's be of some use!
You're right!
Yugi...!
Yugi!
It can't be...!
That's Grandpa's voice!
Yugi! I'm this way!
Grandpa! Where are you?!
Yugi! Please save me!
Search thoroughly!
There's gotta be a spy camera or something around here!
There's nothing here!
Maybe Pegasus honestly beat Kaiba-kun...
I highly doubt that.
Whenever I'm forced into trials I'm bound to lose, I always become cunning.
Um, really...
Huh?
What's wrong?
Look!
Eh?
Did you find something?
This light...
It's coming in from the opening up there...
Honda, can you stand on that platform?
Wha...?
Stand there just like Kaiba-kun was!
R-Right...
That's...!
That's bingo alright!
I see a tower!
It's very possible that he had someone holding a camera, viewing the Duel Ring from there!
That way, it'd be easy for someone to spy from the window there,
and they can reveal the enemy's cards to him!
That's about as cunning as you can get!
And with a camera view of that, he'd be able to completely reveal the opponent's strategy!
There's got to be a secret room in that tower!
In any event, let's head over to that tower.
Eh?! We're going that far?!
Just relax and follow me!
Grandpa!
Yugi...!
This way!
It's painful...! Hurry up and save me!
Grandpa!
I found something useful!
You can't mean...!
Come on already! I told you to leave it to me!
If I hope to beat Yugi, I must think up a new set of strategies.
But there's no way he's flawless!
He's got to have a weak point somewhere...
Grandpa! Where are you?! Answer me!
Yugi! I'm over here!
Yugi... I've missed you...
It hurts...! Hurry and get me out of here...!
Grandpa! But how...?!
Hey! Try pulling me up before covering my mouth!
Let's hurry!
Geez!
Seriously, let's let it go!
Grandpa, how do I save you from here? I don't know how!
Save me! I'm in great pain!
Yugi!
But how do I do it?!
Grandpa!
Kaiba-kun... And Mokuba-kun as well...!
Get me out of here...!
Save me, Yugi!
Alright! Anzu, you climb up first.
That way, one of us can catch you if you slip by accident.
Eh?! No way!
Why?
Gosh! You don't get it?
What's up?
You see...
It's obvious the men should go first!
No, that won't work!
We can't climb unless someone's here to save you!
Then what're we gonna do?!
I-It's painful...!
Yugi...! Save me...!
Grandpa! Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun!
Yugi... That Pegasus man is a much more terrifying person than you realize...!
Honda-kun, I'm scared!
Don't be scared! Just climb!
But even if she does fall, we can't save her like this!
Uh... Just freaking climb, will ya?!
Honda-kun, don't push me like that!
Shut up! Then just climb already!
Grandpa, what do you mean by that?
That man's heart has been engulfed in darkness!
He's already gone to the Dark World!
Dark World...?
That man lives in the sorrowful darkness, only thinking about gaining the power he needs...!
You'll be fighting against that great darkness itself starting right now!
And that Dark Power is stealing away my life this very moment...!
Grandpa!
Yugi! YUGI!
That was terrible...!
We can't waste our time out here. We've gotta hurry up and search.
Honda! There's nothing up here!
There's no way!
What's this?
Looks like some kind of painting...
It's too dark to see much...
Who's there?!
She's really pretty, but I wonder who she is...
The same thing's in the dining room.
Maybe she's related to Pegasus somehow...
Pegasus!
We got busted?!
It seems you guys have seen right through me.
Then that'll make this go faster!
Pegasus! We know you've been cheating!
There's no use trying to cover it up!
There is no need for me to cover anything up.
And that is because I am about to drag you three into another world entirely.
What'd you say?
Allow me to show you all the world I refer to.
Wh-What the?!
Honda-kun! I'm scared!
Grandpa!
Grandpa! Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun!
Where are we...?
What's that voice?
Let's check it out.
B-But...
There's no point just sitting here!
W-What's this...?
What're they doing?
Honda-kun, let's turn back.
Th-That...!
You lose.
-You saw?
-Who are they?
What do we do?
Grandpa!
Yugi! I believe in you!
That you'll surely save me!
Yugi!
Yugi!!
YUGI!!
GRANDPA!!
Just what were you doing?!
A Dark Game.
Dark Game?!
What's that?!
An ancient ritual played long ago where one's very being is put to the test... the ultimate game.
Only those chosen are able to see it... within the Dark World.
That eye...
What's he doing...?
Is his eye somehow related to this "Dark Game" he's spoken of...?
It seems you've all taken an interest in this eye of mine.
Did he just read our minds?!
He couldn't have..!
That is correct.
The Millennium Eye's power allows me to read other's minds using the Mind Scan.
So long as I hold this power, I am untouchable!
This is the Dark Power given to only the chosen ones!
Would you like me to read your mind as well?
What?
I can't read it!
I've found it.
Could it be, you are...?!
A dream...?
Why am I here...?
I'm back...
Was that... just a dream?
But I'm certain I saw a Dark Game...
I found it... the Millennium Eye!
And with this, you've lost!
Don't screw with me, punk!
This idiot...! He's got such a damn loud voice!
With this... With this I can beat Yugi!
I'm really looking forward to tomorrow!
That wasn't an ordinary dream.
I'm certain Grandpa was sending me a message!
Kaiba-kun! Mokuba-kun! And Grandpa!
No matter what happens, I will save you!
"Preview"
The finals have finally begun!
Yugi's first opponent is the Mai Kujaku we know so well!
I've got no problem with Mai-san, but this Duel is going to Yugi!
Huh? What's wrong with you, Yugi?
You're not stopping any of Mai-san's attacks...!
That's not like you at all, Yugi!
Please just calm down and focus on the Duel!
Next time! "Driven to Temptation! The Shadow of Temptation"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship