Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Demon's Summon can't win against Zera!
That Ultra Rare Card...!
I-I can't win!
Now come out! Other Yugi!
What do I do...?
What should I do?!
"The Broken Millennium Puzzle"
Now Yugi, it's your turn.
Calm down... Keith's been acting a bit strange...
He has all these rare cards that have nothing to do with a Machine Deck.
I can't lose sight of my tactics...
I know I can find a way to attack him...
A Monster in Defense Position!
I'll torture you with my rare cards and traps and back you into a corner.
If I do that,
that man will surely appear from within the Millennium Puzzle.
Holy Knight Dragon!
Followed by another...
The Ultra Rare Magic Jammer!
And then...! The Magic Card, Defense Seal!
Devil Dragon...!
Now your Devil Dragon has been forced into Attack Mode!
Zera! Devil's Claw!!
Devil Dragon is beaten!
Now! Come out!
Other Yugi!
Are you the man I believe you to be?
Don't come out, Other Me!
I'll manage on my own!
Defense Seal ends now, since it's my turn!
My turn!
A Monster in Defense Position!
Holy Knight Dragon attacks your Defense Monster!
Sacred Fire!!
I'll place two cards face-down on the board.
And after switching Zera into Defense Position...
I'll end my turn.
It's your turn. You don't even have one Monster on the field!
What will you do now?
One face-down on the board.
And I'll Summon the Black Magician!
And use the Magic Card, Magical Silk Hats!
So you're trying to hide him?
Then a Magic Card...
Magic Jammer, activate!
Magic Jammer is a rare card that lets me discard a card from my hand...
and then negates the activation of a Magic Card, followed by its destruction.
Ah! My Magical Silk Hats!
And by the Magic Card Evil Ritual...
...the position of all Monsters on the field are switched.
And in that turn,
all Monsters on the field cannot change their battle positions.
This card can only be used during your Standby Phase.
And now, Zera will battle with your Black Magician!
Devil's Claw!!
Now! Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!!
I activate a Trap Card known as Declaration of God!
There's no way! Declaration of God is an Ultra Rare Card!
This card cuts my Life in half,
and in exchange, it negates the activation of a Magic, Trap or Summoned Monster... and destroys it.
It's true my Life Points are halved to 250,
but you only have 100, and you're barely standing!
I made a promise with my other self...
That I'd definitely get the Millennium Puzzle back!
This fight's not over!
My heart won't waver until I lose!
A miracle will surely happen!
No! I'll show you a miracle!
All right!
I'll put a card on the field.
Then a Monster in Defense Mode!
Is he still planning to fight me?
Come out!
The other man hiding in the Millennium Puzzle!
I'll force you out using this card...!
Offering for the Dead.
Offering for the Dead?!
Another Ultra Rare Card?!
That's right. A Magic Card above all other Magic Cards.
Offering for the Dead allows me to discard a card from my hand and destroy a Monster on the field.
This will undoubtedly be the blow that finishes you off!
Is that so?!
That's...!
Magic Effect Arrow!
It allows me to use any Magic Card with the opponent's Monster!
The target is Zera!
What?!
Bandit Keith...!
He's being controlled by someone!
I'll break that control with the power of the Millennium Ring!
Wh-What was that shock just now?!
The Power of Darkness...!
Is there someone else here besides Yugi?!
I... What am I doing here?!
You didn't believe in your own deck and relied way too much on Ultra Rare Cards!
You can't stop my attacks anymore!
You're Yugi...! Why are you here?!
Keith, what's wrong with you?!
Keith! Return to me at once!
You must continue to fight until the other Yugi within the Millennium Puzzle is forced out!
Millennium Puzzle...?
Who's there?!
Who's trying to order me around?!
What?
GET OUT OF MY HEAD!!
Is this what my other self was talking about?!
You must fight this Duel on your own.
Why?
I sense something strange...
Someone is trying to see my true identity.
Is someone controlling Keith?
Bandit Keith! You are my servant!
I have complete control over you!
Stop!
STOP IT~!!
I have to know the identity of the one hiding in the Millennium Puzzle!
You have to continue until I see this person's identity!
This thing?! It's because of this thing that I...?!
Don't do it, Keith!
Keith!
Stop!
Stop it!!
STOP IT~!!
YUGI-KUN~!
Bakura-kun!
Yugi-kun! Anzu-chan told me what happened.
Now then, it's your responsibility to put this back together again.
That's what the Puzzle would want, anyway...
Yes! Thank you!
But I don't know how long it will take to put together the Millennium Puzzle again.
It took me eight years to put it together the first time.
I don't know when I can see you again...
Even if it takes me another seven years or even ten, I will complete it!
This very moment, I have fulfilled my true reason for being here.
Yugi, you don't know the true power hidden in the Millennium Puzzle...
No, not even the other Yugi does.
Hidden in the Millennium Puzzle are the memories of the King from 3,000 years ago...
When the six remaining items are brought together,
the seal will be broken and that memory will be returned.
And of course, one of those keys is this Millennium Ring...
On the tablet in the shrine at Kul Elna, there is a warning that reads...
"The young Pharaoh and the six High Priests gave their lives
to seal the evil power inside the Holy Door."
"I pray that the evil power is not resurrected along with the Pharaoh's memories."
If I can find the young King's memories that dwell in the Millennium Puzzle,
I can make that evil power mine!
The power of the Millennium Ring can seal a part of one's soul inside that of an object!
And this part of the Puzzle is no exception!
Parasite Mind!!
Seal complete!
All I have to do now is wait for Yugi to complete the Millennium Puzzle.
A part of my spirit will become a mind spy...
...infiltrate the Labyrinth of Memories...
...and eventually find what I'm looking for inside the True Room of the Soul.
Yugi-kun!
Eh?
You forgot a piece of the Puzzle.
Thank you, Bakura-kun! If even one piece is missing, I can't complete the Puzzle!
That's right.
Ah! We're gonna be late
if we don't go to school!
Thanks a lot, Bakura-kun!
Are you okay?
Yeah! I'm gonna be on ahead!
Okay! I'm gonna go get the piece of the Puzzle attached to the chain.
Keith! Wake up!
Keith!
What's wrong? You still have some of your Life left.
Who are you? Who the hell are you?!
DON'T YOU DARE ORDER ME AROUND!!
Keith!
Yugi...! Just where did you go...?!
That's...!
A fire?!
Ahh! A fire!
I have to hurry up and take the Millennium Puzzle!
No use! I can't pull it out!
If I don't do something, the Puzzle...!
What should I do, other me?! Answer me!
No good?
I can't just leave my other self here!
If it gets burned in the fire, I'll never get to see my other self again!
The arrows end here!
Is Yugi inside of there?!
Anzu! Go get the fire department!
Got it!
Damn it!
I'm sorry, my other self.
I got your soul broken!
Just wait!
I will complete the puzzle!
Once I do, we'll meet again.
and I'll apologize to you.
Let's do this, Honda!
Okay!
Again!
Just a little more...! Just a little more and I can meet you again...!
Ready, Honda?
Yup!
Let's knock it down!!
Yugi!
What?! Keith!
What the hell's he doing here?!
Wait! Finding Yugi comes first!
O...okay.
Yugi, where are you?
What are you doing, Yugi?! We gotta get out of here!
Honda-kun, Jounouchi-kun!
I have to hurry and put the Puzzle together!
What's that idiot talking about?!
I...I did it.
Hang on! Yugi, are you okay?
I... I can't leave without the puzzle.
The puzzle?
No good! It won't budge!
Honda! Jounouchi!
Are you guys still in there?!
Here!
His deck's safe! Let's get out of here!
No! He won't let go of the Puzzle!
Honda! Jounouchi!
We can't stay here much longer!
If that's the case...!
Yugi! Let go of the Puzzle!
No good! He won't let go of the Puzzle!
We're gonna die here!
Damn!
Huh?
No! I won't even budge an inch!
We can't give up!
Jounouchi-kun! Pull the chain with the pipes!
What was that?
Honda! The pipes!
We can pull the chain out with the pipes!
Okay!
1, 2, 3...pull!
There's people in there!
Please save them!
Yugi!
It's alright! Yugi's fine!
Look! He completed the Puzzle inside of the fire!
He wouldn't let go, no matter how hard we pulled him!
What a bond they have...
It took me eight years to put the Millennium Puzzle together the first time around.
This time I did it in no time at all.
It's as if my other self was helping me put together the puzzle.
I know how you feel.
What's up with you, Jounouchi?
The truth is, back there I heard the other Yugi's voice telling me what to do.
I knew Jounouchi couldn't come up with a plan like that on his own.
Whaaaat~!?
What the hell?! Ain't it true?!
What the hell?!
Stop fighting in a hospital, you two.
My bad!
But I thought I was a gonner.
Thank you, guys
You saved my life!
It's no big deal.
It's something anyone would do.
I'll going to get us something to drink.
The other Yugi...
I thought he'd always existed within Yugi...
Like a split personality the Millennium Puzzle merely brought out...
But is that just what I wanted to believe?
But...
Other Yugi...
Did you come from inside the Millennium Puzzle?
An ancient Egyptian exhibition
is going to be held in Domino.
Even the Director of Archeology from Egypt will be there.
And it seems she's bringing
some very important artifacts.
But why does the image look
so much like Kaiba-kun?
The origin of Duels? The God Cards?
Something is about to happen
in Domino City!
Next time! "The Lost Memory of the Pharaoh"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...