Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"Walk Into the Light"
Now, come on!
Your anger and hatred!
I will take all of it!
I will take in the darkness of heart within this planet!
Other Me!
What?
Stay back, Partner!
This is my battle!
With my way of justice and beliefs on the line!
You can't! Other Me!
Partner!
You can't use this card!
But...
He's just waiting for you to use the card!
But if things keep going this way, I'm bound to lose!
Partner, this is my battle!
One that bets my
way of justice and my beliefs!
But this is different from before.
Partner, the day will come when the two of us must part ways!
A time will come when the both of us will have to fight a difficult battle on our own!
And that time is right now!
Other... Me...!
Not yet!
I am the one who chose this battle!
For the mission that has been passed along to me!
That is both mine
and everyone else's feelings!
My other self...  No matter how much it hurts, please don't waiver.
Believe in the strength of our bond.
You're not fighting alone.
Your friends and the Monsters who believe in you are always by your side.
Partner...
Even if we're separated...
I'm... always... by your side...
PARTNER!!!
Other Me!!
I won't...
I won't let myself be consumed by the likes of you!
Because within me...!
Nameless Pharaoh!
Ironheart!!
Kris!!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun...
Rafael!!
Kaiba!
Brother!!
Brother!
Big Brother!!
Kaiba!
Yugi...
Now I've... paid you back.
Step over my corpse... and go forward...
Kaiba!
What point is there in suffering so much by yourself?
Face reality.
You are nothing more than a cursed soul.
That is the truth.
If I just raise my hand, that fate...
Put an end to all of it.
Bring your existence back to nil!
I'm... nil?
That's right... I used to be nil...
Simply trapped within the Millennium Puzzle...
I am nothing...
Null, from the very beginning...
And if I lose them, I have nothing left...
That is why I have to vanish...
Disappear...?
I'm going to...?
I've got nothing... left within me...
Past memories... My body...
Does someone like me who holds no existence have it...?
Something in my heart that can never be erased...
I see... I never noticed it...
Deep within my heart...
Among the bonds I've woven with my friends...
There's a vessel of memories....
That is my everything...
I am not nil...
As long as I still have the vessel inside of me...
No matter how many times it takes... I can still be reborn!
My memories with everyone deep within me can never be erased!
The vessel of light!
The darkness of heart in this planet!
Using the vessel I hold within myself...
I hereby erase you!!
Other Me!
The tsunami... dissipated!
Did a miracle just occur?
Other Me!
It's gone...! It disappeared, Partner!
Yeah.
You're... such a...!
Dartz!
Father!
Ironheart!
Kris!
Father...
Kris...
Father!
Dartz...
All of the malice you've carried...
The Nameless Pharaoh has taken it all away from you.
Dartz...
Thank you, Yugi!
For saving my father!
I, too, express my gratitude.
Now, you two must return to your world.
A new future is awaiting you all beyond that door.
Ironheart...
Kris!
Let's go, Partner!
To where the others are!
Mhm-hmm!
Father. It is also time for us to cross over.
Mother is waiting for us!
Mokuba!
Brother!!
Good! Let's get ready to leave!
Jounouchi!
Jounouchi, where's Yugi?
Huh?
Wasn't he with you?!
Yugi?
Brother, we gotta get out of here right now!
We're going, everyone! Get on the helicopter!
Yugi!
Stop it, Jounouchi!
Hey! What the hell're you doing, Honda?!
Don't you care what happens to Yugi?!
All we can do for now is believe Yugi's okay!
Damn it all!
Yugi...
Huh?
Where the heck am I?
Last thing I remember...
Oh yeah! The hell you doin' here?!
W-Well...
Right back at you! Why're you?!
Well, ya see...
Anyway...
-I don't know how my soul came back...
-Don't know how my soul came back...
-But Yugi!
-But Jounouchi!
-I won't forgive you!
-Freakin' unforgivable!
-I'm gonna beat you for sure next time!
-I'm gonna beat ya for sure next time!
Miruko...
Look at this.
Humph! And what exactly is that piece of garbage supposed to prove?
This is a...
...memento of my little brother!!
My little brother was...
...killed by your company!
You're wrong.
You couldn't save him. Your little brother!
What... a-are you saying?
You still don't understand?
You couldn't manage to save your younger brother.
You're the loser
based on this point alone.
Brother!
Amelda... If that had been
me instead of you...
I would not have let my little brother die!!
No matter what it took!!
Amelda! Witness the power of a True Duelist and the splendor of the Chosen Ones!
Go!
Tyrant Burst Stream of Destruction!!
You're not bad, Kaiba.
Miruko...
Miruko... I'm going to live as much as I can for you as well.
I...
I'm shaking...?
Me...?!
Am I actually afraid of the bastard?!
No, that's not it...
It's been so long since I've felt like this...!
Now! Let's get on with it, Jounouchi!!
Burning Knuckle!!
Big Bang Dragon Blow!!
Jounouchi, I leave Mai to you.
Ah...
VARON!
So you left, Mai...?
Jounouchi...
Varon...
What a stupid man...
Dueling is not meant to fight for others.
Fighting is to win for yourself.
Aren't you the one who said so?
That's why you lost.
Mai?!
Varon did his best as a Duelist.
Even if it's you, I won't allow anyone to belittle him!
When I fought seriously with Varon, I understood something.
While Dueling with him, we started to understand each other as we spoke.
Me too. I want to feel what you're feeling!
That's why, Mai, I will fight you seriously.
This time, my feelings will reach you.
Me too. I want to receive your true feelings.
You win... Mai...
Jounouchi!
During your battle with Varon, you were already...
I'm sorry...
I won't be able to see your face anymore...
The Duel... was fun.
NO!
Jounouchi!
No... No! Jounouchi!
I knew it all along!
I knew that winning wouldn't change a thing!
I knew it from the start.
That even if you win...
Jounouchi...
Varon...
I will become a Duelist worthy of the both of you and I'll return.
Where are we?
Were we saved?
An aurora!
Black Magician Girl!
Timaeus!
Critias!
Hermos!
Both my Masters, thank you!
Now both the Duel Monsters Realm and your world have been saved!
The God of Orichalcos has returned.
Now that the hatred filling its soul has been destroyed, we're going to try letting it live among us.
I'm sure it will realize how wonderful the world of Duel Monsters is once it lives with us for a while.
Black Magician Girl!
Thank you, Nameless Pharaoh!
Yugi!
Now our grudge...
...has been lifted!
I'm the one who owes you my thanks.
If I didn't have your strength, I wouldn't have been able to overcome the darkness in my heart.
Farewell, Nameless Pharaoh!
Master...
No, it's nothing.
Goodbye!
What's going on? The aurora appeared again...
That's...!
Black Magician Girl and the Legendary Knights...
They're returning to the Duel Monsters World.
The Hermos card...!
Humph... Was it all a dream in the end...?
Or perhaps just an illusion?
Yugi...
Yugi?!
Everyone...
Thank God they're safe!
Yeah.
Yugi!
Yugi!!
You little squirt, you!
Ya had me worried!
Welcome back, Yugi!
Thanks you guys!
Yugi!
Let's get outta here now!
Yup!
C'mon already!
If ya don't hurry, we're takin' off without ya!
Geez, arrogant as always, the idiot.
This happens as soon as he learns Yugi's safe!
Oh shut up!
Man oh man!
Hey now!
Other Me...
What Black Magician Girl was about to say before...
That the curse of this planet is sealed deep within my other self.
And if the other me were to control the darkness in his heart once again...
...that curse could be revived.
But there's no need for me to worry about that.
Because my other self is much different than how he used to be.
He has now overcome the darkness of his heart...
...and is about to walk into a new light!
Because he's been reborn as a true Pharaoh!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
The battle against Doma has finally come to a close.
I guess we managed to protect the world somewhat.
But thinking back on things, it's been a tough battle...
Anyway, Yugi! Jounouchi!
Kaiba-kun!
Thank you for all your hard work!
We're ready to go back to America,
but let's just relax for the moment.
Wait, wha?
We... have no way of returning home!
Next time!
"The KC Grand Prix Opening Game"
Duel standby!