Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Honda-kun appeared before us.
But all five members of the Big Five were sharing his body!
The Big Five challenged us to another Duel to get our bodies.
But we already won our matches with them!
But we've got no choice to fight if we want to get Honda-kun's body back.
Jounouchi-kun, we've got no choice but to accept this Duel!
"Jounouchi is Targeted:
Working Together for a Victory Play"
I shall be your opponent
from here on out.
Draw!
OOH-AH!
You better take it easy, Jounouchi!
Don't you dare Direct Attack!
That's my body you're fighting, ya know, ooh!
Katsuya Jounouchi, this time I'll pay you back for the last time we fought.
I activate my Deck Master Ability!
Life Sentence!
What?! Right off the bat?!
First I slash my Life of 1000 points.
Life Sentence!! Every Monster on the field is removed from play and from the field!
All our Monsters were destroyed in an instant...!
And that is not all.
What...?!
Right. You both take 500 points of damage for each Monster removed!
This is without a doubt Kaiba Land...
This device...
Checkmate.
What are you doing, ooh~?!
He wiped you out, OOH-AH!!
Don't worry, Honda-san!
Just believe in
my big brother and Yugi-san!
The two of you may as well be back at the start line.
I Summon Hysteric Angel!
Now then... That little monkey guy up there said something rather intriguing.
He told you not to Direct Attack me.
Then allow me to have the honors!
Hysteric Angel, Direct Attack Katsuya Jounouchi!
Shit...!
Honda said too much...!
My attack is not through yet!
I then...
...launch Hysteric Angel using Catapult Turtle's Effect!
Jounouchi!
Big brother!
Not good! They're aiming for Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
You alright, Jounouchi-kun?!
D-Dammit...
I wouldn't aim for someone with the Duelist Level Yugi-kun holds.
It only makes sense to go after a team's weak link.
That's the inviolable rule
to winning a match.
Say what you like, but aren't you just pissed about losing to me?!
Humph, interpret it as you like.
I set two reverse cards.
I then activate the Magic Card, Altar of Mists!
Altar of Mists... It's a card that lets you add a Ritual Magic Card to your hand after three turns.
Even more, it can't be destroyed by magic, trap or Monster effects during those three turns.
My turn is over.
My turn! Draw!
Alright! Here goes!
I Summon Rocket Warrior!
It's not really a good idea to overuse my Deck Master Ability at the start of the Duel,
so I shouldn't right now...
...but since I;m down to 3,000 Life, I should make an exception.
I then activate my Deck Master Ability!
I transfer 1000 Attack Points from Flame Swordsman to Rocket Warrior!
Go, Rocket Warrior!
Attack Catapult Turtle!
I activate the Instant Quick-Play Magic, Revenge Sacrifice!
What?!
In the event one of my Monsters are destroyed in battle,
I am permitted to sacrifice the Monster that attacked my Monster,
and Special Summon
a Monster from my hand...
I'm about to play a big one!
I Summon Machine King!
And its Attack Power goes up 100 points for every Machine-type Monster, including itself, on the field!
Turn over.
You're up now, Yugi.
Right.
But right now the only Monster Card I've got in my hand is Death Vorstagalf.
I can't Summon it without a tribute!
I've got no choice
but to bet on this next draw!
My turn! Draw!
Rock Spirit Titan!
By removing one Earth-Attribute Monster from play,
this Monster can be Special Summoned.
I have the Buster Blader in my Graveyard from when he was discarded earlier.
I remove the Buster Blader in my Graveyard from play!
I Special Summon Rock Spirit Titan!
I then sacrifice Rock Spirit Titan!
To Summon Death Vorstagalf!
Yugi, you're still 100 points under matching his Machine King's 2400 Attack Points.
What are you planning?
I'll then place a reverse card and...
...end my turn.
Goddamn! What the hell was that, Yugi?
No matter how you look at it, that's way too obvious!
You may as well be telling the enemy, "This is a trap!"
What the heck is Jounouchi doing?
I wish my brother would take this more seriously!
No, Jounouchi-kun's dead serious!
Yugi-kun just played an awful move.
Even an amateur Duelist like me can see through it clearly.
What?
Jounouchi-kun's trying to warn him!
But why would Yugi
play such a bad move...?
Playing Machine King like that was a huge insult, Ouka!
Please do not misunderstand!
I most certainly was not intending to-
Can it!
Machine King is most suited to work under me, the former President of Military Affairs!
I'll be playing this game now!
You will now face me, Soichiro Ota and my Deck Master, Machine Sergent!
He's...!
He's the one who
made Honda-san this way...
My turn! Draw!
You played a Monster weaker than Machine King along with a reverse card.
Pretty dangerous.
It screams, "I'm a Trap!"
Looks like I'm right on the mark.
See, I told you!
It's completely obvious!
But I want to think Yugi has something else planned!
Using such a childish strategy against me.... You must be seriously underestimating me, kid!
The Magic Card, Heavy Storm!
It destroys all Magic and Trap Cards on the field!
Holy Barrier Mirror Force, eh?
That's right.
If your Monster attacked, it would have been sent back to you.
Huh? Hey, Yugi...!
You mean you didn't
have a hidden strategy...?
I'm sorry, Jounouchi-kun...
"I'm sorry"...? No matter what you say, you're underestimating these Big Five creeps way too much!
Damn right you are!
You just hung yourself!
So prepare yourself, kid!
Machine King!
Wait! It's a trap!
Attack Death Vorstagalf!
You fell for it!
What?!
I set two Traps for you!
Impossible! You don't have any other Traps on the field!
Allow me to explain!
When you used your Magic Card while Death Vorstagalf was in play,
its Ability raised its Attack Power by 200 points for this turn only!
Wh-What did you say?!
So when I played Heavy Storm...!
Counterattack!
Death Vorstagalf!!
What the hell...?!
Now for its second ability!
Also according to Death Vorstagalf's Effect,
you lose 500 points!
You dare ridicule me...?!
We've still got 6400 points left...
You've hardly accomplished anything!
You're wrong. He was after something else as well.
What?!
I see! I get it!
Get what?
If Jounouchi-kun had been attacked this turn instead of Yugi-kun...
Since Jounouchi didn't have any Monsters in play...
My brother would have been attacked directly...
Right. With only 300 Life Points left, Jounouchi-kun would have been a goner.
So that's why Yugi had him attack himself instead!
He used himself as bait.
With an obvious strategy.
So that's what it was...?
Yugi, I can't believe you thought of me that much!
And you played along nicely, Jounouchi-kun. That was some nice bluffing!
Huh?
Eh? Jounouchi knew about it all along?!
Is that so?! I couldn't tell at all!
Ooh-ah! That was some nice teamwork, ooh!
Big brother, you're really awesome!
Eh? Oh, yeah! I guess! It was no big deal!
I was moments away from becoming a robot monkey!
Turn over...
You missed a good chance
to beat these kids.
Your debut has long expired!
I will be taking the next turn!
My turn!
He has no Wall Monsters on his field.
It's a good chance to attack him directly!
Come on! I need a Monster Card!
Draw!
Oh man, I got one! I can use this and-
Snap...
Panther Warrior can't attack unless I offer a tribute!
Shit... It was a good chance to directly attack him, too!
No helping it.
I Summon Panther Warrior
in Defense Position!
But I won't
let him draw next turn!
I set one face-down card and end my turn!
You're up now, Yugi.
Right.
My turn!
Draw!
I'm sorry, Honda-kun!
But this is a chance to beat him!
I know, ooh~!
Don't hold back on me, ooh-ah~!
It'll be alright, Honda-san.
Death Vorstagalf, Direct Attack!
I then Summon Big Shield Gardna to the field in Defense Mode!
Turn end!
Just two turns left, heh...
It's completely empty...
Noah, did you show this slide show to me to prove that you're really Gozaburo's son?
What in the-
Does that mean that Noah's dead?
So who's the Noah that appeared before us?
But why would he go out of his way to show me this?
Could it be that Noah's not the one who's controlling this program?!
I, Kogouro Daimon, will be Dueling you from now on.
I'm on a different level than the other ones you fought.
I suggest you get ready.
That's nice, pal.
Just get a move on!
Draw.
Sorry! I'm not lettin' you draw!
Trap Card! Drop Off!
I know you've been waiting a while for the card you drew, but now you gotta send it to the Graveyard!
You think?
What?
Oh yeah! Your Deck Master...!
You're correct! My Deck Master is Psycho Shocker!
Dammit...
They should have let me handle this from the start.
And I'm not done drawing!
Thanks to the effect of Pot of Greed, I draw again twice!
Since you activated a Magic Card, you activated Death Vorstagalf's Effect!
Its Attack Power goes up by 200 points!
So what?! I Summon Injection Angel Lily!
You played that low-Attack Monster in Attack Mode?!
No! Jounouchi-kun, he's...!
Did you think I didn't have a strategy or something, you fool?
Wh-What?!
Injection Angel Lily allows me to increase her Attack Power by 3000 points during the Damage Calculation Step
if I pay 2000 of my Life Points!
By 3000 points...?!
Go, Injection Angel Lily!
It's time for their psychical!!
Here's your injection!
I can't believe he gave up so many Life Points just to attack...
Don't worry yourself!
My after-plan is flawless!
Instant Quick-Play Magic!
Sebek's Blessing!
Sebek's Blessing?
It's an Instant Quick-Play Magic Card that restores your Life Points by the amount of damage inflicted on your opponent.
That's right! Meaning my Life rises by 1000 points!
And then I set a reverse card!
Turn end!
Now! It's your turn, Jounouchi!
I know! I know that without you telling me!
But how the heck do you beat a Monster with 3400 Attack Points?
If I don't act quickly, I'll lose all of my Life, 3100 points over!
Let me do something before
you make a move.
My set card is...
...Gravity Bind - Supergravity Net!
So long as this card is in play, all Level 4 or higher Monsters can't attack!
What the hell?! Shouldn't Psycho Shocker's Effect destroy that card?!
Normally yes, but his Deck Master Ability will prevent him from destroying my Traps!
Shit...!
Draw!
Bingo!
In that case, allow me
to play Psycho Shocker!
With this, I can destroy his Trap!
I sacrifice Panther Warrior!
I Summon Android - Psycho Shocker!
Eye for an eye!
Psycho Shocker for a Psycho Shocker!
Consider this payback for before!
Trap Search!!
How's that?!
And you think you've won or something?
What?!
Even if you got rid of my Trap, that won't stop Angel Injection Lily's Attack Power from rising to 3400.
How will your 2400 Attack Psycho Shocker block that?
You were careless, Jounouchi-kun!
Did you forget that Lily's Attack Points would go up on his next turn!?
Yugi...
Just her Attack Points.
Just her Attack Points will go up...
"Just"...?
I get it!
Only Lily's Attack Points power up!
But her Defense Power
will remain the same!
Sweet!
Magic Card! Attack Seal!
I'll switch Injection Angel Lily into Defense Position!
What!?
Here goes! Android - Psycho Shocker, attack Injection Angel Lily!
Cyber Energy Shock!!
Now he's lost his only Monster.
You handle the rest, Yugi.
Turn end!
Yeah!
My turn, draw!
I sacrifice Big Shield Gardna!
I Summon Black Magician Girl!
Go, Black Magician Girl!
Direct Attack!
Nice one, Yugi!
We're almost there!
Turn over!
It's far too early to celebrate.
I've been waiting for this moment!
"Waiting"?
Altar of Mists!
Yes! For the third turn of which Altar of Mists was activated!
My turn.
Draw.
Wh-What is it?
What the hell is so funny?!
This Duel's result has just been decided!
What?
The moment I Summon this Monster, you fools have absolutely no chance of victory!
The Big Five finally activate the Altar of Mists Magic Card on their final attempt.
And it's a card used to Summon Five God Dragon!
They sacrifice their Deck Masters in order to Summon the monstrous Five God Dragon!
And without Blue-Eyes White Dragon, they can't Summon Master of Dragon Knight!
Yugi! Jounouchi! Do you have a Monster that can beat it?!
Next time!
"Beat It! The Five God Dragon"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise