Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Finally Summoning all three Blue-Eyes,
Kaiba goes on the attack.
I don't have a Monster on the field that can stand up to these attacks...
Just as I faced certain despair,
Jounouchi-kun's words echoed in my ears.
That's right! There's countless
possibilities in your hand!
Fight alongside me,
Jounouchi-kun's Red-Eyes!
In order for us to win!
"Defeat the Hatred!
Black Paladin"
B-Big brother...!
Jounouchi-kun!
Shizuka...?
And you guys, too...?
Huh...? Where are we?
Why am I here?
Jounouchi, are you really...?
Honda...
What the heck are you doing?
"Wh-What"...?
Big brother!
Hey! Shizuka!
Thank Heavens!
Big brother...!
Shizuka...
Seriously...! Thank God!
But this is impossible!
I don't believe this!
Just a couple of minutes ago,
you were on the
borderline of life and death!
Last I remember,
I was Participating in the Domino City
District Duel Tournament...
Uh, and then I was suddenly
watching Yugi's battle...
Was I dreaming?
Jounouchi! You big jerk!
What the hell are you
acting so calm about!?
Honda-san!
You're really awake, aren't you!?
You damn idiot!
We all thought you were gonna die!
Don't ever die again, asshole!
Honda...!
Oh yeah! I was fighting against Malik!
What about Mai?
What happened to Mai?!
Mai...!
Why...?
Mai!
Hey! Why the hell are you still asleep?!
Weren't you supposed to
wake up if I beat Malik?!
I... knocked that bastard Malik out,
didn't I?!
Right?!
What's the matter?
I won, didn't I?
Big brother...
Well, you see... you lost.
Wh-What did you say?!
There's no way that's true!
I Summoned Gearfried,
and then Malik-
But you passed out before you could!
We were so worried about you...
We thought you were going to die...!
I won...
Gearfried... The...
A... ta...
I see...
So I lost...?
I'm so sorry, Mai...
I couldn't save you...
Yugi, you have
two Monsters on your field...
Since my Blue-Eyes has
superior Attack Points,
you must be planning on outlasting me
by playing Defense Mode for
the rest of your turns...
I set two reverse cards!
Turn end!
But with my next card, I will
cut off your only escape route...
Dammit, Kaiba...
What's he planning next?
My turn!
Draw!
No matter what cards
he's placed face-down,
there's still a chance to win so long
as my Life Points haven't hit zero!
I have to believe that!
I set a reverse card!
Then, Red-Eyes goes into Defense Mode!
You can't run!
Permanent Trap, activate!
What?! A Trap?!
Red-Eyes went back
into Attack Mode!
Permanent Trap Card!
Final Attack Orders!
As long as this card remains on the field,
all Monsters remain in Attack Position!
Furthermore, both players must choose three cards from their decks,
and place the others in the Graveyard!
What the hell?!
Now we won't know the winner
for another three turns.
The cards I've chosen consist of the required
formula to create the Ultimate...
Yugi!
I'm going to clear your head of the
delusions you have of your
so-called past in an instant!
I can only pick three cards from my entire deck...
But what should I do?
Which ones should I pick?
And what about the next match?!
What happened to Yugi?!
He's fighting Kaiba-kun right now!
What!?
I can't be here of all places right now!
Jounouchi!
I have to go watch Yugi's battle!
Big brother!
Hey, you! You're still not recovered yet!
What's the patient's condition?!
Where's the patient?!
It's him...
Wha...?
He was in critical condition
just moments ago!
That was moments ago!
Moments ago!
And now is now.
There's nothin' wrong with me!
I'm the great "Perfect Jounouchi" in the flesh,
makin' a completely miraculous recovery!
Just hold on a moment!
We still have no idea what even
happened to you in the first place!
You still need to be properly tested!
I said I'm fine, pal!
Let's gun it, everyone!
Don't.
The doctor's right...
You have to do what your
medical overseer tells you to!
I get what's goin' on in my body
more than any of you.
You don't know!!
You were practically dead
just minutes ago, you know!
We've all been worried sick over you!
And here you are, making that face
like nothing happened...!
You need to worry about your body
before you start thinking about Dueling!
Anzu...
I'm sorry.
But I have to go do this!
No matter what!
Jounouchi!!
I really am sorry
for worrying you all.
But Yugi's not the only one
concerned about his battles!
I have to fight as well in order
to keep my promise with him!
Your... promise with him...?
I fight because I
promised Jounouchi-kun.
Our Battle City isn't over until
I settle things with Yugi!
Both Yugi and me have been fighting
in order to reach the point when we
can call ourselves True Duelists!
It doesn't matter who
it is we're Dueling.
We're connected to each another.
So I want to watch how it ends!
I'm going to watch Yugi's battle!
I have to go!
Jounouchi...!
Shizuka, take care of Mai!
Don't push yourself too hard,
okay big brother?!
Wait a moment, you!
I apologize!
Oi! Wait up!
I don't know what
to do with them...
Yugi! Don't lose!
What are Kaiba's
last three cards...?
Think...
Read his strategy...
More importantly, I have to decide on the three cards I will choose.
He hasn't played his Resurrection of the Dead Magic Card in this Duel yet...
In order to reach the highest Attack Power he can possibly reach at this point...
...he's going to have to use Resurrection of the Dead to bring back the third Blue-Eyes on his field.
And if he's planning to fuse the three Blue-Eyes into the Ultimate...
I'm going to have to gamble
with this strategy!
Turn end!
Finally made a decision, did you?
But, regardless of the cards you chose,
they may as well be deemed useless!
It's not possible for you to defeat me!
My turn! Draw!
This time you're finished, Yugi...
Magic Card!
Resurrection of the Dead, activate!
So he did use it!
And the Monster I bring back is,
of course, the Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
And I'll then activate my reverse Magic!
What?! He already had
Fusion as a reverse set on the field!?
Become one being,
my three Blue-Eyes!!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!!
Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon...!
The strongest Monster in existence...
It's Attack Points even surpass Obelisk's!
Paying attention, Yugi?
This is the ultimate Monster that
will pave the road of my future!
Yugi, I'm about to defeat you.
And when I do,
I'll obtain something great.
But it's not something as boringly
cliched as revenge against you!
Why have I fixated
on fighting you for so long?
I fought through Battle City in order
to find the answer to that...
And I finally found the answer...
The answer...
Yes!
That stone palette and everything behind it
rose the curtains on Battle City.
And that is where the answer lies.
Yugi, you've fought in order to regain
the memories carved on that palette...
Chasing a past that has
already gone by is nothing but a
foolish act and a waste of time!
The past...
But I'm not like that!
To me, the memory of the past is as
meaningless to me as a
crumbling piece of rock!
When us two siblings lost
our parents at a young age,
those filthy adults forced us
to live in an orphanage...
Then, when we were adopted
by Gozaburo Kaiba,
that monster of a family forced us to live
the worst possible life and undergo an
elite education with no end in sight.
And in order to survive in a world filled
with conspiracy and scheming,
I underwent any and all
tests given to me.
Kaiba Corporation was
destroyed and reborn again.
But even after I took my revenge,
I was filled with a new anger!
My past is nothing
but hatred and anger!
It's not like your
stupid fantasy world!
I only care about the future!
I trample on the past
as if it never even existed!
Yugi! You represent the past!
Once I destroy you, I will shine light down
the bright corridors of my future!
At the moment I
obtain the title of Duel King!
Kaiba...
My brother wants to beat Yugi
so he can forget about the past?
Things were hard back then...
But they weren't as bad
when I was with my brother!
No... They were actually fun
when I was around big brother!
But then...
Will he even forget the smile
he showed me so long ago...?
I will defeat you
and stand at the top!
That time has finally come!
I'm surprised even you
can laugh in this situation...
Kaiba, you're one of the few people
I recognize as a Duelist.
But I'm a bit disappointed in you.
What did you say?!
I'll put it bluntly!
Anger...!
Hatred...!
No matter how much you have,
those things aren't enough to beat me!
To be frank, I'm pitying you
right now for trying to coerce
me with such trash talk...
Let's see if you still feel that way
after seeing this card...
Reverse card, open!
Double Magic, activate!
What?!
Double Magic?!
Indeed it is!
This card lets me use any
of the Magic Cards the opponent
used for this turn only!
Resurrection of the Dead!
And Fusion!
I Summon Buster Blader
using Resurrection of the Dead!
Then I'll activate Fusion!
I fuse Black Magician together
with the Buster Blader!
He's going to polymerize
the Black Magician and Buster Blader?!
The Warrior born of this polymerization
inherits the Special Ability of Buster Blader!
Its Attack Power goes up by 500 points
for every Dragon-Type Monster on the field!
Both the Ultimate Dragon and
the Red-Eyes are present on the field!
Allow me to show you!
The Mighty Magic Swordsman -
Black Paladin!
You're always the type to entertain
until the very end, Yugi...
I presume you know that
Fusion Monsters can't attack on
the turn they're Summoned!
My turn is over.
It's my turn!
Draw!
Kaiba...
Your hatred...
Your anger...
The card I'm about to set
will dispose of it all!
I set a reverse card!
Turn end!
My turn!
Draw!
Yugi, I'm about to destroy
you along with the abominable past!
You'd better prepare yourself!
Kaiba!
Those without a past
have no future to grasp!
What?!
The past forms the foundation...
And the future is built on top of it!
No one's past is meaningless!
The past, present and future
are what holds you together!
Hmph, I already told you!
That I'm only interested in the future!
Big brother...
I will surpass Battle City and
everything that comes after it!
I alone will be crowned Duel King and
rise to a higher plane of being!
Kaiba, your mind is like this
Duel Tower standing in the ruins!
You can pile hate on top of hate
to reach the top, but you'll never
achieve true victory!
You will wander forever, seeking the
next hate and the one beyond that!
Even if you manage to
defeat me, you will only find
an endless chain of hatred!
You will wallow eternally in hatred,
never able to escape the darkness!
Heh! Hatred and anger give me power!
The power to dominate everything!
Then hit me with all of your
pent up hatred and anger!
If you think you can
defeat me with that!
Humph! Prattle on as you like!
But victory has already
chosen me on this turn!
Here I come!!
Ultimate Dragon, attack!
You won't defeat me!
I always fight for those who believe!
For my friends!
For myself!
And to become a True Duelist!
Kaiba, I will defeat you!
As a rival who walked the
road of battle with me...
And as a friend!
Ultimate Burst!!
Reverse card, open!
Magician's Spellbook!
Futile!
I activate Magic Absorption!
The moment your Monster's
Attack Power goes up,
those points are absorbed and
ejected into my Monster's
Attack Power, increasing it!
The Ultimate's Attack Power
went up another 500 points!
Shatter to pieces along with
Black Paladin and your friend's card,
Red-Eyes, Yugi!
The end.
He did it!
What the...?!
Yugi!!
I won...
Is that so?
Kaiba...
You can pile hatred on hatred...
...but it's fragile!!
What was that?!
Did you really think you could win
bearing things like anger and hatred?!
Shut your mouth!!
There's no way your Monster
could defeat the Ultimate!
Then I'm going to show you...
...the last attack
that will grant my victory!
Reverse card, open!
Fusion Cancel!
Fusion Cancel...?!
It splits up one Fusion Monster
on the field and negates their
attack for the turn!
Did he know I was going to
play the Ultimate...?!
My Ultimate Dragon...
...is splitting apart!
There are now two more
Dragon-Types on the field!
Increasing Black Paladin's Attack Points!
And because the fusion of Ultimate was
canceled, your turn comes to an end!
What...?!
My turn!
Draw!!
Kaiba! This card will tear apart the
darkness that controls your heart!
I activate a Magic Card
from my hand!
Diffusion Wave Motion!
By paying 1000 of my Life Points,
I can direct my Magician's attack order
to cover every Monster on
your side of the field!
That means Black Paladin can attack
all three Blue-Eyes at the same time!
Each of the Blue-Eyes has
3000 Attack Points...!
And his Black Paladin has 4900!
Attack, Black Paladin!
Kaiba...
Hatred does not lead to true victory!
Beyond Magic! Fierce Slashing Wave!!
Kaiba...
You had to lose to me...
so you can defeat your own madness!
All right!
Yugi won!
Yugi tells a confused Kaiba-kun...
It's true I won and you lost.
But we have no difference in skill!"
And, "My rival... My friend...
Why does this line stand between us?!"
And an outraged Kaiba-kun replies,
"I don't need the strength of friends!"
Which causes Jounouchi
to confront him!
Eh?! "This time you're gonna Duel me!"
Are you nuts?!
Next time!
The Deadbeat's Road of Flame:
Jounouchi VS Kaiba"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other