Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Varon!
It's finally time for us to put an end to this.
Armor Monsters that you can equip on yourself...
Is that your trump card?
"Victory is everything"?
But Duels are not tools for us to use to defeat our opponents and measure our strength.
I cannot lose to someone like you!
"Full Armored Gravitation"
Darn! Let's attack, since we have no other choice!
Don't be reckless, Honda!
Yugi!
Brother!
I don't have time for such trash!
I will finish them with one blow!
Timaeus...
Come on, Timaeus!
Come out, Critias!
Here I go!
My turn, draw!
I Summon Marauding Captain in Attack Position!
When this card is successfully Summoned onto the field...
I can Special Summon one Level Four or lower Monster from my hand.
I Summon Kung-Fu Fighter Ultimator in Attack Position!
There's no Monsters on the opponent's field!
Go, Marauding Captain! Direct Attack Varon!
Next, I attack with Kung-Fu Fighter Ultimator!
How's them apples?
Don't get a big head after dealing such low level attacks.
What?
Don't disappoint me, Jounouchi.
If you want to defeat me, then you'll need to use your strongest attack!
You won't beat me with half-ass attacks like those.
What is this guy thinking?
The situation is already unfavorable for him.
Where is his confidence coming from?
Turn over!
My turn. Draw!
What?
The Armor Monster that disappeared is back again!
When Psychic Armor Head is in the Graveyard...
I can Special Summon it onto the field in Attack Position during my Standby Phase!
I already told you... That this card is the crutch to Summoning the invincible Armor Monsters!
No! That again?!
Dread all you like, but there will be no escape for you!
From my hand, I activate a Magic Card!
The Barrier of Orichalcos!!
That's...!
Found them!
Only the winner can walk out of this barrier in one piece!
I then activate another Magic Card!
Full Armored Gravitation!
This card allows me to draw ten cards from my deck...
...and Special Summon any Armor Monsters that got picked.
Did you say ten?!
Burning Knuckle!!
Jet Gauntlet!!
Over Boost!!
Active Guard!!
Buster Knuckle!!
Advanced Shield!!
I Summon them in Attack Position!!
This guy Summoned seven Monsters out of the blue...
Full Armored Gravitation!!
They combined again!
This is the invincible Armor Deck!!
Using power to destroy enemies and obtain the ultimate glory!
Enemy player: 2500 Life Points.
Enemy Monster: Marauding Captain. Attack Power: 1200.
Battle Warrior. Attack Strength: 700.
But regardless of how many Armor Monsters he has on the field...
...their Attack Power only increased from zero to 500.
Is he going to activate some Special Ability?
Here I come, Jounouchi!!
Confirming target.
Lock on.
Possibility of defeating Marauding Captain: 99%.
Buster Knuckle power injection: Begin.
What?
The Attack Power...!
Buster Knuckle gains 200 Attack Points for every Armor Monster on the field!
Y-You bastard...
What did you just do?!
How's it feel, Jounouchi?
This is how an "attack" is supposed to be felt!
After obtaining the Power of Orichalcos, my Armor Monsters's attack...
...not only decreases your Life Points, but it also inflicts damage onto the opposing player's body as well!
What...?!
We aren't just fighting your average Duel here...
It's a "real fight"!
Listen up!
Every single one of my attacks will pierce your insides and decrease your strength!
Only one Armor Monster can attack per turn.
Your life is saved for the moment, Jounouchi.
I end my turn.
What's wrong with you now?
It's your turn, you know.
Or are you unable to even stand up?
I really felt that one...
But I'm not so weak that I'll collapse and give up just like that!
That just shows you're an idiot who doesn't know the big gap between our abilities.
Shut up!
You can't be sure of that until the end!
You're dead if you think that you won't win.
That's why I've always believed in my own power!
Even if I get defeated, I'll stand up again!
Then, someday I'll surely win!
I see.
That stupid way of thinking is the reason why Mai can't stand you.
What?!
What about Mai?!
Mai is different from you.
Mai is more like me...
You did say you wanted to win, did you not, Mai Kujaku?
From this day forward, you will be one of us... of Doma!
How'd it feel, Mai?
The feeling when you received that power?
I'm thankful to you for letting me meet Dartz.
But that doesn't mean that I'll be indebted to you.
Oh?
I won't be defeated anymore.
In order to continue winning, cooperating with others will only mess things up.
No matter who it may be, I'll defeat anyone that stands in my way.
Even if that person is you or Dartz.
I like you.
I guess you could say you and I are like birds of a feather.
I think the same too.
To keep winning is everything to me.
What's wrong?
Why don't you look happy even though you've defeated the renowned Pegasus?
It's nothing.
With the way I am now, beating him hardly broke a sweat.
This is not the kind of Duel that I'm after.
The person whom I want to fight with...
The thirst for victory...
The fear of loss...
Do you understand such emotions?
There's no way you would understand!
You aren't the one who's able to understand Mai's heart and support her!
That would be me!
It's true that I may not understand Mai's feelings...
But...!
Stand up, Jounouchi!
Save those tears for if you lose the Duel!
Moron!
It's just a runny nose!
Shit...
It won't stop coming...!
Here.
Just clean it up. It's disgraceful.
Jounouchi, don't give up on your desires so easily.
Th-This is...
But she's not someone who will sacrifice others just for her own victory.
She can't possibly be sharing the same wish of destroying the world you guys have!
Your point?
I want to bring Mai back.
Until then, I won't give up, no matter what happens!
My turn, draw!
I sacrifice Kung-Fu Fighter Ultimator to Summon Android - Psycho Shocker!
Enemy Monster: Android - Pyscho Shocker.
Attack Power: 2400.
Special Effect: "Trap Search"
Go, Psycho Shocker!
Attack Psychic Armor Head!
Changing target of attack.
What?!
When any Armor Monsters come under attack...
I can redirect the attack to any Armor I choose!
But you can't beat my Psycho Shocker with the armor you've got left!
Do you really think so?
Why is he looking so relaxed?
Is he hiding some special tactic?
H-H-Help us!
Anzu! Rebecca!
Yugi!
Are both of you okay? Anzu! Rebecca!
You did it, Big Brother!
Everyone make it?
Yes, somehow...
It's like a nightmare seeing these monsters walk the streets.
Wait up, Brother!
Kaiba-kun?
We can't waste any more time here.
We need to get inside Paradias Headquarters ASAP and put an end to all of this.
Yugi.
What are you going to do?
I'll go after I find Jounouchi-kun.
Do what you like.
Kaiba Corporation may be taken over, but the satellite system should still be working.
That's right!
By infiltrating the satellite system and accessing Jounouchi's Duel Disk,
we'll be able to know where he is!
Kaiba...
There's no room for you.
I'll defeat Dartz myself.
Wait!
It's dangerous with just the two of you!
They're gone.
But it can't be too easy to hack into the system of a company...
Becky can surely do it!
She's a Jack-Of-All-Trades and a genius, afterall.
My turn! Draw!!
Target: Lock-on.
Its Attack Power is going up again!
Can it be...?
That's right.
Burning Knuckle also gains 200 Attack Points for every Armor Monster on the field.
Even so, it's not enough to get past Psycho Shocker!
I'll attack.
Burning Knuckle!!
That's impossible!
I already told you!
In my Duels, using all my power, I'll continue attacking my opponents until they drop!!
What? Look, you're on the losing end, aren't you?
What's so funny?
Look carefully.
His Attack Power dropped to 700?!
Any Monster attacked by Burning Knuckle...
...will have its Attack Power decreased by an amount equal to its own Attack Points.
Damn...
He decreased Psycho Shocker's Attack Points at the expense of his Life Points.
What a reckless guy.
But that unwavering confidence and decisiveness to attack without hesitation...
He's really strong.
But I can't let myself lose either.
Right, My turn! Draw!
I Summon Rocket Warrior in Attack Position!
I then use Rocket Warrior to attack Over Boost!
Invincible Mode!!
Changing attack target.
Come on!!
Even though their Attack Powers are both 1500...
Due to the Special Effect of Rocket Warrior, I will take zero damage!
And even though its Attack Power may have been decreased...
Psyco Shocker has yet to attack!
Jet Gauntlet!!
P-Psycho Shocker...
Is that yet another Special Effect of Armor Monsters?
That's right.
When Jet Gauntlet is destroyed, one of my opponent's Monsters is destroyed as well.
You're not bad at all.
You too.
The Barrier of Orichalcos was activated somewhere near here...
Where can they be?
I must defeat Jounouchi...
If not, I'll...
Woman!
Those who lose a Dark Game, their souls will be eaten alive by the darkness!
Slowly! Oh, so slowly!!
No...
No!!
Let me out, please let me out!
Save me!
I don't want to go back... I don't want to go back to that dark place..! Anything but that...
No matter who it may be, I'll defeat anyone that stands in my way.
Be it Jounouchi or Yugi...
Anyone that obstructs me. Even you, Varon!
Hey! You still don't know where Jounouchi is?!
Calm down.
Don't distract Rebecca.
That's right.
Let's believe in her and continue waiting.
But while we're here, Jounouchi may be battling a Duel with that Varon bastard!
That may be true, but...
Why didn't I stop him?!
Honda-kun...
Jounouchi blames himself for what happened to Mai.
He thinks it's his responsiblity.
It's my fault.
Jounouchi...
Why didn't I notice anything before Mai became that way?
Didn't notice anything...
Jounouchi...
That's why I'll put an end to this.
I'll definitely save her this time.
Honda...
Please keep this a secret from Yugi and the rest, okay?
Jounouchi, you...
How can he be at fault?!
But Mai, she...
Jounouchi actually said that...
Jounouchi-kun, please don't be rash.
My turn, Draw!!
I Summon Buster Pyle in Attack Position!
Another Armor Monster?!
That's right.
And this Buster Pyle has a Special Ability too!!
Target: Lock-on.
Rocket Warrior.
Take this!
Wire Shoot!!
Buster Pyle has a Attack of 500, but it defeated Rocket Warrior who has 1500 Attack Points?
The Special Ability of Buster Pyle...
...is that it receives no Battle Damage and destroys the opponent's Monster!
In addition, it inflicts 500 points of damage to the opponent!
Then, from my hand, I activate a Magic Card!
Data Brain!
I equip this to Psychic Armor Head!
I end my turn.
What's up with that Equipment Magic?
What kind of Effect's he gonna use this time...?
No...
I can't get scared now.
My turn...! Draw!
Good, I got it!
I'll stake everything on this card!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Both Jounouchi and Varon are in the battle to decrease each other's battle spirit.
Their Duel is getting more intense!
With the Claw of Hermos, Jounouchi drives Varon into a corner.
But Varon keeps steady!
In between the attacks and defences...
With both their bodies and spirits nearing their limits...
Both of them get drawn to each other.
Next time! "Reverberating Soul"
Duel standby!