Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
My Dueling opponent
has been decided as the winner of the KC Grand Prix Tournament, Leon.
If it's Leon, we should have a find Duel!
However, the Leon that once enjoyed Dueling is now fighting seriously for his mission.
Just what is happening?
What?! You're Sieg's little brother?!
"Golden Castle of Stromberg"
I'll then activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Iron Cage!
This card sends one Monster on the field into the Cemetery!
What?!
The one to be trapped within the Iron Cage will be...
Iron Hans!
Eh? His own Monster?
When Iron Hans leaves the field, the inner power of Iron Knight can be drawn out!
Its Attack Power went up!
Now I see! That's what he was after!
I attack Retrained Elf Swordsman using Iron Knight!
Next, I'll use Forest Hunter to attack Yugi-san directly!
Not good! His Life was lowered by a large amount!
I will complete my turn.
I would expect nothing less from the one who defeated Rebecca.
Mhm... This child is a True Duelist.
Not only does he have superb talent and ability.
He truly cares for his cards, and the cards respond to those feelings.
You're right. Leon-kun's enjoyed Dueling ever since he first started playing.
The love he has for the cards might even give Yugi a run for his money.
He truly enjoys Dueling from the depths of his heart.
You're good, Leon. I expected no less.
It's really a pleasure to be praised by you, Yugi-san.
It's been my dream to Duel against you with this deck.
Even back when I was little, I never had any friends to play with.
Reading books alone by myself, I was very lonely.
When I became interested in Duel Monsters, I wrote Pegasus a letter.
"I would like for you to make new cards based on old folklore."
And after he did, he sent them all to me.
Leon-kun...
And I am serious when I say I want to defeat you, Yugi-san!
Using these cards that have always been with me!
And for my brother, who's always believed in me!
I will win this!
I understand.
If those are the reasons you're fighting, I'll give this everything I've got.
Other Me...
Partner, Leon's determination is strong.
No matter what we say to him, he's dead set on fighting for his brother.
Even if that means injuring his pride as a Duelist.
Then the least I can do is give this all I've got!
I'll play at my full strength, so we can have a Duel with no regrets.
Mm-hm! Good idea!
Here goes! My turn, draw!
I Summon Queen's Knight in Attack Mode!
Queen's Knight, attack Forest Hunter!
I'll then place a reverse card, ending my turn!
My turn! Draw!
During my Standby Phase, the Iron Hans that was placed in the Cemetery by the effects of Iron Cage...
...will return to the field once again!
Now that Iron Hans has returned to the field, Iron Knight's Attack Points return to 700.
But...
I activate Iron Hans' Special Effect!
When I successfully Summon Iron Hans, I can Special Summon an Iron Knight from the deck!
I then activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Spinning Wheel Spindle!
That's from the Sleeping Beauty fairy tale.
That's the card he used back then...!
It's a Monster Destruction Card!
Using Spinning Needle Spindle, I destroy one Monster on the field!
Queen's Knight!
The destroyed Monster can be Special Summoned
from your Cemetery in Attack Position on the third turn after its activation.
Until then, she'll stay in a deep sleep.
Crap! Yugi's lost the Monsters on his field!
Yugi!
And I Direct Attack Yugi-san using Iron Hans!
Reverse card, open!
Holy Barrier - Mirror Force!
When a Monster attacks the Holy Barrier, Mirror Force,
all of the opponent's Attack Position Monsters are destroyed!
Sweet! Nice one, Yugi!
Good going!
Yugi!
This is reality.
No, this is hardly what I would call Leonhart's true ability.
It will do you no good to belittle him.
Leonhart... Do not betray my expectations.
I'm not done!
I'll also activate the Magic Card, Water of Life, from my hand!
Using this effect, I Special Summon one Monster in my Cemetery in face-up Attack Position!
The one I'll bring back is...
Iron Hans!
And along with Iron Hans comes another Iron Knight!
I Special Summon Iron Knight in Attack Mode!
Just when he put them in the Graveyard...
Give 'em a rest already, will you?
This is the scariest factor of Leon's deck.
The balance between his Monsters, Magics and Traps is flawless.
I guess it makes sense why he made it this far.
True...
I end my turn.
My turn! Draw!
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
Using this effect, I can draw two new cards from my deck.
Good. This is the first card I've drawn!
That card is...
When Watapon is added to your hand from your deck by the aid of a Magic Card,
it can be Special Summoned onto the field!
I Summon Watapon in Attack Mode!
Then I sacrifice Watapon...
Come on, Black Magician Girl!
Black Magician Girl...
I can't believe I'm seeing the one Yugi-san uses...!
I-I can't...
I can't fight her seriously...
Go on, Black Magician Girl!
Attack Iron Knight!
Black Burning!!
Turn end.
I always knew Black Magician Girl was amazing...
But even if I'm facing the Black Magician Girl I respect so much,
I'm going to defeat her!
That's it. Very good.
We will be the winners when all is said and done.
So, Leonhart, the time has come for you to show us your true abilities!
What are you plotting, Sieg?
My turn!
Draw!
Is this a coincidence...?
No... I guess this must be fate.
I activate Pot of Greed!
Using its effect, I draw two cards!
This card...!
Have you drawn it?!
Have you drawn it?
Brother!
You have done very well to have made it this far, Leonhart.
I believed in you.
That is my little brother, alright.
You are most certainly a Schroeder!
Yes, Brother!!
Your brother came to give you a congratulations present before you enter the final battle.
For me...?
Thank you, Brother!
I've never seen this card before.
It is an extremely rare card.
I got it just for you, Leonhart.
When you draw it, use the card without restraint.
I am certain that the Goddess of Victory will smile upon you.
Yes!
You have drawn it during the perfect scene.
Destiny must be guiding you, Leon.
Brother!
Leonhart, it is now time for you to use that card!
None of them will be able to obstruct our victory!
Here goes, Brother.
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Golden Castle of Stromberg activates!
What the heck's that card?
That's...!
Mm-hm...
Sieg...! You didn't..!
Golden Castle of Stromberg...
What kind of effects does it have?
Huh?
What's the matter?
I'm picking up some noise interference all of a sudden...
There's no abnormality in stability.
System check, complete.
Nothing abnormal.
Maybe you were just imagining it?
Maybe...
I activate the effects of Golden Castle of Stromberg!
I can Special Summon one Level Four or lower Monster from my deck.
I Summon Cinderella in Attack Mode!
When Cinderella is Summoned,
her Special Ability activates!
I can Special Summon Pumpkin Carriage from my hand or deck!
And then, an Equipment Magic!
I can equip Glass Slippers to Cinderella!
Be careful, Yugi!
That gave me a lot of trouble!
If Pumpkin Carriage is on the field, Cinderella can attack the player directly!
Go, Cinderella!
Direct Attack Yugi-san!
And when Cinderella attacks, Glass Slippers will be equipped onto the opponent's Monster!
A Monster equipped with the Glass Slippers will have their Attack Power slashed by 1000 points.
This is bad!
Dumbass! Yugi's not gonna be beaten that easily!
But what exactly is this Golden Castle of Stromberg card all about?
You bastard...
What a disgusting trick...!
So that's Golden Castle of Stromberg?
I never thought I would see that card here of all places!
Indeed.
What do you mean?
Grandpa, do you know something?
Could that be...?
Among the many cards Pegasus has created,
there are a small number of rare cards meant as prototypes, which are prized articles.
So that's one of them?
But why would a proto-type card be played here?
I heard that is was offered up as the prize for a contest about seven years ago.
Of course, being a prototype as it was, the card couldn't be used in your average Duels...
But that does not change the fact that is a very valuable card created by Pegasus.
It's one of the many legendary cards collectors would do anything to get their hands on.
For us to be able to see it for ourselves here...
So that would mean you used your power as a Schroeder to obtain it?
I would rather not hear that from you.
But a forbidden card like that would normally not respond to the Solid Vision.
You don't think...!
Yes... There is a limiter set on the Duel Computer that prevents the use of forbidden cards.
Hey...! Doesn't that mean he's cheating?!
So this was your true goal when you hacked the main computer, is that it?
Whatever do you mean?
I simply obtained a rare card and handed it to Leonhart.
But don't you think it is an appealing gesture?
A retired card once created by Pegasus is now about to place you in a bind.
Truly an ironic meeting of fate, wouldn't you say?
Humph. So you call it "fate"?
Nonsense.
If you believe fancy performances or cheap tricks will be enough to win this Duel, give up now.
Humph. I realize you intend to continue this Duel,
but you can still throw in the towel.
I never go back on what I say.
It will continue.
I do wonder how much longer you will say that?
Either way, you can no longer escape from the trap I have bound you in.
This is a forbidden card?
It can't... It's a card my brother gave me...
There is no need for you to pay it any worry, Leonhart!
The card has already appeared on the field!
That alone means it has been acknowledged as a legal card!
Now you must show us the true power of the card!
But...
Sieg...! You scum!
What a bastard!
You want to win that badly?!
Leon-kun...!
Leonhart! We must win by any means necessary!
Whatever we end up doing, all that matters is that we win in the end!
It's for the Schroeder family!
Our mother is sure to be ecstatic!
Even so...
Sieg!
Yugi-san?!
You've hurt not only Dueling itself, but the very souls of us Duelists!
You have no right to even call yourself a Duelist!
Yugi-san!
Duelist's soul, you say?
And just what will that get you?!
Dueling is meant as nothing more than a game!
Brother...!
Sieg...
Don't you understand?
All of the Duelists who have fought in this tournament...
And everyone out there rooting for us...
All of these people have gathered around us!
People from all over the world who love Dueling!
And even Leon, who's fighting for you with every ounce of his heart!
You've hurt the feelings of every single one of these people!
Playing hero now, are we?
How inexperienced you are.
Brother, do you really not believe in me?
That's why you did this?!
It is simply to cover all my bases and ensure your victory.
You have done more than enough to prove yourself to me.
Now you must continue the Duel, Leonhart.
I said I'd do anything if it meant helping you out, Brother...
But I don't want to use this thing!
Magic Card, activate!
Cyclone!
I use Cyclone to destroy
Golden Castle of Stromberg!
Good! Good one, Leon!
Now you can destroy that card!
He really is a True Duelist!
Why...?
It is truly unfortunate, Leonhart!
But you have no other choice than to obey me.
Golden Castle of Stromberg cannot be destroyed by Magic or Trap Cards!
Impossible!
That isn't in the card text...!
Does that mean that he altered the text's data...?
You lowly scum...!
Kaiba!
This is where my true method of revenge will begin.
Brother! Look!
What?!
Did you think bypassing the limiter's suppression on this card was the only thing I did?
Golden Castle of Stromberg is but the switch.
The very moment the card was Summoned onto the field...
...my virus program started.
Activate the Anti-Virus software this instant!
Sir!
You are too late!
All of Kaiba Corporation's programs operate at an intense, swift speed.
By the time this Duel concludes...
Kaiba, you will lose all of the Duel Monsters data you have collected!
You bastard!
Sieg!
I'm sorry... It looks like I can't...
...listen to what you say, Brother.
Leon!
I love Duel Monsters.
If I were to lose it, I'd...
With my own two hands...
That won't be of any use, Leonhart!
Even if you surrender, the virus that has infected the system will not be stopped!
No way!
However, there may be a way to stop its quickness.
And that is...
...to destroy Golden Castle of Stromberg in your Duel!
No way!
Magics and Traps won't work on the card!
So that pretty much means we can't stop the virus!
Brother...!
Leon, let's continue the Duel.
Yugi-san...?
But...
I caused all this trouble...
You're a True Duelist who loves Dueling from the bottom of his heart.
Even now, that hasn't changed.
That's why you can't give up.
Fighting with all you've got, show that man your pride as a Duelist!
And I'm going to break this trap he's woven!
Yugi-san...
Believe in me.
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
Golden Castle of Stromberg is the card Sieg gave to Leon.
I can't believe it launched a computer virus that infected the Duel System...!
The only way to stop the virus is to destroy that card,
but the data was rewritten so it can't be destroyed by any Magic or Trap Cards!
Is there really a way to do it, Yugi?!
Next time!
"Closing of the KC Grand Prix"
Duel standby!