With the Millennium Puzzle complete,
The young boy Yugi Mutou became a master of the Dark Games.
He was challenged by a person that has a Millennium Item like him,
the owner of the Millennium Eye, Pegasus, and went to the Duelist Kingdom.
To save the soul of Sugoroku, that was stolen by him.
Together with his friends and with his other self.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
Yugi!
Use your card to slit my throat!
Here I go, Kaiba!
Elf Swordsman!!
Yugi, you mustn't!
Yugi! Return to your usual self!
Yugi...! You...!
I'm scared...!
I'm scared!
Of this game and my other...!
"Duel of Tears!
Friendship"
Yugi...
Use your card to slit my throat!
Here I go, Kaiba!
Elf Swordsman!!
Stop it, Yugi!
It couldn't be helped... I had no other choice...
If I continued the Duel, Kaiba-kun....
But by doing this, I stood in my other self's way...
I became a burden...
Without the other me, I can't do anything...!
Without him....
It's all my fault...
If I hadn't stopped Yugi...
Yugi, take my Star Chips.
Jounouchi-kun...
It was because you gave me one of your Star Chips
that I got to play in the first place.
These belong to you, Yugi.
Jounouchi...
It's not time to give up yet.
In exchange, just do your best in the coming Duels!
Now Yugi. Take them.
Oi, Yugi!
Don't just sit there, at least say something!
Jounouchi!
Don't you care about gramps!?
I have to do something...!
If this keeps up...!
What are you all doing out here?
Mai-san!
Huh?
Jounouchi... You collected 10 Star Chips?
Ah... But it's about to be half that.
That can't be...!
Yugi!
Pegasus... I'm coming!
Beautiful!
The flame of anger around him is clearly visible.
This scene is beauty beyond description.
Yes...
I particularly love the hatred charging
point-blank at me.
Yugi lost?!
Don't screw around with me!
How can you be defeated without entering the castle?!
I won't accept that!
Mai-san!
If you do that, then you...
Who do you think I am?
16 Star Chips...!
Amazing... That's Mai Kujaku for you!
Not bad.
Of course I am.
I'm paying you back what I owe.
In return, you must battle me in the castle!
You're lucky, Yugi.
Just accept them!
Now you can enter the castle.
Looks like I overrated you!
Just because you lost one Duel, you lose your morale!
You're not so great after all!
That's not it...!
Yugi lost because I...
I know!
If you won't suck it up and enter
how about we have a Duel right now?
You'll agree to that much, won't you?
Now!
Wait!
Mai-san, I'll Duel with you!
If I win...
those Star Chips are mine!
Oi oi, how can you win?!
It's my responsibility to get Yugi into that castle no matter what!
Mai-san, fight me!
Ridiculous...
You really think you can defeat me?
I will surely win!
I have to win!
As long as Yugi gets those chips...
It's fine by me...
All right, I accept.
But I have a condition for this fight.
Condition?
If you lose, you will never again mutter a word
about comrades or friendship!
Understand?
It sorta...
The air feels tense...
Duel start!
I'll go first!
The air's filled with tension...
How should I say it.... the tension feels
different than other matches somehow...
My turn!
Petite Angel in Attack Mode!
That's so weak~
What the hell is that cute thing gonna do?!
My turn!
Harpie Lady in Attack Mode!
Also, I play this card on the Field.
Battle!
Hey, hey!
If you seriously want to beat me, play something with a higher Attack than that!
My turn.
Fairy's Treasure!
Attack Mode!
Amateurs really give one a headache...
It's not enough to just
increase your Attack Points!
This is...
Calm down.
Emissaries of Harmony's effect is...
A Trap Card that renders all damage
to the opponent's monsters 0 for one turn.
That may become useful later on...
Also...!
I set a card.
She got that in a Playing Pack didn't she?
It may help her win...
Battle!
Fairy Dust!
Her Attack is higher than the enemy...!
Why?
You're too naive.
Magic Card, Rose Whip activate!
This increases Harpie Lady's Attack by 300!
Here we go, Harpie Lady!
Red Hell Whipper!!
You'll defeat me?
Don't make me laugh!
She's good.
She taunted her opponent into attacking
only to spring a trap.
When the enemy thought she had
the advantage with the higher Attack...
she immediately activated her set card
to increase her Attack Points.
Didn't you say it was your fault Yugi lost?
That's what I hate the most about you!
Stop thinking so high of yourself!
I'm not thinking highly of myself!
Once the fight starts, every Duelist is alone.
You can't rely on other's power.
You can only trust yourself.
Yugi lost because he wasn't good enough!
There's no way!
If you only win because of your friends,
what's the point in it!?
If you really think you can make Yugi win this way
then it's the same as thinking high of yourself!
This is the next one.
I set one and end my turn!
Another set card?
What is it this time?
Friendship...
"Friendship"...
This is the proof of our friendship!
Right... My bond with everyone is more precious than anything else.
That's what makes a true "friendship".
I must protect this card no matter what!
You can do it, Anzu!
Don't you lose!
Yugi...
I've made up my mind.
I'll bet everything on this card!
I'll bet on our friendship!
Friendship! Attack Mode!
You still think this type of
monster can defeat me?!
Battle!
Harpie Lady!
Red Hell Whipper!!
Trap Card activate!
Emissaries of Harmony!
That Anzu's not doing too bad!
Yeah.
By the way, weren't you beaten by Anzu countless times?
Mind your own business!
Mai-san, I'll show you how I'll protect
this friendship until the very end!
This card represents our friendship.
No matter what you say,
I believe in my friends....
I believe in Yugi!
That's right... we've always stuck by each other....
And we finally made it this far.
That's why we can't press
on without one of our group!
No matter what that won't do!
Yugi.
Did you hear what Anzu just said?
She's serious!
In order to get you into the castle,
she's betting everything on this Duel!
Even seeing that, can you still just give it all up that easily?!
At least win the Duel before you spout nonsense.
I won't lose!
I will never lose!
Saint Magician!
Defense Mode!
Also, the Magic Card Silver Bow and Arrow
to increase Friendship's Attack
and Defense Points up by 300!
Too naive.
Magic Card...
Cyber Bondage!
This adds more armor to Harpy Lady...
...and raises her Attack Points up by 500!
Also, Undo Magic activate!
Not good...
As I thought, there's still a huge gap
in strength...
I'm not sure what you set...
but I'd better dispose of this one first.
Saint Magician is beaten!
Stop spacing out!
The Saint Magician was destroyed!
You get to return a Magic Card from the Graveyard!
At this level, it's a 100 years too soon for you to beat me.
I've said it before.
Foolish words like "comrade" and "friendship"
are the two words one must never say in this world!
That's not true at all!
Win or lose, the cruelties of the world still remain.
So as long as one exists in this cruel world
many use their friends to relieve the pain of life.
But in the end, all you can rely on is yourself!
When one is pushed into a corner during a Duel...
what is it they need more than anything to press on?
That is one's own strong will and determination!
Your own determination...?
A Duelist lacking this courage
will only end up betraying themselves
and their friend's expectations.
Even so, I still want to protect my friends!
I want to protect Yugi!
It's true in the end it's Yugi's decision whether he accepts them or not...
but I want to do more than just cheer all the time!
Therefore no matter what you say,
I will get Yugi into that castle!
Anzu...
No matter what happens...
I will protect Yugi until the end!
Because I'm his comrade....
and I'm his friend!
I won't lose!
I'll show you how I guard our friendship!
If you can, give it a try.
A Magic Card, Elf's Light...
It increases the Attack Points of a Light Attribute Monster by 400 points.
I also have an Undo Magic...
Mai-san used this same card
on her last turn.
That's it! That way Silver Bow and Arrow would
increase its Attack Points to 1600...
Also, with Elf's Light, its Attack will increase again to 2000...
And Undo Magic will get rid of Cyber Bondage!
My turn!
Magic Card, Silver Bow and Arrow!
It increases Friendship's Attack Points up by 300!
Following, I activate my
second Magic Card, Elf's Light!
This increases Friendship's
Attack Points again by 400!
Hm. Looks like the match is mine.
Battle!
Also...!
I'll use the Undo Magic card
to destroy Cyber Bondage!
Battle!
Friendship!
Silver Lightning Arrow!!
Harpie Lady is beaten!
Alright!
I wonder if she's stronger than you?!
-Alright.
-Shut up!
That's a Trap Card...
I lost.
Your heart was stronger.
But the match isn't...
Once I lose my Harpie, my Duel is over.
My pride won't allow me to fight on.
Alright!
You were amazing, Anzu!
You did it!
Mai-san...
Mai-san, that set card was
Harpie's Feather--
Stop joking around!
It wasn't thanks to you that I lost you know!
Let's settle the score inside the castle.
Mai-san...
Yugi!
Please use these to save your grandfather!
Anzu...
Yeah!
I'll try!
Yugi...!
To Duel with your own will and determination.
That's a Duelist.
Isn't that right, my other self?
I'll be cheering you on until the end!
Yeah! Thank you!
Sweet!
Our friendship conquers all!
Hey, how long are you gonna take?!
If you don't hurry you won't make it in time!
Ahh...
Okay, let's go!
YEAH!
Into the castle!
"Preview"
We finally made it to Pegasus' castle and the finals of the tournament!
But before that, it seems Kaiba-kun and Pegasus will be dueling in a special stadium.
In order to save his little brother, Mokuba-kun,
Kaiba-kun has to beat Pegasus.
But with Pegasus' power to see into people's minds...
He is not able to even use the Duel Disks!
Next episode: "Rescue Mokuba! Kaiba VS Pegasus"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship