The history of games can be traced back...
All the way to Ancient Egypt 5,000 years ago.
These ancient games decided the fate of the citizens and the kings.
They were called the Dark Games.
Now, the time where a boy has solved the Millennium Puzzle
and released the Dark Games has come.
A boy with both a heart of light and darkness.
People refer to him as Yuugiou: The Game King.
A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"The Illusionist
No Face's Trap"
How 'bout this, Anzu?
I use Gigantic Evil Spirit Rock Ogre to attack!
Alright, Happy Lover has 500 Defense Points.
And Ogre Rock has 800 Attack Points!
It's beaten!
It's my turn now.
Then I'll use this Magic Card.
Breath of God will handle this.
What's that?
Ogre Rock will be blown away by Breath of God.
And it'll be wiped out!
And now Jounouchi's Life Points are 0.
I win again!
Jounouchi sucks!
Yugi, why?
Tell me why can't I win.
Jounouchi-kun, let me see your Deck.
Right...
Here ya go.
Okay.
What is this?
They're all fighting-type Monsters!
Yeah, I'm collecting the strongest Monsters for a good battle force.
But that's not going to work!
In Duel Monsters, the important thing is using your Monster Cards and Magic Cards in combination.
Monsters alone won't cut it.
They'll be done in by the opponent's Magic Cards.
Yugi, please teach me how to play Duel Monsters!
"Duel Monsters National Championship, Grand Prize: ¥3,000,000"
Grandpa, I'm home!
Oh, welcome back.
Gramps, you feeling better now?
I'm doing better than ever!
So, you here to buy more cards?
Nope, I'm here today specially for Duel Monsters training.
But why are you so interested in this all of a sudden?
Eh? Well...
"Duel Monsters National Championship, Grand Prize: ¥3,000,000"
Don't tell me you're dreaming of entering the National Tournament and claiming the championship?
N-No way...
You want the ¥3,000,000 cash prize?
There's no way, Jounouchi-kun.
Please, Yugi!
I wanna win the tournament no matter what it takes!
But they'll start picking Duelists within a month.
He'll do fine if I, Sugoroku, teach him.
Huh?
You, Gramps?
Grandpa's a great Duelist, though he doesn't look like it!
What'dya mean "doesn't look like it"?
But, the special training will be tough!
Y-Yes...
Please do so...
First, I must fix that shitty habit of entering game tournaments for the sole purpose of cash prizes.
I must teach you the heart of the cards!
Do it once more!
All Duel Monsters fans from around the country!
All of you ten-million Duel Monsters fans,
it’s time to get the final match-up of this tournament underway!
Who will reign supreme over the 200 Duelists
picked through the nationwide regional preliminaries!?
Now, here come our contestants!
Representing East Japan,
Contestant Insector Haga! Age 14!
Representing West Japan,
Contestant Dinosaur Ryuzaki!
15 years old!
Shit, I should be the one fighting in there.
But you did your best.
You made it to the tournament's Best 8, right?
W-Well, I suppose!
You had some serious training this past month, haven't you?
Gramps, enough is enough already!
It's not enough!
Jounouchi, you aren't good enough to start entering tournaments yet!
Yeah, but by "Best 8", doesn't she mean in your own neighborhood?
I can't show my shameful face in front of Gramps...
Show me what now?
Gramps, I'm sorry!
You did a good job.
Though I knew you hadn't a chance in hell to win this tournament,
you still did your best.
Gr-Gramps...!
By the way, Yugi.
You got a package here.
A package?
From who?
There's no sender written on it...
I wonder what's in it.
But why didn't you enter the tournament, Yugi?
If you entered, you may have won the tournament!
I decided that I won't enter any tournament unless its with a certain person.
You mean Kaiba-kun?
Yup.
I want to fight Kaiba-kun again fair and square once he understands the heart of the cards.
I can't trust that guy.
Looks like it's starting!
Yugi, who do you think will win?
Insector Haga is good at using his Insect Cards with his Armor Cards in a Combo Attack.
And then there's Dinosaur Ryuzaki from west Japan.
He uses his Dinosaur cards to attack his opponents with megaton power!
Well, it's pretty obvious the guy with Dinosaur cards is gonna win.
The winner'll be Ryuzaki, without a doubt.
No, I wouldn't bet on that.
This round'll decide the winner.
Dinosaur Ryuzaki plays the strongest Dinosaur card Two-Headed King Rex!
How's that?
This is my card.
On the other side, Insector Haga plays another low-level Insect, Basic Insect.
What's the deal with that weak-looking Monster?
Ryuzaki's gonna win for sure.
No, Insector Haga is leading him into a trap!
He's mine!
King Rex, attack!
You said "attack" just now, didn't you?
That attack was the switch for my Trap Card!
Messiah Antlion's Pit activates!
What'd ya say?
A Trap Card?
King Rex will now be trapped in the hellish vortex, unable to move!
King Rex!
And it's now my turn.
And then I Equip Basic Insect with the Magic Card
Firearm-equipped Insect Armor Level Five!
Attack!
King Rex was annihilated.
I lost...
This very moment, Contestant Insector Haga has won the championship!
I can't believe Insector Haga won...
And here to hand the Memorial Trophy to the championship winner,
Contestant Insector Haga, is a very special guest!
Our presenter is the proud president of Industrial Illusions,
as well as the genius game designer who created Duel Monsters,
Mr. Pegasus J. Crawford!
Congratulations.
Th-Thank you...
I would like to invite you to participate in an event
soon to be held by our company, with no limitations.
Master Pegasus, we are guaranteed to bring many talented Duelists
to our event because of the announcement just now.
No, not a single Duelist in that tournament interests me in the least.
And the thing I asked of you?
I mailed it just as you ordered.
Is that so?
Yugi, I'm dying to know what's in that package.
Oh yeah!
What could it be?
What's all this?
Maybe the video tape explains it?
On the video tape?
Try playing it.
Right...
Hello.
Nice to meet you, Yugi boy.
He's...!
He was just on TV!
He's the creator of Duel Monsters.
Pegasus J. Crawford.
This is a video letter for my dearest Yugi boy.
I am aware that you defeated Kaiba boy.
So I would like to test your playing strength.
But there will be a time limit in this Duel.
The Life Points will total 2000.
After 15 minutes have passed on the time counter, the side with the highest Life Points will win.
Sound good?
He wants to fight against a live person on a video tape?!
That's not possible!
Grandpa!
Jounouchi-kun!
Honda-kun!
Anzu!
No one can get in the way now.
Shall we begin...
Yugi boy?
Is this a Dark Game?
In that case, I'll be your opponent.
The Duel starts, now!
I shall take the first turn.
Over.
Your turn, Yugi.
Alright, I use this card.
The Devil Dragon card, am I right?
What?
I already knew that you would play this card.
The Trap Card, Dragon-type Sealing Jar.
Devil Dragon will be sealed within the jar.
Now, let's continue the game.
Why did he have this card on the field when I hadn't even played a Dragon-type card yet?
In the last game you played, you defeated Kaiba boy's Super-Rare Card.
Even Blue-Eyes White Dragon is powerless before this card.
Blue-Eyes White Dragon is?
This game is evolving every day.
Then I'll use this card to fight you!
The Beast-type card, Silver Fang.
I already knew that you would play a Beast-type card.
And that you would use the Magic Card Full Moon to power Silver Fang up.
This card is more than enough to handle Silver Fang.
Jar Genie has really weak Attack Points.
But it's the only card that can open the seal on the Dragon-types.
You're going to release my Devil Dragon and use it against me?!
Yes!
The Jar Genie will now revive Devil Dragon, and give it new life!
My Devil Dragon!
Wow! Wouldn't you call something like this "omotsubo,
or jarring into someone's plans in Japanese?
A joke!
It's a joke, okay!
Yugi boy, you must be really shocked.
But this is reality.
You cannot defeat me.
If you are to lose, you will have to participate in my upcoming event.
What?
It is meant to determine who is the real King of Duelists in the game of Duel Monsters.
King of Duelists?
That's right!
The winner will receive the title of "King", along with a cash prize and great fortune!
Such an event doesn't interest me.
What if I were to decline?
No no!
You don't have the privilege to decline.
The very fact that you cannot defeat me ensures the fact that you shall not escape me.
I haven't lost yet.
Okay, then let us continue the game.
My turn is over.
Now Yugi boy, it's your turn.
There has to be a reason Pegasus knows my hand.
But what is it?
I'll play the Undead Warrior as the next card.
Wait, I'm supposed to decide the cards I use on my own.
But if I'm being controlled with magic somehow...
And if his "magic" was like some kind of hypnosis...
Then that's the same thing as him being able to see my hand!
I discovered the secret of his so-called "magic".
Now, Yugi boy, it's your turn!
If I use a card from my hand, I'll be under the influence of his "magic"...
I believe in my Deck!
I will bet everything on them!
You have no way of attacking me.
Your card should be the Undead Warrior.
Trap activate!
Sun Shower!
All Undead Zombie-type Monsters will be illuminated by the sunlight!
I knew it.
Your "magic" has come to an end.
Though you know the cards in my hand with this little trick of yours,
you have no idea what the cards I draw from my Deck are.
My card is...
Black Magician!
No!
It is not an Undead Zombie-type!
First of all, Black Magician will attack Devil Dragon!
And why did you not attack the Jar Genie?
I'll destroy a card of my own with a card of my own.
If I fall into the enemy's hands, it's a bit sad.
And that over thinking of yours just cost you your life.
Black Magic!!
Okay!
Because you discovered the secret to my power, you pass this test!
But you underestimate the extent of that power!
What?
It's my turn.
Unbelievable!
The Illusionist No Face card!
That's a rare card I've just seen for the first time.
But among the Spellcasters, Black Magician should be the strongest.
I use the Magic Card Eye of Fascination
with Illusionist No Face in a Combo Attack against Black Magician.
I'll take you on!
Black Magician!
Black Magic!!
Illusion-Spell Technique: Eye of Fascination!
Who won?
A draw?
If it was a draw, both should have been destroyed!
Could this be an effect of the Eye of Fascination?
There's just 5 minutes left on the video counter.
If I battle him once more, I can still win so long as I have more Life Points.
But that's the path of a coward.
I'll fight until the last moment!
I have to take Pegasus's Life Points down to 0!
That's true victory!
I use Elf Swordsman to attack No Face!
During this brutal battle, Elf Swordsman wins with its higher Attack Points!
Do you believe that's true?
Eye of Fascination doesn't raise the Attack Points of Illusionist No Face at all!
What?
Why's Elf Swordsman...?
You...
Black Magician!
Dammit!
Black Magician is being controlled by the Eye of Fascination this turn!
Pegasus is really able to read my mind...!
Now once I end my turn, it'll be time up!
Nice fight, Yugi boy!
The game's not over yet!
My last card...
Is of the Fiend-types, Demon's Summon!
Battle!
Game over.
Oh, so close!
Had the battle just now succeeded, I would have lost!
Yugi boy, you hold far greater skill than I originally anticipated.
I have a strong feeling we will be fighting again soon in Duelist Kingdom.
What if I don't want to?
You are unable to escape me.
My power is the Shadow Power of the Millennium Eye.
Millennium Eye?
I'll see you again at the Kingdom.
If you want back your most valuable treasure.
Yugi...!
Yugi!
Grandpa!
Grandpa!!
Grandpa!!!
To get back grandpa's stolen soul from Pegasus...
Yugi must participate in Duelist Kingdom.
Hold on a minute!
We can't just let Yugi go alone!
But Jounouchi, you can't participate in the tournament since you didn't receive an invitation!
Huh? For your little sister?
On a ship filled with countless events, Yugi is lead into a trap!
Next time!
The Lost Exodia
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship