Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Bakura!
I'm going to destroy your Occult Combo!
The Magic Card Resurrection of the Dead!
Dark Necrofear revives!
Now that Dark Necrofear has been brought back from the dead,
the Effect of Dark Sanctuary disappears!
Shit...!
"D-E-A-T..."
You've gathered four letters of the word "death".
But you'll never get to play the last letter!
Card draw!
That's far enough, Yugi!
So long as I have this card, you can't stop my Occult Combo!
What?!
"Smash the Darkness - God Attacks!"
Too bad for you, Yugi!
I praise you for pushing me this far into a corner...
..but your defiance will now come to an end!
Prepare yourself!
Summon Jowgen the Spiritualist!
Jowgen the Spiritualist?!
Jowgen?
What the heck does that do?
What the heck? You don't know?
So you know?!
Hell if I know!
I'm not a Duelist!
Due to this Monster's Effect, I discard one card from my hand,
and I can then destroy all Special Summoned Monsters on the field!
Then that means...!
Right!
He can destroy Yugi's Dark Necrofear
because he Special Summoned it with Resurrection of the Dead!
But if he destroys Dark Necrofear, the Dark Sanctuary...!
I'll send this to the Graveyard!
Jowgen the Spiritualist!
Target all Special Summoned Monsters on the field...
Destroy Dark Necrofear!
So Dark Necrofear will once again return to Bakura's Graveyard!
That's right, Yugi!
Now that Dark Necrofear is once again buried on my side,
the Effect of the Field Magic Dark Sanctuary will return!
So I can now play up to 10 Magic and Trap Cards again!
This weird Field came back again!
Idiot! Now isn't the time to be getting scared!
If this keeps up, Yugi is certain to lose in one turn!
Yugi-san!
Yugi!
No! I'll believe in Yugi 'till the end!
Big brother!
One turn is more than enough!
Yugi will win!
He's won and gotten this far already!
There's no way to stop my Occult Combo!
Next turn, the final letter of the message of death will be gathered!
Die with the declaration of "death"!
I sacrifice Jowgen to meet the requirements of Dark Sanctuary!
I set one reverse card and end my turn!
Let me tell you this, Yugi...
You can't see it...
...but the Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary has once again returned to roaming your field!
What?!
I only have one turn left!
Thanks to the Effect of The Dark Door, I can only attack with one Monster!
But one of my Monsters has been possessed by the Onryou?!
That's not all!
My reverse card is another Dark Spirit of the Silent!
Dark Spirit of the Silent?!
That's right!
In other words, no matter which Monster you pick,
thanks to Dark Spirit of the Silent,
the Onryou will automatically change your attack order to the possessed Monster!
This truly is the final turn!
On the End Phase of this turn,
all the letters on the Ouija Board will be gathered and I'll lose.
But I don't have any card in my hand that can turn this around...
So you finally understand, Yugi?
You have a literal 0 percent chance of victory!
It's true that Yugi-kun has no chance of winning this turn!
Otogi! You're still saying that?!
Honda!
I understand how you feel,
but unfortunately he's right.
Bakura's combo is perfect.
And Yugi knows that more than any of us.
Is that true, big brother?
I believe in Yugi!
Jounouchi!
I said I'd believe in him, and I believe!
A True Duelist never gives up hope until the very last moment of the end!
I suppose that's true...
It's true that Yugi's not the type of man to give up that easily.
Yugi! Go for it!
Don't you dare lose, Yugi!
Yugi-kun!
Yugi-san!
We'll see, won't we?
It's futile!
Even if you all cheer him on until you run out of breath,
Yugi's got no chance of defeating me!
No...
I still have one card that can make the impossible possible.
Only one...
Everything depends on the next card I draw!
Go for it, other me!
Partner!
We can't lose before we recover your memories!
We've got to do whatever we can!
We've got to draw it!
Yeah! You're right.
The card you put in my deck!
Call God, Yugi!
I bet everything I have as a Duelist on this draw!
Card draw!!
I sacrifice Black Magician Girl...
...Magnet Warrior Gamma...
...and Big Shield Gardna, totaling three offerings!
The advent of... Osiris!
Osiris?!
Just as I was about to complete the Ouija Board's lethal combo this turn...
he managed to take the only chance he had and Summon the legendary dragon?!
Wh-What...?
A-Amazing!
That's... Osiris?
Yugi's God Cards...!
Drawing a God Card on his last turn...
I knew it, Yugi...
You are the only one rivaling the title of the ultimate Duelist!
The God Card...
The servants of the Pharaoh that carry out his every bidding...
At the end of Battle City...
...the one who gathers the three God Cards...
...will earn the title of Pharaoh!
And when this trial has been overcome...
...the Pharaoh's lost memories will be restored.
My memories are locked in darkness...
And I must fight in order to cast light on them!
Brace yourself, Bakura!
Having Osiris Summoned on you...
Things aren't looking so good, are they, "Bakura"?
Malik!
Osiris' Attack Points are determined by the number of cards in the player's hand.
Yugi currently has three cards in his hand...
Therefore Osiris has 3000 Attack Points.
3000 Attack Points...
But you only have 1200 Life Points left...
So if Osiris attacks you, you're finished, "Bakura"!
Not yet!
The Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary still wanders the field!
Go, Hateful Spirit of Dark Sanctuary!
Possess God!
What?!
The Onryou was dispelled?!
It's useless!
A low-level Monster like the Onryou doesn't have the power to possess God!
The Onryou won't work...?!
So, my hand...
I don't even have one!
I don't have a Wall Monster on the field!
If only I could use my Dark Spirit of the Silent reverse card...!
But I can't use it on his Monster, Osiris...!
Since there's no other Monster to change his attack order to...
I can't use this Trap!
I no longer... have a strategy...
I win this Duel, Bakura!
Woo-hoo!
Go, Yugi!
Turn Bakura back to normal with a shot from God!
Here I go, Bakura!
It's over...
What now...?
I've still got one trick left up my sleeve.
What?!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon, attack!
Thunder-
He's...!
Malik! What the hell are you doing here?!
Jounouchi-kun!
Calm down, Jounouchi!
Let me go!
Interrupting other people's Duels...!
There's no way I'll forgive you!
Malik...!
You bastard!
Listen carefully, Yugi...
That boy is being controlled by my Millennium Rod, having now been turned into my puppet.
What?!
What do you mean?
Bakura's already being controlled by his Dark personality!
Correct.
That boy is being controlled by two people.
I'll show you proof...
I'll release his real personality this very moment.
What?!
What are you thinking, bastard?
If you plan to beat Yugi, you'd better do as I say and release him.
What'd you say?
Hurry it up!
Don't you want to win?
I-It hurts...!
It hurts!
Bakura!
Bakura-kun!
Yugi-kun!
Where am I?!
Why am I here?!
Why do I have this wound...?!
Bakura...!
As you can see, that boy is badly wounded...
Yugi, it's true an attack from God will grant your victory,
but the damage from the shock could very well take the boy's life.
What?!
Are you willing to do that?
You're using Bakura's life as a shield, Malik?!
That's low, Malik!
Bakura! Pull yourself together!
Yugi!
That's good enough, Rishid.
Lord Malik...
The pain I am feeling in my heart is not from this cold wind whipping past me...
It hurts... Yugi-kun...!
Bakura!
Wait, Yugi Mutou!
It is strictly forbidden for players to have contact with their opponents!
If you leave your Dueling platform, you admit your defeat!
If I attack Bakura, this Duel is over!
But, Bakura will...
Hurry up and stop this Duel!
If we don't hurry and get Bakura some help, he could seriously die up there!
Yugi...
If you hesitate to attack on this last turn...
All the letters of the Ouija Board will be gathered on your End Phase,
and you'll lose!
Now continue the Duel, Yugi Mutou!
Yugi-kun...!
The Bakura in front of me right now doesn't have enough
mental strength to withstand God's attack!
What's the matter?
Why did you stop your attack?!
Finish him off already, Yugi!
Yugi Mutou, if you do not attack the player, you automatically forfeit the Duel!
You have 20 more seconds!
Hey dude!
Stop this already or he's gonna die!
This ain't a joke ya know!
Calm yourself!!
Otherwise I'll disqualify you!
What?! Disqualify me?!
Well, fine!
If you're gonna do it, let's see ya do it!
-Then afterwards I'm gonna...
-Calm down, Jounouchi-kun!
Now continue the Duel!
Do it, Yugi!
Other me...
So I see, Malik...
You've tied Yugi's hands now.
As per our agreement.
I'm impressed, Malik...
Your dirty tricks surpass even my Occult Deck.
But still...
Even I have ways I like to win and ways I hate to win!
Stay out of this, Malik!
What?!
Bakura's body is back in the control of his dark personality!
Yugi, I'll humbly admit my defeat this time!
Attack me!
What?!
What? Your little friend Bakura won't die, so don't worry!
This host is very important to me!
I can't allow him to be killed off!
So come at me, Yugi!
Then here I go!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Direct Attack!
Yugi...
I swear to bury you in eternal darkness someday!
I'LL BE THE ONE TO GAIN THE POWER OF DARKNESS IN THE END!
And the winner is Yugi Mutou!
The first round of the tournament is over!
Bakura!
Enough already!
Just lower the Duel Ring already!
Hang in there, Bakura!
Bakura!
Yugi-kun...
He's all right! He's conscious!
His arm is bleeding badly!
He needs to be treated right away!
Right, then let's just hurry and get him to his room.
Yeah!
Alright Bakura, I'll carry you on my back.
Here. Hang tight, Bakura.
Are you alright, Bakura-kun?
The dark spirit residing within the Millennium Ring...
He sacrificed himself to save the life of his host, Bakura...
Perhaps that's the fate of the souls residing within the Millennium Items.
Even if that item is possessed by an evil being...
In terms of protecting its other self...
I'm no different than him.
I think it's a little different, other me.
Partner...
I know what you mean about protecting me...
And I know that the Millennium Ring's dark personality and Bakura-kun
are two minds in one body, like us...
But...
I want to help you too!
Ever since I solved the Millennium Puzzle and met you,
I've wanted to become stronger!
For myself, and...
...for you!
Partner!
But right now, the only thing I can do is switch my mind with yours.
You must be exhausted from your Duel with Bakura-kun.
So get some rest!
Yes!
I'll do that, partner!
High five!
Hold on!
According to the Ante Rule, first round winner Yugi Mutou
is permitted to take one card from Ryo Bakura's deck!
I don't want it!
Bakura-kun's got bigger problems to worry about!
So Yugi won the first round of the tournament just like we thought, right big brother?
Of course he did.
The only person who can beat him is a Duelist chosen by the gods, just as he was.
Just you wait, Yugi...
I will defeat you in the finals!
We did the best we could for now,
but he should get some good rest for the time being.
Yes...
Even though Yugi won the first round of the tournament,
it just doesn't feel good.
The other me really could have lost this time.
Eh?
On the last turn when Bakura-kun turned back to his good self,
the other me couldn't attack.
If Bakura-kun hadn't switched minds again,
we'd have forfeited the attack and lost.
So you're saying the Millennium Ring's personality let you win?
I think he thought the other me was going to attack.
So he switched places with his host, Bakura-kun, to keep him from being hit by the attack.
Then why expose Bakura's real personality in the first place?
No, it wasn't Bakura-kun's other personality that exposed him.
It was Malik!
So Malik used his Millennium Item to take over his mind again?
That's right.
Malik used Bakura-kun as a shield so he could win.
But then the evil spirit residing within Bakura-kun took over again.
It was actually Malik who knew what the other me was thinking.
Damn that Malik!
I swear I'm gonna beat his ass!
Hey, don't push yourself too much brother!
Yugi, wouldn't it be better for us to land and drop Bakura off at a hospital?
Yup!
You're right!
Let's go ask Kaiba-kun!
Alright! Let's all go together!
I'll say here and keep an eye on Bakura-kun.
Oh yeah, good point.
We'll leave him to you, Anzu.
Huh?
What's wrong, Yugi?
Let's get moving.
It's gone.
Gone...? What is?
The Millennium Ring!
Bakura-kun's Millennium Ring went missing after he was hit by the attack.
God... You can't take your eyes off that ring for a second.
Alright, we'll search for that thing later.
But let's go talk to Kaiba first.
Right!
You're right!
"Preview"
Bakura-kun has fallen to Yugi!
But Kaiba-kun won't land the Battle Ship!
While searching for the Millennium Ring, Honda-kun and Otogi-kun see a ghost!
And then Shadi appears before Yugi one more time!
And what's this secret about the birth of Duel Monsters and the God Cards...?
Next time!
"Hidden Power: The Purpose of the God Cards"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise