Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
So you really are dead, Noah?
Even if you are nothing more than electrical signals running through a computer network,
no matter who it is challenging me to a match,
I'll crush anyone who stands before me, no matter how many times, and press onward!
It'll take more than your "Duel of the Creation of Heaven and Earth" to frighten me!
Very well, Noah.
I accept this Duel!
"The Invincible Deck Master: Ark of Miracles"
Look at that, Yugi!
They're...
All the Monsters in the Graveyard are being drawn into the ark!
What's going on...?
One of my Deck Master's, Miracle of Ark's, Holy Abilities has just been activated.
Holy Abilities...?
Every single card in both of our Graveyards will now be removed from play and stored in the Ark of Miracles.
Seto, now even your Vampire Lord's Immortal Ability won't be able to activate.
Seto, keep both of your eyes wide open.
These are the seven turns of the creation of Heaven and Earth!
Seven turns of the
creation of Heaven and Earth?
Will something happen on the seventh turn?
And what is so funny exactly?
Trying to shake me with wondering what will happen on the "seventh turn of creation" won't work.
Giant Flood is a card that destroys all Monster Cards on both players' fields and in their respective hands and Graveyards.
And because of that effect, your field is empty!
Both sides have no
Monsters in their hands...
This gives me the upper hand if I can Summon a Monster Card before he does.
My turn!
Draw!
As I thought, the Goddess of Victory smiles on me alone!
Come forth, Spear Dragon!
Direct Attack Noah!
You sure underestimate me.
Do you really believe
that attack will get through?
What...?
I activate the second Ability of my Deck Master, Ark of Miracles.
Come forth, being chosen by the ark!
Vampire Lord...!
The second Ability of the Ark of Miracles...
It's called Absolute Protection!
When my opponent holds more Monsters than I at the start of their Battle Phase, I can call out a Monster at random in Defense Mode.
Spear Dragon inflicts damage to the opponent equally the difference in their Attack and Defense Points.
At least he was able to scratch Noah's Life a bit...
So no matter how many Monsters Kaiba has out on the field, he'll always have something to protect him.
He's really totally untouchable!
It's the second turn of creation!
The ark...!
What's about to happen?
Look! The water...!
The water's evaporating!
The scenery is changing!
Into something really strange, OOH!
Following that, the Earth entered the age of the dinosaurs.
I Summon Giant Rex!
Giant Rex, attack!
Spear Dragon is a card that automatically changes into Defense Position after attacking.
Thanks to that Effect, your Life Points remain unchanged, Seto.
Seto, I said this right from the beginning, didn't I?
That my very existence is superior to you in every way.
Since I lost my flesh-and-blood body, my conscious has lived in inside of this super computer.
Inside of the computer...?
So Noah is really dead, right...?
No, I have been resurrected from the abyss of the dead...
...as a being that exceeds
any one of your imaginations.
I didn't know how to
deal with it in the beginning.
But I soon became surprised at how comfortable it was.
It wasn't boring in the least.
That's because there's a hoard of information from the Human World stored within this realm.
No matter how thick a book...
No matter how complicated a set of data that would take an ordinary human several hours to absorb may be...
My computer-like brain can register it in a matter of seconds.
And because of that, I have learned everything there is to know about the Human World.
I've learned about everything dating back to when the universe was first born all the way to present world history.
I know all the details.
There is no human brain in existence that knows as much as I.
Seto, there is a huge difference
between your brain and mine.
You were nothing more than a test given to me by Father so that I would become equal to that of a king.
Did Noah say Kaiba was a test?
What's so funny?!
Creation of Heaven and Earth...
The age of mankind...
I've heard about as
much as I can take from you.
What was that?!
Whatever happened to you in your past has nothing to do with me.
But regardless of what you think you are, you're about as human as you can get.
Because all that ridiculous self-praising and arrogance is nothing more than an excuse to seal away your heart from the world.
And that is what any foolish human being who is too absorbed in themselves would try and do!
You think you can shake me with such childish insults?
Then answer this...
If Gozaburo really intended for you to inherit Kaiba Corporation,
why didn't he just give it to you and let you compete against me openly?
Why didn't he choose direct methods?!
Well...
I'm sure you feel it as well.
It's because Gozaburo couldn't trust his future into someone like you, a trapped being inside an AI Computer!
I was certain that I was hit by a car...
I get it! That was all a dream!
Father!
Why...?
Father! Father!!
What is...?
Father!
Father! Please let me out of here!
Why not, Father?
Please! Let me out of here!
Noah, listen to me carefully.
You aren't able to leave that place.
Your body... is dead.
No way...!
But your spirit is still very well alive.
I may not be able to touch you with my hands, but the fact that you are my son will not change.
I'm... dead...!
That's a gift from me.
It's cute, isn't it?
Father gradually expanded the world I lived in.
He added the data of places I wanted to travel one after the other.
Good morning, Noah-sama.
Why hello there, Noah-sama.
Hey!
But this world is so delicate...
Welcome, Noah-sama.
What can I get you?
It sure is a nice day today!
Welcome, Noah-sama.
What can I get you?
Something was wrong.
Shut up!
Get lost!!
Noah...
Do you like the birthday present
that I gave it to you?
Yes
I never thought I'd get to travel into space!
I wanna show you how blue the Earth is-
Oh yeah, you saw the data when you uploaded it for me, so you saw exactly what I saw.
Noah, where is Sunny?
I made a few modifications to him/ Now he's really rabid.
Modifications?
What's that?
It's a muzzle that locks up his face so he doesn't bite anyone again.
The one you had before was no good.
The program was too simple.
I had to remake him from scratch.
Father.
I made a simulation of something interesting not too long ago.
I calculated that if we used the entire financial resources and weaponry of Kaiba Corporation,
we could destroy the entire world in just 30 days.
I bet you didn't know that!
Huh... But how many people would survive after this plan of yours was commenced?
About 3%, more or less.
Don't you think that's a bit too little?
I don't really care.
It has nothing to do with me, after all.
I have already surpassed the level of human thinking.
I've started to see a much larger perspective of Kaiba Corporation now!
It does intrigue me.
But I'll listen to it some other day.
It wasn't long after that you entered the Kaiba family.
Despite how much information I had to offer,
Father began to
stop coming to visit me altogether.
That goes to show that even someone like Gozaburo has some sense of human conscious.
All you can see is this invented world.
But human society exists in chaos.
The world is weaved by both light and darkness.
And the feelings of those who struggle for the strength to live...
Only someone who has lived in the world would be able to comprehend those feelings.
Gozaburo probably started to become confused.
It was then after that he came up with the idea of having you compete with a real flesh-and-blood human being - me.
If you could win a competition against a real human being,
he would have been able to accept you and all of your knowledge.
He must have thought like that.
How pathetic.
You've lost every important aspect a human being needs while living in that cold world!
Seto, you are mistaken.
I haven't lost my feelings as a human being.
I have surpassed them!
It's all a part of walking down
the path of a creator!
So you're a "creator" just because you invented this world?
That really makes me laugh!
Then allow me to prove once and for all that I am now the creator of mankind.
I shall make a prediction in the name of "creator".
In the third turn of creation,
an event will occur that will shock the very core of your existence!
Shock the... very core of my existence?
My turn will end there.
Big brother...
Here I come, Noah!
My turn!
I activate a Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
Its Effect allows me to draw two more cards from my deck!
I then activate
Kaiser Sea Horse's Deck Master Ability!
He allows me to Summon a Light-Attribute Monster without the need of a sacrifice!
As such, I can Summon the Level 5 Twilight Zone Dragon without a tribute!
I also place three set cards!
And that will end my turn!
This ain't good! Noah's Giant Rex has 2000 Attack Points.
Kaiba's Monster will be destroyed next turn!
If he tries to Summon another Monster,
it's done for!
This is Kaiba-kun we're talking about.
At least one of those Set Cards must be intended to cancel a battle.
My turn. Draw.
Seems you were never qualified to be my opponent.
It looks like the result of this match will be decided this turn.
I activate the Magic Card known as Deepest Impact!
Th-The sky...
This is bad, OOH-AH!
Watch carefully.
The sun was swallowed in a cloud of residue, as per the result of a large meteor shower that bombarded the Earth.
As a result, mankind welcomed the Ice Age.
Noah's Monster...
What's with this dude?
His own Monster was destroyed thanks to his Trap Card.
Deepest Impact destroys
every Monster on the field,
and the Life of both players is halved.
He's... not going to attack my Monster?
I then activate the Ice Age Panic Magic Card.
This card can be activated when I have no Monsters on the field.
It lets me Special Summon an Earth-Attribute Monster to the field!
I'll Summon Last of Tusk Mammoth!
This isn't good, Kaiba!
Now! Twilight Zone Dragon, come back to the field!
Twilight Zone Dragon holds an Effect that gives him the ability to travel through dimensions.
Thus, the Magic Card you used before didn't work on it!
It can't be destroyed in battle, either.
I read through your plan to use that slaughtering Magic Card right from the start!
Now your attack...
Don't mind it!
Go! Last of Tusk Mammoth, attack Twilight Zone Dragon!
Is he seriously gonna attack a Monster with higher Defense Points, OOH~!?
I knew the Ability of the Twilight Zone Dragon from the beginning.
And of course, I'm certain you're aware of Last of Tusk Mammoth's Ability, right?
Oh yeah!
Last of Tusk Mammoth's Effect
takes the damage it receives and shifts it to the opponent!
Noah's taking 700 points of damage!
Kaiba-kun only has 700 Life Points!
That means Kaiba-kun...!
Trap Card! Destruction Ring!
Destruction Ring destroys our Monsters
and both sides take the damage to their Life.
You'll only be blowing yourself up with this trick.
I then activate the Instant Quick-Summon Magic Card, Defense Ring!
Smart!
That's Kaiba for you!
He turned the situation against his enemy!
What's wrong, Noah?
Aren't you superior to me?
Just one more attack will determine the result.
But Noah's Monster Barrier hasn't been broken yet.
It's my turn.
Noah, I'll settle things on this turn!
I anticipate it!
I switch Twilight Zone Dragon from Defense Mode to Attack Mode!
I'll then eliminate Thunder Dragon from my hand.
I activate Thunder Dragon's Effect!
I ca add two more of the card from my deck into my hand!
Fusion Summon!
Come forth, Twin-Headed Thunder Dragon!
2800 Attack Points!
I'll then activate the Magic Card, Quick Attack!
Due to its effect, a Fusion Monster
can attack on the turn it is Summoned.
No matter how many times you increase the number of Monsters you hold, it's all futile.
Come out, chosen beings!
Noah's Monsters appeared again!
Still can't?
Our result was decided just now, Noah.
It's true that your Deck Master is the strongest and is invincible.
But my Dueling intellect far surpasses yours!
This is the last trap I set for you!
Activate now, Dragon's Imperial Wrath!
Thanks to Dragon's Imperial Wrath's effect,
when I attack a Defense Monster with less Defense Points than my Monster's Attack Power,
the opponent receives the difference in value as direct damage.
Go, Twilight Zone Dragon!
Attack Giant Rex!
Great!
Another monster down and Kaiba will be the winner!
Out of my sight, Noah!
Twin-Headed Thunder Dragon, attack Giant Soldier of-
Stop!!
Mokuba...
Mokuba-kun!
I won't forgive anyone who dares to hurt my big brother.
Mokuba, you...
What is he saying?
Yes! Save me, Mokuba!
He's the one bullying me here! He's our enemy!
Enemy?
You bastard...!
Because of that fact that you had the misfortune of having your little brother's memory sealed away by me,
Mokuba now thinks of me as his brother.
Mokuba protects me of his free will.
Because, you know, Mokuba is my little brother and all.
Now Seto.
You can defeat me with one more attack.
Everything rides on your shoulders right now.
Blow me away along with Mokuba!
I'm certain I predicted this earlier.
That something would happen this turn that would shock the very core of your existence.
So Noah anticipated
that he would make it this far...?
Now hurry up and attack me, Seto!
Mokuba-kun blocks Kaiba-kun's path in order to protect Noah!
Is this Noah's prediction?
It's a good chance to beat Noah,
But it is impossible for Kaiba-kun
to attack Mokuba-kun.
Noah attacks Kaiba-kun over and over!
Be patient!
Kaiba-kun!
There has to be a way to recall Mokuba-kun's memories!
Next time!
"Save Mokuba! The Fateful Seventh Turn"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise