Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
In this Duel...
...the only way to save both Mai and me....
...is for me to bet everything on this draw!
What was the image just now?
Are you saying that I'm the last person to be chosen by the Nameless Dragons?
I sense limitless possibility hidden in this card...!
I'm counting on you!
Please lend me your power, Claw of Hermos!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The Miracle of Hermos"
Hermos! Please lend me your strength!
Could that be...!
It's the same as what Yugi has!
That's right.
Jounouchi-kun was chosen as a True Duelist by the Legendary Dragons.
It can't be... Jounouchi got the power of the Legendary Dragons, too?!
Maybe we underestimated this guy too much...
This means he's a stronger Duelist than we thought.
"Claw of Hermos"?!
I never heard a' that card before.
Could that be one of the rare cards he got from Pegasus!?
What?!
Only him?!
That's total favoritism~!
If I don't hurry...!
Yugi-kun and the others will....!
Yes!
The power hasn't been cut!
I should be able to undo the locks using this!
That card....
I can feel a strong power coming from it...!
What exactly...?
I activate a Magic Card from my hand!
Resurrection of the Dead!
I'll revive Magical Gigacyber!
That's useless!
You should know that Gigacyber, with only 2200 Attack Points,
stands no chance against my Harpy's Pet Dragon!
No! I'll bet on this!
Also, I Summon Time Magician in Attack Mode!
And I activate the Claw of Hermos!
Come forth, Hermos!
Hermos can transform into an Equipment Card for any Monster on the field!
I'm counting on you, Hermos!
Create a miracle!
H-Huh...?
What the hell's that?!
I was a wee bit curious as to what was gonna show up...
But what're ya trying to prove
by bringing that toy out?!
Hey, hey...
Is that its strongest form?
Jounouchi! Are you sure you weren't mistaken?!
No, that's fine.
Yeah!
I can sense Hermos's power!
It doesn't matter if it doesn't look cool!
Even though I don't know the power of this weapon, I have no choice but to use it!
I equip Time Magic Hammer with Gigacyber!
Go!
Time Magic Hammer!
He doesn't have enough Attack Power, yet he's going to strike with him?
That idiot!
There's more to it...!
The Claw of Hermos...
No matter what you try to do, it won't work on me...!
Harpy Lady Pharaoh Formation!
This way, even if Gigacyber's Attack is lifted,
the attack damage is 0!
There is no flaw in my strategy!
What's up those numbers?
I don't know.... nothing seems to have changed...
What a pity, Jounouchi!
Looks like you gravely miscalculated the strength of the Legendary Dragons!
Nothing happened...!
My turn is over!
Are you making fun of me, Jounouchi?!
So in the end, you really aren't going to fight me seriously.
Mai...!
I...
Enough already!
Let's end this already!
I'll end this ridiculous Duel right this instant!
My turn! Draw!
My Monsters....!
Wh-What's going on?
Mai-san's Monsters disappeared?
What just happened?
Is destroying the Monsters
part of Hermos's power...?
No...
I don't think that's all....
There must be more to it.
That space twilight-like vortex is still on the field.
What happened to my Harpies?!
I don't know either!
I set one card! Turn over!
I don't know what happened, but since Mai's field is empty, now's my chance!
My turn! Draw!
Gigacyber, Direct Attack Mai!
Sorry....!
Mai!
Shit!
As I thought, he's a Duelist chosen by the Legendary Dragon.
Mai...!
I'll set one card face-down! Turn over!
Just a little longer...
Just a little longer and I can end this in a tie...
That way both of us can be saved!
Must not lose...
I must not lose...!
I can't lose here...!
I've gotten much stronger...!
I have obtained Doma's power...! So I can't lose!
Mai...!
My turn!
Draw!
Mai's Monster is back!
What's going on?
I see!
The number that appeared then...!
The opponent's Monsters will be sent to the future turns by Time Magic Hammer according to the numbers they are assigned.
Then...!
If it is set for next turn, it'll return in the next turn, and if it's set for six turns, the Monster will return on the sixth turn!
So the player can start over fresh and prepare for an attack!
That's the Effect when Time Magician and Hermos are fused together into Time Magic Hammer!
And because Harpy Lady hasn't returned to the field yet, Harpy's Pet Dragon's Attack will drop!
But it still has more than Gigacyber.
It's back...! My Monster's back!
It'll be all right...! I won't lose...!
I'll win...!
Harpy's Pet Dragon! Attack Gigacyber!
She lost her cool.
Mai!
Reverse Card open! Devil Dice!
This card reduces the enemy Monster's Attack by the amount rolled on the dice!
Dude!!
The Attack Points of Harpy's Pet Dragon is reduced by half!
No...!
I can't lose!
Mai!
I... I want to win...!
I have to!
This isn't good. If this keeps up...
Varon!
Shard of the Orichalcos!
Release your power!
Varon!
The boundary disappeared!
That was far too reckless!
Even if the Orichalcos protects us, if we try to release the boundary against its will, it may no longer shield our lives!
Even so, I can't let her continue like this...!
The next time we meet, I'll be taking your soul, O great Nameless Pharaoh!
Great!
The locks should open now!
Mai!
Those guys!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Are you alright?!
Hang on!
Jounouchi!
Mai...! What happened to Mai?
Well...
They disappeared...
No way...!
Shit...
DAMN IT!!
MAI!!!
Shit...!
SHIT!
Why, Mai?!
Jounouchi, don't you get it?
Mai betrayed us.
She went to our enemy!
Stop talking like that!
We don't know that for sure yet!
What are you tying to cover up?!
You saw!
Mai...
She really fought Jounouchi in order to steal his soul...!
Jounouchi-kun...
Kaiba!
Yugi!
Jounouchi!
Guys!
Yugi-kun!
Even Otogi!
Kaiba-kun?
What's going on?
Why are you guys here?
Pegasus called us here.
Pegasus did?!
Is Pegasus okay?
When we got here, he already...
It seems Mai...
It seems Mai Kujaku joined forces with Doma and stole Pegasus's soul.
Did you say Doma?!
Kaiba, do you know about Doma too?
My brother just fought a guy from Doma called Amelda!
The guy impersonated Pegasus, and set Big Brother into a trap!
We pretty much took each other out...
I see...
So that's why you came here.
Looks like we were all called here by Pegasus, relating to the same incident...
That's right...
Pegasus was able to sense this coming crisis...
I have to talk to Yugi boy personally.
Eh?
However, I cannot leave this building.
I am being watched by someone.
He knew he was in danger...
This is Pegasus we're talking about. He must have planned two or even three steps ahead.
For his Duel...
The card Pegasus sent me...
Pegasus must have left some clues for us!
Yugi-kun!
Now that you mention it...
There was one room I couldn't unlock!
That's it!
Good. Take us there.
S-Sure...
Kaiba~!!
You're just as arrogant as ever...!
Let's go, Jounouchi-kun.
Y... Yeah...
Wh-What the?
They're ignorin' us like we don't exist...!
That in itself is in our favor!
There's gotta be some rare cards hidden in Pegasus's hidden room!
YEAH!
Let's go get 'em all!
This is it.
This is the only door I couldn't unlock.
It's too dark to see anything.
It could be a trap Doma set up...
What's all this?
Amazing...!
This room looks like a giant toy box.
This really pisses me off...!
What horridly bad taste he has!
This is all Pegasus's!
There might be some awesome rare cards hidden in here!
Hell yeah!
It's obvious!
Pegasus!
This is... Solid Vision!
Yugi boy, welcome to my private room.
This room is the dreamland I hold deep within my heart.
Do you like it?
That's why your popularity's been terrible lately...!
Keep your mouth shut!
However, Yugi boy...
If you are listening to this message, in all probability, I am no longer safe.
I anticipated this.
Pegasus...
Our company has already
been taken over by another.
We're the same...
Our Kaiba Corporation has been bought out by a larger company.
Big Brother...
This organization is an underground secretive company that is rumored
to rival even the American supremacy in its brilliance and its influence.
Doma.
Doma?!
He said "secretive company"?!
Doma is said to act from the shadows, pulling the strings as the puppeteers...
...for thousands of years as the cause of a multitude of financial changes throughout the world.
You all should have learned this from the text books.
The thriving reign of the Roman Empire, and its sudden downfall.
A mere historical repetition?
Who was truly responsible for providing the winning side with their weapons during the sailing age?
Civil wars...
Was it truly the cause of civilians randomly rebelling against the government?
Who was the one to bring the infamous Napoleon to power?
The Industrial Revolution that began rising throughout cultures all over the world...
As well as the Renaissance of the 1800th century.
Who was the one pulling strings during all of these world events from the shadows?
I do not have any evidence.
Because everyone who knew of the real truth were all slaughtered in history's darkest ages.
But I confirmed this.
They have been involved in the world's deepest history.
Involved in the world's history...?
That same Doma has begun to move again.
They are using the power of the Duel Monsters I created.
Furthermore, they are aiming for something much larger this time.
They are plotting something far more evil this time.
Plotting...?
It shall happen very soon...
It shall happen very soon, Sir Yugi!
Thou shalt his soul
be offered up to our god!
Offered?
Indeed.
The soul of the loser shall be offered up to God as a sacrifice!
Says he, this world shall be guided down the path of destruction!
Be it food to a new, pure world!
Yugi boy.
It is because I wanted to tell you this that I have called you here.
And I hope it is something you can accept.
Hidden within this room is a new card I have created!
-Card?!
In truth, I wanted to hand it to you personally, but it cannot be helped.
You will have to find it yourself!
Pot of Greed!
This is the only thing not related to the world of Toon World!
WE'LL TAKE IT!!
Here!
This is strange. Nothing's written on it!
It's not even complete yet, right?
Then it's just garbage.
A nameless card...?
Yugi boy, I beg of you!
Please save my cute Monsters!
I believe you, Yugi boy, are the only one who can do so!
What the hell?!
I don't get it!
An underground organization that's been around for thousands of years?!
Why would Mai
work with these kind of people?!
Doma is close to us.
I remember...
Gozaburo once said....
"There must be a darkness within the world economy controlling its capital from the shadows."
I never took them seriously, brushing them off as the heroic words of a coward, but...
Yugi! No matter how you struggle, these are opponents you can't reach!
No, Kaiba!
Are you sure about that?
Maybe I can't touch such a huge enemy by myself...
But...
That's...
The Claw of Hermos...
Kaiba, do you also have a card like this?
The Fang of Critias!
If the three of us combine our power...
We may be able to defeat Doma.
Didn't the card tell you that?
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Pegasus revealed the true colors of Doma in his projection.
If our enemies are really them...
how exactly can we fight them?
Our only hope is the three Legendary Dragon cards Yugi, Jounouchi, and Kaiba-kun got from the Duel Monsters world.
But will Kaiba-kun help us that easily?
Next time: "The Target is the Nameless Pharaoh"
Duel Standby!