Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
My final match
with Malik has finally started!
In order to save Mai and Bakura, Malik, I'm going to beat you!
But because of the Dark Game he set up, my partner and Malik's other personality have become sacrifices for the game!
And Osiris' attack was absorbed by Ra in its Phoenix Mode!
Is there a way to defeat Malik and rescue both the sacrifices?!
"Devil's Sanctuary Activates!"
Ra's Special Ability... The God Phoenix.
Malik can pay 1000 of his Life Points and
destroy every Monster on the field.
More than that, every attack
is ineffective against it.
So even Yugi's Osiris will be destroyed?
Well, I'm not sure about that.
No one knows what the gods' powers are capable of.
But I'm worried about the players feeling the damage of their Monsters' life energy being destroyed.
Yugi...
You have to endure this!
Malik!
You haven't evaded all of Osiris's
attacks yet, you know!
Go forth!
Osiris's Special Ability activates!
Summon Lightning Shot!!
What?! The Summon
Lighting Shot had no effect!
Did you think your measly lightning bolt
could penetrate this armor of fire!?
Now then! It's my turn to attack!
Here it comes!
The third power of Ra
inscribed in the Hieratic Text.
"In an instant,
Ra shall become a phoenix."
"And the enemies of Ra
shall return to the Earth."
Does that apply to a god as well?
To activate the Special Power of
God Phoenix costs me 1000 Life Points.
But the darkness shall be more than
happy to accept this offering!
And now, on this turn, you and Osiris
shall burn together, Yugi!
Let the flames consume the deity,
God Phoenix!!
Yugi!
Osiris is dead!
Yugi! Hang in there!
Good...
I need you both to suffer
more and more...
It wouldn't be much of a climax
to our Dark Games if you didn't!
Partner!
You have to hang tough, partner!
I'm fine!
But it took a lot of work to get our God Card out and now it's been destroyed!
Now we've only got
one God Card left!
Ra! You're done for the turn!
Return to the Graveyard once more!
Yes! Magic Cards only work on gods for one turn!
So Ra can't attack again!
Phew! That was way
too close for comfort!
Yugi...!
According to the text of the Trap Card I used this turn, Revival of the Dark,
the Resurrection of the Dead card will return to your Graveyard at the end of your turn.
But that's when I do this!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Zombie's Jewel!
I knew you'd play this, Malik!
Zombie's Jewel activates when a Magic Card is placed in my opponent's Graveyard.
I can add that same card to my hand!
So Resurrection of the Dead returns to my hand once more!
What did you say?!
And... that... means~
Do you know what that means~?
Hmmm, Yugi?
Bingo!
It means I can Special Summon
Ra all over again next turn!
In other words, Yugi, you will be
annihilated by the One Turn Kill!
But the fine print text on Zombie's Jewel says you can draw a card.
Will that card be the savior
that will spare your life?
Or will it serve as a one way trip to
the pits of eternal darkness and destruction?
Other me...
Our fate depends
on the next card I draw!
Now~! Draw your card~!
Yugi~!!
Big brother!
Yugi, unless you draw that one card,
you won't be able to escape
the horrors of One Turn Kill!
Yugi doesn't have any
defensive Monsters on the field!
If he takes Ra's attack this turn,
it's all over!
Still...
I thought Ra's Special Ability
called "God Phoenix" could only
attack the Monsters on the field.
Yeah, but I hear Ra has another Hidden Ability...
Hidden Ability...?
Is there any way to overcome it?
Don't you lose, Yugi!
Yugi... Let me show you
something interesting...
You may have taken notice
that one of your friends has been
missing for a while now.
See? The owner of this thing.
The Millennium Ring! Bakura!!
So it's Malik's fault
Bakura is missing?!
What'd you do with Bakura, Malik?!
This Millennium Ring
is my spoils of war.
Well, by now I'd say he's been
completely consumed by the darkness.
I bet you're just dying to see it!
His pitiful end!
God Blaze Cannon!!
I'm going to show you
on my next turn, Yugi!
Ra's absolute destructive power that sent
Bakura into the darkness of Hell!!
Malik...!
Mai! Bakura! Jounouchi-kun!
I will never forgive you for hurting my
precious friends one after another!
There's nothing you can do...
Other than to draw your useless
card and sink into despair!
Do it! Get on with your draw, Yugi!!
This deck is destiny!
The card lying in front of me
represents a future that can
be seen, yet cannot be seen!
There's a small chance that this is the
one card that holds possibility!
Take this, Yugi!
The card he gave me!
I'll...
...stake it all on this card!
Yugi's deck...!
It's the place where souls meet!
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
What was that?!
He didn't even look at the card he drew before playing it!
He placed the card in reverse without knowing what it is!
What's he thinking?
Hey big brother, what card do you think Yugi drew?
Absurd! Is he telling us he knows
what the card he drew is without
even looking at it?!
It couldn't be...!
Did you just create a miracle?!
Yugi?!
I set a reverse card and end my turn!
Absurd! Is he telling us he knows
what the card he drew is without
even looking at it?!
Did you just create a miracle?!
Yugi?!
Yugi! Reversing a card without
confirming it is an illegal act!
According to the rules, if that card is a Monster-
Isono!
Y-Yes!
Interesting.
Let it continue!
Yes!
So, you don't even have the guts to
look defeat in the face, eh Yugi?!
This could very well be the last card
you draw in your life here!
Why don't you try parting from
this world with a little dignity?
Malik! It's your turn!
My turn, draw!
I'm not going to let you
out of this with a rule violation!
I'm sending you to Hell
screaming in agony as you
suffer the ultimate pain!
Here I go!!
Resurrection of the Dead, activate!!
It's coming...!
Revive!! Almighty Sun God!!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
Behold!!
The power granted to me
by the ancient scriptures!!
What?!
This is one of Ra's Hidden Abilities!
I'm about to demonstrate it for you!
Keep your eyes fixated long enough to
burn this image into your memory!
Malik's body disappeared!
What in the hell's going on here?!
Yugi!
Ra's Hidden Ability is...
I will fuse with God!!
Malik and Ra have joined together!!
Are you watching?!
This is Ra's Hidden Special Ability!
The player takes all but one Life Point,
and all of those points
are transferred to Ra!
What?!
And that's not all!!
By sacrificing the Monsters on my field,
I absorb their Attack Points!!
Increasing Ra's Attack Power!!
4699 points!!
This is the One Turn Kill!
Yugi!
You're finished!
Yugi's only got 3300 Life Points!
If Ra's able to attack players directly, Yugi's Life Points are going to hit 0!
They can't!
Isn't there something
you can do, Yugi?!
Big brother, if this keeps up, Yugi...
Yugi, if you really drew that card...
If you really created a miracle...
Then show it to me!!
Brace yourself, Yugi!!
I'll boil your blood
until it starts to steam!!
RA, ATTACK!!
Reverse card, open!
What?!
Devil's Sanctuary!
Devil's Sanctuary!?
Yugi, how on Earth
did you draw that card...?!
I felt it the moment
I touched the card!
Kaiba! I felt the pulse of your soul!
Cornered as he was in this situation,
he drew that card?!
Is this the power of a friend?!
Is this a miracle!?
Instant Quick Play Magic!
Activate!!
What!?
A magic circle
appeared on Yugi's field!?
And now something's appearing!
Metal Devil Token!!
The magic effect of Devil's Sanctuary
causes one Metal Devil Token
to appear on the field.
And it's power is...
I can see my reflection
in the Metal Devil!
That's right! Metal Devil becomes a
substitute for the opposing player!
And if it's destroyed in battle,
the Metal Devil Token's Attack Points
are equivalent to the player's Life Points
and deducted accordingly!
In other words,
if I use the Metal Devil Token as a
wall against your attacks, Malik...
It becomes you!!
Wha...!!?
Its Attack Points are the same
as the opponent's Life!
So as of right now,
the Metal Devil has 1 Attack Point!
One point...?
The moment Ra attacks
the Metal Devil...
...you will lose all of your
Life Points and the game!!
Awesome!
So this is the key card for defeating Ra!
You did it, Yugi!
Now Yugi-kun wins!
Damn!
I already declared "attack"!
Malik! When the blow reflects
back on you, you lose!
I won!
The Metal Devil is still on the field!
What's going on here?!
Malik's Life Points went up to 4700!
The moment Ra
attacked the Metal Devil,
I went and activated a Magic Card!
What did you say!?
I de-activated the Fusion With God using
the Fusion Cancel card I got from you!
So the moment the fusion between
Malik and Ra was broken,
Fusion Cancel's effects
ended the battle.
In other words, the attack on
Metal Devil was negated!
I never imagined Fusion Cancel
could be used like this!
Furthermore, because Ra's Attack Power
was drained due to Fusion Cancel,
Malik was able to increase his Life Points
to an outrageous amount.
So even the Devil's Sanctuary that
was meant to turn the favor ended up
working in Malik's favor.
Yugi...!
But Devil's Sanctuary isn't
just meant to negate Ra.
Yugi! Can you figure out how to use it?
Thanks to my Life Points coming back,
my sacrifice's body has returned
to normal, as you can see!
He's a tough sucker!
Ri...shi...d...
Ra! Return to the Graveyard!
I'll place Resurrection of the Dead
in the Graveyard as well!
In addition, I set a reverse card!
Turn end!
Dammit! If Malik uses
Resurrection of the Dead on his
next turn, Ra will be Summoned again!
Yugi! You've gotta do something!
It's my turn...!
The maintenance cost
of using Metal Devil Token is 1000
Life Points on my every turn.
Partner!
I'm alright!
I'm fighting alongside you, just as I said!
Draw!
I'm sorry, Partner...
Just bare with it!
I'll pay 1000 points
for the maintenance cost of
Metal Devil Token!
You must be an idiot!
Just 1 measly Attack Point!
What's the point of maintaining a token
that can barely attack or defend!?
So you've figured it out?
Kaiba...
When I drew Devil's Sanctuary,
our souls crossed.
It was passed onto me...
The card I need has already
been placed on my field!
Devil's Sanctuary has the power
to defeat God and call God!
Here goes! My reverse card!
Open!
Multiply!!
What!? Did you say Multiply!?
This card multiplies all Monsters on the
field with 500 Attack Points or less!
Don't tell me...!
Is he going to use them to Summon God!?
The true nature of Devil's Sanctuary is
a magic circle meant to Summon God!
The other card
Yugi won from Seto! Obelisk!
I sacrifice the three
Metal Devil Tokens...
Come forth, God of Destruction!
Obelisk!!
There it is!!
The third God Card!
The Great War God Obelisk!
And Malik don't got a single Monster
on the field to act as a shield!
He's totally completely
defenseless right now!
And Obelisk can
directly attack the player!
The Great War God Obelisk...!
The Great War God Obelisk, attack!
God Hand Crusher!!
Obelisk's God Hand Crusher knocked Malik's lights out!
Yes! Now Malik's Life Points
dropped greatly!
But what's with that demented grin?
He's making a face like he's backed Yugi into a corner!
Is it because Malik's using his dominate half as a hostage?
After Yugi's attack... eh? The Great War God Obelisk appeared behind him?!
Next time!
"The Eternal Wall - God Slime"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other