Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Osiris the Heaven Dragon"
Nightmare's Steel cage is a card that makes it so both of us can't attack each other for three turns.
Dammit!
He plans to use these three turns to generate more Slime Tokens to sacrifice.
Right.
I may not be able to launch the Battle Phase, but,
I can still Summon Slime Tokens to the field.
There's no mistaking this gut feeling...
He must have the God Card in his hand already.
He's going to Summon Osiris!
Burn this image of me into your mind.
The moment I Summon Osiris the Heaven Dragon!
Domino City, A Block. Check complete.
No sign of a God Card.
B Block. No sign.
C Block. No sign.
D Block. No sign.
E Block. No sign.
Seto-sama!
Haven't you found it yet?
The place where the Ghoul Rare Hunters are hiding with the God Cards.
Yes...
We haven't had any luck right now...
They are somewhere within this city for sure.
They will eventually sniff out Obelisk the Great War God.
And appear before me.
I won't let them make the first move.
I'm coming for them first!
If you find them, contact me.
Got it?
Sir!
Seems like they still haven't caught the rats, huh, Nii-sama?
With Kaiba Corporation's technology, it's only a matter of time before we catch them.
They'll never guess we have a net spread across the entire sky!
This entire tournament is a trap I've set for them, after all.
Ghouls... I will take the God Cards from you no matter what.
Let's go, Mokuba.
Now, it's your turn.
I said that, but you can't do anything against me.
Well?
How does it feel to have your freedom snatched away from you as you are locked within this cage.
Humiliation?
Or maybe despair?
That's the fate I've dealt with my entire life!
The Tomb Guardian clan's!
What did I do to Malik and his clan?
The moment I claim the title of Pharaoh from killing you,
is the moment I will obtain true freedom!
And I will become the new Pharaoh!
I'm the Pharaoh...
Yet I have no memories of it...
And that is why I can't afford to lose here.
For everyone waiting for me...
And for the promise to fight a friend who will become a True Duelist...
For the life of my partner!
And in order to get back my lost memories!
I can't lose!
Turn over!
At last, this moment has come!
My turn!
He gathered all his sacrifices...!
Behold.
This is God!
Osiris descends!
This is...!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...!
That's right.
This is one of the three Illusionary Beast cards, Osiris the Sky Dragon!
My body froze against my will...!
It's not just this steel cage...
I'm frozen in fear because of Osiris...!
I can feel the powerful aura flowing from Osiris!
The sky itself is shaking!
Is it even possible for me to defeat this Illusionary Beast?!
You can't!
There is no way to defeat Osiris!
All Duelists are powerless against Osiris's Infinite Attack!
Even you, Pharaoh!
Infinite power...?
Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack Points equal 1000 times the number of cards in the player's hand.
Right now my puppet holds 3 cards.
Meaning it now has 2000 Attack Points.
It's Attack Points are based on the number of cards in the player's hand?!
In other words, if I do this...
The Magic Card Pot of Greed!
With this, I lose one card from my hand.
But Pot of Greed is a card that allows me to draw 2 cards from my Deck.
Now I gain 2 cards in my hand.
Meaning Osiris's Attack is 3000!
That means it'll be 4000 next turn!
No, Duel Monsters states that the End Phase you are only permitted 6 cards in your hand.
Meaning by my turn Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack can reach up to 6000!
Up to 6000?
How naive.
I said infinite power.
I have a card in my hand that will increase it even further.
A Continuous Magic that grants me an unlimited hand!
Moreover, Osiris the Heaven Dragon holds another Special Ability.
When your next turn comes to and end,
the Steel cage disappears.
At that moment, Osiris's attack can reach you.
Now! It's your turn!
Currently, Osiris's Attack is 3000.
My Buster Blader's Attack goes up by 500 points for every Dragon on the field.
It's Attack will go up by 500 points.
In other words, Buster Blader will have 3100 Attack Points.
If I attack right now,
I can defeat Osiris.
But my attack this turn has been sealed by this steel cage...
If he draws a card next turn,
Osiris will gain another 1000 Attack Points.
What's wrong?
Has the terror paralyzed you so much that you can't even draw a card?
Shit!
What should I do?
The Battle Phase is stopped because of the Steel cage,
but you can still play a reverse card or Summon a Monster.
You can at least pretend not to have given up hope, right?
Now! Let me see it!
Your struggling form agonizing in the cage before me!
I...
I won't lose!
Draw!
There's no way I can give up!
There has to be a way to defeat Osiris within this hand.
Think...
That's right.
Think.
Naturally.
If you think about it and think about it some more, you should understand.
That you have no hope of winning.
Alright.
His next turn will determine the match!
I set 2 reverse cards.
Also, I call Kuriboh onto the field in Defense Mode.
Turn over!
And now, the Steel cage will finally disappear.
The steel cage that has been protecting your life up until now.
My turn!
Draw!
And Osiris's Attack goes up by 1000 points!
Here I go!
Osiris, attack!
Super Conductor!
Thunder Force!!
Reverse card open!
What?!
Light Force Sword!
Using this Magic Card, I'll seal one of your cards!
At this moment, Osiris's Attack will drop back to 3000!
Buster Blader evades Osiris the Heaven Dragon's attack!
He counter-attacks with Dragon Sword!
Alright!
I can defeat Osiris!
Have you forgotten?
As long as my Permanent Trap Defender Slime remains on the field, you can't attack any of my Monsters.
And at this moment, I activate a Continuous Magic Card!
Card of Safe Return?
Right.
When a Monster is
returned to the field,
this Continuous Magic
Card allows me to
draw 3 cards
from my Deck.
Now I have 5 cards in my hand.
Osiris the Heaven Dragon's Attack Points...
Rise to 5000!
5000 Attack Points?
Oi, why didn't you Duel him?
He would've been an easy opponent!
You gotta hurry up and get into the Finals!
I can't do it like that.
Getting into the Finals is a huge deal.
Just anyone won't do!
What the hell are you going on about?
Listen!
The Finalists are gonna be determined!
If you just sit around, these other guys are gonna get into the tournament first!
I made a promise with Yugi!
That I would win in Battle City for sure and become a True Duelist on my own.
And fight him in the finals.
In order to become a True Duelist,
there's no point unless I fight those stronger than me.
Brilliant! Rather than stay at your own level, you fight those stronger than you.
That shows you've really got heart.
However, what Honda-kun said isn't exactly far fetched.
If you happen to not make it into the Finals, then you'll...
Kaiba-kun!
Why is a nobody like you wearing a Duel Disk?
Why, you ask?
Because I'm a Duelist.
Your level was supposed to be 2, but...
Very well.
Let's go, Mokuba.
Honda.
It looks like I've found my opponent.
O-Oi, don't tell me you plan on going after Kaiba...!
Kaiba!
Duel me!
You serious?
A-Are you for real, Jounouchi?
I'll show you the ability of a nobody!
Don't get big-headed!
You're 100 years too early to challenge Nii-sama to a Du-
Fine.
That's what I'm talkin' about!
Nii-sama!
I'll let you see God.
Let's go, Kaiba!
W-What the?!
This is overkill!
Nii-sama!
Seto-sama!
We've located a Rare Card with a God Card!
Please get aboard!
Shit!
What's with that helicopter?!
The Duel is canceled!
What?!
You've got good luck!
Your life's been spared for now!
What'd ya say, you bastard!?
Oi!
Get back here, you jerks!
CHEATERS~!
Ah well!
He ran away.
What were you thinking?
You were really scared.
The Duel Point is 350 west.
The Duelist facing the Rare Hunter is...
Mutou Yugi!
Yugi!
Your opponent to fight is me!
Buster Blader is assassinated!
Do you get it?
Nothing can stop God.
For every card in my hand, Osiris grows more invincible!
And this isn't the extent of the god's power.
On your next turn,
I'll show you another of Osiris's terrifying abilities!
Now it's your turn.
I have Kuriboh in Defense Mode and 1 set card on my field.
And none of the cards in my hand will save me.
What's the next card sleeping in my Deck?
I have no choice but to bet on this card!
My turn!
Draw!
Magic Cylinder...!
It's a Magic Card that can only be played in combination with a Magician Card.
Magician Girl...!
I have no other choice than to use this against him!
Here I go!
I sacrifice Kuriboh!
I Summon Black Magician Girl!
Defense Mode!
So you Summoned a new Monster?
At this moment, Osiris's other Special Effect activates!
What?!
Osiris's second mouth...!
Opened!
When a new Monster is Summoned on the field, Osiris automatically delivers the opponent 2000 points of damage.
If that card is in Attack Mode, its Attack Points are reduced.
If in Defense Mode, then their Defense Points.
Then that Monster will be wiped out if they have less.
What?!
Black Magician Girl has 1700 Defense Points!
Summon Lightning Shot!!
A Monster that attacks on the opponent's turn?!
Not a Monster!
A God!
Reverse card open!
Your magical girl's life was cut short.
We'll see about that...
What?!
The Magic Card Magical Silk Hats!
Magical Hats
She's hiding in the Silk Hats?
What a shame.
Osiris failed to guess
the right Silk Hat
she's hiding in.
Well try your very best.
Though it's useless to resist.
As long as I still have some Life remaining,
I will fight!
I place 2 set cards face-down on the field.
Turn end!
So you hid cards beneath the Silk Hats?
My turn!
Draw!
Right now I have 6 cards in my hand.
According to the rules of a Duel, I can hold no more than this.
But...!
If I play this card, I can hold an unlimited number of cards!
A Continuous Magic, Infinite Hand!
Infinite Cards
Infinite Hand, you said?!
So you know
what this means...?
Osiris will increase its Attack Points infinitely!
And now the Battle Phase!
The Heaven Dragon attacks!
Thunder Force!!
Aim for the Silk Hat on the right!
His aim was spot-on...
Because I'm very accurate.
This is my final bet!
The Silk Hat and Black Magician Girl have been annihilated!
What?!
Magic Cylinder has absorbed Osiris's attack!
I hid 2 cards in the hat you attacked along with Black Magician Girl!
Magic Cylinder and...
Hexagram Curse as well!
Spellbinding Circle
And now your Thunder Force will appear in the other cylinder and will be aimed at you!
Can I defeat a god?!
It's useless.
Didn't I tell you?
That no one can do a thing against God.
The Slime even blocks redirected attacks?!
Revival Slime reforms.
At this moment, the Continuous Magic Card of Safe Return allows me to draw 3 cards.
Osiris's Attack goes up by 3000 points!
And at the Draw Phase, it goes up another 1000 points!
8300 Attack Points!
Hexagram Curse won't work against God!
All magical effects only work for 1 turn and then disappear!
Behold.
These 5 cards gathered on the field make the Ultimate Combo.
The God Five!
Perfect and completely invincible!
These complete every flaw the god has and make it untouchable!
I can't win...
I can't... defeat Osiris...
Stand up, Yugi!
Your life as a Duelist doesn't end here!
Kaiba!
You're the only Duelist I acknowledge!
A won't allow a shameless loss right before my eyes!
I know you can see it.
Our road of battle goes farther than the eye can see!
Are you unable to stand here?!
If there's a god standing in your way...
Mow the god down!
Preview
Osiris the Heaven Dragon holds the Ultimate Combo.
No attack will work against the God Five!
Its Attack continues to increase by 1000 every turn.
Even if it's Yugi, is there a way to turn around this strategy?!
You found a way?
What's the "infinite combo that goes past the limits of God"?!
Next
time
Overcoming
God !
The Ultimate
Infinite Loop
Next time!
Overcoming God !
The Ultimate Infinite Loop
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...