Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"Counterattack! Gilford the Lightning"
Damn...! My turn!
Hey, Yugi...
If Jounouchi's Monster has
3000 Attack Points,
he should be able to attack and
beat Malik in an instant, right?
True... Malik doesn't have any
Wall Monsters on the field right now.
But that is likely
just what Malik planned.
I have no doubt that his
reverse card is a Trap!
I gotta do something
about his obvious Trap first!
Right! Hurricane!
Please! Please draw Hurricane!
Draw!
I don't have any more
Monster Cards in my hand...
What do I do...?
The problem is his Trap Card.
Even if he uses it to block my attack, it should go to the Graveyard after he uses it.
But still...!
Provided that, of course,
the player can handle his red-hot body
melting around him every turn,
and taking 700 points of
damage every turn as a result!
I guess you could say
this Monster is quite a handful!
700 points every turn...?!
Go screw yourself!
If I just sit here and do nothing,
my Life will continue to drop...!
So I'll step into your trap!
Malik!
I'll attack you with your little
grotesque pet just like you wanted!
Really~?
I thought you'd be too scared of my
face-down to try and attack me.
Oh yeah?!
But you have quite a good hunch.
Yes. Just as you figured, this Trap does not have a permanent effect.
It will disappear from
the field on my next turn.
What the heck? Malik just told
Jounouchi that he has a Trap!
Damn it... He's making fun of him!
Even I don't know what will happen if you fire
this hot-headed deadbeat up too much...
Not even Kaiba Corporation's
most advanced computer systems
would be able to predict
the way he thinks.
Here I go!
My pet's ultimate attack
is called "Golem Volcano"!
Let me hear you shout it
nice and loud, Jounouchi!
It's my Monster,
so I'll name it's attacks!
Attack, Lava Golem!
Jounouchi Fire!!
J-Jounouchi Fire, he said...?
G-Good one! Now go!
Jounouchi Fire's really cool!
Reverse Trap activate!
Just like that...
Monster Relief!!
It activates when the
opposing player declares an attack.
The card lets me return
one Monster to my hand
and Special Summon a
Four-Star Monster to take its place!
His own Monster...?
But Malik doesn't have a
Monster of his own on the field!
No, he has the Plasma Eel that's
been causing Jounouchi-kun's
Panther Warrior all its suffering.
I return Plasma Eel to my hand!
And I'll then Summon Plasma Eel
again in Defense Mode!
Plasma Eel won't be destroyed
in battle by any Monster!
Damn it all..!
And now Helpoemer will kill off
another card from your hand!
Turn end...!
And now... Lava Golem's
red-hot body will begin to melt...
...taking some of your
Life along with it.
So hot...!
How unsightly...
Another Dark Game is
being played this very moment...
Will Malik's dark side not be satisfied
until he destroys himself
and sends everyone
else to the darkness?
My turn! Draw!
Machine Reproduction Technique, eh?
Using this, I'll paralyze him for real!
I activate the Magic Card
Machine Reproduction Technique!
Machine Reproduction Technique?!
When I have a Machine-Type Monster with
500 Attack Points or less on the field,
you can Special Summon up to two Monsters holding the same name from your deck...
...using this Magic Card.
What!?
My deck includes two more
Plasma Eels, you see!
Come out! Plasma Eel!!
What!? There's three
Plasma Eels on the field?!
Using their Special Power, they attach
themselves to the enemy Monsters!
No...!
Jounouchi-kun!
That's the sound!
Let me hear more screams!
How many more turns
can you keep this up, Jounouchi?!
You... damn nut job...!
In addition, I place two
face-down cards and end my turn.
If it goes on like this,
Jounouchi-kun will...!
Shit...! Can't he do something?!
As I thought, there was no reason to call God for a worthless deadbeat like him...
Hey, Yugi... Isn't there
something Jounouchi can do?
Jounouchi-kun only
has one card left in his hand...
But there has to be
a way in that one card.
Don't give up.
Believe in your hand until the end!
As long as this Lava Golem is on my field,
my Life Points will continue to be drained every turn.
If I don't do something
about this thing, I'll lose...!
But the only card I've got
in my hand is the Angel Dice.
Yugi...!
That's right! I promised I'd
Duel Yugi in the Final!
I can't afford to lose here!
I'll believe in the next card
I draw from my deck!
My turn! Draw!
Gilford the Lightning!
I need to sacrifice two Monsters on my field
in order to Summon an Eight-Star Monster.
But I can't sacrifice a Monster
the Plasma Eel is attached to...
And just Panther Warrior
by himself won't be enough.
Wait a sec...!
There's still a way...!
Magic Card, activate!
Angel Dice!
Angel Dice lets me increase the
Attack Points of a Monster with
less than 500 Attack.
Malik!
Your Continuous Magic,
Machine Reproduction Technique,
can only make Machine-Type Monsters
with less than 500 Attack Points, right?!
I get it!
Brilliant strategy, Jounouchi-kun!
Then I wonder what's gonna
happen if I raise the Attack Power
of the Plasma Eel on your field!
Plasma Eel's Attack Points
multiply by six!
From 500 to 3000 points
in a single stroke!
And that means the Continuous Magic Card,
Machine Reproduction Technique, is destroyed!
That also means the two
Plasma Eels leeching onto
my Monsters are destroyed along with it!
Now I got my three sacrifices!
Here goes!
I sacrifice three Tributes -
Lava Golem, Rocket Warrior
and Panther Warrior...
...to Summon Gilford the Lightning!
This guy is gonna end
your miserable life!
So get ready, Malik!
What'cha think?!
He's the toughest servant
I got in my deck!
The legendary warrior
who controls the storm!
He's gonna take you down, Malik!
Wow!
He Summoned a
High-Level Monster with ease!
He turned the tables!
Sick him, Jounouchi!
What the hell's so funny?!
A fool to no end...
You just raised the Attack
of my Plasma Eel to 3000!
It's got 200 more Attack Points than
your Gilford the Lightning!
So the "legendary warrior" you worked
so hard to Summon will die in vain!
You're the foolish one here, Malik-chan!
What?!
When Gilford the Lighting is
sacrificed with three Monsters,
his Special Ability activates.
Go on and show him, Jounouchi-kun!
Here goes!
Gilford the Lighting's
Special Ability activates!
Lighting Thunder!!
What...?!
Plasma Eel, who's supposed to not be able
to be destroyed in battle, was beaten?!
It wasn't a battle!
It was a Special Ability.
When Gilford the Lighting is Summoned,
it instantly destroys all Monsters on
the opponent's side of the field!
No matter what kinds of
Special Powers those Monsters may have!
Alrighty! You just lost all the
Monsters on your field!
Get your ass ready, Malik!
I Direct Attack with
Gilford the Lightning!
Lightning Crash Sword!!
If this attack goes through, I win!
You think I'd let you!?
Reverse Trap, open!
Nightmare Mirror!
Wha-
Well, Jounouchi, I guess you deserve
a hand for lasting this long...
But playtime has long past!
What?! I can see
my reflection in the mirror...!
Right! And Gilford the Lightning is going
to attack you inside the mirror!
Listen carefully, Jounouchi...
Attacking the mirror inflicts 1000
points of damage to your Life.
Although, I too must accept some risk
by discarding a card from my hand.
I'll send this card to the Graveyard...
And Helpoemer's Effect will now send a
card in your hand to the Graveyard!
I'd love to say that...
...but there's no helping it,
since you don't even have a hand!
By the way Malik's acting...
...he must be planning
something next turn!
Is he finally going to play it...?!
Turn end!
He doesn't have a Monster or a reverse card on the field.
If I can just get through this turn, I'll win!
My turn. Draw.
What the hell? Quit the creepy laughing
and just get on with it!
I admit that I've
underestimated you a bit.
I never would have imagined
that I would need to use God\M against the likes of you.
God?!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
Ra's Attack Power is determined
by the Monsters sacrificed in
order to Summon it.
Is there a way to Summon it
without sacrificing while still
maintaining Attack Points?!
Big brother!
Is he going to Summon the god?!
Here, in the battlefield of this
Semi-Final match, you've become
a sacrifice, Jounouchi!
In order for me to learn more about Ra!
After this turn, I'll finally learn all
of Ra's Hidden Special Powers!
According to the Hieratic Text
I deciphered on the God Card...
It's first Ability...
Ra shall take power
from three sacrifices...
However, even if the sacrifices are to the god's liking,
the god shall only answer to the one
who speaks the sacred spell.
And its second Ability...
God shall come forth from the Earth...
...when one chants the spell that
grants it the means of resurrection.
Those who face it in war shall be
incinerated by flames in an instant
and burned to a corpse.
And as for its third Ability...
In an instant,
God shall become a phoenix.
And all its enemies
shall return to the Earth.
Magic Card, activate!
Resurrection of the Dead!!
Now behold God!
Big brother...!
He Summoned Ra with
Resurrection of the Dead?
But it will have 0 Attack Points.
Plus, Magic Cards only affect
a god for one turn...
Even if it was Special Summoned,
it should go back to the Graveyard
before it can even attack!
I know what you're thinking,
but Ra has the power of Swift Attack.
And now the third
Ability of Ra activates!
What the hell's he up to now?!
Ra's being covered in flames!
It's changing form!
The Winged Sun Dragon - Final Form!
GOD PHOENIX!
G-God Phoenix...?!
It's completely different
from the time it beat Mai...!
I never thought I would have to show
you the true nature of Ra...
You can be proud of that, Jounouchi!
A-Amazing...
So this is Ra's final form?!
But this is the end, Jounouchi!
You die this turn!!
What is this disturbing feeling...?
I feel like something really bad
is about to happen to my brother...
Ishizu-san!
Are you... not going to watch?
Your elder brother won, did he not?
It's fine.
I need to be here with Mai-san...
She's been with me up until now...
Um...
If he beats this person named Malik,
Mai-san will return to normal, won't she...?
My big brother is the one who is
Dueling that Malik this very moment.
So Katsuya Jounouchi is the one
fighting in that Dark Game...!
My big brother is fighting
in order to save Mai-san!
So that is why I want to do everything
I can to help Mai-san...
I am the same.
Huh...?
I am doing everything I am capable of doing,
now that I have lost the power
of the Millennium Tauk.
All I can do is hope that someone
defeats Malik's dark personality...
...and in order to get Rishid
to regain consciousness...
...I can do nothing but remain by his side.
However, one woman is enough.
Ishizu-san...
I will watch over her for you.
So move along.
But...
You are worried about
your older brother, are you not?
So hurry up and go to him.
Please take care of Mai-san!
A Dark Game is a game of death...
It is very likely that
while you watch his fight...
...all that awaits you is a
cruel memory you will hope to forget...
Big brother!
Despite that...
Because you are his only sibling...
...you have to accept whatever the
outcome may be and fight alongside him.
All because you are his only sibling...
When Ra is Special Summoned
with Resurrection of the Dead,
it should have 0 Attack Points.
But Malik just declared he will
defeat Jounouchi-kun this turn...
Does that mean Ra possesses an
even more terrifying hidden power?!
Yugi!!
Kaiba!!
It's thanks to Jounouchi that you both
will see a preview of Ra's final form!
Why don't you send him off
with a big round of applause!
Make it loud enough for this pitiful Duelist
to hear you all the way down in Hell!
Why you...!
Don't go writing me off that easily!
I still have Gilford the Lighting,
with 2800 Attack Points, on my field!
If you can beat me with
God's 0 Attack Points, go on and show me!
Just be quiet and
wait for death, Jounouchi...
After you bare witness to
God's third Hidden Special Ability,
you will be wandering the pits of Hell,
with the most painful sensation on Earth!
What? A Special Ability?
Ra's Third Hidden Power...
If I pay 1000 of my Life Points,
it incinerates
the Monsters on the field...
...no matter how strong
their Attack Value!
H-He can kill Gilford the Lighting?!
But, even if you're able to use its
Special Power to destroy
the Monsters on the field,
you still won't be able
to lower my Life Points!
Meaning you can't
defeat me on this turn!
Have you forgotten?
This Duel is a Dark Game!
The players feel the same sensations
their Monsters feel!
Big brother!
God's judgment will burn both your
mind and body into ashes!
Regardless of whether
you have Life Points left,
all that awaits you
is death and defeat!
Now watch!
As the phoenix rises for you alone,
to lead you into the darkness!
God Phoenix!
Stop it!
Because of the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra's Special Ability,
if Gilford the Lighting is destroyed,
Jounouchi's life energy will burn up along with his Monster because of the Dark Game!
Please don't die, Jounouchi!
If you fall now,
how will you keep your promise to Mai-san to give her courage?!
You still have some of your Life left!
If you make it through this,
you can beat Malik!
Next time!
"Jounouchi Falls"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise