A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
I activate Dark Eyes Magic!!
Black Magician!
And the Time Bomber card!
In two turns, Sacrifice will be destroyed by Time Bomber.
Yugi boy, your Monster as well.
There's no cards in my hand that can stop him...
Even if there were, Pegasus read them all!
I'll have to draw a card.
But Pegasus' Millennium Eye will see it at the same time I do.
What do I do?
As long as I have the Mind Scan,
you can't do a single thing.
"The Fusion of Light and Darkness:
Black Chaos Descends"
Yugi...
Damn! What should we do?!
Yugi!
Are you alright?!
Answer us!
Answer us! Please!
Yugi!
Grandpa!
You have something other than the cards to believe in.
Something else to believe in?
Your other self isn't the only one with you in your heart.
You may not see them right away, but there should be others here too.
I understand, Grandpa!
Yugi...
Jounouchi! Honda!
Do you guys remember the ring
of friendship we made before?
Yeah!
Of course I do!
Our hearts are with Yugi's!
Yeah.
Even if we're separated, our hearts are always together.
I don't care if it's "Power of Darkness" or whatever, nothing ﻿will break the bond of our friendship
Yugi!
Don't lose, Yugi!
Yugi! We're all with you!
The bond of our friendship will always be linked to your heart!
I'm drawing a card!
Mind Scan!!
It's useless to try and stop me, Yugi boy.
You cannot hide the identity of that card within the depths of your mind for long!
What!?
Something has entered Yugi boy's mind and is blocking me from entering!
I can't see the card!
There's just no way!
Indeed, he had a strong mind throughout the game...
Still, it's unthinkable for a player's mind to be capable of fending off the Power of Darkness!
Pegasus! Don't you even think about invading Yugi's mind again!
Get the hell outta here!
Guys!
Pegasus! Yugi won't lose!
He's gonnna kick your ass!
So get ready, Pegasus!
Guys, I owe you one!
Unbelievable! To think your friends were capable ﻿of repelling me from the depths of your mind...!
The power of your Millennium Eye is
not capable of tearing down the wall of our feelings!
Here I go, Pegasus!
Magic Card, Magic Box of Death!
Two boxes appeared on the field..?
I don't have enough time to counter it...!
Black Magician escapes Sacrifice in time
before Time Bomber self-destructs!
Time Bomber has switched places and is now attached to Sacrifice!
Goddamn!
My turn is over.
My turn!
Brain Control!
What?! The Brainwashing Card?!
Yugi boy can control
Sacrifice for one turn...
Have you completely forgotten
about the time bomb on him?!
By doing such a stupid thing, your Black Magician will be blown up by Time Bomber and you'll lose!
Is that so?
I still have a set card.
The card left behind by my other soul!
Ritual of Black Magic Chaos!
A Ritual Card?!
I sacrifice Time Bomber and Black Magician for the ritual!
To think he was going to use the time bomb for that purpose...!
The Great Magician of Black Magic - Magician of Black Chaos, descends!
M-Magician of Black Chaos...!
My other self left behind but one card when he was on the verge of collapsing.
The Ritual of Black Magic Chaos!
The magician born from chaos, the
fusion of light and darkness!
Controller of insanity!
The master of all magicians!
Pegasus! This is our trump card!
Using this trump card, I will defeat you!
I never expected this of Yugi boy...!
But this turn, Sacrifice will be freed from his brainwashing.
On my next turn, Black Chaos will be absorbed by Sacrifice.
And I will gain all of its powers!
Yugi boy! You cannot defeat me, even if you play to all your limits!
Pegasus, I have the bond
with my friends in my heart!
Even the power of your
Millennium Item can't break it...
An unbreakable power!
I set a card face-down on this turn.
Also, I play another Monster in Defense Mode!
Turn over!
Yugi boy has 2 set cards...
And I can't see any of them due to his friends
blocking me from within his mind.
Shit!
What irritating bundlers!
My turn!
The brainwashing effects on Sacrifice have worn ﻿off, and he becomes my Monster again!
I'll use my trump card to teach you and your little comrades ﻿just how meaningless this "friendship" you speak of is!
Of course, I can just absorb Black Chaos using Sacrifice's Special Ability...
But...
I'm sure the same trick won't work twice on Yugi boy.
In that case, I'll play 2 cards on the field.
I'll power up Sacrifice's Special Ability even further with this!
I fuse Thousand Eyes Idol together with Sacrifice!
The Evil God!
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice!!
It's got eyes covering its entire body...!
Yugi boy, this Duel will signal the grand finale of the Kingdom!
You will be cursed with a cruel defeat!
Let our hearts blend with yours!
Our bond of friendship!
Don't you dare lose
to Pegasus' Power of Darkness!
Yugi, you can't give up!
We're with you!
We won't know the result of this match until the very end!
Thanks to the Special Ability of the Thousand Eyes Sacrifice I now have on the field,
your Black Chaos
will be unable to do a thing.
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice's﻿ Special Ability...?
The very moment my Thousand Eyes Sacrifice opens every eye on its body,
the movement of every Monster on my opponent's field shall become sealed!
Even though it's been fused, the enemy is still a Monster with 0 Attack Points...
It'll surely try to absorb Black Chaos and steal its power.
But I won't let that happen!
I swore to my other self!
Please.... let me draw one final card...
A card that can defeat Pegasus...!
Come on!
Other me...!
Use this card... to defeat... Pegasus!
I will defeat you using Black Chaos!
No matter what tricks you pull, you
won't break the promise we made!
The final turn!
I'm counting on you, my Monsters!
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice's Special Ability!
Thousand Eyes Curse!!
Black Chaos!
And with this, your Monsters have all been paralyzed.
The Thousand Eyes Curse will remain on the field, holding its spell over your Monsters.
In short, you will be trapped in
this everlasting curse forever!
An eternal curse...?
All that remains now is for me to
activate the central Evil Eye!
I'll suck in your Monster and steal its powers!
It's over, Yugi boy.
The Evil Eye activates!
Magic Card, open!
Once the light from the Evil Eye hits Black Chaos, ﻿it'll be absorbed by Thousand Eyes Sacrifice!
You sure about that?
What?! Kuriboh!
You've made a grave miscalculation.
Activating your Evil Eye also affected my set card, Kuriboh.
That Effect will now target him as well.
Wha-? When did you...?!
In addition, I activated
my other set card, Multiply!
Kuriboh will be multiplied endlessly!
What?! All the Kuribohs have been
affected by the Evil Eyes' light...!
Sacrifice has no choice but to absorb every Kuriboh affected by the Evil Eyes' light!
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice is trying to absorb the countless Kuriboh...!
But this was my aim.
For Kuriboh has the Special﻿ Ability to act like a living land mine
and self destruct
on contact with the enemy!
Land mine?!
With Kuriboh's death, my Life Points
decrease by 300 points.
However, all Thousand Eyes Sacrifice's
 thousands of eyes were destroyed!
Dammit...!
Yugi boy sacrificed Kuriboh just for this!
And at this moment, Black Chaos is freed from its curse!
Are you prepared, Pegasus?
My turn!
Black Chaos, attack!
Spell of Destruction! Death Ultima!!
Thousand Eyes Sacrifice ﻿was beaten!
Pegasus...
We've... won!
I...
...lost...!
I, who holds the power
of the Millennium Eye...
I, the creator
of the game we played...!
I lost...?!
Other me.
We did it, Partner!
Everyone gave their hearts.
Yugi!
Guys, thank you.
Don't say a thing!
I already know!
Yugi, I felt your pain while fighting-
I felt Yugi's pain while fighting and his joy of victory! I feel the same way!
Y-yeah, me too!
But I feel like we fought alongside you somehow, Yugi.
Y-yeah, so...!
Yeah! I'm happy!
HEY! You jerks said
everything I wanted to say!
It's alright!
You're right...
You're right!
Because...
YUGI WON!
ALL RIGHT!
Thank you, guys!
That's right! Pegasus!
We have to hurry and make him return your grandpa, Kaiba-kun, and Mokuba-kun back to normal!
That's true.
We'll make him keep his promise!
Pegasus...!
Where'd that guy go?!
Cheater!
Oi, let's go look for him!
But we can't just leave Bakura-kun
and Mokuba-kun behind...
HEY~!
GUYS~!
Bakura-kun!
Did you return to normal?
Eh? What do you mean?
When I woke up, I was on the floor...!
Do you really not remember anything?
That weird ring of yours took control of you again, Bakura.
Eh? Is that true?
The Millennium Ring...?
That ring...!
Yeah, it creeped me out, so I tossed it off the balcony.
Thanks!
Thanks to Honda-kun, I was saved!
Sorry Bakura-kun, can you watch over Mokuba-kun?
Eh... sure, but...
Alright. Let's go look for Pegasus.
Yeah!
Alright! Yugi won!
But we have to hurry and find Pegasus!
Eh? Pegasus was attacked by someone?
Can grandpa and the other's souls return to their bodies?
We then find information about Pegasus'
past and how he got the Millennium Eye.
Next time!
King of Duelists!
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship