Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
The clash between Osiris and Obelisk showed us a vision of our past.
Kaiba, if you insist on denying it,
then good for you.
But for me, without the memories
of my past, I have no future!
If that vision holds some truth to our fated conflict,
then I'm going to awaken it!
I'm going to beat Kaiba and fulfill my promise with Jounouchi-kun!
"The Promise Between Friends:
The Red-Eyes Black Dragon"
It's The Great War God Obelisk!
Did Kaiba-kun Summon
his God Card again?!
Damn it!
What the hell is Yugi doing up there!?
Honda-san?!
Hey, Jounouchi!
How long are you gonna nap for?!
You gotta cheer him too!
Support Yugi!!
Stop this at once!
Honda-san, stop this!
Hold on, Honda!
What the hell are you doing?!
Shut up!!
He wants to see Yugi's fight too!
Honda...
I'm gonna let you see it right now!
Now take a look!
Open your eyes and take a long,
hard look, Jounouchi!
Yugi's... Our Yugi's up there
fighting as we speak!
Yugi...
Your weakness comes from being
trapped in your stupid illusions.
I set one reverse card!
Turn end!
Resurrection of the Dead can only
revive a god for one turn.
Return to the underworld, Obelisk!
Yugi... It's useless to resist.
I'm going to crush you this turn...
...and destroy you along with the
vision of the past in my heart!
My future lies beyond this battle!
My lost memories...
Like Kaiba said, I might just be wallowing in the past...
But I know I can't move forward until I get back what I lost!
Despite supposedly being powerless, the Millennium Tauk showed me a vision of the future!
If I want to make our promise into reality,
I can't let myself lose here!
Yugi?
Where the heck did everyone go?
There you are!
Where the heck were you guys?!
I looked all over!
You're impressive, Jounouchi!
I can't believe you made the Best Eight!
It's cuz I've been training him well!
But in all honesty, I never thought you'd make it this far.
You're pretty good!
What'd ya mean?
The great Katsuya Jounouchi's not satisfied with the Best Eight position!
He aims only for the championship!
For first place!
That's the spirit, Jounouchi-kun!
Yeah!!
Your hand holds
countless possibilities.
If you keep that in mind and work hard, winning the championship may not just be a dream!
What the hell do
ya mean by "may not"?!
You both total at 2000 Life Points.
Tributing is not required.
You may only attack once per turn!
You are not allowed to directly attack
the player with your Monsters!
Understand?
Yes!
Yup!
Then let us begin the first match of the Quarter-Finals!
Here I go! It's my turn!
I will Summon Cat's Fairy!
Turn end!
I'm up!
My turn!
Draw!
Listen carefully, Jounouchi.
You must understand that Monster Cards are meant to be played in combination with Magic Cards.
I'll teach this squirt
the fundamentals of Dueling!
I Summon Magnets #1!
And then,
the Magic Card Legendary Sword!
The Warrior-Type Monster,
Magnets #1, has his Attack and
Defense Power increased by 300 points!
I attack the Cat's Fairy
with Magnets #1!
Nothin' to it!
Turn over!
It wasn't that big of a deal!
It's my turn!
Draw!
I set one reverse card...
...and then Summon
the Lizard Dragon!
Turn end!
What's this now?
Endin' your turn
without even attacking?
You ain't beatin' me
with moves like that.
My turn! Draw!
The only thing a real man
knows how to do is attack!
Magnets #1! Attack Lizard Dragon!
I activate my Trap Card!
Reinforcement!
What?!
Reinforcements grants the Monster
you attacked 500 Attack Points until the
end of the turn it was activated in!
It was sent back?!
Shit!
I can't believe you didn't even
consider my Trap Card!
You must've
made it this far by luck alone!
Am I wrong?
Dammit!
I Summon Tiger Axe!
My turn's over!
You're beyond reckless.
Which one of you lucky mortals is going
to become my offering to the darkness,
and fill my being with the happiness
of enjoying your hellish anguish?
Hurry up and let me choose one of you.
I grow impatient...
My turn! Draw!
Yugi, you believe that our consciousnesses
were reborn thousands of years later
from that of a Pharaoh and a priest...
You're welcome to believe in that
image of the past if you like...
And if you insist on believing that this Duel
is the manifestation of a conflict that began
3,000 years ago, then good for you.
Then allow me to do you the favor
of breaking that illusion
you live by into pieces!
You, along with your past...
I'll destroy that past along with you!
This will be the last turn, Yugi...
I switch Lord of Dragons
into Defense Position!
Magic Card, activate!
Flute of Dragon-Summoning!
The Flute of Dragon-Summoning...!
When Lord of Dragons plays this flute,
I am able to Summon up to
two Dragon-type Monsters
in my hand to the field!
There's only one set of Dragon-Types
Kaiba would play now...!
Come forth!
Blue-Eyes White Dragons!!
Three Blue-Eyes...!
It's my turn! Draw!
I'll Summon Giant Steel Idol!
1400 Attack Points?
He's stronger than my Tiger Axe...!
Shit...
This guy's gonna be trouble.
Dude, your level's way too low!
No way I'd fight you
with such low Attack Points!
Wha...?
I activate a Magic Card!
Fusion!
I polymerize Giant Steel Idol
with Lizard Dragon!
In order to Summon Metal Dragon!
Metal Dragon will attack
your Tiger Axe!
Damn it all! My Life...!
Turn end!
Okay, it's your turn now, dude!
R-Right!
I don't need you to tell me!
My turn, draw!
The Flame Swordsman?
This guy has 1800 Attack Points...
Aww, damn...!
He's 50 Attack Points lower
than his Metal Dragon...!
No helpin' it...
I'm gonna have to hide behind
a Defense Monster!
I Summon Hero of the East
in Defense Position!
Turn over!
I have four Monsters on my field.
And you, Yugi, have nothing but
the Black Magician and that trash Monster.
There's no way you can escape the attacks from all four Monsters this turn!
Yugi! You lose!
Not even Yugi can
get out of this predicament!
My brother's got
this Duel in the bag!
I wonder which
one of them is winning...
I don't care which one of them wins.
I just don't want any more casualties.
Don't worry! I'm sure
Yugi-kun and Kaiba-kun are playing
a fair Duel up there!
I'm rooting for Yugi!
Along with this guy...
It's my turn!
Draw!
I won't let you get away, bro!
The Magic Card, Defense Seal!
What?!
Thanks to the effects
of Defense Seal, Hero of the East
is forced into Attack Mode!
Metal Dragon,
attack Hero of the East!
Aw, shit! My Life Points fell
all the way down to 300!
I set one reverse card
and end my turn!
Let me just say this, dude.
This is the very definition
of "hanging by a thread"!
Stuff a sock in it!
My turn!
Draw!
Shield in the Right Hand,
Sword in the Left Hand
It's a card that switches
the Attack and Defense Points
of all Monsters on the field.
So if I can get out a Monster that
has higher Attack Points than his
Metal Dragon's Defense Points...
I can beat it!
Aw, damn! No luck!
I don't got a Monster
like that in my hand...!
Toss in the towel already, brother!
Nothing you try now will
turn the situation around!
So this is it...?
Your hand holds
countless possibilities.
Wind Fan!
It's an Equipment Magic
that increases the Attack Power
of a Wind Monster by 400 points
and decreases its
Defense Power by 200.
That's it!
Hell yeah! Let's do this!
I Summon the Flame Warrior!
Hey, your Metal Dragon's a
Wind Attribute Monster, isn't it?
Uh-huh...
Then I'll Equip the Magic Card,
Gust Fan, with Metal Dragon!
What was that?
Gust Fan is an
Equipment Magic Card meant
to increase your own Monster's Attack!
On the contrary, purposely increasing your
opponent's Attack Power by equipping it
with them instead is no less than suicide!
Please be serious about this!
I'm about as serious as you can get!
I'm deadly serious!
Magic Card, activate!
Shield in the Right Hand,
Sword in the Left Hand!
With Shield in the Right Hand,
Sword in the Left Hand in effect,
both sides swap point values!
Metal Dragon's Attack Power is 1500!
And Flame Swordsman has 1600!
I-I can't believe you
thought of that combo!
Now go, Flame Swordsman!
Attack the Metal Dragon!
Spear 'im!
Metal Dragon's as good as go-
Wha...
Flame Swordsman was killed!
What's the big deal?
You see, just before you
activated Shield in the Right Hand,
Sword in the Left Hand,
I activated my Trap!
A Trap, you said?!
Castle Walls increases Metal Dragon's
Defense Points by 500 for
the turn this card was activated.
So that means it also changed with the effect of Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand?
Yes.
Flame Swordsman had
1600 Attack Points.
While Metal Dragon had 2000!
So that's 400 points of damage...
That means...
The Duel is finished!!
I did it!
Guess I lost...
But I fought with all I had.
I'm content with that.
I lost completely.
Good luck in the Semi-Finals.
Right!
Thanks a lot, man!
Not just anyone could come up
with such a complicated combo!
You're something else, bro!
I'm sorry for saying that
your level was too low.
Forget about it.
See ya!
Will you Duel me again some day?
Sure! But I'm gonna win next time!
Brace yourself, Yugi!
And carve this
into your memories!
My name! The name of the true winner!
Kaiba's right...
On my field, I have Black Magician
and Magnet Warrior Beta...
There's no way they can stand up
to the attacks of three Blue-Eyes!
Looks like the endgame to me!
So Seto Kaiba's gonna be the first
offering to my darkness, eh?
Blue-Eyes!
Triple Attack!!
Is this the end for me...?
Don't lose, Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Didn't you always used to tell me...
...there's always a chance, as long
as you got cards in your hands?
My hand?!
Don't give up, Yugi!
That's what it means to
be a True Duelist, right?
Now I see!
You have no hope left!
Let the light of the Burst Streams
lead you to darkness, Yug-
What!?
The Red-Eyes!?
The Flute of Dragon-Summoning
lets you Special Summon Dragon-Types
from your hand!
But that effect wasn't just
limited to your hand!
It affected the ones in my hand as well!
The Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
The Soul Card
Jounouchi-kun gave me!
You still had that
cards in your hands?!
What the hell?!
You sure are naive, Kaiba!!
Then my Blue-Eyes will
dispose of the Red-Eyes!!
Get rid of that pest!
Triple Force
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
The first target is the Black Magician!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Magician's Selection!!
Magician's Selection?!
It's a Trap that activates only when a
Spellcaster you control is being attacked!
That attack is negated!
And the Monster with the lowest
Attack Strength on my
opponent's field is destroyed!
But you won't be able to stop
the other two attacks!
Magnet Warrior Beta is gone!
Now go to Hell!
Ghost of Jounouchi!!
His soul can't be broken!!
Reverse Trap, activate!
Hexagram Curse!
The Monster ensnared
by the Hexagram Curse is
rendered unable to attack!
And their Attack Power is
reduced by 700 points!
And now for
the Red-Eyes' counterattack!
Black Fire Bullet!!
Blue-Eyes is destroyed!
Why you...!
My Blue-Eyes lost to
Jounouchi's ghost?!
Jounouchi-kun...
You gave me strength!
Thank you!
Go and win, Yugi!
I will!
Big brother?!
Jounouchi!
The emergence of Red-Eyes
interferes with my plan...
But it won't stop me from wining!
Two more Blue-Eyes!
My memories of the past!
My promise to a friend!
In order to grasp that light,
I will win!
Thanks to the Red-Eyes Jounouchi left with him, Yugi managed to get through all three of the Blue-Eyes attacks!
And somehow, the Summoning of Red-Eyes brought Jounouchi conscious again!
Jounouchi then urges us to go and cheer for Yugi!
And finally, Yugi and Kaiba-kun's
Duel reaches its climax!
Next time!
"Destroy the Hatred!
Black Paladin"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other