Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
Damn you Noah... So you've chosen to use cheap methods like kidnapping my brother, Mokuba?
But I'll get Mokuba back no matter what.
Daimon, if you insist on getting in my way,
I'll just knock you down
and continue forward!
Even if your Deck Master
is Psycho Shocker,
I will win this Duel!
"The Attack from Space:
Satellite Cannon"
What was that thing just now?
It looked like a rocket or something...
That couldn't be...
How the heck do I go about telling them that I'm Honda?
Big brother, let's continue on ahead.
We have to hurry up
and look for Honda-san.
Shizuka-chan~
Oh yeah...
If things go on like this, I'll get to ride in Shizuka-chan's arms all the time.
Shizuka-chan's boobs are as soft as candy floss~!
They're so soft~!
I thought I heard
Honda-kun's voice just now...
Me too...
Did we imagine it?
If this happiness can go on,
this man, Hiroto Honda, doesn't mind living the rest of his life as a monkey!
It can't be...!
This robot...
Huh? What'dya want?
You jerk!!
So you're Honda inside this monkey?!
How dare you disguise
yourself as a monkey!?
Oi, what the hell's this about?!
We still don't know if you're the real Honda-kun. We can't trust you yet.
But it's true!
How else can I prove it?!
But I feel kind of sorry for it...
Shizuka-chan~!
Knock it off!
With 3600 points, I'm practically untouchable now.
Lay off.
My turn!
I activate
Injection Angel Lilly's Special Effect!
I give up 1000 Life Points to increase Lilly's Attack Power by 3000 points!
Go, Injection Angel Lilly!
It's time for your diagnosis!
Here's your injection!
But I'll activate
Dol Dora's Special Effect!
A Regeneration Ability, eh?
How persistent.
I set one card on my field.
I'll then activate the Instant Quick-Play Magic, Emergency Rations, from my hand!
Emergency Rations allows me to sacrifice my other set cards in exchange for 1000 Life Points per card.
Turn end!
His Life just increased again...
If I don't stop his Life Recovery Combo,
I've got no hope of winning.
All that aside, that card he played sent a rocket into the sky...
The moment he declared "turn end", the lever on that meter raised.
Just what the heck is that meter?
Kaiba-kun!
Yugi!
So his friends finally arrived, eh?
Seto, you've got an audience now to watch your last moments.
Big brother...
There's no way
my brother's going to lose!
He'll be here to save me!
You're so convinced
Seto cares about you...
...but what does he think?
Yugi, look at the Deck Master Kaiba's fighting against.
Psycho Shocker!
Then does that mean...?
Kaiba-kun can't
use any of his Trap Cards?
No way!
Then fighting him is pointless, isn't it?!
It's true that this Duel was near impossible from the start.
But only I can open the path I want to walk with my own strength!
My turn!
Daimon, this card will destroy your Life Recovery Combo!
Magic Card! Heavy Storm!
Heavy Storm is a card that destroys all Magic and Trap Cards!
Now you'll lose every Magic and Trap Card on your field!
Seto Kaiba, I'm about to show you that reality is crueler than you think!
Counter Trap, activate!
Imperial Command of the Royal Palace!
What?!
Imperial Command of the Royal Palace is a card that, by the cost of 700 of my Life Points per turn,
negates the effects of all Magic Cards on the field.
Now you can no longer activate Magic or Trap Cards!
Kaiba-kun...
This ain't good. He just got in an even worse situation.
Big brother...
That's Daimon for you.
He's completely analyzed
Seto's Dueling style.
My turn.
Draw card.
Life Recovery Combo, activate!
I then initiate Imperial Command of the Royal Palace.
Now, it's time for me to utilize Gozaburo's ultimate weapon.
Behold its terrible destructive strength!
What did you say?
Satellite Cannon, prepare to fire!
Fire!!
Where did that attack come from...?
It couldn't...!
That's correct. The Satellite Cannon is stationed up in space.
It's the ultimate form of weapon.
That's impossible!
There's no way a Monster could attack all the way from up in space!
As for Satellite Cannon's Special Ability...
It cannot be destroyed by a Level 7 or lower Monster!
What did you say...?
And the weakling of a Monster you had on the field wouldn't have had enough Attack Power to stop it anyway.
And when my turn comes to an end,
Satellite Cannon charges its Attack Energy by 1000 points!
Well? How's it feel to be tortured by the great weapon Gozaburo invented!
I bore witness on the day you drove Gozaburo to his death!
And you will now
be punished for your crime!
For that purpose, you used your innocent little brother Mokuba as if he were a tool!
Kaiba-kun did what...?
No way! My brother used me?!
You weren't aware?
Then you'd better keep an open heart as you listen to what he says.
Seto's true form.
Think back.
To the day Gozaburo Kaiba set that test up for you.
On that day, you proved you had what it took to be a ruthless business dominator.
But your ability to earn such a large sum of money in a small period of time surpassed even Gozaburo's expectations.
But it more than anything, that day set you off on a path of cruelty.
Seto-sama, why did you call the five of us to such a secretive meeting?
If the five of you
work together with me,
we will be able to steal President Gozaburo's wealth from right under his nose.
How would you like to work with me and take over Kaiba Corporation?
We all worked together and began slowly buying Kaiba Corporation stocks.
However, we soon ran into trouble.
Because someone began leaking information of our plan to Gozaburo.
And you put the blame on Mokuba!
That's right... That day...
Big brother...?
Just how far
do you think I'll tolerate this?!
Big brother, please believe me!
It wasn't me!
Silence!
Throw him out of here!
That was the worst day of my life...
Feeling hurt and betrayed, the saddened Mokuba went to Gozaburo for comfort.
But of course, Gozaburo was only after the two "cards" Mokuba held.
With Mokuba's share, Gozaburo held 51 "cards" in his hand.
Believing he had won, he stopped buying stocks.
As agreed, it has been one year since our last meeting.
As such, I called you hear to discuss something very important.
It's useless, Seto!
I know you intend to buy me out,
but you only hold 49%.
I hold 51% on my side.
As such, I have no intentions of handing over my position as president.
Starting right now, Kaiba Corporation declares bankruptcy!
All our assets will be transferred to a subsidiary!
So that makes your stocks worth garbage!
You will mortgage your life to me,
and I will continue to hold the title you worked so hard to obtain!
Wait!
Mokuba...!
I... I give my two cards to my big brother!
You can't!
He disowned you!
My brother was
just a bit angry then!
Mokuba!!
I won't betray my big brother!
In these events, it looks like you were the one to lose everything.
On the very same day, having lost everything he worked so hard for, Gozaburo committed suicide.
And what are you implying?
Weren't you the one who caused it?
The one who leaked
the plan to Gozaburo...
Seto Kaiba! It was you!
That's not possible!
You tricked Gozaburo into thinking it was another responsible for leaking the information.
You set it up so he had no chance of winning.
So you used both Gozaburo and Mokuba to achieve your desire.
You betrayed Mokuba and had him go to Gozaburo for comfort.
That was your plan from the start!
You did all that, knowing Mokuba would return to your side!
I... I just believed in Mokuba.
That our bond would beat Gozaburo!
Enough excuses, Seto!
Can you imagine how Mokuba felt when you took advantage of his trust and used him?!
And you pushed Gozaburo to his death in the same manner!
You gotta be kidding...
My brother used me...?
And you used us, the Big Five, in the same exact way.
We thought we
were in on it together at first,
but in the end we realized we were just being used by you!
I'll pay back that anger in ten-fold!
Life is a game.
I won't let you crush my dream!
My turn!
I Summon Spirit Dragon!
I switch Dol Doral into Attack Mode!
Spirit Dragon, attack Lilly!
Spirit Sonic!!
Have you gone mad, Seto?
I activate Lilly's Special Ability!
Kaiba-kun!
Not good! If this attack fails, Kaiba's Life Points will hit zero!
Now I'm the winner!
Let's not rush here. I activate Spirit Dragon's Special Ability!
For every Dragon-Type Monster I discard from my hand,
Spirit Dragon's Attack Power goes up 1000 points!
Unreal! You raised your Monster's Attack Power just to spare a few Life Points?!
Kaiba-kun's fighting style
is way too risky!
Is he on a suicide mission?!
No, that's not it!
It's part of Kaiba-kun's plan!
Kaiba's plan?
Dol Dora, attack Lilly!
Oh no!
I don't have enough Life to activate Lilly's Special Ability!
No~!!
He runs a deck using a Life Recovery Combo along with his Monsters.
But if that cycle is disturbed...
My turn!
Daimon, don't forget to pay 700 Life Points in order to keep Imperial Command of the Royal Palace in effect.
On this turn, I will destroy Imperial Command of the Royal Palace!
Now he can use Magic Cards again!
I get it! If his cycle is broken when he can't pay Life Points anymore,
that begins the self-destruction of his own combo!
Now Kaiba-kun has a chance!
Daimon, if this is the level of your strategical ability, you wouldn't stand a chance running my company.
Silence!
My turn isn't over yet!
A Monster in Defense Mode!
And then, I fire the Satellite Cannon!
My turn!
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
Using its effect, I draw two cards from my deck!
In addition, I Summon Possessing Blood Soul!
Blood Soul, attack his Defense Monster!
Soul Burning!!
It's no use! Dream Sprite!!
Dream Sprite's Effect lets me redirect your attack to any other Monster I have on the field.
As such, I switch Blood Soul's attack to target Satellite Cannon!
No good! Kaiba's Monster can't reach all the way up into space!
My turn!
Just one turn and my Satellite Cannon will be charged enough to attack.
And then Seto's Life will hit zero!
My turn is over!
Bastard! He didn't even attack!
He's probably trying to gather its energy to finish the match.
Satellite can only be attacked by a Monster with over Level 7!
Seto, your life ends in just one turn!
It's impossible... Getting a Monster higher than Level 7...
No... Kaiba-kun has that Monster in his deck!
Everything is riding on this draw...
My turn...
Awaken, the blue flame burning within my deck!
You couldn't have...!
Here I go!
I Summon a Monster in Defense Mode!
I'll then activate my Deck Master Ability right now!
Lord of Dragon's Deck Master Ability allows me to Summon a Dragon Monster from my hand for the cost of 500 Life Points!
I'll then sacrifice both these Monsters!
Two sacrifices?!
It's time to show yourself before us!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Aim for space!
Blue-Eyes!!
Blue-Eyes is a Level 8 Monster...!
I can't believe you actually drew that Monster!
Blue-Eyes, soar straight through the clouds!
At the moment you attack Satellite Cannon,
this Monster loses its attack strength.
So that makes its true Attack Power...
...zero!
Dammit!
My dreams of creating games won't lose to some weapon!
Disappear, ghost of Gozaburo!
Burst Stream of Destruction!!
He did it!
Kaiba completely turned this around!
Where's Mokuba?
Who knows...!
But Seto, don't think this is over!
He did it!
My big brother won!
Mokuba, you don't hate Seto...?
Even though he betrayed you?
I trust in my big brother!
No matter how I might feel at the time, it still doesn't matter!
Mokuba...
MOKUBA!!
Now that Kaiba-kun won, that means all five of the Big Five have been defeated.
But Mokuba-kun hasn't come back,
and Honda's still a monkey.
Isn't this different from what they promised us?!
Kaiba-kun goes on
alone to save Mokuba-kun,
and me and Yugi wind up in Kaiba-kun's old mansion while following him!
And what we find there...
Next time!
"The Mystery Deepens: Noah's True Colors"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise