Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
"The Secret of the Hieratic Text"
Th-That's the
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra?!
O-Oi!
It's...!
That's the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra?!
I get that it's round like the sun...
But is that all?
This don't look a thing like what appeared in my Duel!
But I feel it...
I feel its overwhelming presence!
And it shines with a divine light radiant of God!
I'm certain this is authentic!
This can't be...!
The three Harpy Ladies I sacrificed should have met the Summoning Conditions...!
So... How did this happen?!
Relax, woman.
What you Summoned is the true Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra...!
That's its true form?!
I knew it!
But it's a pity...
It's impossible for a Duelist of your caliber to control a god.
Only Duelists chosen
by God can wield a god!
Don't be stupid!
When a card falls
into the hands of a Duelist,
all its powers belong to the Duelist who possesses it!
As of now, the God Card is mine!
In that case, take a look at the God Card set on your Duel Disk.
What in the-
In the text space of the card...
Some kind of hieroglyphics?!
How strange...
When I took the card from Malik,
there was nothing written in the text space!
But...
Now there's definitely hieroglyphs written there!
Can you decipher the script?
It contains the key to awakening the true powers of Ra!
Ra's true powers?!
That's right...
Ra has quite the terrifying Special Abilities hidden within it...
Hidden Special Abilities within Ra?!
Shit! I can't see it!
What's the card look like?
Mokuba, use the "Satellite Search" to capture the image of it set on Mai Kujaku's Duel Disk.
Then scan the God Card.
I get it!
Good idea, big brother!
I'll start on it right now!
What secrets lie in Ra's card text?
It's no use...
There's no way I can translate this text's meaning!
It's impossible...
Unless you can read that text, you can't control Ra or activate its Special Abilities.
But I'll tell you one thing...
Those letters are Hieratic Text!
Ancient letters written by the priests.
What the heck's that?!
Hieratic Text...?!
Ancient letters written by the priests?
It was a language used for law, literature and religion in Ancient Egypt.
Unlike the common demotic text, only those with special status were taught it...
And of course...
The chosen ones can
read it with their hearts!
And it's only natural we Tomb Guardians know it as well!
There's no way!
A card existing in a card game that only "special people" can use?!
Even the creator of Duel Monsters, Pegasus J. Crawford,
couldn't decipher the
hidden abilities of Ra.
He was forced to literally transcribe the Hieratic Text right onto the card.
And it holds a special feature that makes the letters only become visible in the light emitted by Ra.
He let me steal his God Card on purpose, knowing I can't use it?!
Right now, Ra is in Sphere Mode.
It acts as a motionless ball.
Now try solving the riddle to change it to Battle Mode!
Hurry up and take control of the god, Mai Kujaku!
Mai!
Damn that Malik! Bastard!
So he was never afraid of losing Ra from the start?!
Malik wanted Mai to Summon Ra!
Mai Kujaku sacrificed three Harpy ladies to Summon the God...
Ra's Attack and Defense Power is determined by the total points of the Monsters used to Summon it.
In other words, Ra should have 5400 Attack and 4200 Defense.
And yet the god remains silent...
It's not showing any signs of attacking or defending...
What does the text say?
What is the condition to activate Ra?
I don't know...!
Is there any way to use it?!
As far as you are concerned, that god may as well not exist on your field.
Even if I attack you with one of my Monsters next turn, the god won't protect you.
Unless you decipher the secret of God,
you will suffer that
hellish pain once again.
Hey now...
You could always pray to God...!
I've got no choice!
I set a reverse card!
Turn over!
My face-down Trap is Gravity Bind!
If I activate it, all 4 Star Monsters are forbidden to attack!
In the meantime, I'll work on trying to decipher Ra's secrets!
My turn...
I Summon Holding Legs!
I pity you...
This thing has a Special Ability.
When this card is played on the board,
all reverse cards are sent back to the player's hand.
Furthermore, when the two cards Holding Arms and Holding Legs are gathered together...
...the Sacred Palette
of Wadjet is called forth!
Neither Magic nor Traps nor God can protect you...
Let the darkness and pain embrace you, Mai Kujaku!
Holding Arms!
Holding Legs!
Mai!
Impossible!
This should only be Solid Vision...!
But I can't move!!
I thought I told you
that this is a Dark Game...
Everything that happens here is real!
Even the pain you feel from the attacks!
Directly attack the player!
Mai!
Hang in there!
I... hear it again...
That warm voice...
-Give yourself to the pain!
-Stop it!
Malik!
Quite an entertaining show, isn't it Yugi?
I shall now begin the preparations for the Sacrifice of Darkness!
Sacrifice of Darkness?
Listen very closely!
Ra has three Special Abilities!
I'll reveal just one of them!
What?!
Three Special Abilities?!
What...?! He's chanting some kind of spell...!
Yugi, take a look at that!
Ra's changing its form!
This must be...!
This is one of Ra's abilities.
God himself will serve the player who utters the sacred text!
Bring me victory!
Awaken, Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!!
This is the Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
So that's...!
The Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
My turn!
With one attack from Ra, I'll burn this woman up with Ra's sacred flames!
Mai!
On this turn, Ra's attack will reduce Mai's Life to nothing!
If this is a Dark Game, the moment Mai loses...!
You're a perfect sacrifice, Mai Kujaku...
Restrained as you are, unable to move your arms and legs...
You can't even place your hand on your deck to surrender.
I'll make it quick,
just one attack from Ra!
Become ash and spread into darkness!!
Damn him...! If he doesn't stop, Mai will...!
Stop it, Malik!
This match is over!
There's no reason to attack her!
Keep your eyes open, Yugi!
I will sacrifice this woman to the darkness!
And draw out all
your hatred in the process!
Malik!!
On my back is
carved the Seal of Memories.
It tells the location of the Pharaoh's memories that my family has protected for thousands of years!
All so that one day, it can be presented to the resurrected soul of the Pharaoh.
The Seal of Memories...!
For that purpose and that purpose alone,
countless generations of my family lived and died.
Our only birthright was darkness...
And a deep scar...
Despair and pain. That is all...
Like it?
That is the trauma that dominates my other self!
Darkness robbed him of his freedom,
and even more darkness was born in his self-pitying heart!
And the pain and hatred that exists within his dark heart...
These things belong to me.
I knew it!
He's Malik's split personality!
My birthday was when he was ten years old.
On the day the Rite of the Tomb Guardians was performed on him.
His father filled him
with pain and sadness...
Until his heart was so enshrouded that all he wanted to do was die.
So in order to survive,
in order to keep living...
...he had to create another self.
From the moment I was born, I always knew I would take his personality over!
But there was one thing which stood in my way.
I can only switch personalities when he is filled with rage...
Rishid...
Without even knowing, that man sealed me away within the carving on his face.
And sealed his anger along with it...
I was confined deep inside Malik's heart.
But the moment he fell unconscious,
I am finally the ruler of this body!
What do you want?!
The God Cards?
Or...?!
What do I want?
I have no needs!
But if you really want an answer...
I want to get rid of all light and order...
And I want to destroy all lives aside from my own!
Destruction!!
Destruction is my pleasure!
That is what gives birth to my world!
A world of darkness and death!
Malik...!
And now...
I will send this woman to perish in the darkness!
Jounouchi-kun!
Before he attacks Mai with Ra...!
Hey!
Lower the Duel Ring!
No way! This Duel is not over!
You'll be disqualified, Jounouchi!
Shut up!
So this is it...?
It's all over now.
Ra! Burn that woman!!
Mai!!
Winged Sun Dragon of Ra! Attack!
-Mai-san!!
Die.
Mai!
Mai, get out of here now!
This voice...
...from before...
Big brother!
Jounouchi!
Futile!
That woman won't remember you!
Damn it...!
Who...?
Mai, you...
I hear something in my heart...
A warm voice.
You...
You really... don't know who I am?
I hear it again...
It's me, Mai!
Jounouchi!
Jou...?
How could you forget?
Aren't we friends who've fought together all this time?!
We're... friends...?
You gotta win so you can Duel against me and Yugi, right?!
I'm not gonna let you forget all that!
I owe you a huge debt!
When I was struck by lightning and fell unconscious in my Duel earlier...
I had a dream about everyone that helped save me!
For some reason I didn't have the strength to stand up,
and then you guys all reached out your hands to help me.
And you were there, too!
It was embarrassing,
so I didn't tell you before!
Mai, you were there!
Jou...
Jounouchi!
Mai! So you remember me?
So their bond actually broke the Power of Darkness...?
But it's too late!
Move!
This is my fight!
Are you crazy?!
Hurry and get outta here!
Shit! Isn't this Solid Vision?!
Why won't it budge?!
Jounouchi...
You're always by my side...
But I...
Run, Jounouchi!
You dumbass! You think I can do that now?!
Go! Winged Sun Dragon of Ra!
God Blaze Cannon!!
You've got another fight waiting for you! Come on!!
You think I can stand and watch my friend get killed?!
Jounouchi...
Damn it all!!
Thank you, Jounouchi...
The reason I entered this tournament was so that I could see you again!
-Yugi!
It almost makes my cry.
Throwing yourself in front of Ra's attack to prevent your pals from dieing...
Malik...! Your anger and hatred...!
I'll take it all on my back!
But I swear to send
you back to the darkness!
-Yugi!
Talk while you can!
Soon I'll crush you into pieces along with the Millennium Puzzle!
And scatter them into
the darkness for all eternity!
-Yugi!
Yugi!!
Yugi! Pull yourself together, Yugi!
In Ra's attack just now, the woman lost all her Life Points.
It's game over.
Hey judge!
Call my name and
announce me the winner!
And loudly if you will!
Tournament third round!
The winner is Malik!
Malik Ishtar. The real one.
Yugi! Yugi!
Shall I tear him apart
right here and now?
You bastard!
Don't worry. I merely jest.
I'll destroy Yugi in a Duel.
In a match most befitting those chosen by the Millennium Items... in the ultimate Dark Game!
What the?
I can't move...!
I can kill you whenever I wish.
Now then, it's about time you give me my God Card back.
You're lucky you got away with your life...
But you'll regret it.
You'll wish you had
died here painlessly...
The loser of a Dark Game
must be punished...
Punished...?
Mai Kujaku...
I plan on letting you enjoy the inside of the world in your mind to the fullest!
Jounouchi!
We are inside a space that exists deep within your mind.
Don't they seem to be having fun?
But you will never
get to return to them again.
When this Ra card is pulled out,
the sand of memory will fall.
And when it does,
your entire memory will disappear!
and you'll be slowly tortured to death as you perish in the darkness!
It'll be slow...
Oh so slow...
You'll feel the pain of losing one friend after another.
Well then, good night...
I'm taking my card back...
Jounouchi...
Mai!
Malik, what the hell did you do to her?!
As we speak, that woman is falling deeper and deeper into darkness.
She shall suffer both extreme loneliness and suffering in her heart.
This woman won't remember a thing.
Neither you nor Yugi.
What?!
"Where was I born?"
"Where did I live?"
No, she'll forget the very reason she exists.
She'll wander in immeasurable loneliness, doomed to never regain conscious again.
If you defeat me, there's a chance she'll recover.
How much are you
going to hurt my friends?!
I'll kill you, Malik!
I'm gonna kick your sorry ass!
Relax. I'll drown you
in darkness soon as well.
The power inside
me has been released...
The more souls I sacrifice to the darkness, the more it fuels my power!
Mai!
Wake up!
Mai-san!
It's no use! She's still unconscious!
If I don't beat Malik, Mai will...
Wait for me, Mai...
I promise I'll...
Yugi! Yugi's awake!
Yugi!
Yugi, don't overdo it!
I'm alright...!
Jounouchi-kun, what about Mai?!
Well...
Malik did this...
The hidden personality born from Malik's subconscious...!
He won't get away with this!
Yugi, please don't hurt yourself anymore!
Seriously!
Is that you, Mokuba?
Big brother, the text on the Ra card has been successfully scanned!
I'll analyze it right now.
I see.
I'm counting on you.
I'm proceeding to the fourth round of the tournament.
Yugi!
Clear the loser off of my field!
Kaiba...!
It's now time for my god, Obelisk, to descend!
This is going to become a sacred arena!
"Preview"
While Mai-san is still unconscious and not waking up, the fourth match begins.
Kaiba-kun's opponent is the eighth Duelist whom no one has seen.
You're the person we met in the Ancient Egyptian exhibit at the museum, Ishizu-san!
What are you doing here?!
Seeing the future
with her Millennium Tauk,
Ishizu-san declares Kaiba-kun's loss.
I do feel bad for Kaiba-kun, but...
Next time!
"Kaiba VS the Eighth Duelist"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise