Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
We are the warriors of the Ghouls.
Mask of Light.
Mask of Darkness.
We are a Tag Team assembled for the sole purpose of getting the God Cards back!
If we don't combine our power in this Duel, we have no chance of defeating the Ghouls!
Cooperation...?
My turn!
Reverse card open!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Blue-Eyes White Dragon returns!
Here I come!
Mask Spinner, do your thing!
Two of the cards are Magic Cards...
And the other is...
The strongest Monster Card our Decks can produce!
The card was chosen...!
I did it! I'm really lucky!
The Masked Beast Death Guardias!
The Masked Beast Des Gardius
It has 3300 Attack Points...!
It's stronger than Blue-Eyes?!
I have 1 card in my hand that might work...
But if I attack him now...
Now then...
Who should I attack with Death Guardias?
Obelisk the Giant War God
If I were to attack him right now..
it would be in vain!
Yugi, you have Magnet Warrior Alpha on the field in Attack Mode.
If I took him out, you'd receive 1900 points of damage!
In other words, Yugi, you'd die this turn!
But getting rid of just one of them doesn't guarantee us victory in this Tag Duel.
Forgetting Yugi for the moment, leaving Kaiba and that Blue-Eyes of his on the field could present a problem.
No, I'm gonna beat Yugi!
What a coward!
Even with a Monster holding 3300 Attack Points, you still back down.
What?!
I'd thank you for defeating Yugi!
But next turn, my Blue-Eyes would destroy your Monster.
Kaiba...!
Are you actually using your Blue-Eyes as bait?!
It's true Yugi's Monsters are weaklings.
I can beat them any time...
This turn truly...
Destroy Blue-Eyes!
Dark Destruction
Blue-Eyes blew to smithereens!
Forgive me, Blue-Eyes...
Yugi, it's your turn!
Right!
Kaiba! Blue-Eyes's soul...
Will be inherited by this card!
Ghouls! You fell right into our trap!
What?!
My Blue-Eyes was bait.
In order to play an even stronger Monster.
Impossible...!
Your ability to Sacrifice
Summon should be sealed!
It's true we can't sacrifice any Monsters.
But behold the Ability of this card, our alternative!
Magnet Warrior Gamma!
Gamma the Magnet Warrior
And the Special Ability of Alpha, Beta and Gamma!
Change Form!
Change Form?!
What?!
That's...!
The Magnetic Warrior - Magnet Valkyrian!
This is the combined power of our greatest efforts!
What'd ya say?!
Death Guardias only has 3300 Attack Points...
And Magnet Valkyrian holds 3500 Attack Points!
Magnet Valkyrian has more Attack Points!
Yugi, attack!
Destroy the Monster that eliminated my Blue-Eyes!
Kaiba...!
The power of cooperation is indeed great.
But my Blue-Eyes's anger won't be eased by this alone!
It's true they have no reverse cards on the field...
Magnet Valkyrian can easily defeat the enemy Monster.
But I feel it...
Those guys aren't scared of my attack.
What if...?!
Death Guardias has a hidden Special Ability...?
That's right!
Come attack, just like Kaiba said, Yugi!
At that same moment, I'll send you both to hell!
Why are you hesitating, Yugi?!
I sacrificed my Blue-Eyes so you could play your trump card!
Then hurry up and eliminate the enemy Monster with that trump card and ease my anger!
I set a reverse card!
Kaiba, will that really ease your emotions if I do that this turn?!
If it will, I'll attack!
What?
Emotions only hold a Duelist back.
By giving into them, you're falling right into the enemy's hand.
No way!
A fight is about anger!
Stay calm, Kaiba!
And think about the key to victory!
Key to victory...?
My trump card...
Is the God Card Obelisk!
But in order to Summon the god, I require 3 sacrifices...
As long as they hold the Mask of Sacrifice Sealing on their field,
I can't Summon Obelisk.
No, there's a way!
A way to Summon the god!
Is Yugi also using Magnet Valkyrian as bait?
The key to victory...
Is for me to accept the power of cooperation in this Duel!
Yugi, attack.
Right!
Magnet Valkyrian, attack!
Magnet Saber!!
You fell for it!
I beat it...
But this guy's got a Special Ability too ya know!
Special Ability...?
Death Guardias leaves behind 3 masks after it dies.
And those masks...
Form the Mask of Remnant!
To avenge the fall of Death Guardias,
this mask takes your Monster as our servant!
Mask of Remnant attaches itself to Magnet Valkyrian!
Magnet Valkyrian's ours now!
Well done.
It's all over, Yugi!
You got no Monster to protect ya!
Partner, you finish off Yugi.
I'm gonna finish off Kaiba.
Got it.
Cuz Kaiba made
a fool out a me before!
My anger won't settle till I defeat him!
My turn.
Got it.
Mask Army!
This card allows me to control Mask of Light's Monsters this turn!
Go, Magnetic Valkyrian!
Direct Attack Yugi!
Yugi...!
Beat you!
Beat ya!
I'm not so sure of that.
Reverse card open!
Fusion Release!
What!?
That's impossible!
Remember this!
Your anger is no match against us!
My turn!
I'll let you fools see God once again.
God?!
No freakin' way!
I got the Mask of Restrict on my field!
How the hell do you expect to Summon God with your sacrificing sealed away?!
That card restraints us from sacrificing our own Monsters.
Then I'll just sacrifice your Monsters instead!
With this card!
The Magic Card Cross Sacrifice!
I'll sacrifice your Magnet Warriors!
Our Monsters?!
So Yugi fooled us into taking his Magnet Valkyrian so Kaiba could sacrifice them and Summon the god?!
God descends!
Behold!
This is the God of Destruction sleeping in our hands!
I have now awakened
Obelisk the Giant War God!
Seto Kaiba...!
How is this man chosen to wield the God Cards?!
Disappear, weaklings!
God Hand Crusher!!
Partner!
You alright, Partner?!
After Obelisk the Giant War God attacked you, you lost all your Life.
And you fools are about to fall into your own trap!
The Life Counter on my bomb hit 0!
Partner!
OI~!
PARTNER, YOU SAFE?!
Parachute, eh?
Well, I expected that of you guys from the start,
but this isn't much of a "Death Match", now is it?
You no longer have any hopes of defeating us.
How about you surrender?
I won't accept that!
The conditions to win a Tag Match clearly state both opposing members must be defeated.
I'm gonna send him to hell!
Wait, Kaiba.
There's no reason to harm him as well.
Such an act will tarnish our humanity as Duelists.
To crush my enemy is the only "humanity" I have!
What the?
Ma... li...
Malik?!
I saw Obelisk clearly!
The power of the god is really strong!
Malik! Stop hiding and show yourself!
His personality's changed...!
Yeah.
Right now, he's being controlled by another person altogether.
Impossible!
By who, exactly?
The leader of the Ghouls!
Malik!
The man who owns the final God Card!
The owner of Ra the Winged Dragon?!
Pleased to meet you, Kaiba-kun.
Malik...!
He's the other enemy I've been after in this Battle City...
Right, right!
I thank you for getting rid of my weak underlings in this Duel.
They were simply here to buy me some time.
My plan proceeds as scheduled.
To start, these Rare Hunters have allowed me to witness the entirety of your Decks.
There's no way you guys can beat my Deck.
And moreover, my Ra card holds a hidden terrifying power, stronger than both of your cards.
It's the strongest card in existence.
Ra has a power stronger than my Obelisk...?
And there's one more part to my plan.
And Yugi, that is related to our fight that has lasted over 3,000 years...
You must perish at my hands to ease the anger of the Tomb Keepers Tribe and carry our our revenge!
In order to ensure my revenge,
I've prepared a few extra soldiers on my team.
The little followers you call friends have already fallen into my control.
And have become warriors that will be used against you.
My friends...?
He's talking about Jounouchi-kun and the others...?
Malik! What have you done to Jounouchi-kun and the others?!
It seems as though they've become puppets...
Puppets?!
You mean to say you're controlling them like dolls in the Ghoul Rare Hunters?!
That's right.
Your friends have already become my hands.
Now Yugi...
Come to where your friends wait!
And fight Jounouchi on the stage of death!
Malik!
You bastard!!
What have you done with my little brother...
With Mokuba?!
We won this fight!
Return Mokuba to me like you promised!
Promised...?
Return...?
You bastard!
Kaiba, this guy is now just a doll being controlled by Malik!
It's pointless to threaten him!
Malik...!
Kaiba, please!
Help me find Jounouchi-kun and the others!
Mokuba should be there as well!
Of course, I'll get Mokuba back.
But there's something else to take care of before that...
Yugi, take this.
These are the Puzzle Cards we won from beating the Ghouls.
We each get 1.
Now you and me both have 6.
We now both qualify for the Battle City finals.
Kaiba, this is not the time or place to be fighting over the tournament final places!
I have to find my friends right away!
Find your friends?
Big brother!
Mokuba!
Mokuba, you're not hurt?
Yup, Anzu saved me!
Is Anzu safe?
What about Jounouchi-kun and Honda-kun?
Sorry, I only know where Anzu is.
And there was no one else with us.
Get on the helicopter, Yugi.
Seems your friend saved Mokuba.
It's a policy of mine to always return my debts to people.
Kaiba...
Ma'am, gimme some boxed lunches!
Ah, right.
Which one do you want?
Uh, I'll take every one of these boxed lunches.
Hurry it up!
The train's gonna leave!
Could Honda-san have...
Missed the train...?
Sorry for the wait~!
I brought loads of goodies~!
Shizuka-chan, what do you want to eat?
Macaroni, sandwiches, sushi;
I've got anything you can think of!
Um...
What is it?
I know I'm probably annoying you by now...
But do you think I'll just be a burden to my big brother?
Of course you won't be a burden!
But why'd you say something like that?
I felt really dumb when I relied on big brother's courage on the day of the operation...
And I can't do anything for big brother in return...
What're ya talkin' about?
He'll work his hardest because you're there!
He does it for his one and only precious little sister, ya know!
But right now I can only root for big brother.
And I'm too scared to do anything on my own!
I can only rely on my big brother's courage!
But won't he be getting courage from you this time around?
The courage to win all his Duels!
That's true!
This is not the time to be getting scared!
It's my turn to give courage to my big brother!
Right! That's it!
Mokuba, can't you track them?
I found them!
The single on Jounouchi's Duel Disk is coming from Domino Port!
Domino Port...?
That's the place where we all left for Duelist Kingdom, isn't it?
Please be safe!
In order to save Jounouchi and I from the Ghouls,
Yugi heads for Domino Port in Kaiba-kun's helicopter.
Yugi tells the story of Ancient Egypt to Kaiba-kun, who has learned the identity of the leader of the Ghouls, Malik,
and the beginning of his clash with Malik's tribe.
Yugi, what's going to happen to us?
Next time.
Bonds
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...