Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
On our way to Alcatraz, the final site of the Battle City Finals,
we were captured by this brat named Noah and trapped inside Virtual Space.
I need to hurry up and beat Malik so I can save Mai,
but if I don't win this Duel, I won't be able to get out and my body will be taken!
Thus, I began a Duel with one of the Big Five disguised as Judge Man.
But it looks like I may have gotten a bit too cocky with him!
"Betting on Victory"
Now! It's your turn!
Yeah, I know that!
Draw!
Chaos Wizard has
1300 Attack Points...
If I power up my Swordsman of Landstar using my Deck Master's ability...
But still,
that reverse card bothers me...
If that turns out to be a Trap Card...
Don't bother thinking about it...
If I use my 2000 Attack Power Panther Warrior,
he doesn't stand a chance.
I Summon the Jet-Black Beast Warrior, Panther Warrior!
And then...
I set a reverse card!
There's no way his Chaos Wizard can beat the Panther Warrior's 2200 Attack Power.
But even if he managed to increase its Attack Power somehow,
I'll use my Devil Dice
to power it down.
I'd like to take care
of him right now, but...
For now, I'll play it safe.
Turn over!
My turn. Draw!
Reverse card, open.
I activate the Permanent Magic Card, Hade's Leading Question!
While Leading Question is in play,
whenever I attack the enemy's Monster with a Level 4 or lower Fusion Monster,
it gains 800 Attack Points!
Chaos Wizard attacks!
J-Just hold on a minute!
So you powered him
up after all, did ya?!
Then same goes for me!
Devil Dice!
Alright~!
What!?
A one!?
God damn it!
With a one, the enemy's Monster's Attack Power won't change at all!
Did I not tell you?
I am capable of
turning black into white.
Furthermore, you have received damage from Chaos Wizard, a Fusion Monster.
I activate the Permanent Magic, Plea of Darkness!
I receive an 800 point
boost to my Life Points!
Dammit!
You never know the outcome of a Duel until the very end.
Jounouchi-kun!
Hang on!
He just turned this
whole thing around!
Man, what the heck
are you doing, Jounouchi?!
God! Can it!
Now Jounouchi, it's your turn!
Hade's Leading Question...
A Continuous Magic that raises a Fusion Monster's Attack Power by 800 points whenever it battles.
So that means if I don't draw a Monster with more than 2100 Attack Points, I can't beat the Chaos Wizard.
But the only Monster I have in my hand is the 500 Attack Swordsman of Landstar.
Whatever is the matter?
Seems you may have overused your Deck Master's ability a bit!
Lay off!
Shit!
The way this is headed, I've gotta depend on the card I draw!
Hurry up and draw already!
My turn!
Draw!
Angel Dice...
Alright! This will let me power up the Swordsman of Landstar's Attack Points!
I Summon Landstar of Swordsman!
And then...!
I'll power it up with
the Magic Card, Angel Dice!
Go!
Booyah! Did it!
It landed a one again?!
That's freakin' impossible!
I've never seen Jounouchi have such bad luck before...
Yeah...
I activate my Deck Master Ability!
Life Sentence!!
Not good...
I don't have any Monsters left...
What the heck should I do?
Jounouchi...
I place two reverse cards face-down and end my turn.
Then it's my... turn!
Pot of Greed, is it?
Pot of Greed?
With your current hand at zero,
I bet this is a card you'd like to draw, isn't it?
Thanks to the effects of the Pot of Greed Magic Card, I draw two new cards from my deck!
So that puts your hand at six.
Trap Card! Gamble!
When my opponent
has six cards in his hand,
and my hand has two or less,
I can activate it.
It's the Gamble card!
Gamble?
You flip a coin and
declare heads or tails.
If you guess right, you get to draw from your deck until you hold five cards.
It's a Trap Card.
Jounouchi's hand is at 0 right now...
But if you lose the bet,
you are forced to skip your next turn.
I'm counting on you...
If there really is a Goddess of Luck watching over me,
now is the time
to show me you're with me!
That's it. That's precisely what I want.
Continue to increase your addiction, more and more...
...and fail miserably each time!
That is the true terror of gambling.
Coin Toss!
The sea?
This damn Noah...
How long do you plan to keep on twisting my arm?
Dammit!
I thought for sure we were outta the Virtual Space this time!
Noah's such a jerk!
He really pisses me off!
He's definitely the type that has no friends, big brother!
Yell all you like.
We're being monitored by his little cameras anyhow.
You hear, Noah?!
You can keep up this ridiculous clip show all you like!
We've long moved on past these events! You can't wear us down this way!
You better get ready!
Seto, you're sadly mistaken if you think I don't know how to get under your skin.
Now then, I am curious as to what is happening in the current Duel.
Heads!
Tails?!
I failed... again...!
You're kidding!
He failed again?!
Jounouchi-kun...
No matter what you do,
the result will be the same.
I am the only
winner in this courtroom.
Damn it all!
Instant Magic!
Scapegoat, activate!
That sure is pitiful of you, you know.
My turn's not even finished yet!
I activate the Magic Card, Reinforcement!
It allows me to add one Level 4 or lower Warrior-Type Monster to my hand...
Deck Shuffle!
And I'll activate the Fusion Magic Card from my hand!
From my hand, I fuse Armaill and One-Eyed Shield Dragon.
I Summon
Magically Armored Knight Dragoness!
Another low-Attack Monster?
Unless it has over 1500 Attack Points, I can't use my Trap Card.
And thanks to the effect of Hade's Leading Question,
when he attacks,
his Attack Power will rise!
Shit...! He got me!
I use Chaos Wizard to
attack your Scapegoats!
And then I use Magically Armored Knight Dragoness to attack another Scapegoat!
Turn over.
Damn it! My turn!
Thanks to the results of Gamble, you are hereby sentenced to skip your turn!
Th-That's right!
My turn. Draw!
Chaos Wizard, attack his Scapegoat!
In addition, Magically Armored Knight Dragoness attacks the last Scapegoat!
They're all gone...!
My turn is over.
Your have nothing in your hand.
You have no Monsters on the field.
Katsuya Jounouchi, your sentence has been decided!
You shall lose this Duel!
I've already used up the Devil Dice and the Angel Dice...
Dammit...!
I even used Gamble...!
I've got nothing left...!
Stay with us, Jounouchi!
It's still your turn!
Don't give up until the end!
But the Goddess of Luck has completely deserted me!
This must be the end...
Jounouchi...
But to lose a
gamble three times in a row...
It's pretty strange.
Yeah, I was
thinking the same thing, Partner.
He failed a gamble
three times in a row.
It could just be a coincidence, but I feel it's more than that.
This guy is up to something.
If that's true, he's going to lose!
This Duel is canceled!
Noah-sama?!
Noah!
It's that kid...
This Duel is canceled!
What do you mean by that?
No way!
But why, Noah-sama?!
I'm so close to stealing Katsuya Jounouchi's body!
Ouka, did you really
think I wouldn't notice?
That you were cheating in order to win?
What?! He was cheating?!
That's right, Jounouchi.
Every single gamble-based card you've used has failed.
Because Ouka has been controlling them from the very start.
What'd you say?!
You jerk! Is that true!?
I guess we were right...
But why would Noah care if they are on the same side?
Noah-sama, I admittedly planned this from the start!
I-It's not as if we are all participating in the Olympics!
Why wouldn't I?
I can't approve of it.
If we can't even
beat them in a Duel fairly,
we will not truly be defeating Seto Kaiba and his friends, now will we?
And cheating won't let me
completely surpass Seto Kaiba!
Completely... surpass me?
Why is he so content on confronting me and comparing himself to me?
Is someone forcing him to do this?
Is there someone else pulling the strings from behind?
That man is the only one capable!
Gozaburo Kaiba!
No, there's just no way!
He's been long dead!
Just who...
Just who is this Noah person?!
I see.
So that's what happened?
None of my Gamble Cards were working because he was cheating?
But that means the Goddess of Luck may not have deserted me after all.
Jounouchi...
The Duel is canceled.
And as for you, Ouka, you will be punished for your actions.
Y-You can't...!
Let us continue.
What?
Doesn't a cheater suit
this situation perfectly?
There's always cheaters when it comes to gambling.
But even so...
No matter what the case, a Duel must always be played fairly!
Once you start one, regardless of what happens, you must continue on till the end!
Jounouchi-kun!
Hold on! Are you serious?!
I see.
Well, you do appear to be the loser type, if you ask me...
If you want to lose that badly, do as you please.
Alright now, I'll forgive you.
What are ya gonna do, Judge?
Allow me to say just one thing.
Once I plead a legal argument, the verdict will always end in my favor!
Then it's settled.
Considering the situation you were in just minutes ago,
regardlesss of whether
I am cheating or not,
just how delusional can you be?!
Even if my cheating
methods have been blown,
do you seriously think you can change your situation?!
I'll never know unless I try!
Because I now know I wasn't abandoned by the Goddess of Luck!
You fool.
Here goes! My turn!
Draw!
Look! I just got it!
I activate the Magic Card, Pot of Greed!
-Yes!
I'll draw two new cards.
I haven't shown my true strength yet!
I Summon my Deck Master,
Flame Swordsman!
I then equip it with the Equipment Magic, Sword of Heated Ambition - Burning Soul!
Burning Soul?!
But Burning Soul requires a sacrifice in order to use it!
Yeah, Burning Soul certainly does need a sacrifice.
By sacrificing a Monster,
and its effect increases its Attack Power by the sacrificed Monster's.
So this way your
cheating won't work.
But you don't have a single Monster to sacrifice on the field!
Furthermore, your weak Deck Master holds under 1000 Attack Points!
How do you intend to defeat my two Fusion Monsters, holding over 2000 Attack Points together?!
This outta be good!
Hang on a sec, pops!
I still got a card over here!
A Magic Card! Painful Decision!
Painful Decision...
You draw two cards from your deck,
and your opponent must choose one of the cards.
What do you mean?
If the card they choose
is a Monster Card,
you can Summon it to the field.
But if it's not a Monster Card,
you must send it to the Graveyard.
I'll believe in my luck!
Now choose one!
But let me warn you in advance.
One of them is a Monster Card, the Goblin Attack Force.
The other one's a Magic Card; Shield in the Right Hand, Sword in the Left Hand.
I can't believe you'd actually tell me the cards you have.
In other words, if you choose the Magic Card, you'll win.
But if you choose
the Goblin Attack Force,
I'll use them as a
sacrifice for the Burning Soul,
and the Flame Swordsman's Attack Power will rise to 3300!
S-So that means...!
If he attacks my Magically Armored Knight Dragoness, who holds 1200 Attack Points...
My Life will be inflicted
by 2100, and I'll lose!
That's our judge for ya!
You're pretty clever!
Now then, my left hand or my right hand? Choose one!
Good thinking, Jounouchi-kun!
He won't be able to cheat his way out of this one!
This is a true gamble
betting both your lives!
This is a strategy only
an idiot would think up.
But they're both at risk...
He's got a 50% chance of failure.
Anzu, we've just got to believe in Jounouchi-kun's good luck.
What's wrong with you?
There's just two choices.
Pick one already!
The card on your left.
You sure you want this one?
You really sure you want this one?
Very good! You came very close to deceiving me!
But this time, you're up against someone with more than enough experience in that department!
You can't fool me
with that poker face!
Did you really think a game of bluff would work against someone who spends his every day making lies into truth?!
The card in your
left hand is a Magic Card.
There is no doubt about it.
Katsuya Jounouchi,
you have lost this Due-
No!
The card in your right hand!
This card?
Sorry to disappoint you!
He did it!
I Summon the Goblin Attack Force!
Then, I sacrifice the Goblin Attack Force!
I activate the effect of
Heated Sword of Ambition - Burning Soul!
Now let's get 'im!
I use my Deck Master, the Flame Swordsman, to attack Magically Armored Knight Dragoness!
Heart's Burning Sword!!
F-For me...
I've spent my entire career deceiving countless numbers of people...!
To be fooled by
a mere child such as this...!
Booyah! I won this Duel!
You did it, Jounouchi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Heh! Oh yeah!
Oh yeah, baby!
Huh?
That Noah bastard
was here before...
He's probably making preparations for the next Duel.
By "next Duel"...
Who's it going to be?
It could be Kaiba-kun...
Maybe Otogi-kun...
But it could be...
There's a chance it
might be Shizuka-chan!
What was that?!
Jounouchi!
Don't be ridiculous!
There's no way Shizuka could Duel with these guys!
Yeah... That's why we have to find Shizuka-chan and the guys as soon as possible!
Damn right we will!
Dammit!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Wait for me, Shizuka!
I'm on my way!
Now that Jounouchi won, there's only two of the Big Five left.
But one of the Big Five might be after Shizuka-chan!
I knew it! Shizuka-chan's already started a Duel!
Eh? Otogi-kun and
Honda are in it as well?
You would think that three-on-one would be an easy win,
but Honda's a complete amateur,
so will they be alright?
Next time!
"A Man's Passage to the Stage: Honda's Death for Honor"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise