Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
"Malik's Opening Play:
The God Combo"
You did it, Jounouchi!
But why didn't you take the Great Moth card?
Isn't it much more of a Rare Card?
You really don't know about this stuff.
Listen.
I don't have Larvae Moth or Cocoon of Evolution.
Thus, even if I took Great Moth, I couldn't use it.
But if you ask me,
after taking away Haga-kun's Puzzle Card, you just couldn't take his Great Moth too!
T-That's not it...!
That's fine!
Jounouchi is becoming quite the Duelist!
Yugi better watch himself.
No~!
There's no way that's the case!
Yugi...
I wonder what he's up to...
Alright! Let's go, Jounouchi!
Let's find you another Duel!
Yeah!
Yugi...
Just you wait.
I'll definitely become a True Duelist and challenge you again.
I'm sorry, but that friend of you guys, Mutou Yugi...
No, the hateful Pharaoh who destroyed our tribe will soon die!
Lord Malik...
The Doll is ready to move.
Ah, I'm about to control the Doll and battle against the Pharaoh.
And kill the Pharaoh!
Oi, come on...
Oi!
Does this person think he's cool in that outfit?
It's amazing.
He hasn't moved even an inch in over two days.
Is it even human~?
Move!
I-I'm sorry!
Run!
Wh-What the hell was that...?
Run...
Run!
To where Yugi is!
I know what it is you're fighting for in Battle City.
That is your memory.
Isn't that right?
You know?
I didn't know from the start,
but why would you enter this tournament if you weren't after Rare Cards?
But you really wanted to find something important to you.
When I was little, I tried again and again to solve the Millennium Puzzle.
And I was able to meet an important person like you.
I wanted friends, and you gave me courage.
And now I've met many companions.
I think it's because of you.
That's not it.
It was your own strength.
That's why this time, I'll lend you my strength.
We'll fight together...
though I may not be able to do much.
That's not true at all.
Partner.
Because you're by my side, I'm able to do my best.
Now and forever.
Something's coming...!
You are...!
Vessel Yugi...
So we meet again.
Malik!
You remembered.
Right.
I'm the one controlling this doll.
It's Malik.
And this Silent Doll is merely an empty shell.
Empty shell?!
Right. With the power of my Millennium Rod,
This pantomime has severed all ties with emotion in his heart.
Thus, this is no longer a being standing before you.
It's no different than scrap.
Unforgivable!
You're misusing the power of the Millennium Items for your own gain!
I won't forgive you!
Malik!
This is a battle that's been destined for 3,000 years.
If this Duel is destined, I have no choice but to accept.
I'll take this Duel!
Yes. That's fine.
You're my true enemy.
If I win this Duel,
this doll will kill you.
No matter where you run, this doll will chase you until it kills you.
No matter where.
That's if you can beat me.
Be careful!
He has a God Card with him!
God Card?
Then I'll defeat God!
I can see it.
A battle involving the Pharaoh from 3,000 years ago is repeating itself.
This is the future I've seen.
Those involved in this destiny have been called to the city.
The Millennium Ring is showing me...
A Millennium Item has appeared in the city.
And the wielder lies within here.
He's coming...!
They escaped...?
What's this palette?
I have no clue what's about to happen in this city,
but it's interesting.
Then let me join in as well.
He's also being driven by the fate resolving around the Millennium Items.
And Malik...
As I figured, you're coming, aren't you?
Move and let me pass.
Can you really use your Millennium Rod against me?
If it's for the sake of our future, then I can.
Even if it's you, dear sister!
Malik!
I knew I should have tried harder to stop you back then...
When the two of us meet again....
Will we fight?
Or...
I'll win.
And after I beat you,
I'll go after Kaiba in this city and take the final card.
Obtaining the three God Cards will grant me the title of Pharaoh,
and I will be freed from a curse lasting over a thousand years!
And then I will obtain everything!
I can't lose...
I'll triumph in this Duel in order to gain my lost memories!
Let's go!
Here I go, Malik!
Duel!
I draw first!
Here I come!
I set 1 reverse card!
And Humanoid Slime...
Attack Mode!
Turn end!
800 Attack Humanoid Slime in Attack Mode?
My turn!
Card Draw!
He's luring me into attacking...
In order to activate his reverse card Trap.
Alright.
Then I'll use a Trap against a Trap!
I place 1 reverse card!
And I'll Summon this guy!
Illusion Beast Gazelle in Attack Mode!
Turn over!
You're being awfully cautious to not attack.
No, "cowardly" hits the nail on the head.
You can't defeat me like that.
We'll see about that.
At least don't die until you see the God Card Osiris with your very own eyes.
Just shut up
already and draw.
I Summon Worm Drake!
And I'll pull out a card from my hand.
The Magic Card Fusion!
I Summon the Fusion Monster Humanoid Drake!
2200 Attack Points...!
He fused Monsters into a more powerful Monster in order to attack fiercely this early?
But Fusion Monsters can't attack in the turn they are Summoned.
I'm safe for the time being!
Are you sure about that?
The reverse card I have on the field, the one you thought was a Trap Card...
That wasn't a Trap.
What?!
Let me show you!
Reverse card open!
The Magic Card Quick Attack!
That card is...!
It increases the speed of a fused Monster,
and allows them to attack in the turn the appear.
I don't fear my opponent's cards.
I'm not the type to play it safe and not attack until I have the upper hand...
I'm different from cowards like you who are afraid of one messily reverse card!
Here I come!
Humanoid Drake, attack!
Take apart Illusion Beast Gazelle!
Reverse card, open!
What?!
Fusion Release, is it?!
Malik...
From the time you Summoned Humanoid Slime,
I knew you were going to fuse it into another Monster.
You knew I was going to fuse?!
Sacrifice Summon, unlike Fusion Summon,
you can Summon a high-Attack Monster without wasting a turn.
Now then, Malik.
I'm sure you've already planned your next move.
I've already planned for the move after that!
This is fun, Yugi.
Your moves weren't strong enough to touch my Life.
You were too weak!
I was simply testing the waters on that turn.
I cast a pebble to see how big a ripple you make...
and to see your skills as a Duelist.
That move didn't even make a ripple.
A Duelist is like a vessel while strategy is water being poured into that vessel.
The water takes the shape of the vessel...
And if the vessel is shallow, you can see the bottom.
As the rumors state, you are a Duelist with great depth.
But if I were to cast the great stone I have hidden,
it shall shatter the very vessel itself!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...!
A great stone with the name of a god!
Let's go! My turn!
Alright.
This turn, I'll call another Monster to the field...
For now, I'll take out his Monster.
Next turn, I'll Sacrifice Summon Buster Blader!
I Summon Magnet Warrior Beta!
Battle Phase!
Magnet Warrior Beta, attack Worm Drake!
Also, Illusion Beast Gazelle...
Attack Humanoid Slime!
Worm Drake and Humanoid Slime have been beaten!
Alright.
Now all the Monsters on his field have disappeared in that attack.
I now have the upper hand in this Duel.
You just don't get it!
You're the one who's been cornered!
My turn!
Draw!
I compared water to strategy before, didn't I?
I'll show you that ultimate strategy right now.
At times, water can become a shield that can protect against any attack.
And at other times, it can become a sword capable of piercing the enemy's heart.
This Monster wields that power!
I Summon Revival Slime!
Revival Jam
Defense Mode!
Revival Slime?!
And one more
card on the field!
Slime Breeding Machine, activate!
This device Special Summons 1 Slime Token with 500 Attack and an Attribute of Water.
Of course, I can't Summon another Monster but the Slime Tokens,
until this Machine is destroyed.
I see, Malik!
Your aim is to sacrifice the Slimes on the field,
and Summon a high-level Monster!
Right.
In order to Summon the God Card Osiris the Heaven Dragon,
I must sacrifice 3 Monsters!
Osiris the Heaven Dragon...!
He's using this ability to Summon the Ultimate Monster...!
Could it be he has that card in his hand already?
My turn!
Draw!
Buster Blader...
Anyway, before he Summons Osiris, I have no choice but to lower his Life to 0!
I sacrifice the 2 Monsters I have on the field!
I Summon the Dragon Slayer Swordsman Buster Blader!
Buster Blader!
The legendary swordsman known for slaying dragons.
You Sacrifice Summoned for Buster Blader, eh?
Go! Attack Revival Slime!
Destructive Sword!!
Revival Slime is beaten!
Look closer...
Wh-What?!
Surprised?
This is Revival Slime's Regeneration Ability.
Just like water, no matter what you do,
it will return to the field unharmed.
Regeneration Ability?!
Didn't I tell you?
It's a shapeless, invincible shield.
As long as this guy remains on the field, your Monsters' attacks can't touch me.
A Monster that returns after being defeated?
Like this, I can't reduce his Life to 0!
There's nothing you can do now.
This is the ultimate strike combo designed to let God descend.
You only have...
3 turns left!
My turn!
Slime Breeding Machine, activate!
A Slime Token has appeared!
I also set a reverse card...
Turn over!
Now what are you gonna do, Yugi?
Every turn a Slime Token is generated...
When 3 are made, you will sacrifice them...
You plan to use them to Summon the God Card Osiris the Heaven Dragon.
A good strategy with one flaw!
I have Buster Blader on the field with 2600 Attack Points.
Your Slime Token's Attack is 2100 points weaker!
If Buster Blader defeats Slime Token,
your Life will be reduced by 2100 points!
You won't make it to the third turn!
In 2 turns, you're finished!
Here I go!
Buster Blader, attack Slime Token!
Reverse card open!
The Permanent Trap Card, Defender Slime!
What did you do?!
Revival Slime moved in the way!
Defender Slime is a card that forces the opponent to do battle
with only Monsters with the word "Slime" in their name as long as it remains in play.
I predicted you would try that, Yugi!
Of course I know my Life is wide open if you aim for the Slime Tokens!
Now it's my turn!
There's 2 Slimes now...
On my next turn, God will descend.
And to prepare for that, I've prepared a little something for you!
This card!
The Magic Card Nightmare Steel Cage!
This is...!
With Nightmare's Steelcage in play, Yugi is sealed from attacking.
In the meantime, Malik is preparing to Summon the God Card!
After a long struggle, the God of the Sky Osiris the Heaven Dragon appears!
Yugi, is there a way to defeat this Demon God Monster?!
"Osiris the Heaven Dragon"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...