Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Dartz has activated the second barrier!
Orichalcos Deuteros!
With it, he regains Life Points on every one of his turns,
and we're not able to Direct Attack him.
And... the Monsters he's Summoned onto the field...
The Mirror Knights...
Their true identities are...
The souls that were stolen - Partner, Jounouchi-kun and others as well!
That's really dirty, Dartz!
"The Captive Mirror Knights"
Partner...
Dartz, that's a really cheap trick!
All souls that have been taken are under my control.
Nameless Pharaoh! Seto!
The souls of your comrades have taken residence within the Mirror Knights.
They will heed to my will as my loyal pawns.
Yugi!
That's really low, Dartz!
I am simply giving you a push.
What was that?
If I were to sacrifice your souls as they are now...
...you would be of the lowest ranking.
Dartz...! You bastard...!
Nameless Pharaoh. Seto.
I need the both of you to struggle and suffer much more than this...
Once you have, the darkness in your hearts will have grown tremendously...
...and you will have become fitting offerings for my God.
Now, my Mirror Knight Yugi...
Proceed with an attack on the Nameless Pharaoh!
Ho? You still possess the will to oppose me?
Intriguing.
Let me see how far the bonds you all place your faith in ever so will get you!
Dartz!
I set a card face-down on my field...
...and finish my turn!
My turn!
Now that I've destroyed Mirror Knight Calling, they can no longer regenerate with that Immortality Ability they had.
In that case...
Magic Card! I activate Pot of Greed!
I add two cards from my deck to my hand!
Then I activate Cost Down from my hand!
By discarding a card from my hand, this card reduces a Monster's Level by two!
Using that effect...
...I Summon Different Dimension Dragon - Twilight Zone Dragon!
Twilight Zone Dragon cannot be destroyed in battle by a Monster with 1900 or less Attack Points!
And Kaiser Glider is a Monster that can't be destroyed by a Monster that has the same Attack Power!
Now I've completed my lineup.
I'll use my Kaiser Glider to attack Mai Kujaku!
You serious, Kaiba?!
Brother...!
Kaiba!
Dartz, if this is some kind of trap you've set up, it's ridiculous!
It makes no difference to me that they are acting as your warriors!
All standing in my way, whoever they may be...
I will just mercilessly destroy them!
Stop this, Kaiba...!
Be quiet, Yugi.
Don't you understand?!
That this is a restraining trap he's set for us!
It's just...
It's true that if we lose here, all the souls that were taken will...
And my promise with Black Magician Girl...
Still...
If I attack them all...
Let me ask you something.
What will happen when they disappear?
Who knows? I haven't a clue as to where dead souls reside.
Nor do I have the time to ponder the mysteries of death.
Go, Kaiser Glider!
Go on and attack Mirror Knight Mai Kujaku!
Golden Burst!!
Her Mirror Shield disappeared!
If she takes the next attack, Mai-san will...!
After, I attack with Twilight Zone Dragon!
Stop, Kaiba!
Rainbow Burst!!
Mai!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi just...
...guarded Mai-san!
What an amusing scene!
The unconscious Jounouchi actually guarded Mai Kujaku!
But all that means is the bonds you share within your hearts will only fortify my alignment!
Damn that Deadbeat...
Always getting in the way...!
I place a card face-down and end my turn.
My turn.
Yugi, Jounouchi and Mai are defenseless now.
Attack them!
But... To me...
You pacifist! Do you intend to stay back and wait for your loss?!
Every one of them here...
...are irreplaceable friends to me.
I...
I will end my turn without doing anything else.
Yugi! You bastard!
There's no way the other Yugi could attack any of them...!
It's unfair! This Dartz bastard's playing dirty!
My turn!
Draw!
Right now, as a result of Orichalcos Deuteros' effect,
my Life increases by 2500 points!
Nameless Pharaoh...
If one were to say your destiny can be decided at will, allow me to decide it for you!
Engage activation!
Continuous Magic! Double Centaur Archer!
Double Centaur Archer will fire its arrow towards one of our teams.
A Monster it hits is removed from the Duel.
And the Attack Power of that Monster shall be casted upon the player as damage.
The targets will be Kaiser Glider and Mirror Knight Jounouchi.
What?
Does that mean Jounouchi will disappear if he gets hit with that arrow?
But it could also hit my brother...!
Seto... Jounouchi...
Destiny beckons you.
Destiny appears to have chosen you, Seto!
Brother!!
Kaiba!!
On the turn I activate Double Centaur Archer's abilities, I am unable to attack with a Monster.
Thus, I will be ending my turn!
Wretched dolt...
This time for sure, I'll dispose of that pitiable wreck once and for all!
Here goes! Twilight Zone Dragon, attack!
Kaiba!
Deadbeat! If you have even a shred of Duelist's pride,
act like a man and be gone!
Jounouchi-kun!
What?!
This time, Yugi guarded Jounouchi...!
Now I see how magnificent your bond is!
Defend one another.
Protect one another!
My soul prisoners!
My turn!
If I don't destroy that Continuous Magic,
he'll once again...
Quick-Play Magic! Cyclone!
I'll use this card to destroy Double Centaur Archer!
Turn end!
It's my turn!
Even if you destroy Double Centaur Archer...
Seto, your Life is nothing more than a light flickering in the wind!
Arise, Orichalcos Diabolos!
And due to the effects of Orichalcos Deuteros,
my Life rises to 15500!
15500...?!
If that Monster attacks my brother...
It is a shame, Seto.
It would appear that this is as far as you proceed!
But among your sacrifice, a new world lies in wait.
Eliminate Seto!
Orichalcos Diablos!
Attack Twilight Zone Dragon!
Brother!!
You're...!
Trap, activate!
Attack Guidance Barrier!
This card allows me to switch the attack target to another Defense Mode Monster,
and increase their Defense Power by 600 points in the process!
And the Monster I choose...
Big Shield Gardna!!
That makes Big Shield Gardna's Defense Power greater!
Dude!
But all the damage I receive is absorbed by Orichalcos Kyutora!
When he receives an attack, Big Shield Gardna switches into Attack Mode!
And because of the effect of Attack Guidance Barrier, your turn is forced to a close!
You've spared your life but a moment longer, Seto.
Now I've given you temporary aid.
My turn!
But I only have 600 Life Points left...
And I can't Summon any of the Monsters in my hand...
I switch Twilight Zone Dragon into Defense Position!
I set two cards on the field and end my turn!
My turn!
Yugi, Summon a Monster and attack them!
Other... Me...
Forget... about us...
You have... a much more important mission ahead of you...
Partner!
Look closely, Yugi.
These guys are fully prepared to be wiped out.
Still...!
Still, Partner... In order to rescue you, I...
Say, what's wrong with you, Nameless Pharaoh?
I switch Big Shield Gardna into Defense Mode...
Placing a reverse card face-down...
I finish off my turn.
Damn you, Yugi...!
Nameless Pharaoh. Seto.
In the end, you are nothing more than beings struggling against destiny.
You will come to know your fate!
Rafael!
Lord Dartz!
You must stop this at once!
This battle is pointless!
We have been mistaken!
Ho?
It is true that everyone has darkness within their hearts...
But it can still be shattered!
There is still possibility among the human beings on this planet!
Rafael... I certainly never expected to hear those words uttered from your mouth.
Lord Dartz... The fact is, I have been saved from the darkness in my heart by the Nameless Pharaoh!
I beg of you...
Those people...
Along with the souls of Varon and Amelda!
Please return them to us!
Rafael... Do you truly believe you have been saved from the darkness residing within your heart?
What are you referring to?!
Hatred... Sadness... Despair...
It is possible to remove these things from your heart.
If that is true, then why...!?
"Why"?
Hmph. Because these things alone do not make up the "truth" behind humanity.
The... truth behind humanity?
Yes.
I am talking about those who have attempted to extinguish the darkness in their hearts long ago!
Gaze your eyes towards the inhabitants of these slates!
Many of them were wise beyond humanity and learned how to free themselves of the darkness in their hearts and their troubles.
By doing so, they found peace of mind.
But even they could not completely eliminate it.
That is because the human spirit holds onto the smallest of fragments of discontent.
As the darkness in their hearts continued to come closer to them once more...
...their hearts became weak and fickle as a result.
No! That is wrong, Lord Dartz!
I...
They've...
The feelings they hold deep within themselves...
They have taught me the importance of the strength they possess!
And from now on, my soul will no longer be swallowed by the darkness in my heart!
Rafael...
Well said!
That gives some meaning to what Yugi's been risking his life for!
Lord Dartz...!
Allow me to enlighten you...
...of the true identity of the darkness of the heart and where it generates from from within humanity!
All of you should have it somewhere within your hearts.
For human beings are insecure creatures!
And you're saying that's wrong?
Well, with people inferring such ambiguous terms such as "possibility" the way they see fit,
it is no wonder they are insecure.
But how about facing reality?
Those with wealth, those who neglect, those with anger...
Those with talent, those with reason, those who are blessed...
Those who are hated simply because they were born...
This world is destined to be plagued by imperfection.
That is what drives the darkness of the heart.
And no one is able to escape from that fact.
That is the truth of this world.
Lord Dartz...
That is why I am trying to rebuild this world.
With the goal of creating perfect human beings capable of warding off the darkness of their hearts in mind.
Rafael...
As well as Varon and Amelda...
You three are also tenacious warriors born with
the purpose of indulging in the darkness of your hearts.
For I required beings who questioned their fates.
What does that mean?!
Destiny created these powerful beings...
Amelda...
After losing his beloved younger brother at the hands of weaponry created by Kaiba Corporation,
he welcomed the darkness in his heart with open arms.
Amelda...
Is this true, Mokuba-kun?!
It is...
That's why Amelda went after my brother...
However, on that very same battlefield he lost his brother...
...was Gozaburo Kaiba truly the one responsible?
And the one who burned down Varon's orphanage until it was nothing more than a pile of cinders...
This can't...
Rafael!
Why was it that the one ship you happened to be riding conveniently sunk to the bottom of the ocean?
And why was it that you alone managed to survive such a tragedy?
Why...?
You couldn't have...!
Help me, Big Brother!
Sonia!
Big Brod'er!!
Sonia!! Julien!!
There's no way that's true!
Your destinies were decided from the very start.
I simply gave them a slight... shove.
For I needed you three.
The inevitable resurrection of the Legendary Dragons...
And the Chosen Duelists whom they fell under the control of.
I needed beings who could control the darkness within their hearts...
Formidable pawns!
Dartz! How could you do such a thing?!
My parents...
My little brother and my little sister...!
They are of little importance in the face of Doma's mission!
Dartz! You bastard!!
That's the Barrier of Orichalcos!
But Rafael's barrier should have already disappeared!
Stop! Stop right now, Rafael!
Once activated, the Barrier of Orichalcos will never completely vanish!
That is irrefutable proof that the darkness of your heart never once left you!
Become food for the rebirth of my God!
Rafael!!
H-Hey!
Stay with us!
Rafael... You have shown us the inevitable...
That people will never completely rid themselves of the darkness infesting their hearts!
Dartz...! You monster...!
It is my turn!
Now our interference has left us.
Nameless Pharaoh! Seto!
I will reveal the true power of the Barrier of Orichalcos!
As I offer you onto my God!
The Barrier of Orichalcos...!
It's true power...?
Indeed.
Engage activation!
The third Barrier of Orichalcos!
Orichalcos Tritos!
Dartz has activated the third barrier of the Orichalcos...!
With the three boundaries in play, the Barrier of Orichalcos has been completed!
Not only can we not attack with our comrade's Monsters,
but our Direct Attacks have been sealed away...!
Can Yugi and Kaiba-kun get out of this desperate situation?!
Next time!
"The Third Barrier of Orichalcos"
Duel standby!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other