Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Worried that this full tank of energy will lose it's destination
Whoever shakes for just a minute their boredom, will explode!
I ride, atop the white line, Oh, Oh, Oh
Sit down, in the place you have faith Oh, Oh, Oh
Go to the place that tempts you!
If each person took one thing at a time, freedom and passion in their hand
For the shine to come, continue our journey
The unclear everyday trump-card that sustains me, is your soul
The best growth is coming forth, unstoppable wild drive
We are both yet to settle down, striking the door
The Big Five pulled out there trump card, the Five God Dragon, to fight us.
But the combined power of me and Jounouchi-kun had enough Attack Points to bring it down!
We beat the Big Five and won the Duel.
But Honda-kun's body didn't return.
And the Big Five were wiped out by Noah!
Noah! What in the world are you planning?!
"Noah VS Seto:
Duel of the Creation of Heaven and Earth"
What the hell do you think you're doing, OOH-AH~!?
Honda, I'm sorry. I don't think you're gonna be returning to normal.
Like hell you are, OOH!!
But we can't just ignore Mokuba when he was captured by Noah, either.
And just how the hell is that related to you turning me upside down, OOH-AHH~!?
We're at a dead end right now.
The only clue we've got to find them and figure out how to get out of this world is the body you're in that was made here.
You must have some sort of secret switch, right?!
CUT IT OUT, OOH-AH!!
There's a ton of em.
Maybe this one?
What the heck was that? Man!
How about this button?
A miss?
What do you think, Yugi?
This one looks like an
emergency button to me.
Emergency Mode! Emergency Mode!
What's wrong, Honda-kun?
That's Kaiba Land!
So you're here to welcome me...?
Welcome, Seto!
I invite you to my world.
Noah!
Big brother, who is that?
He looks a lot like you.
A guest will be coming here shortly.
I have to go make some preparations before his arrival.
You be a good boy and wait here.
Kaiba and his brother are here?
Huh? Where did Honda-san go?
Honda-kun!
Hey, wait up Honda!
Only staff and personal are permitted beyond this point.
Only staff and personal are permitted beyond this point!
So that means there's something behind here we shouldn't see!
If you do not leave willingly you will be made to!
Outta the way!
Are you alright, Honda-san?
Huh? What's up, ooh?
Welcome, Seto.
Bastard! Where's Mokuba?!
Don't fret over it.
Don't fret over it. Regardless of how our destiny pulls us into fray, this doesn't involve Mokuba. He will be released.
That aside Seto, isn't this place beautiful?
We stand atop the Earth
before it was born.
You can create any world you want using Kaiba Corporation's advanced simulator,
whether it be the universe
or a pit of magma.
Using this, even be it a war contrived by a revolution on the verge of society,
it's possible to thrust
mankind into a new age.
If there's something you want to say to me, how about you just come out and say it?!
I am appalled by you!
You only use this outstanding technology on worthless games!
Seto, isn't it about time we settle things?
And for us to decide who is most suitable to run Kaiba Corporation!
It's meaningless.
What did you just say?!
Because, Noah, you're already dead.
I saw it on that video!
No way!
Impossible!
Is this supposed to be
Noah's funeral service?
If that's true, this means Noah's dead!
Wait, but that's...!
Then who's the Noah who's been talking to us this whole time?!
You saw those old records?
Then that will make
this go much faster.
You're right. It's true that my body is made up of virtual flesh.
But I'm much different up here.
Behold, Seto!
That is the container
holding my true brain!
My conscious lies dormant inside it!
Guys! Come over here, ooh!
There's a railroad over here, ooh-ah!
Do you think Kaiba-kun went this way?
There's no way to tell that, ooh-ah!
But there's no other paths we can take.
We've just got to check it out.
You're right.
But should we just wait and hope a train comes?
I found something useful, OOH~!!
Good work, monkey!
I'm scared~!
You're going way too fast!
Heh, whatcha talkin' about?!
Just hold on tighter!
Whoo yeah!
Even if you say that, we're seriously going too fast!
Jounouchi! Hit the breaks! The breaks!
You mean... these...?
That's... your brain?
That's right. Just like you said, my body is certainly dead.
But everything started the moment of my death.
Born the only son of Kaiba Corporation,
I was spoiled more than anyone.
As if I was born superior
to all other children.
Because I had already been selected to take over Kaiba Corporation someday, my lifestyle had been decided.
My father invested in the most elite teachers to ensure I received a top-level education.
In not just studying...
But also music...
...sports...
Because he wanted me to grow up to be a person at the top of all fields, someone on par with a king.
And I tried my best to answer my father by doing the best I could all the time.
Had things gone on that way, you and Mokuba would have never been adopted by Kaiba Corporation.
You said before that life is a game.
If that's the case, you almost say I was cheated...
Noah!
Noah!!
NOAH!!
Hurry it up!
Make Noah like he was before!
B-But, sir...!
Are you disobeying me?!
Why the hell were you hired?!
I'm terribly sorry, but in his current condition...!
You're nothing but a pathetic quack!
You're useless to me!
They say the human brain is made up of electronic-like signals.
My father had all of my memories transferred
into an AI Computer,
a system invented by Kaiba Corporation for war.
And I was granted a new life!
And afterwards, Seto, you and Mokuba were taken in by the Kaiba's.
Father took you in as a my rival and my motivation.
You were intended to push me further in my studies, all the way to the top.
Seto, you were never intended to inherit Kaiba Corporation.
I trust you won't have any complaints...
...if we use the thing you're most comfortable with, Duel Monsters, to decide my victory.
I'm positive you'll be most satisfied losing like that.
Relax.
I'll inherit your body.
You will be used for the benefit of Kaiba Corporation.
So you're basically saying all of my suffering, all of my aggravation and my entire life occurred for you?
That about sums it up. And if you do what I want now, it'll save you a humiliating loss later on.
Screw you!
Listen well, Noah! I've never lived for anyone but myself!
My future is decided
on a road of glory!
And if you insist on blocking that road, whoever it may be...
...I'll eliminate you with
my own two hands!
Seto, you don't know when to quit.
You run your mouth too much, Noah!
My deck has already been decided!
As for my Deck Master...
Come forth, Kaiser Seahorse!
I've been dreaming of this moment for a long time.
Now let's have our match, Seto!
DUEL!!
Here I go, Noah!
My turn! Draw!
I Summon Giant Virus in Attack Position!
I then set a card face-down!
Noah, the Goddess of Victory smiles over me in this Duel.
The card I have set is the Deck Destruction Virus of Death.
Its effect activates the very moment you attack the Giant Virus.
Every Monster in your hand or deck holding 1500 or greater Attack Points will be wiped out.
My turn comes to an end here!
I'm going now, Seto.
My turn!
I Summon Chiron the Mage!
It's the exit!
Where are we?
That hurt!
Wh-What?
What's with this space?!
Yugi! Look over there!
Kaiba-kun! Noah!
Yugi!
Your friends are all here.
You got here just in time to watch my Duel with Seto.
Now I get to show you guys!
My Creation of Heaven and Earth Deck!
"Creation of Heaven and Earth Deck"...?
I activate the Special Ability of Chiron the Mage!
Mirror of Truth!
Chiron the Mage's Mirror of Truth allows me to see the face-down card on my opponent's field and destroy it.
Seto, that set card you've got is...
...the Deck Destruction Virus of Death!
What?!
I saw through your entire plan.
Go, Chiron!!
Attack the Giant Virus!
I activate Giant Virus's Special Ability!
A Regenerative Ability, eh?
What a pain...
Even if you got rid of my Death Virus, my victory hasn't changed.
My turn!
I sacrifice Giant Virus!
I Summon Vampire Lord!
Vampire Lord, attack!
Disciple of Darkness!
And now for Vampire Lord's
Vampiral Effect.
Each time I damage you, I must declare one type of card in which you must send to the Graveyard.
Noah, toss away a Monster Card!
Not too shabby, Seto.
But such an evil Monster does not fit in well with the holy land I've created.
My turn!
Demons shall be sent back to the darkness they came from!
Magic Card! Fissure!!
I then Summon Celestial Warrior Aries!
Not good! Kaiba-kun just
lost his Wall Monster!
Go, Aries!
Direct Attack!!
Kaiba-kun's Life...!
Is this the same Kaiba we know getting beaten so easily...?
I then place one set card.
If you don't take me seriously, this match will be over before you even realize it.
That ends my turn.
Now what's wrong, Seto?
Is this all the strength your prestiged Power Deck can muster?
Or, perhaps, you've been taking me seriously all along?
Damn you, Noah...
My turn!
Revive, Vampire Lord!
Vampire Lord holds two Abilities.
The first is a Vampiral Ability designed to assault your enemy.
And when he is destroyed by one of your Card Effects,
his Immortality Ability lets me revive him on the turn after you do so.
I will also Summon Newt!
Attack Position!
Sweet! Now Kaiba's got two Monsters!
Time for a counterattack!
You've got some never dirtying my holy land with evil Demon-Types.
Noah, if you want to keep on pretending you're the creator of this world,
then allow me to descend to that world alongside you!
Here I come!
Attack, Vampire Lord!
You're long-winded, Seto!
I will return those evil souls to where they came from!
Trap Card, activate!
Earth Reformation!!
Earth Reformation makes me pick two Attributes.
You then must choose one of the two.
Following, all Monsters on the field holding that Attribute are destroyed.
I have chosen the Wind Attribute and the Darkness Attribute.
So choose whichever you like, Seto!
Vampire Lord is a Dark Attribute.
And Newt is a Wind Attribute.
Vampire Lord has more Attack Points.
Come on!
I choose Vampire Lord!
Now be gone!
Vampire Lord!!
Why would you do that, Kaiba?
He just picked the Monster with higher Attack Points!
No, he's got his reasons!
Vampire Lord will be recovered next turn thanks to his Card Effect.
I get it! Kaiba can just recover him next turn!
Don't forget that I still
have Newt on my field.
Go, Newt!
Graviton Punch!!
They're just about equal now.
Noah and Kaiba-kun both use Power Decks - calling out extremely powerful Monsters instantly.
If either of them holds back even a little in this Duel, they'll lose.
My turn!
"Long ago, when evil beings roamed the earth, God washed them all away."
And that time is now.
Magic Card, activate!
Giant Flood!
What's that sound?
Big brother, over there!
We gotta get outta here!!
There's nowhere to run!!
Newt's being taken away!
No! All the Monsters in the Graveyard, too!
What's the meaning of this?
It means that my Deck Master Ability has just been activated!
Your Deck Master?!
Correct...
Come forth, my Deck Master!
Ark of Miracles!!
So that's...
...his Deck Master?
Seto, this is where the Duel of the Creation of Heaven and Earth really begins.
A huge ark appears behind Noah.
Is that Noah's Deck Master?
What kind of power does this Deck Master have?
And what does he mean when he says, "This is where the seven turns of creation starts"?
On a field that changes scenery each and every turn,
sparks fly as Kaiba-kun
and Noah clash fiercely.
I can't take my eyes off their fight!
Next time!
"The Invincible Deck Master - Ark of Miracles"
Duel standby!
The unsinkable sun, wherever it rises
A dream is a dream, and it won't stop
The straight rail and the steep route
To go, or not go all of yourself
I'm getting tired of counting my advances in a cage
Respect! Boys, show me your strength
It's awkward, but draw the map
Now let's walk forever with our head up high...
The unsinkable sun, if it starts to get to familiar like you
answer freely to the everyday discomfort
I want to believe you, because I am losing my way with everything
Hiding in my heart... this secret paradise