Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
"The KC Grand Prix Opening Game"
Breakfast is ready~!
Ouch~!
C'mon and get up already!
Ow! What the hell?!
You scared me...
What do you expect? How long were you planning to sleep?
What's the problem? A lot's happened and we're exhausted.
Let us sleep in peace~!
Where's Darling?
He ain't here?
Where could he have gone?
Feels great!
Partner.
Looking at things now, it almost seems like everything that happened was just a bad dream.
Other Me?
I can't simply forget about that battle and everyone involved in it...
And about the Duel Monsters World...
And because of me, you've suffered greatly...
Other Me...
Hey, when we return to Japan, we can finally release the seal on your memory, right?
I don't know exactly what will happen when we do...
But no matter what happens, I won't forget...
...all the happy and painful moments I shared with you.
Because they're memories that are precious to me.
Partner...
Yugi!
Darling!
So this is where you've been hiding.
We finished preparing breakfas...
DARLING!
Geez! You disappeared again and had me worried!
I-I'm sorry...!
I was just taking a walk...
E-Everyone's waiting... Let's go eat our breakfast.
Shall we go?
Y-Yeah...!
You're so slow, Yugi!
Sorry!
Hurry and eat your food!
It's delicious~!
By the way, what are you all planning to do now?
We're planning to go back to Japan as soon as possible.
Wha? You don't have to rush! Take your time!
That's right! You're still on vacation, aren't you?
If you need advice, I'll be your tour guide.
Great idea! We did come all the way to America, after all.
Yeah! Let's eat American cuisine! A huge steak and maybe some lobster!
Is eating the only thing you care about?
What'd ya say?! Then, Anzu, what're you gonna do?
It's my phone.
Hello?
Ah, that you?
Yeah...
Excuse me? Come again?
Hey, Yugi... It'll be a big waste if we go back this soon.
Yeah... but...
That's right... We have to hurry back and help the other Yugi...
Yeah...
That's right...
Partner...
As long as we have the God Cards back, there's no reason for us to rush.
Isn't it okay for us to enjoy ourselves a little bit?
Other Me...?
That's right...
Since we've come all this way, let's enjoy ourselves!
Alright!
Oh yeah! That's what I'm talkin' about!
Where do you wanna go?
Let's see...
Huh?
Where's the professor?
He just went out somewhere.
Looky, I think you guys should head to all the theme parks around the area!
Y-Yeah...
Steaks! STEAKS!
We gotta watch some American classics! Like, you know, those old western movies!
We have to have steak first!
How long can you stay here? Have you figured out how you're going to get back yet?
What's wrong?
That reminds me... How the heck are we getting home?
That's right! We came here at Pegasus' expense!
We never thought of how to get back home!
What should we do?
How much does a ticket cost?
I... don't have any money!
Me either...
In that case, you can just live here for the rest of your life, Darling!
No way! What about school?!
Kaiba... Corporation?
Say what now? If that's all, I can get it done easily.
Really, Mokuba?
Yeah!
I can send you back with one of Kaiba Corporation's private jets!
Seriously?!
Awesome!
You saved us!
However...
...under the condition that you enter
the greatest Duel Monsters Tournament ever held by Kaiba Corporation, the KC Grand Prix!
A tournament?
So what's the deal with this Duel tournament?
You know Kaiba Land's going to open in America, right?
Yeah, I saw it in the news. They said it was almost completed.
That's right!
And for it's grand opening, we're holding a huge Duel tournament in place of an opening ceremony.
I'm very sorry, Seto-sama...
We're doing our very best, but...
I'm sick and tired of hearing this over and over!
Start showing me some results.
Y-Yes sir...
Brother?
You did get back all the stocks Doma bought, right?
Yeah...
But after this incident, Kaiba Corporation was left with enormous debts.
The stock price is very low.
God, this is really annoying.
But once our tournament starts up,
everyone is sure to be turning their attention to Kaiba Corporation again!
If it works, all of those bad rumors will be tarnished!
That's true...
Isono, how's the registration on our network going?
Yes, it is underway.
Also, are you still planning to invite those guys?
Of course we are.
They owe us for a lot of aid we gave them before.
In that case, let me get to it.
Isono, I'm going too!
Mokuba?
Leave it to me, Brother!
I'll be sure to get those guys to come!
And that's why I've come to pick you guys up.
Hold on, man! Aren't you guys just deciding that on your own?
In this situation, shouldn't Kaiba come here bowing his head and begging us to join?
That's for sure.
Kaiba Corporation's all about propaganda, after all.
And if Battle City Finalists like Yugi-kun and Jounouchi-kun take part,
it'll be all over the news.
I'm telling you...! My brother's really busy!
Because he's the organizer of this tournament, he's too busy to even join!
Kaiba's not gonna Duel?
He must really be in trouble.
Now I get it. He's afraid of losin' to me and Yugi, so he's not even gonna show his face, eh?
If he's beaten again, Kaiba Corporation's reputation will fall through the floor!
Like hell my brother would lose!
It's just that... His job as a CEO is far more important than being a Duelist at the moment!
All to fulfill our dream of spreading Kaiba Land throughout the world.
Mokuba-kun...
Jounouchi, you went too far.
Uh... well...
I guess he really does have it hard...
Yugi, this tournament is putting the future of Kaiba Corporation on the line!
We're aiming to hold the greatest Duels with the strongest Duelists chosen from around the world.
That's why I'm asking you to join. As the Duel King!
Duelists from around the world? Sounds exciting!
I think we'll have fun Dueling there!
So you'll enter?!
Thank you, Yugi!
If Yugi's gonna do it, count me in too!
I'll enter too!
As the U.S. Champion, I should be entitled to!
Say Darling, let's go sign up together!
Y-Yeah...
Of course! I planned on asking you as well, so I brought your invitation with me.
Show me the greatest Duels!
Just leave it to us. Right, Yugi?
Now this event will surely be amazing!
Herr Sieg, you have received a new e-mail.
Yes.
"KC Grand Prix," eh?
How inexperienced you are...
You believe holding this event will restore the faith consumers once had in Kaiba Corporation, Seto Kaiba...
You bet your life on this...
This is Kaiba Land USA!
It's so big!
It's sure got a lot of attractions!
When it comes to attractions and size, there's nothing like this in the world!
Looks like fun! Right, Yugi?
Yeah!
Let's go on a date after the opening, Darling!
What the hell? I wanna stay with Yugi too...
Money sure does talk!
This is the main gate, where the shopping carts are located.
Of course it's here!
What're you doing, Jounouchi?!
Say, Mokuba...
Hmm? What's up?
You said you invited many outstanding Duelists to this tournament, right?
That's right! The best in the world!
Well in that case, Mai...
Did you also invite Mai Kujaku?
Yeah... I did include her in the invitation list...
But we have no idea of her whereabouts.
I see...
Jounouchi-kun...
Knowing her, she's probably off somewhere nice and healthy and Dueling.
Yeah, you're right.
Huh? There's some people here already.
Admission's free for today because it's the opening.
You guys can play around all you want later as well.
Seriously?!
AWRIGHT!
I'm gonna ride the rollercoasters!
YEAH!
You're both so childish...
And this'll be the Duel Stadium for the tournament!
Blue-Eyes Dome...?
Wouldn't normal people call this "going too far"?
Y-Yeah...
That's the Main Duel Stage!
The entire Duel will be broadcast around the whole world!
The whole world?!
You have to be careful not to embarrass yourself out there Dueling.
I attack Blade Knight with Gagagigo!
Alright!
Quick-Play Magic activate, Scapegoat.
Hey... Why are you using Scapegoat now?
I just ended my turn...
What's with this computer? Doesn't it know how to Duel?
Just watch.
It must be planning to use that reverse card over there, huh...?
Yeah...
My turn!
Activating Trap Card. DNA Surgery.
As long as this card remains on the field...
every Monster on the field will become a Type I choose.
No way!
I will choose the Dragon-Type.
Even Gagagigo...!
What the?!
Awesome!
Furthermore, activating Magic Card from hand.
Fusion.
It's fusing all its Monsters?!
Could it be...?
I will fuse together all Dragon-Type Monsters on field...
...Summoning Five God Dragon onto field.
Are you kidding me?!
The Five-God Dragon with 5000 Attack Points?!
Are you serious?
Even though it's a computer, it has such advanced tactics...!
Surprised, are we?!
This Duel Computer is installed with elite Duelist card data from across the globe!
And that of course includes my brother, Yugi and even Jounouchi's data.
Mine too?
Jounouchi's data? So it depends on luck?
Say that again!!
But isn't it pointless to fight against such a powerful computer?
No need to worry about that.
There's a level setter so even beginners can enjoy it.
This is one of Kaiba Land's specialties!
It's interesting! You can even Duel against yourself with this!
You're right.
Five-God Dragon, attack.
I lost.
That's why we told you the level was set too high.
I'll go next!
But you learned something good from that. Now you can re-construct your deck for next time.
AHH! It's the Duel King, Yugi Mutou!
Seriously?!
Amazing! It really is him!
And even the American Champion, Rebecca!
Please gimme your autograph!
Me too!
It's amazing! Yugi's become famous!
T-Think so?
I'm Leon. I've admired your Duels for a long time!
I'm moved to be able to meet you!
Thank you!
Hey. Hey! Want my autograph?
Don't want it!
Who are you, dude?
See? It's Katsuya Jounouchi from the Battle City Best Four!
Never heard of you!
Too bad, Jounouchi!
Why?!
Umm... Would you mind looking at my deck?
Your deck?
I always lose... How can I be as strong as you, Yugi-san?
What's this? They're all Dragon-Types.
I like Dragons, so I traded with my friends and got a whole bunch!
I understand that you like them, but the balance here is terrible.
No good?
That's not what I meant...
It's alright. Liking your cards will only make them stronger!
Your cards will respond to your thoughts.
Really?
Yeah.
Oh, that's right.
I'll give you this.
Eh? You sure?
Mmm.
Huh? It's not a Dragon...
But that card is sure to help your Dragons out.
Really?
Yeah!
You're lucky!
I want one too!
Hey Yugi, what card was it?
Well...
I'll try this out in a Duel!
Do your best!
You'd better not set the level too high!
Yeah, right...
Then I'll challenge Level Two!
A greeting is in order. A friendly grüßen.
-Duel.
-Duel!!
W-What? A blackout?
Everyone, it's dangerous, so don't move!
Oi, Mokuba! What's going on?!
It's strange... This shouldn't...
Maybe it needs a tune-up. There could be some kind of problem with the system.
Anyway... Stay calm, everyone!
The power'll be back soon!
It's back.
What the?
What's wrong?!
Why did the emergency shutters go off?
It's no use, it won't work! This is impossible!
Let me give it a try.
Anything?
It's no use.
The program has been locked and the entire system has been connected to the Duel Computer.
If we don't stop the Duel Computer, we can't open the exits.
How could this even happen? This computer was designed for Dueling only!
It has nothing to do with the main system!
Someone hacked the system from the outside and rewrote the programming.
But who could've done something like that?
I can't figure that much out.
So... We just have to destroy the computer, right?
All right, let me!
Wait!
If you do that, we'll never get outta here!
Then what should we do?
If the Duel Computer is beaten, the locks should open.
So the only way out is to defeat it in a Duel?
Oh no!
What?! What's wrong?!
Duel start. My turn.
Summoning Berserk Gorilla in Attack Position.
I also set one reverse card card and end my turn.
It's Dueling him?
What's the level?
Look!
Isn't that the highest level?
That's a child fighting against it! Can he win?!
I'm scared~!
He can't fight in this position.
The deck's been chosen already. We can't change it!
What?
We have to play with that horribly unbalanced Dragon Deck?
There's no way that'll beat the computer at its highest level!
Other Me!
Yugi?!
Calm down!
I'm with you!
Eh?
Your name is...?
Rick.
Rick... You put all your feelings into that deck. Please let me borrow it!
O-Okay!
Yugi!
Darling! You can do it!
I'm counting on you, Yugi.
I'll be your opponent!
I'll get everyone out of here!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
Doesn't the KC Grand Prix sound pretty fun?
Just as we were happily touring Kaiba Land, the Dome was hacked by someone and we were trapped inside it!
And we can't escape unless someone beats the computer in a Duel!
The opponent's level is set to its maximum!
We're fighting with an awful unbalanced Dragon Deck!
Can you really win, Yugi?
Next time!
"The Conspiracy Begins to Move"
Duel standby!