Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
Why was it that I was brought back to this world after 3,000 years?
That's because, Dartz, I was brought back in order to defeat you and change the world's future!
Along with the nameless cards whose seals were broken - the Legendary Knights!
Finish off Dartz!
What?! Evil God Gē?!
Its Attack Power reached infinity?!
"Infinite Attack Power: Evil God Gē"
Disappear from this realm!
Black Magician Girl!
I activate the Special Effect of Legendary Knight Hermos!
He absorbs the power of the Monsters from my Graveyard!
Freedom Sword!!
He has gained the power of Retrained Elf Swordsman!
He's now protected against Monsters with 1900 Attack Points or greater!
What?
We are the Three Knights!
We bet all on our title!
In order to protect all!
My turn!
Dartz. It looks like this is about to be decided.
Between you and me.
The time for us to settle this has come!
Gē's Attack Power is infinite.
It is improbable to surpass that.
Partner...
Jounouchi-kun...
Kaiba...
Mai...
Rafael...
And everyone else...
All of their feelings now lie in one place.
Legendary Knights! Critias and Hermos!
Attack Evil God Gē!
Wisdom Sword!!
Freedom Sword!!
What futile effort.
You really think so?
Impossible! There should be no power capable of surpassing that of infinity!
Dartz, if you believe in the infinity of darkness of the heart,
then the bonds we believe in are also infinite!
Absorb Attack Guidance Barrier!
I add its power to Critias!
It's the power to send a Monster's attack to another Monster!
Thus, the attack will be sent to Hermos instead!
What?!
Then I activate the Special Ability of Legendary Knight Hermos!
He absorbs three of the Monsters from my deck!
He then adds their total Attack Power to his own!
You couldn't have...!
Right! An "infinite loop" was created between the powers of Critias and Hermos!
Their Attack Points have surpassed Gē's infinite Attack Power?!
Here I go, Dartz!
I attack with Legendary Knight Timaeus!
The Special Ability of Timeaus is to fuse with the Monsters on the field and become an entirely new being!
The power of our bonds will now open up a brand new future!
Gain the power of infinity!
Divine Dragon Knight - Timeaus!
What did you say?!
Watch carefully, Dartz!
The moment when the power of bonds overcomes the darkness!
Justice Sword!!
What the hell is that?!
I-Impossible...!
For me to...
Dartz!
I've won this Duel!
Return everyone's souls at once!
Dartz!
What the...?
Wh-What is that?
Mai!
Pegasus!
Chosen Duelists!
Return to us once more!
This is...!
Mokuba!
Mokuba! Come back to me!
Brother!
Big Brother!!
Kaiba! Mokuba!
Anzu!
Hey! Anzu!
Pull yourself together!
Honda!
We're...
H-Hey, Anzu...
Yugi?
Is that you, Yugi?
Yugi...
Yugi!
Anzu!
Yugi! You really came back!
I can't breathe, Anzu!
Yugi!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jo-Jounouchi!!
Yugi!
We made it back to our world!
Jounouchi-kun!
Jounouchi!
Yugi! Jounouchi!
Partner! Finally... Finally we met again!
Other Me!
Dartz vanished into the darkness somewhere...
Then the Legendary Knights revived your souls.
But it's still too early to rejoice...
Other Me!
If my brother's soul returned, then everyone else's souls should also...
No, that's not the case.
We're the only ones who returned.
The others' souls are still...
Seto-sama!!
Bad news!!
That's...!
That's...
Is that Atlantis?!
That means it really exists?
There's no time to think about it!
I'm positive the god Dartz mentioned is still alive!
That must be where all of their souls...
So if we don't beat that thing, Mai and Varon...
Amelda's and a ton of other souls as well!
What is...?!
Not good! The winds have created a tsunami and it's headed right for us!
And the height of the tsunami has already surpassed 100 meters!
It will reach America's coastline in approximately one hour!
What did you say?!
I suppose we're going to have to go there in order to settle things.
But how?
We might be able to get there by helicopter.
Wait. I think I know another way we can get there...
The dimension Dartz vanished into...
It's got to be there. I'm going!
Yugi!
Yugi, I'm gonna go too!
Jounouchi!
You can't do that! We just finally managed to get your souls back!
Doma were opponents we couldn't reach to begin with!
Anzu, you should already know that's not the case.
If we use the power of the Duel Monsters,
we can stop the Orichalcos God.
Yugi's right! I'm going to get back Mai and Varon's souls!
I know more than anyone how it feels to be trapped there so long.
How scary and lonely it is.
But I always believed that Jounouchi-kun, Kaiba-kun and my other self would rescue me!
And I'm sure the others trapped there are believing that we'll rescue them!
Yugi...
That's why we've got to go.
This is not good, Director!!
In just one hour, a massive tsunami is going to hit this place!
What was that?!
Brother!
Kaiba-kun!
You guys wait here.
My anger won't calm until I settle things with Dartz!
Hold it, Kaiba!
Who the hell said you could run off on your own?
As if some deadbeat could save the glory of the future.
Say that again!
Yugi!
Anzu!
Just wait a minute. I'll switch with my other self.
It's fine. Stay the Yugi you are now.
Yugi, you better come back.
Tell the other Yugi that as well.
Anzu...
Okay!
I promise I'll be back!
You better! Yugi! Jounouchi!
Brother! I'm going too!
Don't!
Let's just wait here and have faith in them.
This is...! Could it be?
The God Cards!
Obelisk!
Ra!
Osiris!
They're finally back with us again.
But the hidden power within these cards has been stolen.
But I'm sure the cards are just happy to be back with us.
Right.
Let's hurry, Partner!
Right!
The soul cards carved on the wall are all empty!
Did that monster eat them all?!
Jounouchi-kun! Kaiba-kun!
Hermos!
Critias!
Now that I've got this, I'm even more courageous!
Humph. This was mine to begin with!
Now, enter.
My Chosen Duelists!
Dartz!
Let's move, guys!
I don't need you to tell me that!
Is this...?
Are we really standing in Atlantis?
Dartz must be somewhere around here.
Hey! Look over there!
Dartz must be up there!
Dartz!
Is he there?!
He's...!
Dartz!
What the heck?
Does that mean Dartz's body was already destroyed?
You were too late, my Chosen Duelists.
Dartz!
My God has already been resurrected!
Ridiculous! I thought you couldn't revive the God of Orichalcos without our souls!
Indeed, it is far from complete.
But I shall offer up my soul in your stead!
What did you say?!
Wh-What the hell?!
What?!
That's the God of Orichalcos!
It's freakin' huge!
That's...!
Dartz!
He's sacrificed his own soul!
My Chosen Duelists!
No one shall be able to stop this God any longer!
Shut your mouth! So that's what the real you looks like?!
That despicable form?
Then allow me to personally put you out of your misery!
I wonder if you can!
Don't think you're gonna just blow us away after we came this far!
Let's go, guys!
Come out! Black Magician!
Demon's Summon!
Kuriboh!
Come on out!
Flame Swordsman!
Psycho Shocker!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Come forth! Blue-Eyes Ultimate Dragon!
Gadget Soldier!
Blood Vorse!
And finally...
Come forth, nameless dragons!
Lend us your powers!
Show us your true forms! Legend of Heart!
That's the true forms of the Legendary Dragons?
Go on, our Monsters!
Super Charged Black Magic!!
Time Energy Black Flare!!
Ultimate Burst Missile Strike!!
I use the power of Kuriboh and Multiply and I'll let Timaeus absorb their Landmine Ability!
Let us go, my sword!
Justice Sword!!
You did it!
Now everyone will-
What!?
Impossible!
Is this a joke? He wasn't even scratched after all those attacks?!
Hold on a damn minute!
If that attack hits us...!
Legendary Knight Timaeus!
Absorb the abilities of Big Shield Gardna!
Activate his Special Effect!
It wiped all of our Monsters out in one strike!
Damn it...
If this goes on, we'll never win this!
It's coming again!
That's...
That light pattern...!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
We finally beat Dartz!
But despite that, it looks like...
Dartz used his own soul as the sacrifice and managed to revive the God of Orichalcos!
Does that mean the Legendary Knights are useless in front of such enormous power?!
And it's only a matter of time before the world is submerged by a massive tsunami!
But we still believe!
That Yugi and the guys won't lose!
Next time!
"Battle of the Gods"
Duel standby!