Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Light so glaring that it can't be hidden shatters the silence and revives in this world
The violently quaking and thirsty Earth stakes its life and clashes together with sparks
Just one more time is enough to create a miracle
For the power to regain the pages of memory lost in the past
The believing heart that penetrates the darkness searches for the place where its soul sleeps
And burns a sharp glance of eyes that can't sparkle
Two hearts of light and shadow head toward the future that the crystal reflects
Now they start to move, these eyes brimming red
Where are you going?
Leave me... Leave me alone!
It's useless trying to escape.
You still have a mission to complete.
Mission?
The Millennium Items are now in the possession of the Pharaoh, you and Shadi.
Shadi will surely hand over his items to the Pharaoh one day.
Eventually, all the Millennium Items will be in the hands of you and him.
The time is now.
However, having all seven Millennium Items
isn't enough to open the Door of the Underworld.
Apart from these seven Millennium Items,
an additional hidden item known as the Eighth Key must be found.
I...
The Eighth Key will open the Door of the Underworld.
That secret is hidden in the Pharaoh's Memory World.
I know nothing about all this!
Nameless Pharaoh!
When the door to your memory opens...
...the Ultimate Dark Game from three thousand years ago will start!
"The Ultimate Game"
[Year 1960]
Are we finally here?
If you're going to turn back,
now's the time, Sir.
From here on out is
the territory of the dead.
As the sun goes down, darkness will soon devour everything...
It might even eat up the souls of the living.
The Valley of the Kings... This is the burial grounds of Ancient Egyptian Pharaohs.
I'm here in search of the ultimate game.
There have been more than sixty graves discovered in this valley.
But it's said that nobody has been able to enter the inner chambers of the King's tomb.
Before the World War,
a member of the British Royal Archaeological Team said this with his last breath...
'The Dark Games"... or so they say.
"The Dark Games"...
That sure is an interesting name.
That tomb has many traps that nobody could solve.
I'm sure there must be wonderful treasures hidden in the depths of that tomb.
But Sir, we've made a promise.
We are different from death-seekers like yourself.
We'll guide you until we reach the entrance of that tomb.
But you will need to lead us to the treasures after that, Sir.
I know.
I have no interest in treasures.
Let's have something to eat first.
Graverobbing is best done at night, after all.
It's almost time.
Yeah.
Sir, we've actually been wanting to ask you about your strange attire...
Are you planning to propose to someone in the tomb?
Something like that.
I live only for games.
So I always show my greatest respect towards my gaming opponents.
And if I ever lose a game...
...then I'll trade my tux in for denim jeans and overalls,
...while collecting years instead of chips.
Tonight's game could cost you more than just the clothes on your back.
You'd better be careful.
I've traveled the world,
playing cards, Chess and various other gambles.
I have won in countless games.
It was at that time that I heard of a rumored legend...
About the most dangerous game that exists in Egypt's Valley of the Kings.
There lies glory that nobody else has ever claimed.
That's right...
With my gaming life at stake, I take on this challenge for the ultimate honor.
Let's have you go first, Mister Mutou.
Yes.
This is...!
The bones of graverobbers...
Are these the remains of the people who lost in the game?
Hey Brother, look at that!
Here too!
The treasures have appeared!
Brother!
Alright!
Don't move!
What are you doing? We are the ones that found them!
Looks like the game has started.
What is this? We've reached a dead-end!
Where's the treasure?
Does our journey end here?
Don't be impatient.
"Beyond this point... rests the great Pharaoh...
The Gods shall punish you, o ye who dares disturb him...
Your body will rot and your soul be cursed to eternal darkness."
You can interpret hieroglyphs?
I can't... So I'm rather amazed myself.
Either way, the real entrance is here.
But I don't see an entrance anywhere.
What is this?!
What is going on here?
This is the entrance.
Horus, the Falcon God,
represents the Pharaoh...
"The Opener of The Way."
Just what... is this place?
Looks like this is one of the main stages in the game...
It's impossible for us to climb down.
We can only take that path.
Let's go ahead then!
There must be treasures lying ahead!
B-Brother, I don't want to go...
I don't want to die here.
I'm going back.
Shut up!
Now listen to me! We're not the ones in danger.
We just need him to clear the game and then we can get to the treasures.
Brother...
Heh... Don't worry. If the need arises...
O-Okay...
Good.
The entrance..!
The wall is..!
A-At this rate...!
So the only way out is
through this passage?
But there's no telling what kind of traps lie ahead...!
Damn!
Hey, you! Get moving this instant!
Stop hesitating!
You must cross it first!
Damn! I've got no choice but to take this path...!
What?!
It's impossible to get past this many statues!
Think of a way!
If this is truly a Dark Game...
...there must be a solution to this puzzle hidden somewhere!
But if this goes on...
It stopped for a moment just now!
You lousy fraud!
All that talk about showing your greatest respect towards games?!
Games?
I see.. That's what it is.
In Ancient Egypt, the Pharaoh is God!
And statues dedicated to the Pharaoh always have the left foot forward.
It symbolizes taking your heart
from the left side of your chest and presenting it to your god, the Pharaoh.
A display of ultimate loyalty.
This is the area of the gods.
No matter who it may be,
all must be humble.
Those who forget respect are punished with death!
I've solved the puzzle of this room!
Walk by keeping your left foot forward!
You'll get attacked by the statues if you walk with your right foot forward!
Left foot?
I've never heard of this method of walking!
Do it!
You're nearly there! Be careful!
Mushara!
I'm sorry, but this is the rule of the Dark Games.
Fine, keep moving!
This is the second room.
"The Ka sealed in the stone slabs shall judge you...
The cowardly will have their souls eaten by demons...
The courageous will be shown the way..."
Look at that!
There's got to be treasure inside!
Go on!
Quickly!
What is this feeling?
Like I've seen this before...
What's wrong? Go on already!
Just a bit more...
With this, I will have conquered the legendary game.
Looks like he's going to get across safely.
Now that I know this bridge is safe, I have no further use for you.
You solved the Dark Games.
Now you can die in peace!
You bastard..!
I'm going ahead, you odd-ball.
All the treasure belongs to me now!
Am I imagining things?
But this drawing is really mysterious.
What the..?!
I've come so far...!
Is this... the end...?
I've been waiting for you, Shimon.
I was...
This is the symbol of glory.
And that was how I obtained the Millennium Puzzle.
Grandpa, you were cool back in your day.
I may have exaggerated things a little.
But why are you asking
me about the past?
Are you planning to go to Egypt?
Yes.
The stone slab in the museum has been sent back to Egypt already.
That's right... We'll embark on our journey to Egypt tomorrow.
And when I show the three God Cards to the stone slab...
The other me will set off on a journey to get his memories back.
Hey Grandpa, do you still remember the location of the Pharaoh's tomb?
I can't remember now.
Because I hired special guides back then.
The Valley of the Kings is a big place and there are many caves that look the same.
Is that so?
Since I'm going to Egypt,
I wanted to visit the place where the Millennium Puzzle originally was.
You can't! You can't go there!
Speaking of which, Yugi, can you show me one last time?
Again? This is the fifth time!
Just the thought of not seeing them makes me really depressed!
I get it already, Grandpa!
The God Cards!
I want them~!
No way! You can't have them!
It stirs my blood as a collector!
If you won't sell them,
leave them here when you go to Egypt and let me display them in the store!
No means no!
Okay...
Grandpa, you don't understand just how important these cards are to the other me.
Y-You're right.
The spirit of the Pharaoh
residing in your body
is going to embark on his journey soon.
I've been waiting for you, Shimon.
As I was injured, I brought the Millennium Puzzle straight back.
But there may be areas in that tomb no one has ever set foot in...
And perhaps only the one who solved the Millennium Puzzle can reach those areas.
Yugi, the owner of the Millennium Puzzle inherits the spirit of the Pharaoh.
And as a result, you will be tested endlessly.
Tested?
Yes, and no matter what happens, you must not give up during those trials!
There are things that can only be gained when you overcome these trials.
Things that can be gained?
That's right, things like courage and glory.
You will understand when the time comes.
Right!
I won't lose to these tests.
That's my grandson!
Right, time to sleep.
Good night, Yugi.
Good night!
Other Me...
What's wrong, Partner?
I... have some things I need to tell you.
Are you holding yourself back because of me?
Holding back?
Many things happened after we got the God Cards in Battle City.
And I was thinking that
maybe I was the reason
you've been holding off on
your journey for your memories...
I can't help but think that way.
I met you when I completed the Millennium Puzzle.
Ever since you appeared, I wasn't lonely anymore.
I got to know Jounouchi-kun, Honda-kun,
Kaiba-kun, and many other friends.
Because of you, I've gotten so many things that I'm really thankful for.
But I'm really sad if you're holding yourself back because of me.
Partner...
Other Me, please don't hold yourself back.
I'll be fine even if I'm alone.
I get it, Partner.
No matter what happens to me from now on, I'll never forget you and the others.
Other Me... Just like how I put the Millennium Puzzle together...
It's your turn to put the pieces of your memory back together.
Before you complete your mission, we'll always be partners.
That's right, Partner.
I bet Yugi didn't think we would come and steal the God Cards.
Yup. Now that it's come ta this, let's give it all we got!
Yikes, he's awake! Let's run!
Hold it!
Where did they go?!
It's supposed to be my duty to protect the God Cards and the Millennium Items..!
We made it this far, so we can relax.
The God Cards...
The freakin' God Cards...!
What the hell's all this?
Who the hell're you?!
It's finally my turn to appear.
I know you! You're that guy who's always following Yugi around!
Could it be... You're also goin' after the God Cards?!
It would be a problem for me if you went and took the God Cards.
I'll dispose of anyone who gets in my way.
That was..!
Who are you?!
Bakura-kun!
To show us now...
...a map isn't needed.
Only what tore apart the darkness...
...the hope that lies in my hands.
Without deciding on a goal...
I'll just take a step toward my dream.
EYE'S, while I feel them...
I'll find your eyes.
Oh! EYE'S, if what I wished for...
...shudders my very soul...
...a Duel.
In order to help the other Yugi start on his journey to the Memory World,
Yugi made up his mind to go to Egypt.
Bakura-kun appeared as well.
Is he our enemy? Or perhaps an ally?
He got back the God Cards Haga and Ryuzaki stole...
...but he suddenly announced the start of the Ultimate Dark Game.
After that, he goes to challenge Kaiba-kun to a Duel!
Next time!
"Dark Bakura on the Move"
Duel standby!