Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
At last, the KC Grand Prix has started!
No matter who my opponent is, it's decided I'll be the winner!
In the first round, my opponent is... Mask the Rock.
I don't know what type of deck he's using,
but I'm gonna beat him real quick and strip him of that mask!
This guy's using some really ridiculous strategies!
What is that temple about?
"The Illusionary Ancient Dragon"
My turn!
Draw!
I Summon Goblin Attack Force in Attack Mode!
I attack Ancient Giant with Goblin Attack Force!
Reverse card, open! The Permanent Trap, Ordeal of a Traveler!
It activates when the opponent's Monster attacks me.
It allows me to force the opponent to guess a card I hold in my hand.
If you get it wrong, the attacking Monster must return to its owner's hand.
I only have this one card! So guess it, Jounouchi!
Now!
Jounouchi's really thinking hard.
Because old man Sugoroku beat him at dice a little while ago.
A Magic? A Trap? A Monster?
I don't know! Like hell I'd know!
Hurry it up!
Shut up! It's a Magic! I've determined it's a Magic Card!
This was the right answer!
It was a Monster?
Jounouchi! Looks like the luck you've depended on has run out!
Not luck! Ability!
Ability..? Does he even know what he's saying?
Not good... Now Jounouchi-kun has no Monsters on the field.
If Sugoroku-san attacks him directly next turn, then it's decided...
Jounouchi-kun!
I set one card! Turn end!
My turn! Draw!
I'll go now, Jounouchi! I Direct Attack the player with Ancient Giant!
Go, Ancient Giant!
Giant Smash!!
Reverse card, open! Scapegoat!
Don't look down on me! I'm not just some Duelist relying on luck!
So why don't you try using your head a little the next time you guess?
What?
Ordeal of a Traveler is a Permanent Trap.
Meaning every time you attack, the quiz will continue!
Eh... W-Well, that's just fine!
If I just stay calm and think it through, I can guess your entire hand!
One of them has got to be the Killer Snake from earlier...
So the other one...
As long as I know this, I can attack with my Monsters next turn.
I activate the Continuous Magic Card from my hand, Ancient Book!
Awright!
Now I just have that one Killer Snake to worry about!
The Effect of Ancient Book allows me to switch a card in my hand with the card atop my Deck.
You jerk! How could you do that?!
It's a pity, Jounouchi.
I switch the Ancient Giant Tokens to Defense Mode and...
...end my turn!
In the event the Ancient Giant Tokens don't attack the opponent's Monsters,
the player receives 500 points of damage to their Life for each.
He's slashing his own Life...
So why Defense Mode?
Shit... My turn! Draw!
Should I take a gamble and attack again with Goblin Attack Force?
But If I guess it wrong this time,
I'll only have three Monsters, the Scapegoat Tokens!
If he draws another Monster next turn, I'll lose!
But won't his card be Killer Snake?
I Summon Goblin Attack Force in Attack Mode!
So what'll you do?
Turn end!
Ya damned coward!
Jounouchi's being completely dragged along by Old Man Sugoroku's pace.
You can't help but feel a bit bad for him.
Professor Hopkins...?
Grandpa...
Time of death: 53 minutes after the hour.
The winner! Leon Wilson!
Doctor, pull yourself together!
Doctor!
Finally...! Finally, we made it...!
It's not a dream! It's not an illusion! It's the real Kaiba Land!
Now that we got this far, we're gonna join that tournament, no matter what!
That's right! We'll defeat Yugi and Jounouchi this time for sure!
Right!
We tossed aside our pride an' shamed ourselves long ago!
We got nothin' left ta' fear!
Yeah!
My turn! Draw!
In order to keep Ancient Book on the field, I must discard one card to the Graveyard!
And in turn, Killer Snake's Special Effect is activated!
If it is in the Graveyard during my Standby Phase,
I can return it to my hand.
Killer Snake, come home!
Are you fooling around with me or what, ya jerk?!
Nope, Jounouchi!
I'm long done fooling around with you.
What do you mean?
While you've been busy ranting and raving,
I've been treasure hunting at my leisure.
Huh? Treasure hunting?
Right! The Legendary Dragon sleeping within Metropolis of Ancient Times - Ancient City!
That is the identity of my treasure!
The hell're you talking about?
Other Me...
When the Forbidden Door within Ancient City is opened, the Legendary Dragon will be revived!
I have collected all the keys to the door!
Now I see...! So that's what he meant?!
I switch the Ancient Giant Tokens from Defense to Attack Mode!
Switching the Battle Position of the Giant Stone Tokens must be a part of the puzzle!
I will then activate my Continuous Magic, Ancient Key!
Attack! Defense!
By switching the Ancient Giant Tokens from a defensive stance to an offensive stance,
and offering up the Ancient Key as a holy tribute,
I invoke the Ancient Door from my deck, hand or Graveyard!
Wh-What the?!
And the Effect of the Field Magic, Metropolis of Ancient Times - Ancient City activates!
When Ancient Door, Ancient Giant and Ancient Book are all gathered together on the field,
I can sacrifice the three cards...
...in turn reviving The Golden Dragon - Ancient Dragon from its age-old slumber!
That's...!
So that's Grandpa Sugoroku's treasure...
Grandpa...
What's up, Jounouchi? Surprised, are we?
So Sugoroku really was playing for the Ancient Dragon...
Those are...!
Ancient Dragon requires Ancient Door, Ancient Key...
...Ancient Book, Ancient Giant, and two Ancient Giant Tokens.
You can't Summon it without these.
Basically, you have to gather a hoard of mythical cards.
The truth is, like Sugoroku, I too have been searching all over for these cards.
But I was never able to get the remaining card, Ancient Door.
And yet, Sugoroku...
Hello? It's me, Arthur!
The truth is...
Don't get too shocked now!
I finally found that card, the Ancient Door card!
Say what now?!
Now I have all the cards!
Sugoroku?
Wanna see them?
W-Well...!
That's right!
And so, that's why I'm going!
To see everyone's surprised faces!
Grandpa...
Yugi-kun, that's just the kind of person Sugoroku is.
He's a good Duelist, but he loves the cards above all else.
Compared to fighting, he loves the cards more.
That's why when he got the card, he wanted to show it to all of us as soon as possible!
On the greatest stage possible!
Your grandfather's just like a kid!
It's true!
It's fine if he's like a kid.
Duel Monsters was originally created to allow people of all ages regain their lost childhood.
Sugoroku truly enjoys this game for all it's worth.
Enjoys? I see!
Jounouchi, how do you like my treasure?
Amazing, ain't it?
It's just one little dragon. Don't let your ego go to your head.
I wouldn't brag about a deck like that!
Jounouchi... You've grown up to be a very boring man.
In that case, I'll let you see firsthand just how great my treasure is!
I use Ancient Dragon to attack Goblin Attack Force!
Go now, Ancient Dragon!
Golden Bomb!!
What?
Even the Sheep Tokens were destroyed?
Ancient Dragon's Special Effect has activated.
When I use this card to destroy the opponent's Monsters,
I can destroy all the Defense Mode Monsters on the opponent's field.
Shit!
Don't joke around...!
How can I be defeated by this masked bastard here?
I wanna fight with Yugi again!
Yugi?
You have to enjoy the Duel, Jounouchi-kun!
You're making this Duel too much about yourself! You have to enjoy it more!
But I..
Right... That ain't like you, Jounouchi!
It doesn't matter if you win or lose this tournament!
Hey! Honda! Don't say things like that!
Jounouchi! This isn't like you!
Jounouchi-kun!
Guys...
Yugi... Everyone... You are such nice people!
Hey! Why are you crying?
Just enjoy it, huh? Guess they're right.
So I'll just cope with this Duel and let the match finish!
That's it, Jounouchi-kun!
You have to have fun!
I, too, am enjoying this!
You can do it!
Mask the Rock!
Wh-Why?!
Alright!
Okay. I'll go now, Masked Bastard.
Okay! Come on!
My turn! Draw!
I activate the Magic Card, Roll of Fate, from my hand!
This card lets the player draw the same number of cards as he rolls from his deck
and remove the same amount of cards from his deck.
Then I'll use a Permanent Trap of my own! Legendary Gambler!
My roll is...
Four!
Masked Bastard's is...
Three!
Booyah! I'll now activate Roll of Fate!
I'm so excited!
W-What do you pick?
I activate the Magic Card, Landstar Forces, from my hand!
This card lets me Special Summon all Monsters with the name "Landstar"
Level Three or lower from my hand in Attack Position!
I Special Summon Rifleman of Landstar...
Knight of Landstar...
...and Freedom Fighter of Landstar in Attack Mode!
Then I sacrifice all three Landstars!
So I can Special Summon Gilford the Lightning in Attack Mode!
I activate his Special Effect!
Lightning Thunder!!
What?!
When you sacrifice three Monsters in order to Sacrifice Summon this...
I can destroy every Monster on the field!
The Ancient Dragon...
It's not over yet... Masked Bastard!
I attack with Gilford the Lightning!
Then you'll have to guess what this card is!
It's a pity, but I read through this already! That card is a Monster Card!
It's that really annoying snake bastard!
Good answer...
Gilford the Lightning, Direct Attack the player!
Lightning Crush Sword!!
Turn end!
What?!
I activate the effect of the Field Magic, Ancient City!
As long as this card is on the field,
at the end of the turn Ancient Dragon is destroyed,
it can be Special Summoned from the Graveyard.
The dragon protected by the divine temple is impossible to destroy!
Now that's interesting...! This is what I'm talking about!
My turn! Draw!
I attack Gilford the Lightning with Ancient Dragon!
They both have 2800 Attack Points!
If this keeps up, they'll both be destroyed!
But that dragon...
Golden Bomb!!
Gilford the Lightning...!
Turn end!
This is pretty fun...
This is what's great about Dueling.
My turn! Draw!
I activate Pot of Greed from my hand!
I draw two cards from my deck!
Hurricane...
This is a Magic Card that returns all Magic and Trap Cards to the players' hands.
That's it... If I use this to return Ancient City to his hand...
Premature Burial...
Wait... If I use this with Hurricane, my cards will also...
Jounouchi! This ain't like you! Don't think about it!
Just wing the match!
Shut up! Keep quiet!
Masked Bastard!
No, Mask the Rock.
How do I say this?
Gathering card after card while hiding your motives...
Thinking of strategy after strategy, combo after combo like this...
I'm really enjoying this right now!
Jounouchi...
I was like this as well back when I first learned to Duel...
I've started to forget this sensation...
But I'm the one who'll win!
Let's go!
I activate the Equipment Magic Card, Premature Burial, from my hand!
After paying 800 Life Points,
I can Special Summon a Monster Card from my Graveyard and resurrect it in Attack Mode.
Revive, Goblin Attack Force!
And I activate the Magic Card, Hurricane, from my hand!
What?
Due to Hurricane's Special Effect,
all of our Magic and Trap Cards on the field will be returned to our hands!
My...! My temple...!
I see! Without the temple, Ancient Dragon can't revive!
That's not my only aim.
I will once again activate Premature Burial from my hand!
What?!
I Special Summon Gilford the Lightning from my Graveyard!
I attack Ancient Dragon with Gilford the Lightning!
Lightning Crush Sword!!
I can't believe it!
And then, Goblin Attack Force, Direct Attack the player!
Jounouchi just...
Won by... using his head!
Masked Bastard, that was an interesting Duel!
You've grown up...
Jounouchi!
Old man Sugoroku!
Surprised, everyone?! It's me, Sugoroku!
What the hell, old man! you sure like to mess with people!
I didn't notice at all!
I know, right?!
But why are you here?
Jounouchi, I came to see you fight.
Me?
As your mentor, I wanted to see how your Dueling has improved.
Well then? How was my Duel?
Let me see...
You really seemed to enjoy the Duel! You pass!
Hell yeah!
I passed!
He's passed what, exactly?
I'm starting to get a headache...
Man, that grandpa of yours...
Why'd he even come here for? I can't figure him out...
You know, right Partner?
It's obvious!
He wants you to enjoy yourself more than anything else!
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
In the first match of the tournament,
Jounouchi won against Sugoroku-san, A.K.A "Mask the Rock" as he proved his growth!
But Jounouchi didn't know it was Sugoroku-san until the very end...
I don't believe it!
The next game is about to begin!
Rebecca will show up soon!
Let's hurry and cheer for her!
And her opponent is... Vivian Wong?
Right! That strange woman!
Next time!
"Hot Battle! Rebecca vs Vivian"
Duel standby!