Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
"I can't do it." "It's too frustrating."
Break down those hurdles.
There is nothing I can't answer.
Who is being manipulated on the field?
I'm not frightened yet I get told to go away...
The path to the unseen future...
I may not be able to choose it.
Close your eyes, and shuffle your heart
Definitely, just like cards
As promised, yes! you are the winner
Never lose! Shuffle your heart,
definitely, just like cards
Ever since that miracle...
Welcome. I am the second Rare Hunter, Pandora.
Also known as the Conjurer, and user of the Black Magician.
User of the Black Magician?
What?!
It's a 100-tooth carbide tipped saw you see in magic shows!
Do you understand the rules of this duel yet?
Is this fun...?
A battle with people's lives on the line...
I'm asking you if you think it's fun!
Yes. Because I will be the winner.
You filthy scum!
Then I'll show you what a true duelist's fight looks like!
"Black Magic From the Soul"
Black Magician! Direct Attack the player!
Black Magic!!
Pandora, if you cut your cards like that, you're just using them for your own needs!
If you continue the game like this, you'll feel the full anger of those cards!
Give this game up right now to save yourself!
"Give up"? Who will?
This is great! The best!
Listen, Yugi... I am a conjurer.
And you are merely the audience for my show.
For the show I control.
I wouldn't be a real magician if I didn't have some tricks up my sleeve...
I will be this game's victor.
Meaning I will be the one to escape and survive!
And the one who'll be chopped to mincemeat...
...is you, Yugi!
Only a fool blinded by his own greed would say such words...
Let's continue the game, Pandora!
Just where did Yugi disappear to?
Just like Jounouchi predicted, he must have been captured by the Ghouls.
We have to hurry and fine him.
But he could be anywhere. Where should we start looking?
Now then, let's resume the duel!
My turn!
Yugi only has Black Magician on the field.
I can't allow him to direct attack me next turn.
In that case...
Killer Tomato in Defense Mode.
Furthermore, I place a card face-down on the field.
Turn over.
He only has a monster in Defense Mode.
If I can Summon another monster on my turn, I can finish this match.
Yugi will surely Summon a monster.
At that moment, my Black Magician shall revive!
My turn!
I Summon Magnet Warrior Beta!
You fell for it!
Trap Card activate!
What?! A trap?!
Reviving Coffin of Black Magic!
It offers a Summoned monster!
Reviving Coffin of Black Magic takes the soul of an enemy's monster,
as well as one of my own monster's soul.
It then revives the Black Magician's soul residing in my Graveyard.
Revive your Black Magician?!
Come forth! Black Magician!
Now there's two Black Magicians on the field.
Now the true battle begins, Yugi.
Monsters with the same Attack Points.
Neither can directly attack each other.
Therefore, we'll both have to use our Magic and Trap Cards
to try and defeat our Black Magicians.
It's become a battle of wits.
In this turn, I'll place 2 set cards face-down on the field.
Turn over!
I know what you're up to, Yugi.
Whoever uses their Black Magician to the fullest...
Then it's now my turn.
I play 2 set cards.
Over.
It's my turn.
I place two cards face-down. Over.
My turn.
Another set card face-down. Over.
It seems we both have 5 cards face-down on the field.
In that case, I'll take the first strike.
Magic Card!
Mystic Guillotine!
What?! A guillotine?!
Black Magician!
Yugi! This is the end of your Black Magician!
In that case, Magic Card open!
Magical Silk Hats!
Magical Hats
What?!
Magical Silk Hats...
He got away?
Then I'll open my second face-down card! Thousand Knives!
Over there!
How's this?!
You saw through it?
Well then, Magic Removal!
Damn you...! I was so close, too...!
Black Magician, attack!
Black Magic!!
Both Black Magicians have been demolished!
Resurrection of the Dead!
Resurrection of the Dead...! So this was also his hidden trump card?
You've fought against my Black Magician quite well.
I praise you, Pandora.
My turn.
Over.
Pandora, your skills are quite good.
If you're a duelist of this caliber, you shouldn't have fallen to this level so easily.
Why is it you fall so low as to follow Malik, and act as one of Ghoul's Rare Hunters?
Look at this face.
Up till now, I've been a professional magician for a number of years.
I was known around the world, and had built the steady living I yearned for.
And, above all, I met my love, Catherine.
However, after a failed escape trick...
My life as a famous magician as well as Catherine's love for me was taken from me.
I focused on myself, and rejected Catherine's love for me.
Her heart disappeared, as if by magic.
I finally came to realize how important Catherine's love for me was afterwards.
However, it was already too late.
Just when I had given up all hope, that man appeared before me.
So he promised me that if I would kill you,
With his Millennium Rod's power, he would recover Catherine's love for me.
Why don't you encourage your lover to trust and believe in you? Even now, it isn't too late!
Honor your girlfriend with your heart and soul!
You're just a kid after all, aren't you. Your opinion is quite extreme.
Trust isn't possible in anything like this.
Thanks to Malik, Catherine will return to my side.
Catherine is already waiting for me over there.
Let us return to France and start over!
Is Malik controlling her mind as well...?!
Catherine, just let me get rid of Yugi. Then we can be together!
And for that... I will end your life.
Just like in a Duel, you have to trust one another!
No matter what happens, I believe in my Black Magician!
In this duel, whoever trusts in his own cards will determine the outcome.
That's the key to victory!
Yugi, you're more naive than I thought!
You think so?
As expected. You're no doubt qualified to be called a Black Magician user.
Although...
You didn't forget, did you?
Before this duel even started,
I told you I was the real Black Magician user.
In other words, I've made the preparations to control the magician in my deck.
And even more, it's flawless!
Yugi... where'd you go?
The new Duel Disk System should connect with Kaiba Corporation's main computer all at times.
However, because the search can't be completed...
And if Yugi ended up in a duel against the Ghouls...
It's most likely a false duel system.
Search the entire Domino City for any unknown Duel Ring being accessed.
Sir!
I figure that a basement or something is blocking the transmission from reaching,
so there's a chance it's somewhere close.
Big brother!
Big brother, I'll go check it out!
My turn.
I set a card face-down on the field and end my turn.
I place 2 set cards face-down.
Turn over.
I'm coming! Magic Card, Beckon to Dark!
What?! That is...!
The Magic Card Beckon to Dark will snatch one of the opponent's monsters
and drag them into the depths of darkness with a demon's claw.
Yes, I'm referring to your Black Magician!
You think I'll let you?!
Trap Card! Hand Mirror of Spirit!
With this Trap Card, I'll control your Magic Card!
You fell for it, didn't you?
What?!
That hand was merely a decoy to lure you into playing your Trap Card.
My aim was this!
This is a Trap Card that activates in response to another Trap Card!
Nightmare Cross!
Black Magician!
Now your Black Magician can only wait on the side lines
as your death is acted out in front of him!
If Black Magician is taken out of commission, the enemy can easily diminish my Life Points.
Have you prepared yourself well?
Go, my servant! Black Magician!
Direct Attack the player!
Black Magic!!
How about that same Black Magic?
Now~! Showtime~!
The Saw-Blade Cutter will now assault the player!
Now my magic show has finally reached its climax.
The moment your Life reaches 0, my task will be complete.
As soon as you are met with despair, the show's curtain will drop!
Yugi, it's your last turn!
If we just continue to randomly search the city like this,
the kidnappers may do unspeakable things!
But if this keeps up, Yugi will...
Huh? Isn't that Mokuba-kun?
Mokuba, it's terrible!
Yugi has... Yugi has been taken somewhere!
It looks like he's been captured by someone!
I know the location.
I'm about to head there right now.
Really?!
We'll go with you!
Yeah. Let's get going.
I Summon Big Shield Gardna!
Defense Mode!
This turn, I have nothing to stop this guy with.
You put out a wall monster, huh?
I see. You're thinking as long as you have a wall monster, I can't do anything to you.
But that's all in vein.
Yugi, your life will end this turn!
I hope you're prepared.
Have you prepared yourself well?
My turn.
For the time being, I Summon 1 monster.
Killer Doll!
And the Magic Card that will cause your death!
The Field Magic, Ectoplasmer!
What?! That card...!
Of course, there's a price.
This Magic Card transforms my monster into Ectoplasm energy,
and I can then directly attack the player.
It will pass right through all wall monsters!
You can't be...! You're willing to sacrifice your own monster's soul?!
That's right!
The selected monster will die!
If it's to win this match and get back Catherine,
my monster's soul is nothing but a stepping stone to get there!
Catherine, just a while longer!
Just a while longer, and you'll be able to come out of there!
Just wait a little longer!
Now, I'm coming.
In this turn, I shall turn both Killer Doll and Black Magician into Ectoplasm!
Ectoplasmer, fire!
Attack!
Just a bit more and I'm done for...!
Yugi, as a Black Magician user, do you understand the reason I am unbeatable?
I'll tell you.
That's because I can step on my servants with no second thought.
Even if it means their deaths.
The way you try to win is pure naivety.
See there, your servant is unable to move.
He can't protect you or do anything.
Isn't it okay to use the life of your servants to defeat the enemy laid out in front of you?!
You bastard!
My Black Magician devotes its life and soul to my needs.
For my victory!
Now, it's finally the finale.
Ectoplasmer, activate!
Change Black Magician into Ectoplasm!
Pandora, your monster is crying.
It's of no matter! Ectoplasmer, attack!
I win!
What?! Th-That's impossible!
Black Magician...!
Black Magician, in order to stop it, transformed itself into Ectoplasm as well!?
Black Magician... You... For my sake...
This turn, because I turned my monster into Ectoplasm, Black Magician was destroyed...
In other words, his Black Magician was also affected at the same time...
But a mere card chose to extract itself by Ectoplasmer
and protect the player from certain death...?!
Tyranny isn't the only method to win a game!
I'll teach you this, Pandora!
Thanks to Black Magician's sacrifice, Yugi was able to escape a great pinch.
But the next time Pandora launches an attack, it's all over!
Pandora proceeds to Summon his second Black Magician.
But there's another type of Black Magician still hiding in Yugi's deck!
Eh? There's a disciple of Black Magician?
Next time! "Magician's Disciple: Black Magician Girl"
Duel standby!
I feel like I've been here, been in this place before
With the classroom shaded by the setting sun
I laughed along and pointed with my too shortly cut bangs
Little by little, time keeps going
My bangs now over my eyes
The sunset took everyone together
I'm sure nothing changed while we were there
For me to be myself
I kept on searching for something
If you understood such a senseless time
That was the answer
From here, always...