A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
"Duel Monsters Quest 2:
The Legendary Hero, Yugi"
Shit!
We gotta hold em back!
Yugi...!
I'll show you just how foolish it was of you to challenge me, boy!
Shut up!
I'll show you up for the fraud champion you really are!
Duel!!
Let's get this started!
Get on out here, Flame Swordsman!
In that case, I'll play this card.
Harpie Lady!
The Harpie, huh?
But I've got more Attack Points on my side!
Go, Flame Swordsman!
How naive!
Allow me to stop that attack of yours!
Silver Screened Mirror Wall!
Hey, hold your ground!
This attack pattern is...
It couldn't be...
You're about a hundred years too early to be sparring with my Harpie!
There's no doubt in my mind!
There's only one person on this planet with an attitude like that!
It's back to my turn again!
Rose Whip!
W-Wait!
Jounouchi...!
It really is Mai-san!
Yugi! Mokuba!
Wh-Why the heck are you guys here?
That's what we'd like to know!
My big brother's been kidnapped!
Kaiba-kun's life is in danger as long as he stays in this game world!
Kaiba is...?
We're all friends.
We shouldn't be fighting each other here.
What the hell're ya doin'?!
Well, I guess we have to fight if we wanna save Kaiba.
We need that card to cross the desert!
So, you just need that card, right?
If that's all...
To be honest, I've been wanting to get away from here myself.
Harpie!
Wh-What the hell are you doing, gecko?!
I'll be taking this!
Run away!
Right!
Don't let them escape, gecko-
These guys are freaking persistent!
Here ya go!
Pitfall, activate!
-What the heck's this?
-What the hell? Hey!
That sure looks impossible to cross by foot.
Mai, use the Cluck card!
Okay.
But what are you doing here anyway?
I was invited to play some new game,
and then I realized I couldn't get out of this world.
Mai Kujaku is also trapped in a simulator?
What the?!
Sand Stone!
Man, this is annoying!
Come on out!
Red-Eyes!
Dark Mega Flare!!
Serves you right!
Huh?
Looks like that Sand Stone was the one making that sandstorm...
So where are we going?
My brother's trapped in the Cave of Death over by that mountain.
We finally made it.
Hey!
Mokuba!
God, he gets too worked up when it comes to Kaiba!
Why the heck does the Cave of Death have to be like this?!
It's creepy...
In any case, we have no choice but to keep moving forward.
Let's open it.
It can't be...
It's the Labyrinth Field!
This ain't good!
Damn, we're trapped!
What do we do now?!
I see!
This world seems to be modeled on various Duels from the Duelist Kingdom.
If that's the case...
There's got to be an exit around here!
What was that just now?
Someone's here!
We're on the way!
Hey, Jounouchi!
Geez...!
He rushes so fast when he hears a girl scream!
Even when he's got a woman with a nice body right here!
What?!
Demonic Tank of the Labyrinth?!
Run!
Shit! Which way?!
Jounouchi-kun!
Huh?
Run away!
This bastard!
I better get rid of it!
We're trapped!
Shit...
Is this the end?
Don't give up yet!
Yeah, I know, but...!
Magical Silk Hats!
Man, that saved us!
Nice reflexes there, Yugi!
They're still following us!
Which way should we run?!
From before...!
A sprite?
When sprites appear in a game,
it's usually some kind of hint!
Does that means it's trying to guide us away from here?
Let's check it out.
Iru!
M-Mokuba...!
Why the heck are you dressed that way?
Stupid.
I'm right over here.
B-But...!
They look exactly the same!
Seriously!
So the person screaming before was you?
A-And you guys are...?
Save the introductions for later.
For now, do you know where the exit is?
I am sorry.
But Iru can guide us.
We did it!
It's the exit!
Shit!
He really did appear!
What in the world is that?!
We don't have a card that can beat that!
Just leave it to us!
Let's go, Yugi!
Mhm-hm!
Red-Eyes Black Dragon!
Demon Summon!
Fusion!
Come forth!
Black Demon's Dragon!
Damn it all!
It's still not enough to stop that thing!
We're not done yet!
Dark Dragon-Type Claws!
It's Attack goes up by 700 points!
Go!
Meteor Flare!!
A-Amazing...
Thank you very much.
How can I repay you?
Don't mention it.
Now let's get out of here!
Meyari-sama!
Bara!
Meyari-sama, I'm so glad you're safe!
And who might these people behind you be?
These people just saved my life.
I'd like to invite you all to the castle as thanks for saving me.
Wh-Where am I...?
So you have finally awaken, Seto Kaiba?
Death Jinn Satan...
What are you planning to do with me?
Is that not obvious?
You are to become a sacrifice for the Five God Dragon!
Five God Dragon?
The Dark God that will plunge this world into darkness!
However, we require one more sacrifice in order to revive the Five God Dragon.
But it is only a matter of time before that matter is resolved.
You bastard, just play this game with me fair and square!
Quit spouting such nonsense!
My job is to dispose of you by any means necessary.
Or would you like to alter my programming and change that?
What did you say...?
Well, wait here patiently for the next sacrifice.
You bastard!!
We cut it close back there.
I'm starting to wonder if we'll make it back safely.
Don't worry.
This Meyari girl seems to be reliable.
That's right.
Speaking of which, she seems to be a character modeled after Mokuba.
Me?
Man, the Big Five are pretty low!
Shut up!
Oh! Look at that!
Awesome!
This is a true fantasy!
I'm sure that in this castle...
...we should find clues about Big Brother.
Wow...
It seems Iru has taken a liking to you.
Could it be that you're...?
Yes.
I am the queen of this kingdom.
I am Meyari.
QUEEN?!
Jounouchi!
No one will want to eat with you if you act like that at the table!
Hey, are you alright?!
I thought I was dead!
That's why I told you!
By the way, My Lady...
Did you hear any news about my big brother, by any chance?
In the Gouland Kingdom as well as the neighboring one,
we are forced to make sacrifices once a year.
Sacrifices?
What do you mean by that?
If we do not offer sacrifices to the Five God Dragon,
it shall destroy our land completely.
The Five God Dragon?
I heard the other kingdom has offered up a prince from a far away land.
That's Big Brother!
Where's my brother?
I'm certain he is being held in the Dark Castle of the Sky.
Castle of the Sky?
Dark Castle of the Sky?
How do we get there?
Please look at the painting over there.
This is a legend from a thousand years ago.
This is the ancient ship used to get to the Dark Castle of the Sky.
However, we are unsure where to find this legendary artifact.
Can't we just use our Monsters to get there?
The Dark Castle of the Sky is surrounded by a barrier that even Monsters cannot cross.
No way...
It's alright.
This is a game.
There's got to be a way to do it.
Don't pay attention to me!
Anyway, have you decided on your sacrifice?
Yes.
It is me.
But I believe you guys may be able to save this land.
The legend speaks of a group of legendary heroes that come to fight the dragon!
It states "When the strongest dragon teams up, the Evil God will be destroyed."
So that's why you were in that place?
You don't mean we're the legendary warriors?!
Yes!
I am convinced that you can save this world!
Oh yeah, I'm pumped!
This is like a dream come true for a fan of heroics!
You're really simple minded.
Saving Kaiba is our top priority here.
But if we don't beat that Five God Dragon,
we can't save Kaiba.
We're bound to come across it!
Thank you all very much.
Now then, these are the outfits of the legendary heroes for you all.
This kind of gives me a good feeling.
How about you, Yugi?
Y-Yeah.
It's a little embarrassing though.
Really?
It fits you well!
I don't think so...
But this has nothing to do with you...
There's no reason for you to do anything dangerous.
What the heck are you talking about? My god!
All we're doing is riding on some ship!
Mai-san...
By the way, where's Jounouchi?
Hey, why am I the only one wearing a costume like this?
It's fine. Just get out here already!
Freaking ridiculous, ain't it?!
I think so, too!
But that is the official attire of our legendary hero.
Wh-What the?
What the heck's going on?
Princess! It is far too dangerous!
Please return to the castle!
They really came awfully fast!
There's so many of them!
Let's go!
Valkyrie!
It's no good!
There's too many opponents!
Mai-san! Call Valkyrie back!
What are you gonna do?
I've got no choice but to battle them all!
Return, Valkyrie!
I activate Black Hole!
Destroy all the Monsters!
What?!
Dammit!
Blue Ninja has the Effect to destroy 1 Magic Card!
Princess!
Axe Raider!
Attack with the Chain-Equipped Boomerang!
-My dear princess!!
-Meyari!
No way...
Mokuba-sama...
Shit!
By "Mokuba-sama"...
...you mean, you're...!
Princess!
The princess...?
Then the one taken...!
It was Mokuba-sama...
Mokuba-sama...
Change places with me.
If I'm taken as the sacrifice, I'm sure my big brother will be there as well!
It is my fault...
If I had been taken as the sacrifice as planned...
I beg of you!
Please save Mokuba-sama!
But, the Dark Castle...
How do we get there...?
H-hey! Over there!
Look over there!
What's wrong, Yugi?
Is something wrong over there?
It almost looks like the Nazca geoglyphs...
It does...
But take a closer look at the pattern.
C-Could that be a card of some kind?!
So, that's the legendary flying machine?
"To all the citizens of Gouland Kingdom:
It is now the time for us to stand up.
In order to help the legendary heroes enter the Dark Castle of the Sky,
so they can defeat the evil entity, the Five God Dragon!
In order to do so, we require your help.
There must be a hint on how to revive the legendary flying machine in this town.
We must find it, at all costs!"
Just you wait.
Kaiba-kun, Mokuba-kun!
We're on our way to save you!
It's no use.
We couldn't find anything at all.
There wasn't a single clue about the flying machine at all!
And you all?
We made it this far, too...!
Don't give up yet, Jounouchi-kun!
Right!
There's got to be a clue of some kind!
There isn't any!
This is a sick game the Big 5 created!
While we're wasting time here, Kaiba and Mokuba are...!
There has to be some kind of hint...
Think...
Just think!
Something...
A long time ago, the legendary heroes used the ship to enter the Dark Castle in the Sky.
Princess!
How long ago did that legend take place?
1,000 years, I believe.
I get it!
So that's what it means?!
The flying machine has been lying dormant for 1,000 years.
And what about it?
In that case, we just have to go back 1,000 years!
1,000...?
There's no way we can do that-
You can!
You can do it, Jounouchi!
Right.
Why does this symbol resemble that of a card?
It's meant to be revived with a card!
Jounouchi-kun, you have the card to do it with.
That's it!
We can really go back 1,000 years using this.
The Time Magician!
But this is a gambler's card.
There's no guarantee it'll work.
We have to save Kaiba-kun and Mokuba-kun by any means necessary!
Okay.
We're counting on you, Time Magician!
Go back a thousand years!
Time Magic!
Time Magic!!
What in the world is happening?
Damn, it didn't work?
It's no use!
Add another table!
Hurry and come back!
Yugi!
"Preview"
With the Time Magician's powers, they were able to revive the flying machine!
They destroy the Monsters blocking the way,
and Yugi and the others are able to enter the Dark Caste!
They locate Kaiba-kun,
and the game is cleared!
They thought so,
but it turns out to be another one of the Big Five's traps!
Yugi, hurry up and return!
That worlds in a pinch right now!
Next time!
"Duel Monsters Quest 3:
Master of Dragon Knight"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship