A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
When one is pushed into a corner during a Duel...
what is it they need more than anything to press on?
That is one's own strong will and determination!
A Duelist lacking this courage
will only end up betraying themselves
and their friend's expectations.
Even so I still want to protect my friends!
I want to protect Yugi!
Battle!
Friendship!
Silver Lightning Arrow!!
Harpie Lady is beaten!
I lost.
Mai-san...
Yugi!
Please use these to save your grandfather!
Anzu...
Yeah!
I'll try!
Yugi...!
To Duel with your will and determination.
That's a Duelist.
Isn't that right, my other self?
"Rescue Mokuba!
Kaiba VS Pegasus"
We're finally here...
Pegasus' castle!
You guys...!
You earned enough Star Chips?!
That's right!
But only three can now enter as finalists.
We are those three people!
What?!
We've met all the conditions.
There shouldn't be a problem.
Please excuse us.
We finally made it into the castle.
Wait.
What are you guys doing?
We're the cheerleaders!
What?
No way, no way!
You aren't allowed to enter this castle!
-Come to think of it, how did you even get on the island--
-Don't be so cheap!
Just let this pass~
P-l-e-a-s-e~
'Kay?
No! I can't!
I cannot allow them all to--
H-hey!
Now!
Wait!
How's that feel?
Hey, you bastards! Open up!
Okay. Let's go!
Wait for me, Grandpa...!
I will rescue you for sure!
That's...
Bandit Keith!
Oi oi, ain't this a surprise?!
I can't believe you got out of that cave!
Bandit Keith...!
You have the nerve to trap us in a cave!?
Hey, hey!
Don't get all pissed!
I'll be your opponent later!
What'd you say?!
An interestin' show's about to start!
Look over there!
That's...!
Kaiba-kun!
It's about to start.
Kaiba and Pegasus' Duel.
Kaiba-kun and Pegasus' Duel?
That's correct.
The four contestants in the championship tournament...
Welcome to Pegasus' Castle.
Though it seems like some uninvited guests have let themselves in.
Well, I'll let it slide this time.
In any case, a special performance has been prepared for the ones who have survived their matches in Duelist Kingdom.
To show his appreciation of your entering this tournament, Master Pegasus has prepared a special match for our guests.
You will all simply participate as observants.
He just wants to show us how strong he is...
Well now, that may be the case indeed.
He's looking down on us.
Well then, take your time and enjoy watching this special match.
Kaiba-kun...
Mokuba, wait for me.
I'll surely beat Pegasus and bring you back!
Pegasus!
Welcome! Welcome to my castle
once again, Kaiba boy!
I have been waiting for the day where I could battle a proud Duelist such as yourself right here in my Duelist Kingdom.
Don't you worry one bit, Kaiba boy.
Simply defeat me in this Duel,
and I'll return Mokuba boy to you!
Now, Kaiba boy.
Let's enjoy a great Duel!
Pegasus' power comes from his Millennium Eye,
the power to see into minds.
I'd really like Kaiba and Pegasus to both lose...
But if Pegasus loses, we won't be able to enter into the championship finals...
Yeah, so let's hope to see Kaiba as the loser dog this time.
I know in order to save
Grandpa I have to beat Pegasus.
But, then why...?
I don't want Kaiba-kun to lose...
I don't want him to lose!
It seems that the four official finalists have gathered in my castle.
Kaiba-kun!
Yugi!
You found a way into the castle?
I expected no less from you.
It seems you as well, Yugi boy,
share the same fate of fighting me.
Now, let's begin our Duel, Kaiba boy.
Pegasus!
I'll be fighting you with these Duel Disks in this Duel!
Is it supposed to be used as a fan?
But it is a bit heavy for that.
Or maybe you toss it around like this?
Stop screwing around!
Then we can if you want.
I'll allow the use of the Duel Disks, however...
I'll have someone operate it in my place.
What?!
Of course, he will be following the memo I hand him for the cards he chooses.
That bastard...
It will not change the fact that I am your opponent.
Understand?
Pegasus, you bastard...!
Fight me one on one!
It is basic gaming strategy to never fight on your enemy's turf...
The mind games have already begun, Kaiba boy.
Of course, this little trick of yours will hold no advantage over my Millennium Eye anyway.
Bring out the person who will operate the Duel Disk for me.
That's...!
Mokuba!
Mokuba...
Mokuba-kun!
He looks a bit strange, doesn't he...?
What did Pegasus do to Mokuba-kun?
What's the matter, Kaiba boy?
Aren't you glad to have
Mokuba boy as your opponent?
Pegasus!
Mokuba boy's soul has been sealed in this card.
Sealed in the card?!
What's he mean by that...?
Does that mean he's been hypnotized, oi?
The Mokuba boy in front of you is merely a soulless shell.
But, he will respond to simple orders I give him.
Kaiba boy, if you can defeat me
I will release Mokuba boy's
soul from the sealed card.
Pegasus! You bastard...!
Mokuba-kun...!
No way...!
Pegasus' Power of Darkness has sealed Mokuba-kun too?
I see...
Kaiba-kun did such reckless things
in order to save Mokuba-kun.
Now, you will operate the Duel Disk for me, Mokuba-boy.
W-wait!
Huh? What's the matter, Kaiba boy?
Like you wanted, we'll be using the Duel Disks in our Duel!
A-are you telling me to fight against Mokuba...?!
Big brother!
Big brother...
That's the one thing...
that's the one thing I can't do...!
Kaiba-kun...
I understand, Pegasus.
I'll take back using the Duel Disks.
Mokuba boy.
Your cherished big brother unfortunately
does not wish to fight against you.
Mokuba...
Then let's prepare to Duel.
There's a Duel Ring... all the way up there!
Finally it begins...
Kaiba-kun and Pegasus' Duel!
We will play by the "Kingdom Rules".
Is that okay with you?
Then please prepare your Deck.
Kaiba-kun! Watch out for
Pegasus' Dragon-Type Sealing Jar!
Dragon-Type Sealing Jar?
Against this jar, even Blue-Eyes White Dragon is useless!
Choose your cards carefully, Kaiba-kun!
Yugi! Why are you giving Kaiba advice?!
Because Kaiba is fighting to get back
his precious Mokuba-kun!
He can't lose no matter what!
Yugi...
Yugi, I'll take your feelings into consideration.
But I trust in my cards!
Foolish... wasting others' advice...
No matter who the opponent...
I will fight alongside my Blue-Eyes!
And I'll defeat you!
DUEL!!
Well then, I'll take my turn first.
A monster in Defense Mode.
Also, I will set another card.
Turn over.
Is it a Magic Card... or a Trap Card?
My turn!
I already have a Blue-Eyes in my hand...
I can use it and open with an all-out strike...
But the problem is whether he has that Dragon-Type Sealing card Yugi told me about...
I set one card face-down.
Also... Rude Kaiser in Attack Mode!
Attack the Defense monster!
OH NOOO~!
Turn over.
Kaiba boy's monster has
1800 Attack Points, eh?
That exceeds my monster's Defense Points by 200...
Wow! This card may work!
Parrot Dragon, attack!
Then I will activate a Counter-Magic Card!
What?!
The card I had set is Hypnotism!
This card reduces the Attack of your monster by 800 points!
Now's your chance, Rude Kaiser!
Oh nooo~
Are you taking this seriously, Pegasus...?
What the?
Pegasus is pretty weak, ain't he...?
He's so weak he couldn't counter anything...
Yeah...
It couldn't be...! That Pegasus...!
Yeah.
This is Pegasus' way of messing with you...
Don't let your guard down, Kaiba-kun.
I'd say it's about time to end the
entertaining tension I've filled the air with, eh?
Kaiba boy, I can read your mind.
And of course, that includes your hand.
My turn!
With the progress I've made in the turns so far...
there's a high possibility he doesn't have the Dragon-Type Sealing Jar in his hand...
My instinct tells me he doesn't have the Dragon Capture Jar in his hand!
In that case, I'll end this fight!
Stop!
Stay there. Don't move.
Don't show me that card.
I am going to activate a Trap Card against the card you're about to play.
What?
The card I played face-down was the Prophesy card.
This card's effect allows me to guess the Attack Points of a monster in your hand.
So I guess if it's "Big or small".
If I guess right, that card becomes mine.
Wh-what did you say?!
I predict it has more than 2000 Attack Points, big!
But that is not enough to prove this.
I'll predict further details.
That card has 3000 Attack Points, and it is your most trusted card.
Blue-Eyes White Dragon!
Impossible!
Did Pegasus see my hand somehow?!
Well then, this card is now mine.
How's it feel, Kaiba boy?
Your most trusted card being stolen, I mean.
Kaiba-kun's Blue-Eyes...!
Are you serious...?
As I thought... Is Pegasus really reading Kaiba-kun's mind with his Millennium Eye?
I can't believe he actually had a Trap Card waiting to take the opponent's card...
I will now add this card to my hand.
Blue-Eyes...!
Now, let us continue with the Duel, Kaiba boy.
This turn I'll just switch Rude Kaiser to Defense Mode, and it's finished.
Then it's my turn.
I'll pay you back next turn...
It looks like you've got something planned on that face.
But it's no use.
I know everything in your mind.
Mind Scan!
I see...
You have a Virus Card in your hand...
You plan to use the dark clown to activate the Virus Combo...
and destroying my deck with this deadly infection.
Indeed this is a clever plan.
But it won't work against me!
I'll play a set card.
Also, I'll play a monster in Defense Mode.
And with that my turn is over.
My turn!
Pegasus! This turn you're finished!
My card is the Death Virus Combo!
I'll offer Saggi the Dark Clown to activate the Virus Card.
To destroy your entire deck!
Now, go ahead and attack!
Saggi the Dark Clown!
Is this the Virus Combo that caused Yugi to suffer?
If this move works, Pegasus is dead!
No! It won't work!
Pegasus saw through it!
What?!
Then I'll activate my face-down Magic Card!
What!?
And the card is...
Dark Energy!
This card doubles the Attack Points of all Dark Attribute Monsters in play!
Saggi the Dark Clown has a Dark Attribute...
Therefore its Attack is doubled!
Not good...!
The Virus card only works with monsters under 1000 Attack Points!
That Virus Card has been stopped!
He even saw through my Virus Card?!
And it's my turn.
I place my card, Dark Rabbit, in Attack Mode.
Because it is a Dark Attribute Monster, its Attack doubles!
Dark Rabbit, attack Saggi the Dark Clown!
No way...!
The Virus Combo that gave Yugi so much trouble...
was defeated so easily...!
Kaiba-kun...
Kaiba boy.... the fear is beginning to cloud your mind...
But.... it's just begun.
You will experience true terror when you enter my world...
"Preview"
Finally, Pegasus' trump card, Toon World, appears.
Pegasus' Toons are dodging every one of Kaiba-kun's attacks and transforming them into Toons.
He even turns the Blue-Eyes into a Toon to make Kaiba-kun suffer!
Hey, even if you're the one who invented Duel Monsters,
It's too dirty for you to own this card!
Next Time: "Kaiba Falls! The Invincible Toon World"
Duel Standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship