Obey the Rules and manners
to have a fun Duel!!
Sometime ago, for the sake of living, we left behind our happiness.
We deceived ourselves, clinging to this mere illusion as we danced...
With closed eyes, at the end of the horizon,
I was searching for your smiling face...
We embrace our dreams and continue on...
within the swaying traces of memories...
Someday, I will once again grasp hold of
these feelings I have locked away in my heart... Now...
I managed to defeat Dartz using the Legendary Knights.
And I got Partner and the others' souls back!
But Dartz offered up the many other souls he collected along with his own...
...and was able to resurrect the God of Orichalcos!
It surfaced along with the legendary Atlantis...
The remains of the island were entangled by the Orichalcos God.
Is it even possible for us to defeat this thing?
"Battle of the Gods"
This light...!
Everyone! It is now time to lend our master our strength!
Go on!
The Duel Monsters...!
Don't just stare at them, Yugi! Deadbeat!
We need to use this diversion to rebuild our shield!
Stop calling me a deadbeat!
Let's do this!
Gearfried!
Rocket Warrior!
Gilford the Lightning!
Come out! XYZ-Dragon Cannon!
Blade Knight!
Kaiser Sea Horse!
Chaos Soldier!
Buster Blader!
Magnet Valkyrian!
This time for sure...!
Hell yeah!!
Keep it up, baby!
Gearfried! Gilford the Lightning!
What?!
He wiped them all out!
Critias!
Hermos!
The Legendary Knights...!
Goddammit! I guess it really is hopeless!
Shit! Lemme go!
Master!!
Damn...
My legendary Duelists...
Dartz!
You cannot possibly hope to come even near the power of this God.
For the power of this God...
...originally took on the form of the darkness in the hearts of the souls I captured!
Can you guys not hear the voices crying out from within?
The ones you captured...?
These voices...
Rafael! Haga!
Amelda!
Mai! Varon! Ryuzaki!
I feel them...
Mai and Varon... The darkness of many peoples' hearts...
Does that mean it's growing even stronger inside here?
That is right! After all, it is impossible for human beings to extinguish the darkness that lies within their hearts!
Regardless of how much you three may fend off the darkness lying dormant within your hearts,
so long as even the smallest fragment exists, it can be revived at any time!
So everything we've done up until now...
All of it...
All of it was in vain?!
That's a lie! I won't believe it!
I'll never believe something like that!
Jounouchi-kun!
Mai! Varon! He's lying, isn't he?!
We may have only felt it for a moment...
...but we managed to understand each other!
Amelda...! Are you really going to let everything be in vain and give up like this?!
Nameless Pharaoh!
Seto!
Jounouchi!
You shall now become one with my God!
Yugi...!
Kaiba...!
Jounouchi-kun!
Damn you...!
Dartz!!
Master!!
Partner!
Other me! Don't give up yet!
If we can hear their cries, maybe our hearts can cry out to them!
We can cry out to them?
That's it!
Rafael!
Mai!
Haga!
Ryuzaki!
All of you!
Everyone, please listen to me...
It's not that simple to overcome the darkness in your heart...
But I've sacrificed my partner and many others in this battle...
But there is something within all of us that can never disappear.
It's a vessel of memories we've created that contains the bonds we share with our friends!
Even if you yourself... are shattered beyond repair...
If you believe in that vessel...
If you just have faith in it...
We can be reborn time and time again!
With it, the light in our hearts will always shine!
Think back, everyone...
To the people you've fought...!
To the people you suffered along with!
Now my God has been completely resurrected!
Huh?
That's...!
That's right! They're still within Master's deck!
Everyone!
Yugi... The last bit of my strength...!
I'll... give it all to you!!
What is this?!
I feel it...
I feel everyone's feelings.
They've breathed new life into me!
Crossing over 3,000 years of time, engraved in the name of the Pharaoh!
What!?
Revive before us!
Come forth! The Three Illusionary Beasts!
They've...!
Obelisk!
Osiris!
Ra!
He brought them back!
The three gods!
Impossible!
He resurrected the God Cards!?
Other Me...
Dartz!
Curse you, Nameless Pharaoh!
I will erase the Duel Monsters Gods with the God of Orichalcos!
It's a battle of gods...
Is it powerful enough to shroud the entire sky in black?!
Other Me...!
Just how far do you intend to interfere with my plans, Duel Monsters!?
I shall destroy you with a single strike!
Go on! Obelisk!!
God Hand Crusher!!
Osiris!!
Thunder Force!!
Ra!!
God Blaze Cannon!!
Dartz!! We will never lose to the darkness in our hearts!!
This is... not possible!
Does that mean the three gods won?
That means the souls of everyone that were taken...!
Mai...
Wake up.
Mai.
Varon!
We're...
We've been set free.
From the darkness in our hearts.
Because of their strength.
Yugi...
Kaiba...
Jounouchi!
Let's return, Mai.
Yes.
Bro!
Big Brother!
Big Brod'er!
Miruko...
Big Bro!
Sonia! Julien!
Dad! Mom!
Big Brother!
Our souls will always...
...be with you...
...forever!
Sonia... Julien...
Miruko...
Bro!
Dad...
Mom...
Sonia...
Julien...
Amelda...
Let's go home.
Right.
Where am I...?
Hey... You alright?
I see...
I was... by Nameless Pharaoh and the others...
So that light...
Everyone's made it back to where they belong.
What the?!
Other Me!
Partner...
Mhm-hmm.
This place is about to be destroyed!
Yeah!
Let's move!
It's still open!
If we go through there, we'll get back to our world!
I'm jumpin' in!
Wait, Partner!
Other Me!
This presence...
Dartz!
He couldn't have...!
This thing...! After taking attacks from the Illusion Beasts, it's still...!
Timeaus!
Timaeus!
Return, Timaeus!
Other Me...
Just what... is this thing?
It's completely different than any of the other Monsters...!
Nameless Pharaoh...
Dartz!
Any attack you throw at me now is useless.
This monstrosity is the true form of the God of Orichalcos.
What?
So it...
This makes up the resentment of every single human being on this planet.
It represents everyone existing on this world.
On this planet?
Then...
You are correct.
This planet and human beings...
As long as these two things exist, the darkness of heart among this planet will never vanish!
That is what this "Monster" is.
Run, Partner!
I'll stop this thing!
Other Me!
If I don't defeat this thing, the same thing will happen to the world again!
Was it you?! Were you the one who called my soul here?!
Partner...
I finally understand after receiving strength from everyone in this battle.
My great mission as the Pharaoh...
I can now feel it clearly.
To clear this planet's darkness of the heart... I must do it as Pharaoh!
As the Pharaoh?
Now, come on!
Your anger and hatred!
I will take all of it!
I will take in the darkness of heart within this planet!
Other Me!
What?
The houses lined down the street drifting by being dyed red
If I notice pain, it'll turn into happiness
Every time people wipe away tears, they understand bonds
The warm strength that you gave me will change into kindness
Overflowing feelings don't stop
I'll live while I feel it, for me to be myself
Healed by overflowing friendship
Our fated encounter is a truth,
and someday we'll be able to understand each other
The Three Illusionary Beasts were revived.
Obelisk, Osiris and Ra attacked and stopped both the Orichalcos God and Dartz along with his ambition in their tracks!
But he couldn't completely stop the curse that plagues the people of this planet!
Now Yugi takes in the Earth's suffering!
If he loses, Yugi will fall victim to Dartz!
We've given the future of this planet to Yugi!
Next time!
"Walk Into the Light"
Duel standby!