A magazine page I can't finish reading.
I want to read it, but somehow I can't.
Game software is stacked in the corner of the room.
If I don't play them, will they become meaningless?
I'm just beyond the table, and I'm trying to talk with you.
A never changing facial expression is on your face.
Even though I'm right here with you.
They can't reach, they can't reach, these feelings of mine.
I wonder what's really important?
My cards, we're about to face the master
of the kingdom, the strongest Duelist!
Let's fight as one!
Arrow Shot!
Yugi boy is like a small animal struggling
for breath as I crush him with my hands.
For I know every single card
in your entire hand!
Mind Scan!!
That gaze that
pierces through my cards... I
That feeling's not just my imagination!
Demon's Summon, isn't that right!?
He's reading my mind...!
But there's nothing I can do to stop it...!
"Attacks Impossible!?
The Invincible Toon Army"
Yugi, don't let Pegasus shake you!
Be careful, Yugi!
What?!
Mokuba is very important to our plan,
as he's the ﻿one holding the key to the room that holds the contracts!
No matter what, you have to get Mokuba back!
If we don't get him back,
what will we tell Master Pegasus?!
Oi, Bakura, where are you going?
I'm just... going to look for Honda-kun.
Please do that, Bakura-kun.
Geez, that bastard Honda!
What's he doing at such
an important time?! Man!
Yugi boy, I've already read
your plan for this turn.
You will first set the Trap Card,
Hexagram Curse, face-down on the field.
You will then play
Demon's Summon in Defense Position.
You're going to try and tempt my
Monsters into attacking you.
My turn.
I set a card face-down on the field.
Also...
Demon's Summon in Defense Mode!
Turn over.
Okay, my turn.
Very well. I will step into your trap.
We'll see who is truly
trapped in the end, shall we?
I change Dragon Egger into Attack Mode!
Attack the Demon!
Trap activate!
Hexagram Curse!
The one who attacks this card
falls into its trap.
Oh no!
Dragon Egger's Attack
goes down by 700 points!
Alright!
He trapped Pegasus' Monster!
My turn!
I switch Demon to Attack Mode!
Attack Dragon Egger!
Demon Lightning!!
Trap Card. activate!
Trap Displacement!
What?! Trap Displacement?!
Yes!
With this card, I can take a Trap Card used against one of my Monsters and transfer it to the opponent's.
Now Demon's been trapped by the Hexagram Curse instead,
And its Attack Power dropped!
I know every strategy you have.
They have no effect on me.
Dragon Flame!
He's... completely reading
every one of my strategies...!
How do I fight?!
That's too low, Pegasus!
How's he supposed to fight him like this?!
What are you saying?! If we start giving up, what'll he do then?
I-I'm sorry.
You're right.
Yugi's not the type of guy who'd give up, no matter what happens to him!
Yugi... Don't lose!
He's over there! That way!
That's far enough.
Now then, you've got nowhere left to run.
Damn it all...!
What's that sound?!
Bakura, what are you doing here?!
Who the hell are you?!
You bastard! If you don't obey us,
you're a dead man!
Bakura, forget about me!
Just get out of here!
Isn't this interesting?
If I don't obey you, what will you do?
You bastard!
In that case, my weapon is this.
Magical Bonds!
Don't screw with us!
What the hell is this?!
Shit...! I can't move...!
Bakura...! These guys...
Now, let's take this chance and escape.
Y-Y-Yeah...!
Hey, wait!
You bastards!
Shit! Again?!
What the hell is this?!
This is Team A! Send backup now!
My turn.
So this is the power of
Pegasus' Millennium Eye...?
There has to be a way to stop his Mind Scan!
No!
There is no way to stop it, Yugi boy.
He's reading my mind even now...?!
A game is a contest between two minds.
If you can understand the mind of the
opponent, you are guaranteed to win!
You don't have the power to step even one foot into the territory of my mind!
And that includes the world of the game I created as well.
Allow me to show this to you right now!
My card is...
Toon World!
This is bad! That card...!
Toon World is the design of the
ultimate game world I created.
The Toon characters are the best!
That's right! My wonderful Monsters have
turned into invincible Toon Monsters!
Furthermore, all my Toon Monsters ﻿can only be defeated by other Toon Monsters.
I'm sorry, Yugi boy!
Toon Dragon Egger!
Attack the Monster
he has set in Defense Position!
Giant Soldier of Stone
has been annihilated!
After launching their attacks, my Toon Monsters
hide themselves deep within Toon World!
A world where your Monsters
can never reach.
The invincible defensive walls of Toon World make me unable to attack!
This is the card that did in Kaiba...
I place Toon Mermaid in
Attack Mode and end my turn.
Right now, I only have cards suitable for Defense Mode in my hand.
They'll only be defeated!
In that case, I'll test to see if normal Monsters
can attack Toon Monsters.
Elf Swordsman!
Attack Mode!
Elf Swordsman has
the same Attack as Toon Mermaid.
If my attack is successful, they should both be destroyed.
Alright!
Elf Swordsman! Attack Toon Mermaid!
Holy Sword Slash!!
What?!
What's going on?
Elf Swordsman's sword
was stopped dead in its tracks!
It's no use, Yugi boy!
Toon Monsters have the Special Ability to not be destroyed by normal attacks!
Toon Mermaid Arrow!!
Elf Swordsman was...!
Damn...! That's too cheap, Pegasus!
As I thought, attacks against Toon Monsters are impossible!
That is correct!
Toons ﻿can only be defeated by Toons!
Toons are the perfect form of life!
With the power of his Millennium Eye, he sees all my strategies and tactics...!
On top of it, I can't attack head on...
Is there any way I can win this Duel?
It is my turn.
I will place these two cards face-down on the field, and end my turn.
A Magic Card?
Or is it a Trap?
My turn!
If I play a Monster in Attack Mode,
It can't defeat the Toons.
Moreover, he has that Trap Card...
A Monster in Defense Mode!
I thought you would.
This turn, I'll open my set card.
I activate the Trap Card, Gorgon's Eye!
What?! The Imp was turned to stone!
This card is a Permanent Trap that turns all of the ﻿opponent's Monsters into a useless statue.
Furthermore, when your stone Monsters ﻿are destroyed, half their Defense Points
will be subtracted from your Life Points.
In other words, you have no choice but to attack my Toons every single turn!
What useless attacks they'll be, eh?!
Now then, it's my turn.
I'll also Summon another of my lovely, funky friends!
The Magic Card, Copycat!
It is a copy card that takes on
the effect of any card it chooses from the opponent's side of the field.
Copy card...?!
A very loving cat as always!
And just what card
do you want to change into?
Nice!
That's a good idea!
Yugi boy, it seems he would like to change into that ﻿Demon's Summon card you played a few turns back.
What?! My Demon?!
Yes! And furthermore, Toon World is present on the board!
Are you aware of what this means?
Now go forth!
Now it is fully protected.
And the transformation to your Demon in Toon World is underway.
A new page called "Evil Castle"
will now open in Toon World
Now come on out here, my Toon Demon!
Toon Demon, you said?!
What do you think, Yugi boy?
Doesn't my child give off a
"definitely lovely" kind of aura?
Pegasus...! You bastard...!
Ohhh~! How scary, how scary!
Toon Demon, attack!
The stone Imp is destroyed!
And due to the effect of Gorgon's Eye, you will lose half the Defense Points of the Imp, 500, from your Life!
My turn is over!
How was that, Yugi boy?
Doesn't it feel weird being attacked by your own Monster?
It hid in that book again!
Damn! Isn't there any way to defeat those Toons?!
To not only blemish my Monster's dignity but force it to attack me as a Toon...!
It is your turn!
I see you've drawn the Black Magician.
As I thought. Pegasus not only knows every card in my hand, but every card I draw...!
Bakura, what did you do before?
Forget that for now.
Just worry about running!
When this is over, you better explain all this really clearly!
No use! This one's locked too.
Let's go!
There's an exit up ahead!
What!?
Y-You saved me...!
As long as ﻿Toon World remains on the field, I can't damage him in any of my attacks...
But I can't defend myself either...!
Is there any way I can win in this situation?
No!
You cannot possibly defeat me.
I can clearly see your will to fight drifting away.
Well, what do you think? Do you want
to forfeit the Duel, Yugi boy?
Yugi! Don't give up!
If you admit defeat, Mokuba and Kaiba's souls will be lost!
You won't be able to save your grandfather,
Mokuba-kun, and Kaiba-kun that way!
Please, keep trying, Yugi!
Yugi!
But right now, my chance of winning is as close to zero as it can possibly get...!
Grandpa...
Mokuba...
Kaiba...!
I...
Yup, there's nowhere left to go now.
Found them! Up there!
Surround em!
You won't escape this time!
Shit! All the guards!?
To give up hope so easily, that's not like you, Honda!
You have some sort of plan?
Now's not the time to be choosing from a list of strategies.
Yugi!
If I give up now, all three of
their souls will he lost forever.
Even if my chances of victory
are low, I still can't give up!
Pegasus! I won't give up!
I'll bet on the little possibility
I have until the very end!
It is no use, Yugi boy.
No matter how hard you struggle,
you are still finished.
With the Millennium Eye reading his hand,
and Toon World blocking his attacks,
Yugi's attack and defense have both been sealed!
He tries to bring out his Black Magician/Magical Silk Hats combo,
but he's been completely read by Pegasus!
The Mind Scan didn't work?!
I get it! Before he can read his mind, he
just switches minds with the other Yugi!
Next time!
"The Counterattack Begins!
The Mind Shuffle"
Duel standby!
The flask shines bright
waiting in the Science Lab
By rubbing our cold hands together...
They will become warm
An energy shower
It'll shower all over you
I will support your lonely back
An energy shower
You're not alone
Because you're surrounded by a ring of friendship