Say...
What color is your world right now?
Hey. I'm listening,
so play seriously.
It's not like it's for listening.
Then, what are you doing?
It's a part-time job where I transpose
new music to sheet by ear.
I'm just checking
if the sound is correct.
Even so, you can just play normally.
I've quit piano.
But you're playing.
So hot!
Why is it so hot
when it's only April?!
Ah... I am coming back to life.
This is not a room to rest
for club activities.
Are you in a bad mood?
Did I just get in the way
of a middle-aged married couple?
We are not married!
Your tones are matching as expected.
Shut up!
We're just childhood friends!
Stop it! Do you intend to injure
the soccer club's ace?!
That's what I'm going to do!
I'm sorry, I'm sorry!
I'll really give it to you!
I'm really sorry! Really!
Tsubaki and Watari are always shining...
so I think that world is colorful.
But...
my world is...
like this keyboard,
that's monotone.
That girl said that she liked you
for a while, Watari.
And she asked me to introduce you to her.
But is she really cute?
I told you she's cute.
So it's been decided that
you two meet this Saturday.
That's why you should also come, Kosei.
Huh? Why should I?
Because you're free.
Hey...
Aren't we always together since
the middle school entrance ceremony?
Okay?
What's up, Keiko?
Really?!
Got it. I'll be right there. See you!
Sorry. Keiko asked me to come. Bye!
How flamboyant.
But he's a good guy.
So you're okay with Saturday, right?
If you're not coming,
I'll look like a fool alone.
That's why you could
just be Friend A. Please!
Even if you request...
Please!
I got it.
You know, I got first
in the fortune telling today.
And my lucky food is octopus dumplings,
that's why we're having that.
It's Ms. Hiroko.
Lucky you.
You'll have delicious food today.
I'll see you tomorrow then.
I'm home.
Welcome home.
We're making burger steaks.
You don't have to do this, Ms. Hiroko.
You're busy with recitals.
It's alright.
You should eat something nutritious
from time to time.
That's what your father asked me.
But you don't have to worry about that.
He left you because he got
transferred for work.
Your father must be worried about you.
You released a new album.
I'll give that to you.
Thank you.
I'll go get changed.
Kosei.
Have you greeted your mother at home?
I'm home.
They're late.
Coming five minutes early
have already passed.
They're like the Bremen Town Musicians.
It was such a strong wind.
What the hell are you doing,
you sneaky photographing devil?!
- You just photographed me, right?!
- Wait! Wait!
Molester! Pervert!
Give me your smartphone!
I'm going to break it!
No! You got it wrong!
Gimme!
Kosei?
Kao?
Tsubaki!
She's my classmate, Kaori Miyazono.
Nice to meet you.
And he's Ryota Watari.
Let's get along!
Let's get along.
And here is just Friend A.
Nice to meet you.
Let's get going then.
Where are we going?
Music hall.
Kao will be entering
a violin competition.
I'm a violinist.
Really? That's so cool!
Then, we have to cheer for you.
Tsubaki, I'll pass.
Why?
Let's go.
Wow!
I can't hear...
I'm scared!
Kosei!
This way.
Hey, could he be Kosei Arima?
Yes.
He might be that Arima.
The genius Arima?
He's the one who was called
the human metronome.
Yo! Mr. Popular!
You purposely didn't tell me, didn't you?
'Cause if I told you,
you might not come.
That's why...
I did my best not to tell you.
But hey, this is violin.
Right? Violin!
Hey, why are they playing the same piece?
Because it's the set piece
of the preliminaries.
I give up.
I want to sleep.
Even though you were sleeping the whole time?
Kao is next.
Oh! Finally!
Kao! Good luck!
Kao!
May it be reached.
It's somewhat cool, isn't it?
It's totally different
from the other contestants.
The tempo and loudness are haphazard.
To think she's disregarding
the directions of the written music.
What the hell is this?
It's a disrespect to the composer!
This preposterous performance
is out of the question in a competition.
But it's interesting.
Why...
I wonder why you can play
such playful music.
Kosei.
Why can't you notice me
no matter how I many times I call you?
Sorry.
Here. It's thanks for
accompanying me last Saturday.
Thanks.
You were just spacing out.
Have you been thinking about a girl you like?
Why ask that suddenly?
Could it be Kaori?
I get you, I get you.
She sure is cute!
No way!
Besides, she likes you.
That doesn't matter.
It's only natural that the girl you're
crushing on is in love with someone else.
Since you're in love with her,
she sparkles in your eyes.
That's why people fall irrationally in love.
I think I kind of get why
you're such a chick-magnet, Watari.
You just realized it now?
But it's impossible for me.
Whether or not it's impossible...
the girl will let you know.
You really give good advice, Watari.
I know, right?
Hello? Maki?
Club practice today?
No, none.
Us going to karaoke?!
Sounds good!
Friend A!
It's a coincidence.
Are you on your way home?
Ah, right.
How is my violin playing?
It was reckless to play like that
in a competition.
But...
How should I say it...
It was really great.
So it was no problem!
Anyway, where is Watari?
Aren't you with him?
Ah, Watari has club practice.
What?
To think I wanted to surprise him,
so I waited for him.
But if I return to school,
I'll be able see him at his club.
But since the matches are near,
seems he's busy.
You think I'll be in the way if I go there?
That's not what I mean.
Well, I might be in the way.
I got it.
Then, I've decided.
I'm appointing you
to be his substitute.
I've always wanted to eat here!
So yummy!
Aren't you going to eat?
Then, I'll eat it!
Hey, hey!
Okay.
So cute!
Hello!
Do you like piano?
I see!
That guy over there
is really good at the piano!
Why don't you play?
Don't tell me you're going
to ignore the children's wishes.
Wow!
I'm sorry.
Wait!
Friend A!
Why did you...
Huh?
Quick! Hurry!
Hey, wait!
Where are we going?
Hurry!
We made it in time.
Beautiful!
I love watching the sunset here.
I see.
You don't play the piano anymore?
So you actually know about me.
Winner of the Moriwaki
Student's Piano Competition.
Winner of the Urie International
Competition for two consecutive years.
The youngest winner
at the Saiki Competition.
Your playing style
was accurate and disciplined.
A human metronome.
You were a prodigy who performed Mozart
with an orchestra at the age of eight.
You've done your homework.
There isn't a musician in our generation
who hasn't heard of you.
Since you're who we look up to.
Why did you quit playing?
I can't hear the sound of the piano.
But you were just playing awhile ago.
I can hear at first.
But I can't hear it suddenly.
The more I concentrate...
the more I get consumed by the performance...
and then I can't hear
the sound of the piano.
That's right.
This is my punishment.
That's why I can't play.
You should just play
even if you can't.
What's that?
If your hands don't move,
play with your feet.
If your fingers aren't enough,
use your nose.
Mozart?
I've decided.
You'll be my accompanist.
Huh?
From the preliminaries from before,
I passed because I was the audience's favorite.
I can participate
in the second preliminaries.
Did you hear what I said?
I told you that I can't hear.
Oh, shut up.
I've already decided.
Friend A, I appoint you
to be my accompanist.
Kosei as an accompanist?
Yeah.
I want him to.
What do you think?
I think it's a good idea!
But I wonder if he'll really do it.
I'll help you!
I'm really excited!
Hey...
This has been playing endlessly
since awhile ago.
What is this?
Rondo...
Capriccioso.
Please turn to page 24
of your textbooks.
About the past perfect tense from before...
Geez.
We'll definitely make Kosei play.
But don't you think we're a bit pushy?
It's about right to do that to Kosei.
The truth is, I'm fine with Kosei
not playing the piano.
But if he quits,
I want him to understand.
Because the Kosei right now
seems to be doing things half-baked.
It pains me to see him like that.
Seems like you like Arima.
It's a bit different from liking him.
For me,
Kosei is like...
a good-for-nothing little brother.
You know, Kosei suddenly stopped playing
when his mother, who's a pianist, died.
He stopped playing since then.
I just want...
Kosei's time to move again
from when it stopped during that time.
Next stop is Tatsuhara University Hospital.
Tatsuhara University Hospital.
We'll make a stop at the next stop.
Passengers who will leave
at the next bus stop,
please stand up
only when the door is open.
You're late again.
Properly play it.
No! You should play accordingly
like what the music sheet says!
Play everything like what it says!
I can't play, after all.
I'm sorry.
Kosei.
Then, who will play Kaori's accompaniment?
Look for someone else.
There you are.
So you were hiding here.
Why are you here?
Of course, I came to fetch
my accompaniment.
I told you that I can't play!
It's not that you can't play,
you just don't play.
You're just running away from an excuse
of not hearing the piano's sound.
I'm scared.
I'm here.
I'm here, you know.
I know everything, that you can't hear
the piano's sound and that you can't play since then.
But I want it to be you.
We might not be able to play
a proper performance.
But if there are people
who are able to hear it...
I want to perform my very best.
I'm sure it will touch their hearts.
I want to deliver my music.
I can definitely do it with you.
That's what I thought.
That's why, I beg you.
Please be my accompaniment.
Please support me for a bit.
Please support me...
who is about to lose heart.
I won't be responsible
for what happens, okay?
Hurry it up.
You're taking too long.
We'll be late, so hurry!
We've borrowed these bikes.
Let's go!
Thank you.
Come on.
You should hurry too, Kosei.
Alright.
We'll make sure that you'll make it there!
Yeah!
Kosei, don't fall.
So fast!
But will you be okay?
How about practice? Did you match?
It's alright.
We'll make do somehow.
- Don't underestimate us athletes!
- It's just like what Watari said.
We'll even make time for you to match!
- Thank you.
- Whether it's impossible or not...
only this girl will let me know.
By the way, you were awesome the other time.
Really?
That makes me glad.
I'm looking forward to you
playing today too, so break a leg.
Of course, I will!
Ms. Hiroko.
Where is Kosei?
He's backstage.
So Kosei will play.
So hot.
- Ow!
- That hurt!
You hard head!
What is it all of a sudden?
H-hey! Give that back!
There's no time.
Raise your head and look at me.
It's all because you're always looking down
that you end up locked up
with the staff notation.
It's alright.
You can surely do it.
Mozart is saying this from above...
"Go on a journey."
The two of us should just throw away the shame
of the journey, and just be fully shameful.
#14.
Ms. Kaori Miyazono.
Please prepare.
Okay.
Let's go.
You're...
so care-free.
I'm not.
The music is care-free.
Hey.
Isn't he Kosei Arima?
I thought so.
Why is he playing?
Okay.
I played on time.
Kosei is playing piano again.
She's surprisingly playing calmly right now.
Now she's showing her true self.
It's alright.
I can hear the sound too.
I can go on.
As expected of Arima.
Even though the tempo changed,
he accurately catches up.
What's wrong, Arima?
I have no words.
It seems off.
No way. Why?
That's because he'll get in the way
of her performance.
So that it won't fully affect
the review of the judges.
But is it alright that
there's no accompaniment?
As long as she keeps on playing...
the judging will continue.
Yes.
This is unheard of.
Why did you stop?
Again.
Since they started from the beginning again,
it's okay, right?
No.
Her participation in the competition
has already ended awhile ago.
The two of us should just throw away the shame
of the journey, and just be fully shameful.
The music is care-free.
Calm down. Remember the piece that I was
irritated to hear during lunch break.
Remember the music sheet
that was scattered everywhere.
Even if I can't hear the sound,
play everything that I have inside of me now.
Hey, hey, Friend A.
Don't take the leading role here.
Wow.
Both of them are recklessly playing.
It seems like a fist fight.
But that is what attracts the listeners.
Kaori!
You're awesome!
You did it, Kosei!
Thank you...
Kosei Arima.
That's the first time...
you called me by my name.
The people here...
will not forget about us.
I'm sure of it.
I won't forget.
I won't forget even if I die.
Tsubaki, keep it up!
Nice!
Come on, let's go! Fight!
Seems like you're more energetic recently.
I guess so. Since I don't want
to lose to Kosei and Kaori.
I see. Their performance
was really great it seems.
It was great.
It was really great!
That's why he's also pumped up, huh?
So did Arima started playing piano again?
Not really.
Looks like he doesn't play.
Skip, skip, step.
Skip, step. Skip, step.
Here I go!
Skip, skip, step.
Skip, step!
Yo!
Want some canele?
It's good.
Were you...
waiting for Watari?
No.
I waited for you.
Let's take a walk.
Regarding the competition
that I lost at...
I'm really sorry about that.
Ta-da!
I was invited to a gala concert
by the organizers.
I can play again.
The truth is that only winners can be there.
But I'm popular!
Isn't it great?
That's amazing.
I'll go and watch.
Huh?!
That's not what I want to hear.
It should be, "I'll go and play," right?
I can't do that.
Yes, you can.
No.
I want to play with you again.
I might fail again.
Are you seriously saying that?
But I'm someone who gave up
playing the piano.
Do you really think you can forget?
The sensation when you're playing.
The grand applause of the audience.
The moment where your music was delivered.
Do you really think you can forget?
Everyone is scared to go up on stage.
One might fail or be fully denied.
But I will still bear it
and go up on stage.
We perform when we're inspired by something.
That's how the most beautiful lie is born.
We are those type of people.
We are still 17, you know.
Let's boldly jump in!
Like this!
Hey!
I wanted to try this
at least once!
It's awesome!
Hey!
That's right.
There's no way I can forget it.
Feels good, doesn't it?
That was scary!
Thank you.
It's too big, after all.
Um... here's soup.
Hey, where is the piano?
What?
Wait!
You mustn't!
I told you not to.
I'm sorry.
A healthy performance comes from
a healthy environment!
We should clean up first!
Ventilation!
I've decided what to perform
at the gala concert.
Kreisler's "Love Sorrow."
Isn't there a better piece than that?
Something that is more flashy
to perform in a gala concert.
I've already decided.
This is it.
Okay.
So hot.
You know how to play the piano.
I used to play it.
Kao.
Kosei.
Tsubaki!
One more time.
They're working hard again today.
Hey, hey.
Let's take a peek a bit.
Forget it.
Just go. I'll just call you
when it's time for practice.
Forget it.
It's bad to get in the way
of their practice.
She's a handful.
To think she just made such an obvious outburst,
how come she doesn't recognize it herself?
Mom.
I won.
That's no good at all!
Hey, Saki!
What're you doing?!
You misplayed at the 3rd and 11th measures.
The tempo at the 13th measure is wrong.
I told you to play accurately, didn't I?!
I won for you.
Are you listening, Kosei?!
Even though I did my very best,
so that you'll get better...
Even though I won for you...
I've had enough!
I don't care if you die.
My mother went back to the hospital after that.
That night...
She died...
I killed her.
And since then...
the sound went missing.
Kosei is playing the piano!
Kosei, isn't that song...
Why don't we take a walk?
"Love's Sorrow..."
reminds me so much of Mom.
It's the piece that Saki loves the most.
She played it a lot during college.
Since you were born...
it seems like a lullaby
she played to you.
While she was playing it...
you were always so calmly
sleeping beside her.
Will Mom let me play...
"Love's Sorrow" though.
Do I even have the right to play it?
If you're in doubt, just play it.
Play it, then listen to what Saki will tell you.
Can I go and look at the fish?
Go ahead.
But don't tap on the glass.
I know!
Besides...
you are thinking way too much.
You were having so much fun playing the piano
when you were starting, you know.
Come on!
Like before, with all your heart,
try playing like you're passionately
motivating yourself.
If you do that, something might change.
Mommy, come here!
There is a really cute fish here.
Could it be that...
the reason you can't hear
the sound is because...
it might be a gift?
Ms. Hiroko said that...
not hearing the sound may be a gift.
I wonder what it means...
Are you listening?
So you're asleep.
I'm looking forward to the gala concert.
It would be better if it comes soon.
It seems like we have time.
Leave it to me.
I'll be taking the spotlight.
That's why I'm counting on you.
Okay.
No.
You should've said
you are the spotlight too.
But I'm an accompanist.
No, no.
The gala concert is all about standing out.
So pretty.
Yeah.
Thank you.
Twinkle twinkle little star.
How I wonder what you are.
Up above the world so high.
Like a diamond in the sky.
Twinkle twinkle little star.
How I wonder what you are.
If you please...
Would you consider switching the order?
No matter how many times you asked,
the most prominent part of the program
is the winner of the competition.
It's impossible to give the final performance
to someone who is late.
Besides, I was first against in inviting her.
To think she gave such profanity to music.
She didn't gave profanity.
This last minute cancellation is good proof.
She'll come.
She'll surely come.
That's why, please give us more time.
The line-up will not change at all.
We're done here.
Next performer is Kaori Miyazono.
I wonder what happened.
Geez, don't make us worry.
Is Kaori Miyazono here?
Excuse me.
Yes.
Then, please go to the stage wing.
Hey.
She isn't here yet.
The spotlight today
belongs to Kaori Miyazono.
Then, I have no choice,
but to let them know she is here.
But just what are you going to play?
The gala concert...
is all about standing out.
Arima's playing alone
in a violin gala concert?
Just who does he think he is
playing only as an accompanist?
It's different than their usual practice.
Yeah.
Kreisler's "Love's Sorrow..."
Rachmaninoff Piano Arrangement Version.
I will prove it.
I will take the spotlight
at this gala concert.
Why is he playing with such strength?
Huh?
I was playing this strongly?
No.
Mom's playing of "Love's Sorrow"
is more mellow.
There.
This piece is played more like this.
This piece that has been
my lullaby as a child...
I should remember it.
Imagine it.
Kosei, play it more gently.
As if you're gently stroking
the head of a baby.
Play it as if you're embracing the baby.
Maybe the reason you can't hear
the piano's sound...
is because it might be a gift.
There's a sound...
inside me.
You musn't.
Didn't the doctor already say so?
I should go see him.
I have to teach him piano.
Please, let me go.
I don't have much time.
Even if I'm gone...
I should teach him
how to be a proper pianist.
So that he would be able to survive.
So that my treasure...
would be able to be happy.
Saki.
Can you hear him?
Your son...
is bidding his final farewell.
I know this piece.
Memories of Kosei's mom is there.
Isn't this correct, Mom?
The piano is being played
as if you're embracing it.
Even though there is "Love's Joy"
and "Love's Sorrow,"
why is it that you always play
"Love's Sorrow?"
Mom is inside me.
The reason is, Kosei...
so that I get used to the sorrow.
I am connected to Mom.
That's what I believe.
That's why...
That's why, Mom...
Good-bye.
Kosei!
Kosei.
Ms. Hiroko.
I wonder if it reached Mom.
My best piano playing...
Did it reach Mom?
Idiot.
Of course, it reached her.
Just when I was leaving the house,
I stumbled. Just stumbled.
Then, the ambulance came rushing in.
Having called the ambulance
is really an exaggeration.
It's just anemia,
but my head was hit when I stumbled,
so I need to be examined.
So in the end, I'm hospitalized.
But I'm glad you seem well.
Yeah.
I'm well, really well.
I'm really sorry for making you worry.
Don't worry about it.
Kosei did his best for you too.
Really, his performance was awesome.
That much, huh?
Yeah.
Well, I don't know much about music.
But I think it's next to how awesome
you play the violin.
I thought so.
I'm the best in that department.
Of course, you are.
I'll go buy something to drink.
What?
I'll go too.
Okay.
Kosei.
The vending machine is over here.
Sorry, I'm leaving.
Yes?
Friend A!
Why did you just leave?!
Sorry.
I just had things to do.
Don't think you're off the hook that easily.
What?
Just kidding.
I'll let you pass this time.
Next time, be sure to bring canele.
Okay.
Also...
let me hear about you playing the piano.
About you playing the piano
at the gala concert.
Got it?
Okay.
That's good. Bye.
Ow...
What is this?
Why isn't it moving?
Please stand up.
Stand up!
You're my legs, right?!
Get up!
So Miyazono can't get out of the hospital yet.
Yeah. Even though she looked well
when we visited her...
You three seem to get along well.
About that...
No matter how many times we ask Kosei
to come with us, he doesn't.
Even though Kao is waiting for him.
Are you sure? Is it alright
for you to help your rival?
Rival?
No way.
Why is Kao my rival?
I just think that Kosei
is the only one
who can talk to Kao regarding music.
Geez, you're being too kind, Tsubaki.
You don't have to be so hard on yourself.
You like him, don't you?
No, no, no, no!
There's no way I like him.
Hey, stop it already.
You're denying it too much.
You've been caught already. Admit it.
Alright.
You're awfully honest today.
But I'm not kind.
Whenever Kosei says he doesn't
want to go to the hospital,
it makes me relieved.
I hate that about myself.
Makes myself look like
it's nothing and deceiving.
That's excessively unpleasant, huh?
I'm sure...
if you lump it all together,
that is what you call being in love.
I don't know at all!
You always suddenly appear.
So you've just been released.
You heartless guy!
Why didn't you come visit me at all?!
Even though I've been
looking forward to the canele.
Sorry.
You're already well?
Yeah. I'll be joyously coming back
to school starting today.
Hey, where's Watari?
Watari is still at school.
I'll go get him.
Wait.
For a heartless guy like you,
I'll give you a chance for atonement.
I impose you to be the substitute.
Isn't this pretty?
Yeah.
It's pretty.
Okay!
Then, I'll buy this!
Wait!
That's cute!
Thank you very much.
Welcome!
Whoa!
Look!
Isn't it awesome?!
Delicious!
So cute!
Cute!
Hurry!
Here we go.
Okay, cheese!
W-wait!
I'll get wet!
It's okay!
Somehow...
this seems like a date.
But I've never been to one before.
Are you playing piano?
A little.
You know...
I was really glad...
that you said I did great during the first round
of elimination in the competition.
That's why, it's your turn next.
Hey, after all,
you're an expressive performer...
Kosei Arima.
It's the second time.
You called me by my name.
Yeah.
We should get going.
Okay.
I forgot my bag.
Being at school at night
makes me feel excited somehow.
I wonder if a ghost might appear.
Do you believe in ghosts or not?
I just can't believe someone
can leave their bag at school.
True.
What's wrong?
Where's your bag?
That's right.
The bag.
Let's see.
I wonder where my bag is...
Hey, don't tell me...
Sorry.
I lied.
There's no bag here.
But you came to school, right?
You were released at the hospital, right?
I'm sorry about that too.
I'm still not released yet.
I was approved to go out
for just one day.
I can't do many things
when I'm in the hospital.
And also...
I wanted to go to school
no matter what.
My sickness...
is a bit bad...
Just kidding.
I'm sorry.
Huh?
I wonder why?
Let's go back.
I'm fine.
I can walk by myself.
Let's go back.
I'm really fine!
Miyazono!
I'm really sorry.
No. It's not your fault.
Thank you for taking care of my daughter.
Arima.
Kaori asked to see you.
I'm sorry to surprise you.
It's okay.
It's because I'm selfish.
I will always make you suffer.
- That's not true...
- If that's the case...
If that's the case...
It would have been better
if we didn't meet.
Why don't you go visit her?
Don't you think you owe it to Kaori?
Let me see your face.
Kosei.
I...
couldn't say a word.
I just ran away.
That's why...
How should I act when I see her?
That's more the reason...
for you to go visit Kaori.
When she wants her own way...
or a shoulder to lean on...
Whenever she wants somebody
to do something for her...
she always turns to you.
But...
I just don't know what to say to her.
You'll figure that out
once you're there.
But it's impossible for me.
Whether it's impossible or not...
is up to the girl to decide.
Kosei!
Here.
Thanks.
You're opening it awkwardly.
So hot!
You're not too good with hot drinks.
No, this is really hot.
Kosei.
You like Kao, right?
Yeah.
How foolish of you.
Kao likes Watari, you know.
I know.
You're really stupid.
Kao likes Watari.
You are no match for him.
Yeah.
Aren't you stupid?
Kao likes Watari.
That's why...
That's why, you have no choice,
but to love me instead.
What?
To think you're a coward
who can't even visit her.
You'll regret it if you don't
say it to her, you gloom!
That kind of...
That kind of guy is a no for me.
Idiot.
Idiot!
I burned my tongue.
I'm such an idiot.
Yo.
You have club practice today?
The matches are coming up soon,
so we don't have breaks.
Hey, Watari.
I...
I really like Miyazono.
Idiot, I know.
Okay.
Come in.
Hello.
Why did you come?
Because I promised you.
Let's eat.
No.
I want to eat under the sky.
I'll beat you if you say I'm heavy.
Delicious.
I've decided to participate
in the East Japan Piano Competition.
I don't know how far
I'll be able to pull it off.
But I'll move forward.
And I want to perform with you again.
I...
like you.
I know that you like Watari.
But...
I still want to perform with you.
That's why...
Please play with me once again.
You told me, didn't you?
"Do you really think you can forget?"
I can never forget.
The stage we stood on.
And your violin.
You're cruel.
Let's go back.
Are you alright?
I'm scared.
I'm scared and...
I'm scared and I can't help it.
I don't want to die.
No.
No!
I don't want to die!
Don't leave me alone.
I want to respect your decision.
But like I said before,
this surgery involves a big risk.
Yes.
I understand.
But still, let me have it.
No matter how small of hope there is...
I'll hold on to it.
I will go through it,
so that I will live.
I have...
an important promise I have to keep.
It's alright.
Kosei?
Your face looks scary.
Are you okay?
Hey.
Play.
We're pianists.
What you're feeling right now...
express it all in the piano
with all you've got.
Tweezers.
Here.
Carry.
I can hear the sound inside me.
I am here because I met you.
I met you...
and it frightened me a lot...
Made me laugh a lot...
Made my heart move a lot...
They became sounds and it overflowed me.
My sound.
Will it be able to reach you, I wonder...
It would be nice that it does.
This is Kosei's...
love letter to Kaori.
The words we've exchanged...
A little bit of regret...
The humming of "Twinkle Twinkle Little Star..."
The scenery where I can't
regret what supports me.
They cheer me up.
When I'm inspired...
I will play.
I'll play for you.
Next time, I will tell you.
I am here.
I will not leave you alone.
Like I will let you be alone.
Reach it.
Place everything I have.
Reach it!
Dear Kosei Arima.
Writing a letter to someone
I was just with awhile ago...
feels a bit strange.
The first time I saw you perform...
was when I was five.
It was the recital of the piano school
I was attending.
The boy who appeared awkwardly,
hit his butt in the chair
and made the audience laugh.
Facing the piano that was too large...
The moment when a note was played...
you became my admiration.
I wanted to perform with you someday
no matter what, so...
I started playing the violin.
But even still...
you stopped playing the piano.
After influencing one's life,
you are a horrible person.
Dimwit.
Slowpoke. Dummy.
When I found out we were in
the same high school, I was elated.
I always kept thinking how could I
find a way to talk to you.
But in the end,
all I could do was watch you.
After all, the three of you
were always too close.
There was no space for me to slip into.
I had surgery as a child,
and then got treated regularly
as an outpatient.
When I collapsed in the first year of middle school,
I went in and out of the hospital, repeatedly.
The time I began spending in the hospital grew.
One night, at the hospital's waiting room,
when I saw my mother
and father crying...
Why?
I realized that I didn't have
much time remaining.
That was the time...
when I broke into a run.
So that I don't take any regrets
with me to heaven...
I started doing whatever I wanted.
The contact lenses
that I was so scared of...
I even changed my hairstyle.
Even the music scores that
bossed me around haughtily,
I played them my own way.
And then, just one...
I told just one lie.
I, Kaori Miyazono...
lied that I liked Ryota Watari.
Why?
That lie would bring before me...
Kosei Arima.
It brought you to me.
Apologize to Watari for me, okay?
Also...
please apologize to Tsubaki for me.
I'm just someone who is passing by...
I didn't want to leave
an awkward mess behind.
So I couldn't ask Tsubaki
to introduce us.
After all, Tsubaki...
was so crazy about you.
The "you" that my underhanded lie brought forth...
was far from how I imagined you.
You were more dark...
and passive than I thought.
Not to mention, a stubborn guy
and a camera voyeur.
Your voice was deeper than I thought...
and you were more manly than I thought.
And you were just...
as gentle as I thought.
The river that we jumped off
from the Bridge of Bravery
was cold and felt good.
That was scary!
In the sandy beach we walked together,
that squeezy feeling...
There's just something about
school at night, right?
How the most unforgettable scenes
can be so trivial, isn't it weird?
How about you?
Was I able to live inside your heart?
You made yourself home
as soon as you barged in.
Do you think...
you'll remember me
at least a little?
If I forget you, you know
you'd come back to haunt me.
You'd better not hit reset.
As if I ever would.
Don't forget me, okay?
Okay.
That's a promise.
Yeah.
Will it reach you?
I hope it can reach you.
Kosei Arima...
I love you.
Sorry I was so selfish.
Sorry a million times over.
Thank you.
Kaori Miyazono.
You're on a break, right?
Why don't you come in?
It's just that when I'm confined here...
You know!
Right? Right?
Feels great, doesn't it?
Are you properly eating?
Yeah.
I'm eating like half the amount
of what you're eating.
Hey.
What did you mean by that?!
It sounds like I eat a lot!
Don't you?
Ow...
Hey, don't think you're alone.
I'll keep following you everywhere
like a bound ghost.
That's why, don't think you're alone.
So hot!
Why is it already this hot
when it's only spring break?
Ow!
See?
He's also here.
What do you think you're doing?
Are you eating properly?
You two are thinking the same thing.
What?
Kosei Arima.
What color is your surroundings right now?
My life, you see...
was really colorful because of you.
I'll end up letting go of your hand.
"Hurry up," saying that
you're making me worry,
you start running off fast.
As I always only chased you,
I was only watching your back,
without even knowing the tears
that you were hiding.
I was happy
because of that voice
that disappears like wind.
In haste, I called out your name.
That smiling face that looked back,
was saddeningly beautiful.
In this spring,
tears aren't stopping.
That gentle warmth
that was always beside me,
still remains in the palm of my hand.
Hey, the thing that
you aren't there anymore,
even though I know,
I still end up calling you
over and over.
To connect our feelings,
even though I was holding that hand,
your voice was always shaking painfully.
All that I couldn't put into words,
see that they are within me...
living this moment.
Good-bye....
That love...
I won't forget.
Tears aren't stopping,
I won't be able to see you anymore right?
The days we spent together
gradually become a distant light.
Hey, even so, I have to go.
Even if you aren't there,
I'll go looking for tomorrow.
Tears aren't stopping,
I always loved you.
No matter how many times spring comes,
I won't forget anything, so...
Hey, I already conveyed good-bye...
I'll also live in the "now,"
where only you aren't there.